[HAMMERING]
-When does it open?
-Tomorrow afternoon.
Well, let's get up a party in the evening,
if Mrs. Hughes lets us,
after we've had our dinner.
You're right. It doesn't come often,
and it doesn't stay long.
-And what about you, Mr. Bates?
-I don't see why not.
ANNA: Well, there's Lady Mary.
You go on ahead.
I'll see you back at the house.
GWEN: Right you are, then.
Good day, my lady.
Is her ladyship all right?
Has she recovered from...
If you think she'll ever recover
from carrying the body of Mr. Pamuk
from one side of the house to the other,
then you don't know her at all.
Well, I didn't mean recover exactly,
just get past it.
She won't do that, either.
When she dies, they'll cut her open
and find it engraved on her heart.
What about you?
What about your heart?
Haven't you heard? I don't have a heart.
Everyone knows that.
Not me, my lady.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
You wanted to see
the new chauffeur, my lord?
Yes, indeed. Please send him in.
Come in, come in. Good to see you again.
-Branson, isn't it?
-That's right, your lordship.
I hope they've shown you
where everything is
and we've delivered whatever
we promised at the interview.
Certainly, my lord.
-Won't you miss Ireland?
-Ireland, yes. But not the job.
The mistress was a nice lady,
but she had only one car
and she wouldn't let me drive it
over 20 miles an hour.
So it was a bit...
Well, boring, so to speak.
[CHUCKLES]
You've got a wonderful library.
You're very welcome to borrow books,
if you wish.
Really, my lord?
Well, there's a ledger over there that I
make everyone use, even my daughters.
Carson and Mrs. Hughes
sometimes take a novel or two.
-What are your interests?
-History and politics, mainly.
Heavens!
Carson, Branson is going
to borrow some books.
-He has my permission.
-Very good, my lord.
-BRANSON: is that all, my lord?
-It is.
Off you go and good luck.
He seems a bright spark
after poor old Taylor.
And to think Taylor's gone off
to run a tea shop.
I cannot feel it will make
for a very restful retirement, can you?
I would rather be put to death, my lord.
Quite so. Thank you, Carson.
How about some house parties?
She's been asked to one next month
by Lady Anne McNair.
A most terrible idea.
She doesn't know anyone under 100.
I might send her over to visit my aunt.
She could get to know New York.
Oh, I don't think things
are quite that desperate.
Poor Mary, she's been
terribly down in the mouth lately.
She was very upset
by the death of poor Mr. Pamuk.
Why? She didn't know him.
One can't go to pieces at the death
of every foreigner.
We'd all be in a state of collapse
whenever we opened a newspaper.
Oh, no. Of course, Mary's main difficulty
is that her situation is unresolved.
I mean, is she an heiress or isn't she?
The entail's unbreakable.
Mary cannot inherit.
No, what we need is a lawyer
who's decent and honor bound
to look into it.
I... I think perhaps I know just the man.
MATTHEW: Are you going
to the fair while it's here?
Oh, I shouldn't think so, sir.
But I don't mind it. I like the music.
Goodness, what's happened to your hands?
It's nothing, ma'am.
They look very painful.
Oh, no, ma'am. Irritating
more than painful.
Have you been using anything new
to polish the silver or the shoes?
-No.
-May I?
Leave him alone, Mother.
It looks like Erysipelas.
You must have cut yourself.
-Not that I'm aware of.
-We'll walk round to the hospital tomorrow.
-Really, ma'am...
-I insist.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[GROANS]
You've got a cold. I want you out of here.
Anna, there you are.
You know I'm out tonight?
Because I don't want to come home
to any surprises.
[LAUGHING] That'll be the day.
We thought we might go to the fair later.
You'd like that, wouldn't you, Daisy?
Now, you ought to go.
She's been that down in the mouth
since the death of poor Mr. Pamuk.
-Don't say that.
-Well, she has.
We could all walk down together after
the servants' dinner, if that's a good...
[SNEEZES]
You won't be walking anywhere. She's
got minutes to live, by the sound of it.
-Go to bed at once.
-Yes, Mrs. Hughes.
I'll bring up a Beechams Powder.
Right. If there's anything you want
to ask me, it'll need to be before I go.
What would I want to ask you?
I'm preparing a meal for
Lord and Lady Grantham and the girls.
No one is visiting. No one is staying.
Well, that's settled, then.
I'm afraid Dr. Clarkson's out delivering a
baby. We don't know when he'll be back.
No matter.
If you'll just open the store cupboard,
-I can easily find what I need.
-Well, I...
You can tell the doctor
that you opened the cupboard
for the chairman of the board.
I assure you,
he will raise not the slightest objection.
This should do it.
Tincture of steel, 10 drops in water,
three times a day.
And this is solution of nitrate of silver.
Rub a little in, morning and night.
-How long before it's better?
-Erysipelas is very hard to cure.
We should be able to reduce the symptoms,
but that might be all we can manage.
Oh, and you must wear gloves at all times.
I couldn't wait a table in gloves.
-I'd look like a footman.
-You may have to.
The tincture and the salve will help.
Try it for a week and we'll see.
[DOOR OPENING]
-Someone to see you, Mr. Crawley.
-There's nothing in my diary.
It's Lady Grantham.
Well, in that case, show her in at once.
Cousin Cora, to what do I owe the...
I hope I'm not a disappointment.
I thought it might be
nice to cheer it up a bit.
Easier said than done.
Perhaps with a flower
or a bit of veil or something.
I can find you a veil if you like.
I hope you're not expecting me to do it.
-Not if you're busy, of course.
-Good.
And Miss O'Brien,
I've sent Anna to bed with a cold,
so I need you to manage the young ladies.
What, all three of them? I'm not
an octopus. Why can't Gwen do it?
Because she is not a lady's maid.
I am not a slave.
Just do it, Miss O'Brien. Just do it.
I'll pay you the compliment that I do not
believe you wish to inherit
just because nobody's
investigated properly.
No, but...
Nor can Mary accuse you of making trouble,
when you are the one
who will suffer most from a discovery.
You're right that I don't wish
to benefit at Mary's expense
from an ignorance of the law.
Putting it bluntly,
do you think Robert has
thrown in the towel prematurely?
-Good heavens, what am I sitting on?
-A swivel chair.
Oh, another modern brainwave?
Not very modern.
They were invented by Thomas Jefferson.
Why does every day
involve a fight with an American?
-I'll fetch a different one.
-No, no, no, no.
I'm a good sailor.
It will depend on the exact terms
of the entail and of the deed of gift
when Cousin Cora's money
was transferred to the estate.
That is all I ask,
to understand the exact terms.
Is Daisy going to the fair tonight
with the others?
Why don't you ask her?
She needs taking out of herself.
[MAIDS CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
-What's it to you?
-Nothing.
Daisy, I was hoping...
Would you like to go
to the fair with me, Daisy?
There's a few of us going later on.
Do you mean it?
MRS PATMORE: Daisy, don't let it get cold.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
You bastard.
Why is Sybil having a
new dress and not me?
Because it's Sybil's turn.
Can it be my choice this time?
Of course, darling.
As long as you choose what I choose.
Branson, you'll be taking Lady Sybil
to Ripon tomorrow.
-She'll be leaving after luncheon.
-Certainly, your ladyship.
Poor old Madame Swan.
I don't know why we bother with fittings.
She always makes the same frock.
-What do you want her to make?
-Something new and exciting.
Heavens! Look at the time.
Not a minute to change,
and Granny's invited herself for dinner.
Then she can jolly well wait.
So women's rights begin at home? I see.
Well, I'm all for that.
[ALL CHUCKLE]
I'm just off, Mr. Carson.
According to the wine book,
we should still have six dozen of this,
but I'm beggared
if I can find much more than four.
Look again before you jump
to any nasty conclusions.
Long time since you last took a night off.
-You don't think I ought to stay, do you?
-Certainly not. Be off with you.
And Anna's in bed with a cold,
so I'm afraid it's all down to you.
Go.
Thought I'd have a go before I went home.
How about you?
Thank you.
Do you know if your father's
doing anything this evening?
He's not coming to the fair.
Seriously.
Having dinner with his family.
Can I look in afterwards?
May I ask why?
Your grandmother paid me a visit
this afternoon and I...
Well, never mind, but
I would like to see him.
Granny came to see you?
Is it all part of the Great Matter?
So are you enjoying your new life?
Yes, I think so.
I know my work seems very trivial to you.
Not necessarily.
Sometimes I rather envy you,
having somewhere to go every morning.
I thought that made me very middle-class.
You should learn to forget what I say.
I know I do.
How about you?
Is your life proving satisfactory?
Apart from the Great Matter, of course.
Women like me don't have a life.
We choose clothes and pay calls
and work for charity and do the season.
But really we're stuck in a waiting room
until we marry.
-I've made you angry.
-My life makes me angry. Not you.
[MAIDS CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
CARSON: I never put the Sauterne on ice.
Mrs. Hughes goes out for one night
and we all fall to pieces!
Mr. Carson, we wondered if we could
walk down to the fair after dinner?
I suppose so, but don't be too late.
-Where do you think she's gone?
-None of your business.
Like most of what goes on round here.
DAISY: Oh!
Well caught, that man.
Though I say it myself.
Thanks, ever so.
Yes?
Well, you've cheered up a bit.
He's so agile, isn't he?
He could have been a sportsman.
-Who?
-Thomas, of course.
Really?
Which sport did you have in mind?
I ran into Cousin Matthew in the village.
He wanted to call on you after dinner.
Apparently, Granny's been to see him.
Did you tell him
she's coming here this evening?
I didn't know she was.
When he arrives, do your best
to keep her in the drawing room.
Well, I'd like to see you try.
[CHUCKLES]
[DOOR OPENING]
CORA: Don't stay too long.
Let them have an early night.
COUNTESS: Sybil, darling,
why would you want to go to a real school?
You're not a doctor's daughter.
But nobody learns anything
from a governess,
apart from French and how to curtsey.
COUNTESS: Well, what else do you need?
SYBIL: Well, there's...
Or are you thinking
of a career in banking?
SYBIL: No, but it is a noble profession.
CORA: Things are different in America.
COUNTESS: I know. They live in wigwams.
And when they come out of them,
they go to school.
[SOFTLY] If you wait in the library,
I'll tell Papa you're here.
Thank you.
[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[PEOPLE EXCLAIMING]
JOE: Elsie?
It is Elsie, isn't it?
It is. Though there's very few left
to call me that, Joe Burns.
Well, I'm flattered that I'm one of them.
Where's Thomas?
I'm afraid I let some of the servants
go down to the fair, my lord.
I didn't know we'd
have any visitors tonight.
ROBERT: Oh, that's all right.
They don't have much fun.
You should join them.
[CLEARING THROAT]
So, what did you say to Mama?
I haven't spoken to her since her visit.
But I have looked through every source
and I can't find one reason
on which to base a challenge.
I could have told you that.
I'm not quite sure how to phrase it
when I tell her.
She shouldn't have put you
on the spot like that. It was unkind.
I'm afraid she'll think I've failed
because I don't want to succeed.
She will think that, but I don't,
and nor will Cora.
Of course it's impossible for Mary.
She must resent me so bitterly.
And I don't blame her.
Yes, it must have been hard for you
when Ivy died.
Took some getting used to.
What about your son?
Do you see much of him?
Peter? No.
I would have given him a share
of the farm if he wanted it,
but he's joined the army.
-Well, I never.
-Oh, he seems happy.
But it's left me on me own.
Shall I take your plates, then?
-Yeah.
-Thank you.
-So how's life treated you?
-Oh, I can't complain.
I haven't traveled, but I've
seen a bit of life and no mistake.
I notice you call yourself "Mrs.".
Housekeepers and cooks are always "Mrs.".
You know better than anyone
I haven't changed my name.
Well, I know you wouldn't change it
to Burns when you had the chance.
You shouldn't have eaten with us.
The chauffeur always eats
in his own cottage.
Steady on. You can cut him
a bit of slack on his second day.
I'm waiting to take old
Lady Grantham home.
Even then, Taylor never ate with us.
You're taking advantage
of Mrs. Hughes' absence.
What are you doing?
I'm sorting the collars. Removing
the ones that have come to an end.
What happens to his
lordship's old clothes?
What's it to you? Clothes are
a valet's perk, not a chauffeur's.
I get some. But most of it
goes into the missionary barrel.
[SIGHS] I know it's meant to be kind,
but I can think of better ways
to helping the needy
-than sending stiff collars to the equator.
-[LAUGHING]
I thought Anna might have
come down for her dinner.
And show she's ready to start work again?
Not a chance.
-She's still in bed, then?
-She is.
While I'm sat here, sewing like
a cursed princess in a fairy tale,
and not down at the fair with the others.
Would you like me to ask Branson
to bring the car round, my lady?
But where's Robert?
He can't have been
drinking port since we left.
-He'd be under the table by now.
-His lordship's in the library.
All alone? Oh, how sad.
No, he's...
We can say goodbye to Papa for you,
Granny.
He's what?
He's with Mr. Crawley, my lady.
The question is
what do I say to Cousin Violet?
Oh, don't worry about
that. I can handle her.
COUNTESS: Really?
Well, if you can,
you must have learned to very recently.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[KNOCKING CONTINUES]
BATES: Anna?
Mr. Bates?
Can you open the door?
I daren't.
No one can open that door
except Mrs. Hughes.
BATES: Just for a moment.
I've brought you something.
[SIGHS]
-I don't know what...
-Shh.
[DOOR OPENING]
What I don't understand
in all this is you.
You seem positively glad
to see Mary disinherited!
-You speak as if we had a choice.
-Thank you, Branson.
I'm worn out. Tell Lady Mary
and Mr. Crawley I've gone to bed.
Shall I tell them now, my lord?
No. Wait until they ring.
Yes, sir.
I ought to start back.
-This is very late for me.
-Oh, not yet.
It's a long time since I've had a girl
to show off for at the fair.
[GROANS]
-So I take it you never get lonely?
-Well, that's working in a big house.
Though, there are times
when you yearn for a bit of solitude.
[MRS HUGHES EXCLAIMS]
MAN: We have a winner!
Ah! Thank you.
Well, something to remind you of me.
I don't need help to remember you.
But what... What happens when you retire?
I should think I'll stay here.
They'll look after me.
Suppose they sell the estate?
Suppose there's a tidal wave?
Suppose we all die of the plague?
Suppose there's a war?
-What did I tell you? She's found her Romeo.
-It might be her brother.
She hasn't got a brother
or we'd know it by now.
Just a sister in Lytham St Annes.
You know everything, don't you?
[SCOFFS] Everything, my foot.
You're hiding behind him,
but he's not what you think he is.
Oh, go home, William,
if you're going to be such a spoilsport.
All right, I will.
Come back! She didn't mean it!
I must go.
But it's been lovely to see you again,
Joe, really.
-And you know what I'm asking?
-You haven't asked anything yet.
But you know what it is, when I do.
I'm going to stop here at the pub,
until I hear from you.
Oh, and take your time.
I'd rather wait a week for the right
answer than get a wrong one in a hurry.
Think about it carefully.
I will. I promise you that.
To break the entail,
we'd need a private bill in Parliament?
Even then, it would only be passed if
the estate were in danger, which it's not.
-And I mean nothing in all this?
-On the contrary, you mean a great deal.
A very great deal.
[DOOR OPENING]
-You rang, my lady?
-Yes, Carson.
Mr. Crawley was just leaving.
Do you know where his lordship is?
Gone to bed, my lady.
He felt tired
after he put Lady Grantham into the car.
I bet he did. Thank you, Carson.
[DOOR CLOSING]
I'm sorry, I wish I could think of
something to say that would help.
There's nothing.
But you mustn't let it trouble you.
It does trouble me.
It troubles me very much.
Then that will be my consolation prize.
Goodnight, Cousin Matthew.
Goodnight.
I hope I haven't kept you up too late. I'm
afraid we've interfered with your dinner.
It's been rather
a chop-and-change evening downstairs.
Lady Grantham got off all right?
"All right" is an
optimistic assessment, sir.
It's very difficult, Carson.
For her, for Lady Mary, for everyone.
It is, Mr. Crawley,
but I appreciate your saying so.
Well, that's her greatness
done and dusted for the night.
BATES: William, did you have a good night?
-I'm off to bed.
-Wait.
-What happened?
-Nothing. It doesn't matter.
-How was your evening, Mrs. Hughes?
-Very enjoyable, thank you.
The others are just behind me,
so you can lock up in a minute.
Well, I'll say goodnight.
-Good night, Mrs. Hughes.
-Good night.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
-Good night, Mrs Hughes.
-Good night, Mrs. Hughes.
I was right when I said
she was looking sparkly-eyed.
I beg your pardon, Thomas?
He can disapprove all he likes.
Mrs. Hughes has got a fancy man.
[SNICKERS]
-DAISY: Him? A fancy man?
-Don't be so nasty, Daisy. It doesn't suit you.
I reckon there's a job vacancy coming up.
Miss O'Brien, do you fancy a promotion?
Very droll.
If she's got a boyfriend, I'm a giraffe.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Leave me alone, Mr. Bates.
I know you mean well, but let me be.
What chance did he have,
up against a champion?
Now you listen, you filthy little rat.
If you don't lay off, I will punch your
shining teeth through the back of your skull.
Is this supposed to frighten me, Mr. Bates?
Because if it is, it isn't working.
I'm sorry, but it's just not working.
-Daisy, chafing dishes, now!
-They're right in front of you, Mrs. Patmore.
Are you trying to trick me?
Anna's still not well. O'Brien, you'll
need to dress the girls this morning.
All we know about Lady Mary and here I am,
waiting on her hand and foot.
-Will we do anything with that?
-Maybe, but not yet.
What do you look like?
Daisy, what do you think he looks like?
-Do your buttons up.
-Well, go on, then.
-What do you want?
-I've got a message for Lady Sybil.
-From her ladyship.
-Thank you, O'Brien. I'll manage now.
Odious woman. What does Mama want?
I just said that to get rid of her.
This came today.
-I knew they would want to see you.
-Well, it's your reference what's done it.
But how am I going to get there?
They won't let me take a day off.
You're going to be ill.
They can't stop you being ill.
-What?
-No one has seen Anna for a whole day.
They won't notice if you vanish
for a couple of hours.
The only one who never sticks up for me
in all this is you. Why is that?
You are my darling
daughter and I love you,
hard as it is for an Englishman
to say the words.
Well, then...
If I had made my own fortune
and bought Downton for myself,
it should be yours without question,
but I did not.
My fortune is the work of others,
who labored to build a great dynasty.
Do I have the right to destroy their work?
Or impoverish that dynasty?
I am a custodian, my dear, not an owner.
I must strive to be worthy of the task
I have been set.
If I could take Mama's money
out of the estate,
Downton would have to be sold
to pay for it. Is that what you want?
To see Matthew a landless pier
with a title but no means to pay for it?
So I'm to just find a husband
and get out of the way?
-You could stay here if you married Matthew.
-You know my character, Father.
I'd never marry any
man that I was told to.
I'm stubborn. I wish I wasn't, but I am.
Will you have your own way, do you think?
With the frock?
Only I couldn't help
overhearing yesterday,
and from what her ladyship said, it
sounded as if you support women's rights.
I suppose I do.
Because I'm quite political.
In fact, I've brought some pamphlets that I
thought might interest you, about the vote.
Thank you.
But please don't mention this
to my father, or my grandmother.
One whiff of reform and she
hears the rattle of the guillotine.
It seems rather unlikely,
a revolutionary chauffeur.
Maybe.
But I'm a socialist, not a revolutionary.
And I won't always be a chauffeur.
Mrs. Crawley, how nice.
-You're busy. We can come back later.
-Molesley?
What are you doing here? Are you ill?
Poor Mr. Molesley. How's it going?
The solution doesn't seem
to make it any better.
My imagination is running riot.
-I've got Erysipelas, your ladyship.
-Oh, I am sorry.
Mrs. Crawley tells me she's recommended
nitrate of silver and tincture of steel.
Is she making a suit of armor?
-But I take it there's been no improvement?
-Not really.
-And you're sure it's Erysipelas?
-That is Mrs. Crawley's diagnosis.
-What it is to have medical knowledge!
-It has its uses.
Mmm.
I see your father
has been making changes at home.
He has, my lady. He's got no use
for the herb garden now me mother's gone,
so he's turned it to grass.
-And you've been helping him?
-I have.
-Grubbing out the old rue hedge?
-How did you know that?
Because this is not Erysipelas,
this is a rue allergy.
If Molesley wears gardening gloves,
it'll be gone in a week.
Please don't think we're ungrateful
for your enthusiasm, Mrs. Crawley,
but there comes a time when things
are best left to the professionals.
-But I...
-And now, really, I really must go.
-Good day.
-Thank you, your ladyship.
[CHUCKLING]
I hope Cousin Violet
has recovered from last night.
Whatever she says,
my mother is as strong as an ox,
and it's high time she let go of her scheme
for upsetting everything. Time we all did.
I can't deny I'm pleased to hear it.
Are you beginning to
see a future here, then?
In a way, this latest business
has forced me to recognize
that I do want Downton to be my future.
I'm glad.
You must have thought me
an awful prig when I first arrived.
Not a prig.
Just a man thrust into something
he never wanted or envisaged.
I could only see the absurdity
of the whole thing.
-I'm sorry.
-Well, there are absurdities involved,
as I know well enough.
Possibilities, too, and I was blind to them.
I was determined not to let it change me.
-It was absurd. If you don't change, you die.
-Do you think so?
I'm not sure. Sometimes
I think I hate change.
Well, at least we can comfort ourselves
that this will still be here.
Because we saved it.
DAISY: Thomas is lovely, isn't he?
He's funny and handsome,
-and he's got such lovely teeth.
-He's not for you, Daisy.
Of course not.
He's too good for me, I know that.
-No. He's not too good.
-What, then?
He's not the boy for you,
and you're not the girl for him.
Isn't that what I just said?
And why would he be?
When he's seen and done so much,
and I've been nowhere and done nothing.
Perhaps Thomas has seen and done
more than is good for him.
He's not a ladies' man.
-Well, isn't it a blessed relief?
-Daisy, Thomas is a troubled soul.
I don't know what you mean, Mrs. Patmore.
Oh, nothing. I don't mean anything.
Except, if I don't get the ice cream
started, they'll be dining at midnight.
Golly, my corset's tight.
Anna, when you've done that,
would you be an angel and loosen it a bit?
-The start of the slippery slope.
-I'm not putting on weight.
It didn't shrink in the drawer.
Are you coming down?
I don't know why we bother with corsets.
Men don't wear them, and they look
perfectly normal in their clothes.
-Not all of them.
-She's just showing off.
She'll be on about the vote in a minute.
If you mean do I think women
should have the vote, of course I do.
I hope you won't chain yourself
to the railings
and end up being force-fed semolina.
What do you think, Anna?
-I think those women are very brave.
-Hear, hear.
ROBERT: How did you get on
with your dressmaker?
-Find anything?
-I did.
And she says she can
have it done by Friday.
I'm sorry I couldn't come,
but I didn't want to put Matthew off.
EDITH: Were you pleased
with the work on the cottages?
ROBERT: I think they're making
a very good job of them.
You must all go and see.
CORA: You'll restore a few
every year from now on?
It was Matthew's idea.
Old Cripps was rather reluctant,
but I'm pleased we went forward.
EDITH: I suppose it's worth it?
SYBIL: Of course it is.
Because of the people who'll live in them.
You'll be glad to hear
that Matthew's conscience
is much more energetic than mine.
If you'll excuse me, I'm going to bed.
I've rather a headache.
Of course. Shall I bring you
something for it?
No. I'll be perfectly
fine, if I can just lie down.
Mary?
[MARY SOBBING]
Oh, my darling.
What is it?
You heard him. Matthew this, Matthew that.
Matthew, Matthew, Matthew!
Oh, Mother, don't you see?
He has a son now.
Of course he didn't argue with the entail.
Why would he?
When he's got what he always wanted.
-Your father loves you very much.
-He wouldn't fight for me, though.
He wouldn't fight for you
because he knew he couldn't win.
-You're no better.
-What?
You don't care about
Matthew getting everything,
because you don't think I'm worthy of it.
-Mary!
-I wish you'd just admit it.
I'm a lost soul to you.
I took a lover with no
thought of marriage, a Turk!
Think of that! Oh, my dear!
Don't worry, Mama. You can go down now.
Everything will look better in the
morning. Isn't that what you usually say?
I say it because it's usually true.
Papa will wonder where you are.
-Don't quarrel with Matthew.
-Why shouldn't I?
Because one day you may need him.
Oh, I see.
When I've ruined myself, I must have
a powerful protector to hide behind.
I'd tell you off, but I
like to hear you play.
-Where are they all?
-Busy, I suppose.
Haven't you got anything to do?
Yes, I have. Of course I have.
You mustn't let Thomas get you down.
He's just jealous.
Everyone likes you better than him.
Not everyone.
Then she's a foolish girl
and she doesn't deserve you.
Though why am I encouraging you?
Forget all that. For 10 years, at least.
You're a kind woman, Mrs. Hughes.
I don't know how this house
would run without you. I don't, truly.
Stop flannelling and get on,
before I betray you to Mr. Carson.
Oh, is there anything
more thrilling than a new frock?
I suppose not, my lady.
You shall have one, too.
I thought this would be suitable
for your interview.
-I won't be wearing it, my lady.
-Of course you will.
We have to make you look like
a successful, professional woman.
What is it? What's happened?
Well, I won't wear it
because I'm not going.
They've canceled the appointment.
They've found someone more
suited for the post and better qualified.
-This time.
-Let's face it.
There'll never be anyone less suited
for the post or worse qualified than I am.
That isn't true.
You'll see, we're not giving up.
No one hits the bull's
eye with the first arrow.
I've put out the Rundell candlesticks
for dinner tonight.
-Oh. I'm sorry, I'll come back later.
-No. Stay, please.
I've got something I'd like to talk
to you about, if you've a minute.
Before I first came here as head
housemaid, I was walking out with a farmer.
When I told him I'd taken a job at
Downton, he asked ME to Marry him.
I was a farmer's daughter from Argyll,
so I knew the life.
He was very nice,
but then I came here and I did well and...
I didn't want to give it up. So I told
him no, and he married someone else.
She died three years ago.
And last month he wrote,
asking to see Me again.
And I agreed.
Because all this time, I've wondered.
Go on.
I met him the other night.
We had dinner at the Grantham Arms
and after, he took me to the fair.
And he was horrible and fat and red-faced,
and you couldn't think
what you ever saw in him.
He was still a nice man.
He is still a nice man.
Well, he was a bit red-faced and his suit
was a little tight, but none of that matters.
In the real ways,
he hadn't changed.
And he proposed again and you accepted?
[INAUDIBLE]
MRS HUGHES: In Many ways,
I wanted to accept.
But I'm not that farm girl any more.
I was flattered, of course, but...
I've changed, Mr. Carson.
Life's altered you, as it's altered me.
And what would be the point of living
if we didn't let life change us?
You won't be leaving, then?
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
You'd better come.
Mrs. Patmore's on the rampage.
She wants the key to the store cupboard.
You know how angry she gets
she hasn't got one of her own.
Nor will she have.
Not while I'm housekeeper here.
Leaving? When would I ever find the time?
[MRS PATMORE COMPLAINING]
Whatever is holding Sybil up?
She was going on about her new frock.
We'd better go in without her,
or it's not fair on Mrs. Patmore.
Oh, is her cooking so precisely timed?
You couldn't tell.
-I think her food is delicious.
-Naturally.
[LAUGHING]
Good evening, everyone.