MRS HUGHES: Hurry up girls, come on.
Come on, come on,
you should be done here!
They'll be back from the station
any second now.
I haven't had a chance to ask,
how was London?
Oh, much as usual.
Dirty, noisy and quite enjoyable.
There was no need for you
to come back a day early.
I'm perfectly capable
of getting the house ready.
Of course you are,
but I like to have the heavy luggage
back and unpacked before they get here.
I suppose... Steady,
William. This isn't a race.
Poor Iad.
But he did see her?
I was worried when I took him
to King's Cross.
Yes, he had time to say goodbye.
How is he now?
Well, you've only got one mother,
haven't you?
Mmm-hmm.
They're here, Mrs. Hughes.
Hello, William. It's
good to have you back.
What a relief to be home!
Don't listen when his lordship
pretends not to enjoy the season.
When in Rome...
Will Lady Mary be back soon?
She's staying on with my sister
for a couple of weeks.
-So Grantham House is closed?
-It will be by the end of this week.
Dear Mrs. Hughes,
I hope you've had some time to yourself
while we've been away.
I've tackled a few jobs that get
forgotten about when the house is full.
Any local news?
The main topic here is
the murder of the Austrian Archduke.
Here and everywhere else.
I'm afraid we haven't
heard the last of that.
-And how is William?
-Bearing up.
Poor chap. He has our sympathies.
I think I'll wash the
train off before dinner.
Very good, milord.
I can unpack while you're bathing.
I'll see you up there.
Oh, Mrs. Hughes, have you had any thoughts
about the garden party for the hospital?
I've started on it, but there
are things we need to talk about.
Oh, dear. That sounds like trouble.
I'll take my hat off.
Sybil, you were a great success
in London, darling. Well done.
You never say that to me.
Don't I?
You were very helpful dear. Thank you.
I hate to spoil her ladyship's homecoming,
but what are we going to do
about Mrs. Patmore?
She's worse than when
you left. Much worse.
Oh, and I meant to ask, is there a
decision about Mr. Bates leaving?
Oh, not yet. His lordship wants the facts,
and Mr. Bates won't give them.
So, what are you going to say
to her ladyship about Mrs. Patmore?
MRS HUGHES: [SIGHS] I'm not sure.
I don't want the poor woman sacked,
but things cannot go on as they are.
ROSAMUND: There's nothing
like an English summer is there?
MARY: Except an English winter.
I'm sorry you haven't received
more invitations.
But then, after four seasons,
one is less a debutante than a survivor.
My dear, is there anything
you're not telling me?
-No.
-Only one hears stories...
There's nothing, Aunt Rosamund.
So, have you decided
whether or not to marry Cousin Matthew?
Oh, there's no secret Cora can keep
for more than a month.
You'd be surprised!
I've told him I'll give him my answer
the day I get back.
Well, it would be very tidy,
at least we can say that.
-Fancy a smoke?
-Don't mind if I do.
There they go. Guy
Fawkes and his assistant.
-Which is which?
-Here you are.
Surely, if his lordship
hasn't done anything until now,
it means he doesn't want
to take it any further.
WILLIAM: Anna's made me an armband,
Mr. Carson.
For my mother. Can I wear it?
I dare say, not when we're entertaining,
but otherwise.
-Hello, Doctor. I didn't know you were here.
-No, Lady Grantham sent a message.
-Why? She's not ill, is she?
-Not ill, exactly.
Would you mind waiting in the library?
Pregnant?
You needn't be quite so shocked.
Give me a moment.
-You haven't been pregnant for 18 years.
-And I'm pregnant now.
I don't understand
what we've done differently.
Stop right there. If you want to know more,
go down and offer the doctor some whiskey.
I can't take it in.
But you're pleased?
Of course.
Of course I'm pleased.
[CHUCKLING]
I didn't think she'd do it.
I told you she would.
I could see she was interested.
And I was speaking
as one lady's maid to another.
That means something, you know.
Course we thought we had him before,
but he's a slippery devil.
-CLARKSON: It's unusual, obviously.
-Unusual? It's Biblical.
[CHUCKLES] Not quite.
You understand that women
go through a certain change.
Thank you. I know quite as much
as I need to about all that.
Well, sometimes it can result
in a surge of fertility,
for want of a better word.
-But the child will be healthy?
-Oh, there's no reason why not.
How long has she...
Hard to be precise.
Things had become irregular, but...
Please!
I'd say she's about four months gone.
It'll begin to show soon.
And I don't suppose
there's any way of knowing if it's a...
I do beg your pardon, milord.
I thought you were alone.
No, please come in, Mrs. Hughes.
I'm just leaving.
MRS HUGHES: William!
Well, thank you, Doctor.
I'd better start writing some letters.
Show Dr. Clarkson out.
I didn't want to bother her ladyship,
if she's not well...
She's resting, but tell me anyway.
It's Mrs. Patmore, milord.
The time has come
when we really have to make a decision.
Hmm.
THOMAS: Now do you believe me?
Careful, Thomas.
Your position is not a strong one.
Don't punish us, Mr. Carson.
It's Mr Bates who's wanting here.
Tell me, Mr. Carson, do you think it right
a man like that should live and work
at Downton?
[DOOR OPENING]
Mr. Napier, milady.
What a surprise!
I'm afraid you've just missed my aunt.
[CHUCKLES] I know. I watched her leave.
How are your wedding plans going?
Not very well.
In fact, we've decided to call it off.
Really?
Well, it seemed quite
fixed at Sybil's ball.
What a shame!
Please.
It'll be better in the long run.
Perhaps.
I know what high hopes
you have of the institution.
The thing is, Lady Mary,
I am here today because
I needed to tell you something,
face to face, before
you went to the country.
"Face to face"? Gracious me!
I've recently heard gossip about the time
when I came to Downton with Kemal Pamuk.
Gossip that I believe
has made life difficult for you.
I've also heard it said
that I am the source of these stories.
It is very important to me
that you should know that I am not.
From that day to this, I have never
spoken one word on the matter.
Then who did?
It seems to have come
from the Turkish Embassy,
from the Ambassador himself, in fact,
and his wife.
But who told them, if not you?
This is the hard part.
When I discovered the answer,
I debated whether I should relay it,
but in the end I feel you ought to know.
The suspense is killing me.
It was your sister, Lady Edith,
who wrote to the Ambassador.
That is why people accept the story.
Edith?
It is very hard to believe.
Harder for you than for me.
I love the thought of a baby in the house,
but if it's a boy...
It'll be very hard on Mr. Crawley.
I know.
I was no great champion
when he first arrived,
but it seems to me he's tried his best,
and he's done the decent thing.
I can't see that coming off.
-You don't mean the engagement?
-But it's not an engagement yet, is it?
She'd never throw him over!
Mr. Carson, Lady Mary Crawley
does not deserve you.
COUNTESS: And she's not
been in touch with Cousin Matthew?
CORA: Not that I've heard.
Wonderful news, of course.
You must look after yourself.
Don't worry. O'Brien has me
wrapped in silk and feathers.
You're lucky.
I have a horrible feeling
Simmons is about to hand in her notice.
She's looking very fidgety, lately, and I
saw her hurrying to meet the postman.
Oh, you poor thing.
Is there anything worse
than losing one's maid?
I mean, why would she want to leave me?
I've been as gentle as a lamb.
Most of the time.
ROBERT: I want to say
I'll make provision for you,
if it's a boy and you get pushed out.
Don't worry, I know you can't.
If any man living understands
the strength of the entail, it's me.
I can give you Crawley House for life,
if it's a help.
Have you heard from Mary?
No. Have you?
By the way, I want to ask a favor.
What's the name of your cook?
The one you brought with you
from Manchester?
Mrs. Bird.
-I'll get it, Mrs. Patmore!
-Oh! Don't fuss me!
WILLIAM: is that everything? DAISY: Yeah.
How are you feeling?
Well, most people's parents die
before them, and so they should...
Oh, give it a rest.
Your mother knew how to drag it out,
I'll say that for her.
-What?
-MRS HUGHES: Thomas!
Get up to the servery!
[SHRIEKS] You gave me the wrong cloth! Ow!
Here, sit down, Mrs. Patmore.
I can't sit down,
I've got the luncheon to finish!
It was not a suggestion. Sit!
Daisy and I will finish the luncheon.
So he'll give us this house
for life, will he? How generous!
It is generous. He doesn't have to.
But it's made me think.
You must stay here if you want,
but I wonder if it mightn't be better
all round if I went back to Manchester.
It may not be a boy.
Really, Mother. You never
approved of it all in the first place.
If it is a boy, you should see it as
a release, not a disappointment.
What does Mary say?
Nothing yet.
You wanted to see Mrs. Bird, sir.
Yes, Mrs. Bird, Lord Grantham
has rather a favour to ask of you.
I'm surprised Lord Grantham
knows that I exist, sir.
[LAUGHS]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
I'm sorry to disturb you.
Quite all right.
Mr. Bates, it's about
your somewhat startling confession.
As you'll have surmised, his
lordship has yet to come to a decision.
His delay is generous.
However, it will be no surprise to you
that Miss O'Brien has been
unwilling to let things drop.
It seems that, when we were in London,
she made a new friend.
A lady's maid in the house of a colonel
in your former regiment.
Please tell me that this account is false,
at least in part.
I wish I could.
-I'll have to show this to his lordship.
-Of course you will.
I do not like to play the part of
Pontius Pilate, but I'm afraid I must.
Lord Grantham will
decide what's to be done.
Mr. Bates,
I hope you do not feel
that I have treated you unjustly.
On the contrary, Mr. Carson,
I am astonished at your kindness.
Of all of you, Sybil might
find joy in a cottage, but not you.
We don't know it'll be a boy.
Exactly, so ask Matthew
to wait until the child is born.
If it's a girl you can wed him happily,
and all will be as it was before.
But if I delay, won't he think
I'm only after him for his position?
Besides, I'm not sure I want to
put him off, even without the title.
We get on so well, you know.
And he's terribly clever.
He might end up Lord Chancellor.
And he might not.
Oh, come along, Mary, be sensible.
Can you really see yourself
dawdling your life away
as the wife of a country solicitor?
But why would we ever want
a telephone at Downton, milord?
ROBERT: Well, they have their uses.
You could speak
to the housekeeper in London.
That'd be helpful surely?
I hope I've not failed
in my management of the recent move?
Not at all. But the telephone is here now,
and the girls got used to it
when we were in London.
Besides, none of us know
what the next few months will bring.
Because of the Archduke's death?
Austria won't get what it wants from
Serbia. And now Russia's starting to rumble.
Well, there's not much
we can do about that.
-So, will you take care of the telephone man?
-Hmm. Oh, about Mr. Bates, milord,
I expect you've had time
to consider the contents of that letter?
Yes. But I find it very odd.
Regimental silver?
I could more easily see Bates
as an assassin than a petty pilferer.
I agree, and while the letter
is hard to argue with,
I wouldn't put anything past Thomas
or Miss O'Brien.
-So, what did we miss?
-Nothing much.
Although you'd have had
more invitations than I did.
-Have you thought about Matthew?
-Of course, but Aunt Rosamund...
She's written to me.
I should pay no attention.
But, Granny, she has got a point.
Mary can't be completely naïve.
I don't need your help, thank you.
Mary, listen to me, if
you take Matthew now,
when his whole future is at risk,
he will love you to the end of his days.
Why, Granny, you're a romantic!
I've been called many
things, but never that.
And what happens if the baby is a boy
and Matthew loses everything?
Mary can always change her mind.
But I can't do that to Matthew.
It's not how we are together.
-COUNTESS: Oh!
-I'm going upstairs to help Anna unpack.
I'll come with you.
Edith, why don't you go, too?
Sir Anthony Strallan
was at Lady Wren's party.
He asked after you.
Is she really serious about him?
Any port in a storm.
By the way, I was right about my maid.
She's leaving, to get married.
-How can she be so selfish?
-I do sympathize.
Robert's always wanting me to
get rid of O'Brien, but I can't face it.
-Anyway, she's so fond of me.
-Well, I thought Simmons was fond of me.
What am I to do?
Why don't I put an advertisement
in The Lady?
It's always the best place to start.
Oh, that's so kind, thank you.
Now, I really must be going.
Now, don't let Mary wait for the baby
before she gives Matthew her answer.
I'm sure it's another girl.
I know those men of the moral high ground.
If she won't say, "yes",
when he might be poor,
he won't want her, when he will be rich.
Maybe we should knit something.
Oh, yes, I'm sure they'd love
a pair of bootees knitted by you.
-Or what about a christening mug?
-They can buy their own silver.
Anything in the paper, Thomas?
They've arrested this Princip fellow
and his gang.
All Serbian and members of the Black Hand.
"The Black Hand"?
Oh, I don't like the sound of that.
I don't like the sound of any of it.
War is on the way.
Then we'll have to face it,
-as bravely as we can.
-Thank you, Mr. Cannon Fodder.
Don't you think a war's coming?
Oh, there'll be a war, all right.
And it's time to prepare for it.
-The country, do you mean?
-No, me.
You never disappoint.
Daisy, run and find Mrs. Patmore. His
lordship wants to see her in the library.
His lordship wants Mrs. Patmore
to go up to the library?
That is what I said.
And Anna, you're to come, too.
And we thought the assassination
of an Archduke was a surprise.
Mrs. Patmore, milord.
Your lordship, I know things
haven't been quite right for a while,
-but I can assure you...
-Come in, Mrs. Patmore.
I promise you, milord, if I could
just be allowed a bit more time...
Mrs. Patmore, I have not asked you here
to give you your notice.
-Haven't you?
-No.
I understand you've had
some trouble with your sight...
That's just it!
I know I could manage better if only...
-Please, Mrs. Patmore!
-Let him speak!
-Beg pardon, milord.
-Don't apologize.
Now, on Dr. Clarkson's recommendation,
I'm sending you up to London
to see an eye specialist at Moorfields.
Anna will go with you
and you'll stay with my sister Rosamund,
in her new house in Belgrave Square.
I'm afraid I'm going to have to sit
in your presence, milord.
Of course.
[STAMMERING]
But how will you get on here?
Well, Mrs Crawley is lending us
her cook, Mrs. Bird.
She's coming over tomorrow.
You'll be good enough
to show her how things work.
Are the Crawleys to starve while I'm away?
They'll eat here every evening.
Now, my sister's butler will
look after you. He's very nice.
Anna, you won't mind a visit to London?
No, milord. Thank you.
It'll be an adventure.
One with a happy ending, I hope.
Cor.
Let me get this clear, at Sybil's ball
you said you'd give me your answer
the day you got back,
and now you say you will not!
Why do we have to rush into it?
I need to be sure, that's all.
But you were sure.
Shall I tell you what I
think has altered you?
My prospects!
Because nothing else has changed!
-No.
-Yes!
If your mother's child is a boy,
then he's the heir
and I go back to living on my wits,
and you'd rather not follow me there!
Oh, Matthew, you always
make everything so black and white.
I think this is black and white.
Do you love me enough
to spend your life with me?
If you don't, then say no.
-If you do, then say yes.
-I want to...
Granny told me I should say yes now,
then withdraw if you lost everything.
To make that work,
you'd have to be a good liar.
Are you a good liar?
Well, not good enough
to try it, apparently.
How could you not have realized
they'd discover the loss at once?
And to keep them in your house...
-But you only served two years?
-That's right, milord.
So, clearly the judge thought
there was some mitigating factor.
I just want to know the truth.
I cannot speak of it, milord.
You must decide whether I stay or go
on the basis of the evidence before you.
I will respect that.
I'm sorry. I don't believe it.
How can you say that,
when I've confessed to the crime?
Well, his lordship obviously
doesn't think that's all there is to it,
and I don't either.
Anna, are you set for
the 9 o'clock train tomorrow?
All packed and ready.
You'll be met at King's Cross
by Lady Rosamund's chauffeur,
which I think is generous,
but after that you're on your own.
Right, I must get on.
I'm acting referee
for Mrs Patmore and Mrs. Bird.
-Best of luck.
-Mmm.
Will you miss me?
Try not to miss me.
It'll be good practice.
I expect it'll be hard
adjusting to this kitchen,
-after the one you're used to.
-Not to worry.
I'm sure I can have it
cleaned up in no time.
Cleaned up?
I'm not criticizing.
With your eyesight, it's a wonder
you could see the pots at all.
You have met Daisy and the others?
I have. Though what they all
find to do is a mystery to me.
MRS PATMORE: Are you not
used to managing staff, Mrs. Bird?
I'm used to getting it done
with one kitchen maid, Mrs. Patmore,
but I suppose in a house like this
you expect to take it easy.
Do you think we should erect a ring
and let them fight it out?
[CHUCKLES] She's all right, Mrs. Bird.
She's more of a general than a trooper,
but, you know, you need that in a cook.
Mrs. Patmore's the generalissimo.
[LAUGHS]
Well, I'm very sad.
-I thought Mary was made of better stuff.
-Don't speak against her.
Of course, she's taken advice from someone
with false and greedy values.
-Oh, Mother.
-And we don't have to go too far
to know who that is! I've a good mind...
Mother! You are not to go near
Cousin Violet, that is an order.
-Something's not right about it.
-I agree.
Having a silver thief in the house
does not seem right at all,
even if he could walk.
But Carson isn't keen
to get rid of him either,
and he normally comes down on
this sort of thing like a ton of bricks.
What's his reasoning?
He blames Thomas and O'Brien.
He says they've been working
against Bates since he got here.
So I should sack O'Brien instead?
You'll hear no argument from me.
This should do the trick, milady.
Ten years of my life,
that's what I've given her.
Ten bloody years!
-But did she say she'd sack you?
-It's obviously what he wants.
-So when will they tell you?
-When they've found a replacement.
Heaven forfend she should have to put
a comb through her own hair!
And if I'm going, you won't be far behind.
Oh, so what? Sod 'em.
There's a war coming and war means change.
We should be making plans.
-What are you talking about?
-Well, put it like this.
I don't want to be a footman any more,
but I don't intend to be
killed in battle, neither.
[WHISPERING] I'm not saying poison them.
Just make sure they don't find her food
all that agreeable.
-[WHISPERING] By poisoning it?
-Will you stop that!
You don't want it to taste nice.
I want them to be glad when I get back,
that's all.
[MRS PATMORE SIGHS]
This will be for the family
and the one in my pantry is for the staff,
or, more precisely, me.
We don't normally provide two.
Then perhaps we should find
another supplier.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Hold your horses.
All right, where do you see
this other telephone?
Here, in the outer hall.
Good afternoon, Carson. Is Lady Edith in?
I am! I most certainly am!
-I was just driving past...
-Yes?
...and I thought you might like to come
for a spin, if you're not too busy.
Wait till I get my coat!
Is it all right if I make some notes?
I'm so sorry, Mister...
Oh, this is Mr. Bromidge, milady.
He's here about the telephone.
Oh, please make your notes,
dear Mr. Bromidge.
We're so looking forward to it.
What an exciting business to be in!
You must be expanding every day.
Oh, we are, sir, but
that brings its problems.
Training up men for the work,
when many have no aptitude.
I can't even find a secretary
who can keep pace at the moment.
-What?
-It's hard with a new concept.
Too old, and they can't change.
Too young, and they've no experience.
But have you filled the post yet?
Because I know just the woman.
Well, she must hurry up.
We'll close the list tomorrow night.
You'll have her application, I promise.
CARSON: Hmm.
This isn't bad at all, is it?
I don't know. No one told me
there'd be an actual operation.
What did you think?
They were just going to make
magic passes over your eyes?
-All right, Mrs. Patmore?
-She'll be fine, thank you.
And you've been sent to us
by the Earl of Grantham?
That's right.
Very good. You can leave her now.
We'll keep her in for a week.
You can collect her next Friday.
I'll be in to visit every day.
What about the rest of the time?
Don't worry.
[SNIFFLES]
You'll be fine.
Bates, you say?
John Bates. He must have left the army
about eight years ago.
Wait here, please.
-Have you finished the soup?
-I think so, Mrs. Bird.
-And the sauce for the fish?
-Yes, Mrs. Bird.
Well, then, put them in the warmer.
You don't mean John Bates,
who went to prison for theft?
That's correct.
Well, I know who he is right enough.
That was an odd business.
Why odd?
Never mind.
So, you're his cousin
and you'd like to be in touch?
Very forgiving.
Well, I've got no address
for him or his wife,
but I have got one for his mother
which should still be good.
I've written it down for you.
Thank you for your trouble.
Is it true you wrote
to the Turkish Ambassador about Kemal?
-Who told you?
-Someone who knows that you did.
Then why are you asking?
Because I wanted to give you
one last chance to deny it.
And what if I did?
He had a right to know
how his countryman died,
in the arms of a slut.
How's that advertisement getting on
for the new maid?
Well, it's only just come out.
William and I can manage here now.
Go and tell Mrs. Bird
we'll have our dinner in 20 minutes.
Carson, be sure to say to Mrs. Bird
the dinner was really delicious.
SYBIL: Oh, thank you.
So, how was the drive?
It was lovely. Only...
Yes?
Well, he said he had a question for me.
He told me he'd ask it at the garden
party, and he hopes I'll say yes.
You must think very carefully
what your answer will be.
Yes, I should think very carefully
about a lot of things.
-Do your neighbors have one?
-Yes, they do, in London anyway.
MATTHEW: It seems very wise
to get a telephone now.
If there is a war, it may be very hard
to have one installed in a private house.
Well, let me show you
where we're going to put it.
Ah!
First electricity, now telephones.
Sometimes I feel as if I were living
in an H.G. Wells' novel.
[DOOR CLOSES]
But the young are all so calm
about change, aren't they?
Look at Matthew, I do admire him.
Do you?
-What have I done wrong now?
-Oh, please.
Don't pretend Mary's sudden reluctance
can't be traced back to you.
I shall pretend it, I
told her to take him.
Your quarrel is with my
daughter, Rosamund, not me.
So, put that in your pipe and smoke it.
[CHUCKLES]
[DOOR OPENS]
Mr. Molesley, what are you after?
I wanted a word with Mr. Carson.
I'm here to have me dinner.
-You don't want much, do you?
-What were you doing?
Mr. Carson dropped his wallet
in the passage. I was replacing it.
But everything seemed so settled
between you at Sybil's ball.
Things have changed since then.
Not necessarily.
I don't seem to be much good
at making boys.
Any more than I'm much good
at building my life on shifting sands.
You do know I should be very proud
to have you as my son-in-law,
whatever your prospects.
Unfortunately, sir,
your daughter is more practical than you.
-Will you join us, Mrs. Bird?
-I don't mind if I do.
I'm not sure Mrs. Patmore would like that,
Mr Carson.
"Cook always eats separate,"
that's what she says.
Not in our house.
There's only the four of us.
Well, you're going any minute.
She's advertised for your replacement.
That filthy, ungrateful cow.
Let the kitchen maids have theirs
on their own.
You stay with us.
Her ladyship said to tell you
that the dinner was delicious.
She can't have!
Daisy, does that surprise you?
[SPITS]
What have you done with this,
you little beggar?
I knew it.
That's why I said it was for upstairs.
Come on, tell us what's in it!
Just water and a bit of soap.
And you've put something
in the fish sauce as well?
Only mustard and aniseed.
Why, Daisy?
Why would you do such a thing?
[SOBBING]
Mrs Patmore was worried that
they'd prefer Mrs. Bird's cooking,
and they wouldn't want her to come back.
Is that likely? When they've taken
such trouble to get her well?
I'm sorry.
There, there.
There are worse crimes
on earth than loyalty.
Dry your eyes, and fetch the beef stew
I was making for tomorrow.
You've not had a chance to spoil that,
I suppose.
I was going to mix in some syrup of figs
-[ALL CHUCKLING]
-...but I've not done it yet.
Well, at least we'd have all been regular.
Carson said you were here.
Ah! Just checking that
everything's being done right, milady.
Only we never heard back.
That is, Miss Dawson
never heard back from you.
-About an interview?
-Ah, yes.
We got the young lady's letter,
but the trouble is,
she didn't have any experience
of hard work that I could tell, so...
-But she's a very hard worker!
-Oh, I couldn't find any proof of it.
And she gave you as a reference
when you don't run a business, milady.
Well, not that I'm aware of.
Lily, can you find Gwen
and tell her to come to the hall, now.
Yes, milady.
The reason Gwen didn't give any more
details is because she works here,
as a housemaid.
[CHUCKLES] Ah!
And you thought that'd put me off?
But she's taken a postal course
and has good speeds in typing
and Pitman shorthand.
-Test her.
-I will, if I like the look of her.
Ah! So, young lady.
You thought I'd turn up my nose
at a housemaid?
Why, I did, sir.
Well, my mother was a housemaid.
I've got nothing against housemaids.
They know about hard work and long hours,
that's for sure.
I believe so, sir.
All right, well,
is there somewhere we could talk?
Gwen, take Mr. Bromidge to the library.
I'll see no one disturbs you.
Sorry, Papa, you can't go in there.
Why on earth not?
Gwen's in there with Mr. Bromidge.
She's being interviewed.
I cannot use my library
because one of the housemaids
is in there applying for another job?
That's about the size of it.
[GROANS]
So, what is it you want to know?
I want to know the truth
about the case against him.
I want to know why
the sergeant thought it was odd.
I want to know what Mr. Bates isn't saying.
Because you don't
believe him to be guilty?
No, I don't.
I know he's not.
Well, you're right of course.
Then who was it? Who was the thief?
His wife, Vera.
Who do you call
if no one you know has got one?
But they will have. You'll see.
Might I inquire why my pantry
has become a common room?
Sorry, Mr. Carson.
But do you know how it works?
Of course I do.
-Will you show us?
-Certainly not!
A telephone is not a toy,
but a useful and valuable tool.
Now, get back to your work.
[BLOWS]
She worked at the barracks sometimes,
and helping at big dinners and so on.
That night her opportunity came
and she took it.
They knew it was her.
Someone even saw her with a big carryall.
But why did he confess?
[SIGHS WEARILY]
Well, John wasn't the same man
in those days.
The African war had shaken him up
and made him angry.
He'd been wounded.
And he drank a lot more
than was good for him.
-Was he violent?
-No.
No, not violent.
But he could be hard at times,
with a tongue like a razor.
He felt he'd ruined
Vera's life, Miss Smith.
-Do you agree with him?
-No.
No, I thought she was
a nasty piece of work.
But that's why he took the blame.
-Surely, if everyone knew he was innocent...
-But he confessed.
There was nothing anybody could do
once he'd confessed.
Could I ask you something, sir? Only,
I get the feeling that a war's on the way.
I'm afraid we all do.
And when it comes,
I want to be really useful to my country.
How heartening!
So, I've been thinking, what could be
more useful than what you do?
Bringing people back
to health, back to life.
I see.
Well, we are looking for volunteers
to train for the Territorial Force
hospitals, if that's what you mean.
It's exactly what I mean.
-Will you not be missed here?
-Maybe.
But we'll all be going, won't we?
The younger men anyway.
As you wish. I'll make inquiries.
Thank you very much, Doctor.
CARSON: Mr. Molesley walked in
and there he was, as bold as brass,
taking my wallet out of my change coat.
Mr. Molesley would have no reason
to make it up, milord.
He doesn't know Thomas. Why would he lie?
So, Thomas has been caught red-handed.
Well, we knew he was a thief, didn't we?
And now we have unimpeachable proof.
-I'm afraid he has to go.
-Oh, I hate this sort of thing.
With Lady Grantham's condition
and everything.
Can we at least wait
until after the garden party?
Very well, milord.
But then, I think we must act.
-How long will you wear them?
-A week or so.
But I can see much better already,
even with them on.
Thank heaven! Now, we need
to talk about the garden party.
Mrs. Bird and I have made some lists...
[CHUCKLING] Mrs. Bird?
Ooh, I think we can manage
without any help from Mrs. Bird.
Can you?
Well, if you want your garden party to be
run by a Blind Pugh, that's your business.
Mrs. Patmore, there's a lot to be done
and you're only just up on your feet.
-We really cannot manage without Mrs. Bird.
-If you say so.
Now, I've been checking the stores
and I've ordered what you'll need
for the baking.
That's very kind, Mrs. Hughes.
But I believe we should check the stores,
when it's convenient.
Mrs. Bird, at Downton Abbey
the housekeeper manages
the store cupboard, but...
I've never not run me own store cupboard
in me life.
Separate the cook from the store cupboard?
Where's the sense in that?
How long have I been
saying this, oh, Lord?
We're the ones who cook it.
We should be the ones to order it.
Mrs. Bird, I shall be very happy
with your help with the garden party.
I'm sure we can manage it easily,
between the two of us.
[CLEARING THROAT]
Hello, this is Downton Abbey.
Carson, the butler, speaking.
[CLEARING THROAT]
Mmm.
Hello, this is Mr. Carson,
the butler of Downton Abbey.
To whom am I speaking?
WOMAN: There's no need to shout,
thank you. I'M not deaf.
I'm not shouting! Who are you?
-Mrs Gaunt.
-Oh, Mrs. Gaunt.
-What number do you want?
-No, I don't want to place a call.
What were you doing, then?
I was practicing my answer.
Sounds stupid to me.
Well, I dare say a lot of the things
you do sound stupid to other people!
I've written to your mother.
She's very anxious, naturally.
-She suggested coming over.
-Oh, God.
Well, that's what I thought.
So, I put her off,
told her to come and admire the baby.
-I'll just go and run your ladyship's bath.
-Thank you, O'Brien.
Ooh, have you had any answers
about the position?
Quite a few.
COUNTESS: So, what do they sound like?
CORA: There's one I think
has real possibilities.
She learned to do hair in Paris,
while she was working
for the Ambassadress.
COUNTESS: Oh! Oh, that sounds promising.
[DOOR OPENS]
-Carson, I've been meaning...
-ANNA: Your lordship.
Oh! Anna, you're back safely, then?
Yes, thank you, milord.
And Mrs. Patmore's fighting fit again.
"Fighting fit" is the phrase.
-Is something the matter?
-I wanted to see your lordship because...
Please.
While I was in London,
I learned something about Mr. Bates.
-Not bad, I hope.
-No, not bad at all.
I'd have told Mr. Carson,
but I thought you might like to hear it
from me first.
Go on.
You see, I went to call on
Mr. Bates's mother...
O'Brien, how long do you think
it takes a lady's maid to settle in?
-Depends on the maid, milady.
-Of course it does.
Oops! Sorry.
-The other half's under the bath.
-Never mind. Thank you.
I'll just go and sort out
your clothes, milady.
Thank you.
Sarah O'Brien, this is not who you are.
-Milady, if you could just wait...
-[CORA SCREAMS]
[THUD]
The doctor's gone, your lordship.
But he's coming back after dinner.
-Lady Mary's with her now.
-Thank you.
I don't suppose you'll want to change.
But is there anything else
I can do to be useful?
It was a boy.
[SOBBING]
I'm sorry. I don't mean to embarrass you.
I'm not embarrassed. I just wish
you could have been spared this.
I know you do.
Thank you.
By the way, Anna's told me
what she learned in London.
Has she? She's not told me.
Oh!
Well, the good news is
you won't be leaving Downton.
And I need some good news today.
[DOOR OPENS]
MRS HUGHES: That poor wee babe.
ANNA: How's her ladyship doing?
MRS HUGHES:
I'll take her up a tray in a minute,
but I dare say she won't touch a bite.
WILLIAM: What about you, Miss O'Brien?
-What about me?
-That must have been quite a shock.
Yes. Yes, it was.
CARSON: I think you'd better dine
with us, Mr. Branson.
We can't know if you
might be needed later.
Well, I'm to go for the doctor at 10:00.
THOMAS: What a long-faced lot!
Kindly show some respect.
Come on, Mr. Carson. She'll get over it.
They're no bigger than a hamster
at that stage.
Will you shut up?
I agree. What is the
matter with you, Thomas?
I don't know. I suppose all this
makes me feel claustrophobic.
I mean, I'm sorry, course I am,
but why must we live through them?
They're just our employers.
They're not our flesh and blood.
Thomas, don't be so unkind.
Is there nothing left on earth
that you respect?
Hark at him.
Blimey, if he carries on like this
for the unborn baby of a woman
who scarcely knows his name,
no wonder he fell to pieces
when his old mum snuffed it.
CARSON: William!
[ALL EXCLAIMING]
Thomas! William! Stop
that! That is enough!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[PLATES SHATTERING]
Here!
Calm down.
[PANTING]
BRANSON: He had that coming.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
CLARKSON: Oh, Thomas.
I've done as I promised.
General Burton is commanding
the division at Richmond
and I think I may have a place there
for you, under Colonel Cartwright.
These are the papers.
When you're ready,
report to the local recruiting office
and they'll take it from there.
As a matter of fact,
I'm being drafted back in as a captain,
so I'll try to keep an eye on you.
That's very kind of you, Doctor.
With any luck, there may be some advantage
in your having volunteered so early.
WILLIAM: Oh, hang on a minute.
Now, give me yours
and take this one at the same time.
William, I'm sorry
I've been so unkind to you lately.
-Oh, that's all right.
-No, it's not all right.
-I don't know why I said those things.
-You were under an evil spell.
-I'm not under it any more.
-I'm glad.
-Friends?
-Always friends.
I think we should start the ices now.
-If you agree, Mrs. Patmore.
-Certainly, Mrs Bird.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Oh, my Lord, listen to that.
It's like the cry of a banshee.
Mr. Carson's telephone is ringing.
Isn't someone going to answer it?
I wouldn't touch that thing
with a ten-foot pole.
Well, I will, then.
BROMIDGE: is Mr. Carson there?
No, Mr. Carson's busy,
but can I take a message?
I wish ours was.
I've got news, milady.
[WHISPERING]
[GASPING] Oh, sorry.
Mr. Bromidge has rung!
You've done it, Gwen! You've got the job!
[GASPS EXCITEDLY]
Take it! Take it!
[ALL LAUGHING]
Something to celebrate?
I've got the job, Mrs. Hughes!
I'm a secretary. I've begun.
I'm very happy for you, Gwen.
And we'll celebrate
after we've finished today's work.
Of course, Mrs. Hughes.
-I don't suppose...
-MRS HUGHES: Lady Sybil.
Her ladyship was asking after you.
Be careful, my lad.
Or you'll end up with no job
and a broken heart.
What do you mean?
-I don't seem to be able to find your sister.
-I wonder where she is.
Of course, she may have been cornered.
I know there was some old bore
she was trying to dodge.
-Ah, who was that?
-I'm not sure.
He's simply ghastly, apparently,
but he's promised to propose today.
I can't tell you how funny she was
when she acted it out.
-She ought to go on the stage.
-Really?
Ah, how amusing.
Well done, Mrs. Hughes.
Beautifully executed, as always.
The key is in the planning.
Mr. Carson, this probably isn't the moment,
but I've just heard from Dr. Clarkson
I've been accepted for a training scheme
for the army medical corps.
-Have you indeed?
-Yes, and I want to do it.
So I'll be handing in my notice.
I'll serve out the month, of course.
Thank you, Thomas.
We can talk about it later.
And you couldn't have planned that
any better, either.
[CHUCKLES]
-You can't be leaving yet!
-I'm afraid I must.
Please, make my excuses to your mother.
But...
I wish you'd come inside, milady.
No.
People mustn't think I'm really ill.
I don't want to cast a
dampener on the party.
Very well.
But are you sure you have everything
you need, milady?
Dear O'Brien.
How sweet you are.
O'Brien! O'Brien!
Can I have a word?
I need a favor and I don't want
to bother Lady Grantham with it.
Certainly, milady.
She's been helping me find a new maid
and we've had quite a few answers
from her advertisement.
Can you find where she's put them
and get Branson to bring them
to the Dower House?
Her ladyship was helping you
find a new lady's maid?
Yes. We should have asked you, really.
You might take a look at the letters
if you have a minute.
There's one we liked the sound of,
who'd been trained in Paris.
Do you know where
she might have put them?
The answers?
Oh, yes, milady. There are only
two or three places they could be.
Oh! Thank you, O'Brien.
You're a treasure. Thank you.
I didn't know a garden party
was a spectator sport.
Pretty, though, isn't it?
Hard to believe the clouds are gathering
on a summer's day like this.
Mr. Bates, I know you think I was wrong
to call on your mother.
I don't think that.
She likes you, by the way.
I had to find out the truth.
But you see, you don't know
the whole truth, not even now.
-You know my mother's truth.
-But not your wife's?
-Where is she now?
-I couldn't tell you.
I'd better get back.
You're here, Mr. Molesley?
I didn't know that.
Just helping out.
Nice girl, that Anna.
Do you know if she's got anyone special
in her life?
I'd like to say she hasn't.
I would, truly.
But I'm afraid there is someone.
And do you think he's keen on her?
Or is it worth a go?
Well, he keeps himself to himself,
and he's very hard to read at times,
but I'd say he's keen.
I'd say he's very keen indeed.
Daisy! I said ices, not iced cakes!
Now, unclog your ears
and get these to William
before they turn into soup!
-But I don't understand, nothing's changed.
-Everything's changed.
You can't be sure I was going to
refuse you, even if it had been a boy.
-Because I'm not.
-That's the point.
I can't be sure.
Of you, or of anything, it seems.
The last few weeks have taught me that.
But you can't leave Downton.
I can't stay. Not now.
Well, what will you tell Papa?
That I'm grateful for what he's trying
to do, but the experiment is at an end.
I'm not a puppet.
I must take charge of my own life again.
Would you have stayed,
if I'd accepted you?
Of course.
So I've ruined everything?
You've shown me I've been living in a
dream, and it's time to return to real life.
Wish me luck with it, Mary.
God knows I wish the best for you.
Well, Rosamund.
I'm afraid your meddling has cost Mary
the only decent offer she'll ever get.
I'm sorry, Mama, but you know me.
I have to say what I think.
Why? Nobody else does.
Are you quite well, milady?
Of course! You know me, Carson.
I'm never down for long.
[SOBBING]
I know you have spirit, milady.
And that's what counts.
It's all that counts in the end.
There, there.
So Mary is to be denied
her countess's coronet after all?
Don't crow at me.
I think she was very foolish
not to take him when she could.
And I told her so.
Well, if I'm perfectly honest,
I wonder if Matthew isn't making
the same mistake right now.
Are you warm enough?
I am when you're holding my hand.
-Your lordship, this has just arrived for you.
-Thank you.
Oh, and I'm happy to tell you
that Thomas has just handed in his notice.
So we'll be spared any unpleasantness
on that score.
What a relief!
Please, would you stop, please.
My lords, ladies and gentlemen,
can I ask for silence?
Because I very much regret to announce
that we are at war with Germany.