1
00:00:02,326 --> 00:00:04,038
Mike Ross never went
to law school.

2
00:00:04,062 --> 00:00:05,975
I knew it,
and I hired him anyway.

3
00:00:06,000 --> 00:00:07,313
I still can't stay, Harvey.

4
00:00:07,337 --> 00:00:08,448
I know.

5
00:00:08,472 --> 00:00:10,586
I just want to stop lying
to the people I love.

6
00:00:10,611 --> 00:00:12,290
This makes it look like
Forstman's payment

7
00:00:12,314 --> 00:00:13,492
never went to
any offshore accounts.

8
00:00:13,517 --> 00:00:14,795
That's forgery.

9
00:00:14,819 --> 00:00:16,633
Which is less of a crime
than what you did.

10
00:00:16,657 --> 00:00:17,658
I had no choice.

11
00:00:17,660 --> 00:00:19,037
Bullshit, you had no choice.

12
00:00:19,061 --> 00:00:20,974
You could've said no at
any goddamn point along the way.

13
00:00:20,999 --> 00:00:23,548
One thing is for sure:
When all this is over,

14
00:00:23,572 --> 00:00:25,452
I'm gonna fire the shit
out of you.

15
00:00:25,476 --> 00:00:26,477
I went to Robert Zane,

16
00:00:26,478 --> 00:00:27,822
and I asked him
to give Louis a job.

17
00:00:27,847 --> 00:00:30,161
You want to see if I can break
my partnership agreement.

18
00:00:30,186 --> 00:00:32,668
If you can't do that,
what the hell good are you?

19
00:00:32,692 --> 00:00:35,005
Louis won't be going to Zane,
and neither will you.

20
00:00:35,030 --> 00:00:37,244
I'm here to ask you
to take Louis anyway.

21
00:00:37,268 --> 00:00:38,546
And why would I do that?

22
00:00:38,571 --> 00:00:39,616
If you do, I'll owe you one.

23
00:00:39,640 --> 00:00:41,051
Mike Ross doesn't forget
anything.

24
00:00:41,076 --> 00:00:42,956
See, the reason
he didn't recognize this

25
00:00:42,980 --> 00:00:44,894
is because he didn't go
to Harvard.

26
00:00:44,919 --> 00:00:48,603
You've been lying to me
since the day Mike Ross arrived.

27
00:00:48,627 --> 00:00:49,805
I am your friend, Louis.

28
00:00:49,830 --> 00:00:50,874
No, you're not.

29
00:00:50,898 --> 00:00:52,410
And don't you ever say that
to me again.

30
00:00:52,435 --> 00:00:53,879
You might as well spit it out.

31
00:00:53,903 --> 00:00:56,419
You asked me what I wanted
once before, and I told you,

32
00:00:56,444 --> 00:00:58,256
and then you told me
that I couldn't have it.

33
00:00:58,280 --> 00:01:01,764
Pearson...

34
00:01:01,788 --> 00:01:06,273
Specter...

35
00:01:06,297 --> 00:01:08,067
Litt.

36
00:01:13,113 --> 00:01:21,122
♪

37
00:01:48,690 --> 00:01:50,102
Want to tell me
what was so important

38
00:01:50,127 --> 00:01:51,128
I had to get back here?

39
00:01:51,129 --> 00:01:53,066
He knows.

40
00:01:55,238 --> 00:01:56,683
I know what you're thinking.

41
00:01:56,707 --> 00:02:00,291
Why didn't Donna tell you?

42
00:02:00,316 --> 00:02:04,434
I'll tell you why.

43
00:02:04,459 --> 00:02:06,905
Because as my first official act
as name as name partner,

44
00:02:06,930 --> 00:02:07,931
I told her not to.

45
00:02:09,403 --> 00:02:10,404
What?

46
00:02:10,405 --> 00:02:12,418
You heard me.

47
00:02:12,443 --> 00:02:13,888
You can look at her
as long as you want.

48
00:02:13,912 --> 00:02:15,256
She can't help you.

49
00:02:15,281 --> 00:02:17,428
Because my name's going up there
first thing tomorrow.

50
00:02:17,453 --> 00:02:18,454
No, it isn't.

51
00:02:18,455 --> 00:02:19,567
Yes, it is.

52
00:02:19,591 --> 00:02:20,769
But it won't be tomorrow.

53
00:02:20,794 --> 00:02:22,075
I'm not waiting
just so you can...

54
00:02:22,086 --> 00:02:23,331
Louis, I have to sell this

55
00:02:23,333 --> 00:02:24,678
to the senior partners.

56
00:02:24,702 --> 00:02:27,384
I can't just slap your name
up there one morning.

57
00:02:27,409 --> 00:02:28,888
You did it for him.

58
00:02:28,912 --> 00:02:30,123
I didn't resign the week before.

59
00:02:30,148 --> 00:02:31,693
- I don't care.
- Louis.

60
00:02:31,718 --> 00:02:32,763
That's enough.

61
00:02:32,787 --> 00:02:34,500
This is going to take time,

62
00:02:34,524 --> 00:02:36,136
and while it does, you're going
to keep this to yourself.

63
00:02:36,161 --> 00:02:37,506
Bullshit.

64
00:02:37,531 --> 00:02:39,411
You're just trying to buy time
so you can get out of this.

65
00:02:39,435 --> 00:02:40,747
I'm not trying to buy anything.

66
00:02:40,772 --> 00:02:44,589
We have an agreement,
and this is for your own good.

67
00:02:44,613 --> 00:02:45,958
Well, for your own good,

68
00:02:45,983 --> 00:02:48,185
you better remember what I'll do
if this takes too long.

69
00:02:53,431 --> 00:02:54,952
Please tell me
you had no other choice.

70
00:02:54,969 --> 00:02:56,213
You know damn well I didn't.

71
00:02:56,238 --> 00:02:57,416
No, I don't.

72
00:02:57,440 --> 00:02:59,287
That's because
you didn't see him.

73
00:02:59,311 --> 00:03:01,447
All he's ever thought about
since the day he was born

74
00:03:01,450 --> 00:03:02,928
was getting this.

75
00:03:02,953 --> 00:03:05,300
So if I have to choose
between giving it to him

76
00:03:05,325 --> 00:03:06,336
and going to jail...

77
00:03:06,360 --> 00:03:07,405
He really threatened that?

78
00:03:07,429 --> 00:03:09,041
He didn't just threaten it.

79
00:03:09,066 --> 00:03:10,913
He was going to do it.

80
00:03:10,937 --> 00:03:12,415
And what are we going to do?

81
00:03:12,440 --> 00:03:14,721
We're going to take it.

82
00:03:14,746 --> 00:03:17,126
We give him this,
it is never gonna end.

83
00:03:17,151 --> 00:03:20,868
Harvey, before you say
another word to me,

84
00:03:20,892 --> 00:03:22,939
I want you to think
about the fact

85
00:03:22,964 --> 00:03:26,379
that I just ate
a big bowl of shit

86
00:03:26,403 --> 00:03:28,350
because you brought that kid
into my house.

87
00:03:28,374 --> 00:03:31,356
And I had to take it,

88
00:03:31,381 --> 00:03:33,051
so you're going to take it.

89
00:03:40,501 --> 00:03:41,502
Harvey.

90
00:03:41,503 --> 00:03:42,504
You don't need to say it.

91
00:03:42,506 --> 00:03:45,188
Yeah, I do.

92
00:03:45,212 --> 00:03:47,425
Louis came looking for you,
and I didn't know what to do.

93
00:03:47,450 --> 00:03:50,399
He was gonna call Sheila
and tell her everything.

94
00:03:50,423 --> 00:03:51,935
I'd never seen him
like that before.

95
00:03:51,960 --> 00:03:52,938
Donna, this is not on you.

96
00:03:52,962 --> 00:03:54,875
Yes, it is.

97
00:03:54,900 --> 00:03:57,246
He pressed me, and I broke.

98
00:03:57,270 --> 00:03:59,350
It doesn't matter,
because he already knew.

99
00:03:59,375 --> 00:04:00,620
How can you know that?

100
00:04:00,644 --> 00:04:03,193
Because I know Louis,
and I know you.

101
00:04:03,218 --> 00:04:04,997
And he couldn't have broken you

102
00:04:05,021 --> 00:04:06,600
unless he knew
the truth already.

103
00:04:06,625 --> 00:04:08,270
So this is not your fault,

104
00:04:08,295 --> 00:04:10,017
and I never want to hear you
say that again.

105
00:04:10,032 --> 00:04:12,113
I should've at least warned you
before you got here.

106
00:04:12,137 --> 00:04:14,219
All that would have done
was antagonize him even more

107
00:04:14,242 --> 00:04:17,658
because he would've known
you did it.

108
00:04:17,682 --> 00:04:20,029
You did everything
you could've done.

109
00:04:20,054 --> 00:04:21,355
Okay.

110
00:04:24,363 --> 00:04:26,009
We have to tell Mike.

111
00:04:26,034 --> 00:04:27,146
No, we don't. Not now.

112
00:04:27,171 --> 00:04:28,148
Harvey.

113
00:04:28,172 --> 00:04:30,051
Look, I'll tell him
in the morning.

114
00:04:30,075 --> 00:04:31,420
We just had a huge win,

115
00:04:31,445 --> 00:04:33,448
and I am not in the mood
to ruin his night.

116
00:04:39,663 --> 00:04:41,032
Louis.

117
00:04:44,574 --> 00:04:45,575
What are you doing here?

118
00:04:49,117 --> 00:04:50,196
They didn't tell you.

119
00:04:50,220 --> 00:04:51,531
Tell me what?

120
00:04:51,556 --> 00:04:55,440
Jessica made me name partner.

121
00:04:55,465 --> 00:04:56,466
But, uh...

122
00:04:56,467 --> 00:04:58,112
But? But?

123
00:04:58,137 --> 00:04:59,514
But what?

124
00:04:59,539 --> 00:05:02,188
I resigned in shame?

125
00:05:02,212 --> 00:05:05,562
Well, that's all changed,
and it's all because of you.

126
00:05:05,586 --> 00:05:06,865
Remember this?

127
00:05:06,890 --> 00:05:08,168
No, you don't,

128
00:05:08,192 --> 00:05:12,109
because you can't remember
something you never knew.

129
00:05:12,134 --> 00:05:13,746
Cool to the end.

130
00:05:13,771 --> 00:05:16,753
Well, it doesn't matter,
because Donna told me.

131
00:05:16,778 --> 00:05:18,156
And Harvey.

132
00:05:18,180 --> 00:05:19,325
And Jessica.

133
00:05:19,350 --> 00:05:21,630
When I told them
that I knew you were a fraud,

134
00:05:21,655 --> 00:05:24,137
did they run from you
like you were the plague.

135
00:05:24,161 --> 00:05:25,162
What do you want?

136
00:05:25,163 --> 00:05:26,574
I already got
what I wanted from you.

137
00:05:26,599 --> 00:05:28,178
- Name partner.
- You must want something else.

138
00:05:28,202 --> 00:05:29,483
Otherwise, you wouldn't be here.

139
00:05:29,505 --> 00:05:31,185
See, that's what
I love about you, Mike.

140
00:05:31,209 --> 00:05:33,390
Almost always a step ahead.

141
00:05:33,415 --> 00:05:35,161
What I want from you

142
00:05:35,185 --> 00:05:38,401
is to know that you're dead
at my law firm.

143
00:05:38,426 --> 00:05:39,603
You can't fire me.

144
00:05:39,627 --> 00:05:41,341
Why would I fire you
when I can break you?

145
00:05:41,365 --> 00:05:46,685
You see, I'm going to bury you
under a mountain of shit so big

146
00:05:46,710 --> 00:05:48,990
you're going to be begging me
to take it off.

147
00:05:49,015 --> 00:05:50,828
And all you have to do
is say two simple words...

148
00:05:50,852 --> 00:05:52,898
The same two words
that you let me say

149
00:05:52,922 --> 00:05:55,003
to Harvey and Jessica.

150
00:05:55,028 --> 00:05:57,398
"I resign."

151
00:06:05,485 --> 00:06:07,164
Louis.

152
00:06:07,188 --> 00:06:09,102
- What are you doing here?
- Leaving.

153
00:06:09,126 --> 00:06:12,097
That way I don't have to look at
either one of you two liars.

154
00:06:16,708 --> 00:06:18,989
Oh, my God, he knows.

155
00:06:19,014 --> 00:06:21,595
He doesn't just know.

156
00:06:21,619 --> 00:06:23,523
He's a name partner.

157
00:06:26,764 --> 00:06:30,447
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪

158
00:06:30,472 --> 00:06:33,789
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪

159
00:06:33,813 --> 00:06:36,962
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪

160
00:06:36,987 --> 00:06:40,671
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪

161
00:06:40,695 --> 00:06:43,643
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪

162
00:06:43,668 --> 00:06:47,651
♪ Me and Missy is so busy,
busy making money ♪

163
00:06:47,676 --> 00:06:49,112
♪ All right

164
00:06:49,113 --> 00:06:50,627
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪

165
00:06:50,652 --> 00:06:54,656
♪ Suits 4x11 ♪ Enough Is Enough
Original Air Date on January 28, 2015

166
00:06:54,658 --> 00:06:56,628
♪ The greenback boogie

167
00:06:56,652 --> 00:07:03,159
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man.

168
00:07:04,444 --> 00:07:06,056
- You know.
- Yeah, I know.

169
00:07:06,081 --> 00:07:07,682
And a little heads up
would've been nice.

170
00:07:07,684 --> 00:07:08,963
I wanted to give you the night.

171
00:07:08,987 --> 00:07:10,432
Well, the night
kind of got blown up

172
00:07:10,457 --> 00:07:12,035
when Louis showed up
at my apartment

173
00:07:12,060 --> 00:07:14,007
and said he was gonna break me.

174
00:07:14,032 --> 00:07:15,477
What do you want from me, Mike?

175
00:07:15,501 --> 00:07:17,681
I want to know how you let him
become name partner.

176
00:07:17,706 --> 00:07:19,351
Would you rather we let him go
to the police?

177
00:07:19,376 --> 00:07:21,657
I don't believe that Louis
would actually go to the police.

178
00:07:21,682 --> 00:07:22,893
He would because Jessica said
he would.

179
00:07:22,917 --> 00:07:23,929
So if you're here to say

180
00:07:23,954 --> 00:07:25,365
that we can figure
some way out of it,

181
00:07:25,389 --> 00:07:26,801
that's not going to happen.

182
00:07:26,826 --> 00:07:29,842
He knows, and it's done.

183
00:07:29,867 --> 00:07:31,646
Did you hear what I said?

184
00:07:31,670 --> 00:07:33,916
Louis came to my apartment
filled with rage,

185
00:07:33,941 --> 00:07:35,186
and he told me he was making it

186
00:07:35,210 --> 00:07:37,423
his personal mission
to break me.

187
00:07:37,448 --> 00:07:39,462
Then you make it your mission
not to let him.

188
00:07:39,486 --> 00:07:41,166
Harvey, he's name partner.

189
00:07:41,190 --> 00:07:42,835
Did I ever tell you
the story about the gym?

190
00:07:42,860 --> 00:07:44,740
I'm not really in the mood
for a story right now.

191
00:07:44,765 --> 00:07:47,336
Then you're going to hear it
anyway.

192
00:07:50,644 --> 00:07:53,125
When I was a kid,
my father put me in boxing camp.

193
00:07:53,149 --> 00:07:55,429
Middle of summer, 90 degrees.

194
00:07:55,454 --> 00:07:57,568
Every day after sparring
in that,

195
00:07:57,592 --> 00:08:00,340
they'd make you do 100 laps
and 50 pull-ups.

196
00:08:00,365 --> 00:08:02,145
They'd push you
until you either threw up

197
00:08:02,169 --> 00:08:04,650
or passed out or both.

198
00:08:04,674 --> 00:08:06,888
Anyone could leave at any point.

199
00:08:06,913 --> 00:08:07,994
All you had to do was quit.

200
00:08:08,015 --> 00:08:09,427
And let me guess,
you didn't quit.

201
00:08:09,452 --> 00:08:10,797
I quit every goddamn day.

202
00:08:10,821 --> 00:08:12,968
I just never said it out loud.

203
00:08:12,993 --> 00:08:14,504
Because no way
was I gonna give them

204
00:08:14,529 --> 00:08:17,678
the satisfaction of breaking me.

205
00:08:17,703 --> 00:08:21,354
So I guess it's time for me
to drop down and give Louis 20.

206
00:08:21,378 --> 00:08:23,882
I think it's gonna be
a little more than 20, buddy.

207
00:08:35,741 --> 00:08:36,920
I see you noticed

208
00:08:36,945 --> 00:08:39,794
I scraped your little
associate title away.

209
00:08:39,818 --> 00:08:41,229
You scraped it away?

210
00:08:41,254 --> 00:08:43,100
Yeah, just like
I'm gonna scrape you away,

211
00:08:43,124 --> 00:08:44,702
starting with these.

212
00:08:44,727 --> 00:08:45,972
Oh, Louis, go ahead.

213
00:08:45,997 --> 00:08:47,977
Give me all of the shittiest
cases that you can find,

214
00:08:48,001 --> 00:08:49,681
but I'm telling you,

215
00:08:49,705 --> 00:08:50,749
it's not gonna break me.

216
00:08:50,774 --> 00:08:52,788
You overestimate yourself.

217
00:08:52,812 --> 00:08:54,926
Did you think when I said
I was going to bury you in shit,

218
00:08:54,951 --> 00:08:55,962
I meant legal work?

219
00:08:55,986 --> 00:08:57,231
No, no, no.

220
00:08:57,255 --> 00:08:58,466
You're not a lawyer,

221
00:08:58,491 --> 00:08:59,903
which means
you must be a paralegal,

222
00:08:59,928 --> 00:09:04,613
and that's exactly the kind
of work you're gonna be doing.

223
00:09:04,637 --> 00:09:06,584
Louis, you can't do this.

224
00:09:06,609 --> 00:09:09,123
Everyone out there
thinks of me as a lawyer.

225
00:09:09,147 --> 00:09:10,548
And two days ago,
they thought of me

226
00:09:10,551 --> 00:09:11,832
as someone who used to
work here.

227
00:09:11,854 --> 00:09:13,232
Look at us now.

228
00:09:13,257 --> 00:09:15,070
Oh, and if you're thinking
of crying to Harvey.

229
00:09:15,094 --> 00:09:16,272
That would be a major mistake,

230
00:09:16,296 --> 00:09:18,801
because this is
between you and me.

231
00:09:26,420 --> 00:09:28,400
What are you doing here?

232
00:09:28,424 --> 00:09:30,303
I'm here because
I know you're angry

233
00:09:30,327 --> 00:09:32,440
and you're feeling betrayed,
but I am not gonna let you

234
00:09:32,465 --> 00:09:34,312
throw our friendship away.

235
00:09:34,336 --> 00:09:35,414
I can't throw away something

236
00:09:35,439 --> 00:09:36,951
that never existed
in the first place.

237
00:09:36,976 --> 00:09:38,421
- Louis...
- Donna, we're not friends.

238
00:09:38,445 --> 00:09:40,927
We were never friends, because
it was all based on a lie.

239
00:09:40,951 --> 00:09:42,529
So you think my giving you this

240
00:09:42,554 --> 00:09:44,434
and every other nice thing
that I ever did for you

241
00:09:44,459 --> 00:09:46,406
was just to keep you from
finding out about Mike?

242
00:09:46,430 --> 00:09:48,410
No, I don't.

243
00:09:48,434 --> 00:09:49,745
But I do think
if you had the chance

244
00:09:49,770 --> 00:09:51,349
to take back
all those nice things you did

245
00:09:51,374 --> 00:09:53,787
in exchange for me never finding
out about your little secret,

246
00:09:53,812 --> 00:09:54,924
you'd do it in a heartbeat.

247
00:09:54,948 --> 00:09:56,392
You want a chance
to tell me the truth?

248
00:09:56,417 --> 00:09:58,933
Go ahead.
Tell me the truth right now.

249
00:09:58,957 --> 00:10:00,803
And that answers my question.

250
00:10:00,827 --> 00:10:01,872
You know what, Louis?

251
00:10:01,897 --> 00:10:03,141
It was a bullshit question

252
00:10:03,165 --> 00:10:05,446
designed to do nothing
but make me feel like shit.

253
00:10:05,471 --> 00:10:07,049
Mission accomplished.

254
00:10:07,074 --> 00:10:08,720
And now I'm gonna tell you
what I told Mike.

255
00:10:08,745 --> 00:10:10,692
- You're dead to me.
- Okay.

256
00:10:10,716 --> 00:10:12,696
You want to hate me? Hate me.

257
00:10:12,721 --> 00:10:14,567
You want to hate Mike?
Hate Mike.

258
00:10:14,591 --> 00:10:16,705
But everybody at this firm
can't be dead to you,

259
00:10:16,730 --> 00:10:19,076
because sooner or later,
you're going to need someone.

260
00:10:19,101 --> 00:10:20,179
Thank you, Donna,

261
00:10:20,203 --> 00:10:22,373
but that someone
isn't going to be you.

262
00:10:28,655 --> 00:10:29,933
Donna said you wanted to see me.

263
00:10:29,958 --> 00:10:32,039
No, I didn't want to see you,

264
00:10:32,063 --> 00:10:33,641
I needed to see you.

265
00:10:33,666 --> 00:10:35,067
I know you're under
a lot of stress,

266
00:10:35,070 --> 00:10:37,483
but that was a one-time thing.

267
00:10:37,508 --> 00:10:39,087
I don't need you to do that
to me.

268
00:10:39,112 --> 00:10:40,257
Louis has already done it.

269
00:10:40,281 --> 00:10:41,426
What are you talking about?

270
00:10:41,451 --> 00:10:42,528
Look at this.

271
00:10:42,552 --> 00:10:45,267
He's buried me
in paralegal work.

272
00:10:45,291 --> 00:10:47,337
Okay, that's bullshit.
He can't treat you like that.

273
00:10:47,362 --> 00:10:49,409
Rachel, I don't care
how he treats me, all right?

274
00:10:49,433 --> 00:10:51,413
I can take it
until he gets over this.

275
00:10:51,438 --> 00:10:52,883
But look at these deadlines.

276
00:10:52,907 --> 00:10:54,587
There's no way I can get
all of this work done

277
00:10:54,611 --> 00:10:55,622
on time without your help.

278
00:10:55,647 --> 00:10:57,168
I will do whatever you need,
but, Mike,

279
00:10:57,184 --> 00:10:59,531
he is not going to get over it
until you make him get over it.

280
00:10:59,555 --> 00:11:01,868
- Rachel, please...
- Mike.

281
00:11:01,893 --> 00:11:05,544
The day after what happened
in here happened,

282
00:11:05,569 --> 00:11:06,680
I shut you out.

283
00:11:06,704 --> 00:11:09,051
But then, a week later,
you came to my door,

284
00:11:09,076 --> 00:11:11,758
and you said you weren't gonna
let me go without a fight.

285
00:11:11,782 --> 00:11:13,127
That is not the same.

286
00:11:13,152 --> 00:11:15,099
I wanted you
to fall in love with me.

287
00:11:15,123 --> 00:11:18,606
I was already in love with you,
and you knew it.

288
00:11:18,631 --> 00:11:20,243
Yeah, well,
Louis is a lot of things,

289
00:11:20,268 --> 00:11:23,383
but he's not in love with me.

290
00:11:23,407 --> 00:11:26,389
He used to be.

291
00:11:26,414 --> 00:11:28,317
You just have to
make him remember that.

292
00:11:31,525 --> 00:11:33,071
Okay, the first thing
we need to do

293
00:11:33,096 --> 00:11:34,574
is finish all of this work.

294
00:11:34,599 --> 00:11:35,777
Okay.

295
00:11:35,801 --> 00:11:38,383
Unless, of course,
that offer still stands.

296
00:11:38,407 --> 00:11:39,818
I don't recall making an offer.

297
00:11:39,843 --> 00:11:41,623
You did say whatever I need.

298
00:11:41,647 --> 00:11:42,992
That's not what I meant.

299
00:11:43,017 --> 00:11:45,788
And then you said never
take no for an answer, so...

300
00:11:47,994 --> 00:11:51,177
Lock the doors.

301
00:11:51,202 --> 00:11:52,881
- Are you serious...
- Take yes for an answer.

302
00:11:52,905 --> 00:11:54,374
I'm locking the door.

303
00:11:56,848 --> 00:11:58,560
Louis, you sounded urgent
on the phone.

304
00:11:58,584 --> 00:11:59,585
What's going on?

305
00:11:59,586 --> 00:12:01,399
I'll tell you what's going on.

306
00:12:01,423 --> 00:12:02,936
I'm back at Pearson Specter.

307
00:12:02,961 --> 00:12:04,139
What?

308
00:12:04,164 --> 00:12:05,175
I don't understand.

309
00:12:05,199 --> 00:12:07,680
Let me explain it to you.

310
00:12:07,704 --> 00:12:09,217
I just became name partner.

311
00:12:09,242 --> 00:12:13,025
Louis, this is amazing.

312
00:12:13,049 --> 00:12:14,829
I'm so happy for you.

313
00:12:14,854 --> 00:12:15,966
Okay, well, you can keep
being happy for me,

314
00:12:15,990 --> 00:12:17,235
but you better start
being happy for you,

315
00:12:17,260 --> 00:12:18,436
because I'm bringing you back.

316
00:12:18,460 --> 00:12:21,209
What? I... oh.

317
00:12:21,233 --> 00:12:23,546
Katrina Amanda Bennett,

318
00:12:23,571 --> 00:12:26,788
will you be my associate?

319
00:12:26,813 --> 00:12:29,861
Louis Marlowe Litt,

320
00:12:29,886 --> 00:12:31,766
I will be your associate.

321
00:12:31,790 --> 00:12:33,169
Again.

322
00:12:33,194 --> 00:12:34,873
You've just made me
the happiest attorney on earth.

323
00:12:34,897 --> 00:12:36,944
When do we consummate our new
preexisting relationship?

324
00:12:36,968 --> 00:12:39,148
As soon as my new position
is official.

325
00:12:39,173 --> 00:12:41,453
- Wait, why isn't it official?
- I can't tell you that.

326
00:12:41,478 --> 00:12:43,558
Louis, I think I've more than
proven you can trust me.

327
00:12:43,582 --> 00:12:44,583
Oh, are you kidding me?

328
00:12:44,585 --> 00:12:45,797
You're the only one I can trust.

329
00:12:45,821 --> 00:12:46,865
It's not that. It's just...

330
00:12:46,889 --> 00:12:48,410
Okay, Louis,
you don't need to tell me.

331
00:12:48,426 --> 00:12:52,845
But if you won't tell me,
and they won't tell the world,

332
00:12:52,870 --> 00:12:54,014
something's wrong.

333
00:12:54,038 --> 00:12:55,451
Katrina, I know what I'm doing.

334
00:12:55,476 --> 00:12:57,155
And Jessica knows
what she's doing,

335
00:12:57,179 --> 00:12:58,982
which is playing you for a fool.

336
00:13:06,847 --> 00:13:09,227
Harvey, I was just gonna
call you.

337
00:13:09,251 --> 00:13:10,396
I'll save you the trouble.

338
00:13:10,421 --> 00:13:12,267
We're bringing Louis Litt
back to the firm.

339
00:13:12,291 --> 00:13:13,403
That doesn't matter.

340
00:13:13,427 --> 00:13:14,708
Because that call was
to tell you

341
00:13:14,730 --> 00:13:16,676
I'm hiring him, and you owe me.

342
00:13:16,700 --> 00:13:18,213
Bullshit.

343
00:13:18,238 --> 00:13:19,516
You calling me a liar?

344
00:13:19,541 --> 00:13:20,702
I'm not calling you anything,

345
00:13:20,709 --> 00:13:22,923
but you are calling
Sylvia out there a liar.

346
00:13:22,948 --> 00:13:25,162
Oh, no, no,
Sylvia wouldn't tell you shit.

347
00:13:25,187 --> 00:13:26,188
Wrong.

348
00:13:26,189 --> 00:13:27,434
One compliment about her hair,

349
00:13:27,458 --> 00:13:31,008
and she told me you gave Louis
the bad news an hour ago.

350
00:13:31,033 --> 00:13:32,712
See you around, Robert.

351
00:13:32,736 --> 00:13:35,218
Harvey, one more thing.

352
00:13:35,242 --> 00:13:37,289
You do still owe me that favor.

353
00:13:37,313 --> 00:13:38,524
What kind of math are you doing?

354
00:13:38,549 --> 00:13:40,328
The kind of math
that says Jessica Pearson

355
00:13:40,352 --> 00:13:43,168
hiring Louis Litt back
adds up to shady.

356
00:13:43,193 --> 00:13:45,239
If that's all you've got,
you can collect your favor

357
00:13:45,263 --> 00:13:46,809
when the clock strikes
kiss my ass,

358
00:13:46,834 --> 00:13:49,114
because partners leave firms
and come back all the time.

359
00:13:49,139 --> 00:13:52,055
Maybe, but they don't come back
with their name on the wall.

360
00:13:52,079 --> 00:13:55,127
Ah, I'm guessing he wasn't
supposed to tell me that.

361
00:13:55,152 --> 00:13:59,370
But he did, and Louis Litt
is not name partner material,

362
00:13:59,394 --> 00:14:01,709
which means he must have
something on you.

363
00:14:01,734 --> 00:14:03,814
So unless you want me
going around town

364
00:14:03,838 --> 00:14:05,750
flapping my big mouth
that something isn't right

365
00:14:05,775 --> 00:14:09,792
in your kitchen, you're gonna
make good on that favor.

366
00:14:09,817 --> 00:14:11,664
Sylvia didn't slip up at all,
did she?

367
00:14:11,688 --> 00:14:12,699
No, she didn't.

368
00:14:12,723 --> 00:14:14,737
You have your girl Friday;
I have mine.

369
00:14:14,762 --> 00:14:16,642
But you can still tell her
how nice her hair looks

370
00:14:16,666 --> 00:14:17,777
on the way out.

371
00:14:17,801 --> 00:14:19,435
I'll be in touch.

372
00:14:23,446 --> 00:14:25,627
Oh, you're tapping out already?

373
00:14:25,652 --> 00:14:27,654
I thought you'd have
a lot more backbone than that.

374
00:14:27,656 --> 00:14:30,371
I'm not tapping out.

375
00:14:30,396 --> 00:14:31,641
I finished all of the work...

376
00:14:31,665 --> 00:14:33,309
Which I expected to be done
an hour ago.

377
00:14:33,334 --> 00:14:36,083
Come on, Louis, you didn't
expect it to be done at all.

378
00:14:36,108 --> 00:14:38,690
Just like
you didn't expect this.

379
00:14:38,714 --> 00:14:40,025
What the hell is that?

380
00:14:40,049 --> 00:14:41,695
It's a gift certificate.

381
00:14:41,720 --> 00:14:43,131
What, are you trying
to bribe me now?

382
00:14:43,156 --> 00:14:47,508
It's not a bribe,
it's a reminder.

383
00:14:47,532 --> 00:14:51,316
Look, the gift certificate is
from Peter's Steak House,

384
00:14:51,341 --> 00:14:53,354
the place that you and I saved
together.

385
00:14:53,378 --> 00:14:54,489
And after we saved it,

386
00:14:54,514 --> 00:14:56,494
you told me that
we had something in common.

387
00:14:56,518 --> 00:14:57,496
Yeah, I don't give a shit.

388
00:14:57,520 --> 00:14:58,521
Yes, you do,

389
00:14:58,523 --> 00:14:59,768
because what we had in common

390
00:14:59,792 --> 00:15:02,841
was a love of the law.

391
00:15:02,866 --> 00:15:04,187
You told me that
when you asked me

392
00:15:04,202 --> 00:15:08,253
to be your associate, Louis,
and I am still the same person.

393
00:15:08,277 --> 00:15:10,490
And if I found out a woman
I had something in common with

394
00:15:10,515 --> 00:15:12,495
was actually a man,
I wouldn't keep seeing her.

395
00:15:12,520 --> 00:15:15,035
Okay, what I did is not at all
the same thing.

396
00:15:15,059 --> 00:15:17,073
No, it's worse.

397
00:15:17,097 --> 00:15:18,508
You say you love the law
so much,

398
00:15:18,533 --> 00:15:21,382
but every single case
you've ever touched is tainted.

399
00:15:21,406 --> 00:15:23,552
So you get exposed,
Peter's gets bulldozed.

400
00:15:23,577 --> 00:15:25,724
It wouldn't even be there
to get bulldozed

401
00:15:25,749 --> 00:15:27,228
if you and I hadn't
worked together.

402
00:15:27,252 --> 00:15:29,098
All right, genius.
You want to work together?

403
00:15:29,123 --> 00:15:31,536
You love the law so much?

404
00:15:31,561 --> 00:15:34,043
You're gonna memorize
every case that I've ever done.

405
00:15:34,067 --> 00:15:35,068
Louis.

406
00:15:35,069 --> 00:15:36,114
No, get to work,

407
00:15:36,138 --> 00:15:37,951
and use that magnificent
memory of yours

408
00:15:37,975 --> 00:15:38,976
for something more than

409
00:15:38,978 --> 00:15:40,680
bullshitting
your way through life.

410
00:15:49,100 --> 00:15:50,378
We have a problem.

411
00:15:50,402 --> 00:15:52,249
Unless it's urgent,
I don't have the time.

412
00:15:52,274 --> 00:15:54,153
Louis is telling people.

413
00:15:54,177 --> 00:15:55,488
What people?

414
00:15:55,513 --> 00:15:56,791
For starters, Robert Zane.

415
00:15:56,815 --> 00:15:58,996
Why the hell is Louis even
talking to Robert Zane?

416
00:15:59,021 --> 00:16:01,301
I asked him to hire Louis
after we took back VersaLife.

417
00:16:01,326 --> 00:16:02,872
And you didn't think to tell me
that after last night?

418
00:16:02,897 --> 00:16:04,141
I was handling it.

419
00:16:04,165 --> 00:16:05,945
From what I can tell,
you handled it like shit.

420
00:16:05,969 --> 00:16:07,047
So this is my fault?

421
00:16:07,072 --> 00:16:08,353
Well, it sure as hell
isn't mine.

422
00:16:08,375 --> 00:16:09,586
You know what, Jessica,
I'm not the one

423
00:16:09,611 --> 00:16:10,822
who wanted to fire Louis,

424
00:16:10,846 --> 00:16:12,726
and I'm not the one who wanted
to deny him clients.

425
00:16:12,751 --> 00:16:15,065
I did that because of
his performance as an attorney.

426
00:16:15,089 --> 00:16:18,304
You antagonized him for years
for your own pleasure.

427
00:16:18,329 --> 00:16:19,640
Tell yourself whatever you want.

428
00:16:19,665 --> 00:16:21,345
You handed out
your share of abuse.

429
00:16:21,369 --> 00:16:23,049
Tell yourself whatever you want.

430
00:16:23,073 --> 00:16:25,387
You're the one who hired a fraud
and gave Louis leverage.

431
00:16:25,412 --> 00:16:27,024
And I told you
Louis would get worse,

432
00:16:27,049 --> 00:16:28,210
and you said I had to take it.

433
00:16:28,217 --> 00:16:29,796
Well, I don't care whose fault
it is,

434
00:16:29,821 --> 00:16:31,867
he is getting worse,
and I'm not gonna take it.

435
00:16:31,892 --> 00:16:34,006
Oh, yes, you are.

436
00:16:34,030 --> 00:16:35,342
You're going to take it,

437
00:16:35,367 --> 00:16:37,213
and you're gonna do it
with a smile on your face

438
00:16:37,237 --> 00:16:39,718
until I say otherwise.

439
00:16:39,742 --> 00:16:41,789
And what the hell
are you gonna do?

440
00:16:41,814 --> 00:16:45,153
I'm going to clean up this mess
once and for all.

441
00:16:47,826 --> 00:16:49,038
What do you mean, you don't have

442
00:16:49,062 --> 00:16:50,507
diamond-encrusted
business cards?

443
00:16:50,532 --> 00:16:52,144
Fine, what about
the embossed ivory?

444
00:16:52,169 --> 00:16:54,450
Okay, great, well, how much
would 10,000 of those run me?

445
00:16:54,475 --> 00:16:56,488
Money's no object.

446
00:16:56,512 --> 00:16:58,314
What, are you crazy?
I'm not paying that much.

447
00:16:58,317 --> 00:16:59,761
Unless it comes
with a reach-around.

448
00:16:59,785 --> 00:17:01,699
Which, by the way,
I'm still not paying that much.

449
00:17:01,724 --> 00:17:03,092
Elite Printing, my ass.

450
00:17:06,266 --> 00:17:08,113
I give you
one simple instruction...

451
00:17:08,138 --> 00:17:10,919
To keep your mouth shut...
And you couldn't even do that.

452
00:17:10,943 --> 00:17:14,327
Um, okay, did you make
an appointment with Norma?

453
00:17:14,351 --> 00:17:15,629
- What?
- To see me.

454
00:17:15,654 --> 00:17:18,636
Did you check
with my secretary, Norma?

455
00:17:18,660 --> 00:17:20,473
Cut the shit, Louis.
I'm not in the mood.

456
00:17:20,498 --> 00:17:22,745
Well, get in the mood,
because I hold all the cards.

457
00:17:22,769 --> 00:17:24,815
And those cards are getting you
your name on the wall,

458
00:17:24,840 --> 00:17:26,086
but you need
to keep this to yourself.

459
00:17:26,110 --> 00:17:27,155
Why?

460
00:17:27,180 --> 00:17:28,624
So you can figure out a way
to screw me?

461
00:17:28,648 --> 00:17:30,027
I gave you my word.

462
00:17:30,052 --> 00:17:33,935
Well, no disrespect, Jessica,
but your word means shit.

463
00:17:33,960 --> 00:17:35,873
So if you want me
to stop telling people,

464
00:17:35,897 --> 00:17:39,414
you better start
telling people yourself.

465
00:17:39,438 --> 00:17:41,016
I told you, in good time.

466
00:17:41,041 --> 00:17:44,459
And I just told you
I don't give a shit.

467
00:17:44,484 --> 00:17:47,199
So I suggest you call a meeting
with the senior partners.

468
00:17:47,223 --> 00:17:48,534
Those meetings are on Thursdays.

469
00:17:48,558 --> 00:17:49,869
Well, consider today Thursday.

470
00:17:49,894 --> 00:17:52,977
I told you, I have yet
to figure out how to sell it.

471
00:17:53,002 --> 00:17:55,182
You want to sell it?
I'll tell you how to sell it.

472
00:17:55,207 --> 00:17:57,020
You and Harvey do it together,

473
00:17:57,044 --> 00:18:00,026
you do it like you mean it.
And you do it now.

474
00:18:00,050 --> 00:18:01,719
Got it? Good.

475
00:18:08,654 --> 00:18:10,236
I'm sure you've all heard rumors

476
00:18:10,238 --> 00:18:11,918
about why we called
this meeting,

477
00:18:11,942 --> 00:18:14,924
but that's because it's hard
to keep good news quiet.

478
00:18:14,948 --> 00:18:16,828
We'll be making this official
later this week

479
00:18:16,853 --> 00:18:21,505
but we're here to announce
our newest name partner,

480
00:18:21,529 --> 00:18:24,835
Louis Litt.

481
00:18:28,778 --> 00:18:30,791
Thank you, Jessica.

482
00:18:30,816 --> 00:18:33,565
Harvey.

483
00:18:33,589 --> 00:18:36,972
Some of you may be wondering
how this happened.

484
00:18:36,996 --> 00:18:38,676
There's a simple explanation,

485
00:18:38,700 --> 00:18:42,073
and all it requires is for me
to admit something.

486
00:18:43,843 --> 00:18:45,489
I made a mistake.

487
00:18:45,514 --> 00:18:49,298
I never should have accepted
Louis's resignation,

488
00:18:49,323 --> 00:18:51,436
because not only is he
a billing machine

489
00:18:51,461 --> 00:18:52,973
and a damn good attorney,

490
00:18:52,997 --> 00:18:55,545
he has personally gotten me
out of more than one jam,

491
00:18:55,570 --> 00:18:58,085
and there's no one
I'd rather have my name next to

492
00:18:58,109 --> 00:19:01,325
than my friend Louis Litt.

493
00:19:01,350 --> 00:19:04,299
Thank you, Harvey.

494
00:19:04,323 --> 00:19:08,372
Even though it's "not official,"
I already feel like

495
00:19:08,397 --> 00:19:09,998
my name's been up there
as long as yours.

496
00:19:10,969 --> 00:19:13,785
And I definitely feel like

497
00:19:13,810 --> 00:19:18,786
it's gonna be up there
for a long, long time.

498
00:19:24,065 --> 00:19:25,410
A lot of good that did.

499
00:19:25,435 --> 00:19:27,715
Leave it to Louis to take
his big moment like a dick.

500
00:19:27,739 --> 00:19:28,740
Harvey, calm down.

501
00:19:28,742 --> 00:19:29,753
Calm down?

502
00:19:29,777 --> 00:19:31,356
I just did exactly
what he wanted,

503
00:19:31,381 --> 00:19:33,343
and he acted like a dick,
and he's not gonna stop.

504
00:19:33,351 --> 00:19:36,032
He's not gonna stop because
you didn't do what he wanted.

505
00:19:36,057 --> 00:19:38,304
Jessica, I just got up there
and kissed his ass

506
00:19:38,328 --> 00:19:39,707
in front of
the entire partnership

507
00:19:39,732 --> 00:19:40,910
and pretended to like it.

508
00:19:40,934 --> 00:19:42,045
Exactly.

509
00:19:42,070 --> 00:19:43,071
Pretended.

510
00:19:43,072 --> 00:19:45,754
Oh, you want me
to actually like it?

511
00:19:45,778 --> 00:19:47,591
I want you to make him
feel accepted.

512
00:19:47,616 --> 00:19:48,794
Jessica.

513
00:19:48,818 --> 00:19:50,798
Harvey, what Louis wants
is to be accepted.

514
00:19:50,822 --> 00:19:51,983
And like it or not, the person

515
00:19:51,992 --> 00:19:53,671
he wants that from
the most is you.

516
00:19:53,695 --> 00:19:55,609
So you're gonna go to him,
you're gonna make nice,

517
00:19:55,633 --> 00:19:58,348
and that's how we're gonna
put all of this to bed.

518
00:19:58,373 --> 00:20:00,186
You want to tell me
what the hell that was?

519
00:20:00,210 --> 00:20:02,357
If you'll excuse me,

520
00:20:02,381 --> 00:20:04,494
I'm gonna let Jessica handle
this conversation.

521
00:20:04,519 --> 00:20:06,088
I have to go kill myself.

522
00:20:09,864 --> 00:20:11,544
Jeff, I can't do this right now.

523
00:20:11,569 --> 00:20:12,747
Should I make an appointment?

524
00:20:12,771 --> 00:20:14,918
Because the partners may have
bought that fairy tale

525
00:20:14,943 --> 00:20:17,658
about Louis's triumphant return,
but they don't know what I know.

526
00:20:17,682 --> 00:20:18,683
What exactly is that?

527
00:20:18,684 --> 00:20:20,730
That Louis committed a crime,

528
00:20:20,755 --> 00:20:23,002
and then he resigned
five seconds

529
00:20:23,026 --> 00:20:24,773
before you were
about to fire him.

530
00:20:24,798 --> 00:20:29,083
And now he's not only back,
he's name partner.

531
00:20:29,107 --> 00:20:32,189
I reconsidered,
which, as managing partner,

532
00:20:32,214 --> 00:20:33,359
I am entitled to do.

533
00:20:33,383 --> 00:20:36,531
And as someone with a brain,
I'm entitled

534
00:20:36,556 --> 00:20:40,808
to come to the conclusion
that Louis has something on you.

535
00:20:40,832 --> 00:20:44,483
Jeff, you said you didn't
want me to lie to you anymore,

536
00:20:44,507 --> 00:20:45,918
and I'm trying like hell not to.

537
00:20:45,943 --> 00:20:47,588
And that's the same thing
as lying to me.

538
00:20:47,613 --> 00:20:48,625
No, it's not.

539
00:20:48,649 --> 00:20:50,662
Oh, you are one hell of
a lawyer.

540
00:20:50,687 --> 00:20:54,338
So are you,
which is why you're here.

541
00:20:54,362 --> 00:20:56,175
So I'll come clean.

542
00:20:56,200 --> 00:20:58,915
I can't tell you the truth
about this,

543
00:20:58,939 --> 00:21:02,388
and that's as honest as
I can be with you right now.

544
00:21:02,412 --> 00:21:05,061
Can you handle that?

545
00:21:05,085 --> 00:21:08,167
I can handle it for now.

546
00:21:08,192 --> 00:21:09,894
But I won't handle it forever.

547
00:21:19,182 --> 00:21:20,527
Louis, what are you doing here?

548
00:21:20,552 --> 00:21:22,799
I noticed you haven't
congratulated me yet,

549
00:21:22,824 --> 00:21:24,704
so I wanted to give you
a chance to make up for it.

550
00:21:24,728 --> 00:21:26,774
Right, congratulations.
We're all so happy for you.

551
00:21:26,799 --> 00:21:27,810
Is that what you wanted?

552
00:21:27,834 --> 00:21:29,514
Seemed a little disingenuous.

553
00:21:29,538 --> 00:21:31,684
Then let me be clear.

554
00:21:31,709 --> 00:21:32,988
I don't mean a word of it.

555
00:21:33,012 --> 00:21:35,025
You really want to talk that way
to a new name partner?

556
00:21:35,050 --> 00:21:36,429
I'm talking to you that way

557
00:21:36,453 --> 00:21:38,699
because you threatened to throw
the man that I love in jail

558
00:21:38,724 --> 00:21:40,170
to become that name partner.

559
00:21:40,195 --> 00:21:41,306
So, you know what, Louis,

560
00:21:41,330 --> 00:21:42,842
I'm sorry
that I didn't bake you a cake.

561
00:21:42,867 --> 00:21:43,868
That's too bad.

562
00:21:43,869 --> 00:21:45,114
You didn't do anything for me,

563
00:21:45,139 --> 00:21:47,887
but I got something for you.

564
00:21:47,911 --> 00:21:48,989
Doc review.

565
00:21:49,013 --> 00:21:50,926
Filings to be done
in triplicate.

566
00:21:50,951 --> 00:21:54,167
Paralegal work,
since you like doing it so much.

567
00:21:54,192 --> 00:21:57,642
You know I don't like doing it
at all.

568
00:21:57,666 --> 00:21:59,445
You helped your boyfriend
with his work.

569
00:21:59,469 --> 00:22:00,748
You didn't think
I'd figure that out?

570
00:22:00,773 --> 00:22:03,120
You know what? I don't care.

571
00:22:03,145 --> 00:22:04,423
You have no authority over me.

572
00:22:04,447 --> 00:22:06,161
I'm Harvey's associate.

573
00:22:06,185 --> 00:22:07,998
Yeah, but I run the associates.

574
00:22:08,022 --> 00:22:10,435
Therefore, I run you.

575
00:22:10,460 --> 00:22:12,140
I know what you're doing.

576
00:22:12,164 --> 00:22:13,944
But do you know
what you're doing?

577
00:22:13,969 --> 00:22:15,290
Not only do you live
with a fraud,

578
00:22:15,304 --> 00:22:16,649
you're just like him...

579
00:22:16,674 --> 00:22:18,320
Pretending to be a lawyer
when you're not.

580
00:22:18,345 --> 00:22:19,724
I'm not pretending
to be anything.

581
00:22:19,749 --> 00:22:20,726
I am in law school.

582
00:22:20,750 --> 00:22:22,161
Are you really gonna make it
through?

583
00:22:22,186 --> 00:22:23,664
You could barely handle
the LSATs.

584
00:22:23,688 --> 00:22:25,067
You couldn't get into Harvard.

585
00:22:25,092 --> 00:22:27,339
As a matter of fact,
your boyfriend may be a fraud,

586
00:22:27,364 --> 00:22:29,277
but he's a better lawyer
than you'll ever be.

587
00:22:29,301 --> 00:22:32,016
You have no idea what kind of
lawyer I'm gonna be.

588
00:22:32,041 --> 00:22:33,653
Don't I?

589
00:22:33,678 --> 00:22:36,360
You learned from
the best liars around, Rachel:

590
00:22:36,384 --> 00:22:40,034
Harvey, Mike,

591
00:22:40,058 --> 00:22:42,405
your father.

592
00:22:42,430 --> 00:22:47,183
Yeah, I know exactly the kind of
lawyer you're gonna be.

593
00:22:47,208 --> 00:22:50,691
But until that day,
this kind of work

594
00:22:50,715 --> 00:22:52,417
is all you're good for.

595
00:22:59,534 --> 00:23:01,180
So you like marinated meat?

596
00:23:01,205 --> 00:23:02,283
Oh, yum.

597
00:23:02,307 --> 00:23:03,952
Okay, wait,
but which one do you make?

598
00:23:03,977 --> 00:23:05,422
Kansas City or Memphis style?

599
00:23:05,447 --> 00:23:07,294
Oh, hell, when it comes to ribs,

600
00:23:07,318 --> 00:23:09,298
I make 'em
every which way I can.

601
00:23:09,323 --> 00:23:13,140
I am now officially starving.

602
00:23:13,164 --> 00:23:15,010
- Harvey.
- Please have a seat.

603
00:23:15,035 --> 00:23:17,249
Don't let my law firm get in
the way of your coffee klatch.

604
00:23:17,273 --> 00:23:18,952
Oh, now, now,
don't blame Donna here.

605
00:23:18,976 --> 00:23:20,889
I told her you and I had
some unfinished business.

606
00:23:20,914 --> 00:23:22,292
Already?

607
00:23:22,316 --> 00:23:24,998
What, did you pick something
out of your generic favor file?

608
00:23:25,023 --> 00:23:27,704
I've never done anything generic
in my life.

609
00:23:27,728 --> 00:23:30,477
This favor is tailor-made
for you.

610
00:23:30,501 --> 00:23:32,748
It's very specific
and very personal.

611
00:23:32,773 --> 00:23:34,887
We're in a little dispute
with another firm.

612
00:23:34,912 --> 00:23:36,657
I need you to get them
to back off of it.

613
00:23:36,681 --> 00:23:37,960
Why can't you do it yourself?

614
00:23:37,984 --> 00:23:39,797
'Cause I don't know the lawyer
on the other side.

615
00:23:39,822 --> 00:23:41,858
You do. Good luck.

616
00:23:44,132 --> 00:23:45,453
What the hell
is he talking about?

617
00:23:45,467 --> 00:23:46,745
- It's Scottie.
- Aw, shit.

618
00:23:46,770 --> 00:23:47,882
I know.

619
00:23:47,906 --> 00:23:49,518
Scottie doesn't do favors
like this,

620
00:23:49,543 --> 00:23:50,954
and I don't have any leverage
on her.

621
00:23:50,979 --> 00:23:52,859
Yeah, you do.

622
00:23:52,883 --> 00:23:54,653
You're just not gonna
like using it.

623
00:23:59,164 --> 00:24:00,443
Hey, there you are.

624
00:24:00,468 --> 00:24:02,590
Look, I just finished memorizing
all of Louis's cases,

625
00:24:02,605 --> 00:24:05,320
and I had an idea
I wanted to run by...

626
00:24:05,344 --> 00:24:06,923
Rachel, what happened?

627
00:24:06,948 --> 00:24:10,364
Nothing happened.

628
00:24:10,389 --> 00:24:12,268
What did Louis do?

629
00:24:12,292 --> 00:24:13,871
It's nothing.

630
00:24:13,896 --> 00:24:15,541
He found out that I helped you,

631
00:24:15,566 --> 00:24:17,279
and now he's giving me
paralegal work,

632
00:24:17,303 --> 00:24:18,882
and I was a little upset,
but now I'm okay.

633
00:24:18,907 --> 00:24:20,185
You weren't just a little upset.

634
00:24:20,209 --> 00:24:21,488
You were crying,

635
00:24:21,513 --> 00:24:23,292
and a little paralegal work
wouldn't do that.

636
00:24:23,316 --> 00:24:24,317
It is not important.

637
00:24:24,318 --> 00:24:25,296
And you know what?
I had it coming.

638
00:24:25,321 --> 00:24:26,399
You had it coming?

639
00:24:26,423 --> 00:24:27,635
What are you...
Rachel, what did he do?

640
00:24:27,659 --> 00:24:29,170
Mike, I was the one that
told you to make up with him.

641
00:24:29,195 --> 00:24:30,641
- Rachel.
- I helped you with the work.

642
00:24:30,666 --> 00:24:31,744
- What did he do?
- And you know what?

643
00:24:31,768 --> 00:24:32,746
I lied to him
as much as you did.

644
00:24:32,771 --> 00:24:34,984
What did he do?

645
00:24:35,008 --> 00:24:40,462
It's not what he did,
it's what he said.

646
00:24:40,487 --> 00:24:41,499
What did he say?

647
00:24:41,523 --> 00:24:43,236
Mike, I'm a big girl,

648
00:24:43,260 --> 00:24:44,704
and I can take care of Louis.

649
00:24:44,729 --> 00:24:45,841
This isn't about you,

650
00:24:45,866 --> 00:24:47,913
this is about me and him,

651
00:24:47,937 --> 00:24:49,673
and I'm gonna make him
remember that.

652
00:24:54,685 --> 00:24:55,686
You piece of shit.

653
00:24:55,687 --> 00:24:57,099
You said this was
between me and you.

654
00:24:57,124 --> 00:24:58,235
It is between me and you.

655
00:24:58,260 --> 00:24:59,781
No, it stopped being
between me and you

656
00:24:59,795 --> 00:25:00,940
the second you went to Rachel.

657
00:25:00,965 --> 00:25:01,976
You put her between us

658
00:25:02,000 --> 00:25:03,245
the second you went to her
to help you.

659
00:25:03,270 --> 00:25:04,382
God, are you insane?

660
00:25:04,406 --> 00:25:07,254
Rachel has never been
anything but kind to you.

661
00:25:07,278 --> 00:25:08,723
I can't even count
the amount of times

662
00:25:08,748 --> 00:25:09,859
that she defended you.

663
00:25:09,884 --> 00:25:11,664
And now, she tries to help me
just a little bit,

664
00:25:11,688 --> 00:25:13,368
and you rip her to pieces.

665
00:25:13,392 --> 00:25:15,873
No, that's not the help
I'm talking about, fraud.

666
00:25:15,897 --> 00:25:17,911
Then what the hell
are you talking about?

667
00:25:17,935 --> 00:25:20,650
You went to her to help you
lie to me about who you are,

668
00:25:20,675 --> 00:25:23,390
and like the good little lackey
that she is,

669
00:25:23,414 --> 00:25:25,561
she came to me
and lied to my face.

670
00:25:25,586 --> 00:25:27,565
She did it to protect me, Louis.

671
00:25:27,589 --> 00:25:28,590
Well, good for you,

672
00:25:28,591 --> 00:25:29,702
but when I found out about it,

673
00:25:29,727 --> 00:25:31,508
I felt like shit
for the 180th time.

674
00:25:31,532 --> 00:25:33,294
So I just went to her
and did the same thing.

675
00:25:37,278 --> 00:25:38,957
You know, Louis,
I've just been memorizing

676
00:25:38,981 --> 00:25:42,130
all of your old arguments.

677
00:25:42,155 --> 00:25:45,103
I was actually gonna try
and come in here

678
00:25:45,127 --> 00:25:47,575
and use one of them
to change your mind about me.

679
00:25:47,600 --> 00:25:49,446
- It won't work.
- Oh, I know.

680
00:25:49,470 --> 00:25:53,921
Because while I am the same
person that I was before,

681
00:25:53,946 --> 00:25:55,058
you're not.

682
00:25:55,082 --> 00:25:57,697
You're right.

683
00:25:57,721 --> 00:26:00,269
I'm not the same person.

684
00:26:00,294 --> 00:26:01,606
I used to be a man of my word,

685
00:26:01,630 --> 00:26:03,632
but you people taught me
that doesn't mean a thing.

686
00:26:03,635 --> 00:26:05,381
So when I told you

687
00:26:05,405 --> 00:26:08,454
it was between me and you,
I lied.

688
00:26:08,478 --> 00:26:10,825
I found your weak spot,

689
00:26:10,850 --> 00:26:13,197
and you know what I'm gonna do?

690
00:26:13,222 --> 00:26:15,436
I'm gonna keep hammering on her

691
00:26:15,461 --> 00:26:17,664
until you break.

692
00:26:32,258 --> 00:26:33,435
Jessica.

693
00:26:33,460 --> 00:26:36,375
Please, if it can wait,
I've had a long day,

694
00:26:36,399 --> 00:26:37,577
and I need to go home.

695
00:26:37,602 --> 00:26:38,603
Too bad.

696
00:26:38,604 --> 00:26:39,849
You're staying here

697
00:26:39,873 --> 00:26:44,392
and drafting Louis Litt's
new partnership agreement.

698
00:26:44,417 --> 00:26:46,130
So now you're piling on too now?

699
00:26:46,154 --> 00:26:47,833
I'm not piling on.

700
00:26:47,857 --> 00:26:50,706
I am giving you this
because it's non-billable work

701
00:26:50,731 --> 00:26:54,916
and the only reason
it exists is because of you.

702
00:26:54,940 --> 00:26:57,722
This again?

703
00:26:57,746 --> 00:26:58,747
Excuse me?

704
00:26:58,748 --> 00:27:00,428
You heard me.

705
00:27:00,452 --> 00:27:02,132
I've seen this movie before.

706
00:27:02,156 --> 00:27:04,235
And the reason
it keeps rerunning

707
00:27:04,260 --> 00:27:06,273
is because every time
I think I'm done with you,

708
00:27:06,297 --> 00:27:10,014
you and your dirty little secret
rear your ugly heads.

709
00:27:10,039 --> 00:27:11,040
You know what, Jessica?

710
00:27:11,041 --> 00:27:12,453
I have had it up to here

711
00:27:12,478 --> 00:27:14,825
with you saying that this is
my dirty little secret.

712
00:27:14,850 --> 00:27:17,197
You could have fired me when
you found out, and you didn't.

713
00:27:17,222 --> 00:27:19,002
No, you decided to keep me
around

714
00:27:19,026 --> 00:27:20,338
because you were more concerned

715
00:27:20,362 --> 00:27:22,775
with beating Daniel Hardman
and keeping your power.

716
00:27:22,800 --> 00:27:24,146
And then you kept me around

717
00:27:24,171 --> 00:27:25,749
because you didn't want to
lose Harvey.

718
00:27:25,774 --> 00:27:28,121
And then you wanted to use
my secret to beat Harvey,

719
00:27:28,146 --> 00:27:30,226
and then again
and again and again.

720
00:27:30,250 --> 00:27:32,197
So please, Jessica,
why don't you tell me,

721
00:27:32,222 --> 00:27:35,427
when the hell does this become
your dirty little secret?

722
00:27:51,197 --> 00:27:53,233
This seat taken?

723
00:27:55,672 --> 00:27:57,385
Hi.

724
00:27:57,409 --> 00:27:58,955
Hey.

725
00:27:58,980 --> 00:28:01,494
Since your message
was so cryptic,

726
00:28:01,518 --> 00:28:03,565
I'm assuming
this is about business.

727
00:28:03,590 --> 00:28:06,071
I need a favor.

728
00:28:06,095 --> 00:28:08,042
Hey, Scottie.

729
00:28:08,066 --> 00:28:09,177
How are you?

730
00:28:09,202 --> 00:28:11,015
How have you been
since you left?

731
00:28:11,039 --> 00:28:13,019
I heard that
you took some time off.

732
00:28:13,043 --> 00:28:14,256
Where did you land?

733
00:28:14,281 --> 00:28:16,828
I need you to settle your case
against Robert Zane.

734
00:28:16,852 --> 00:28:18,030
And why would I do that?

735
00:28:18,054 --> 00:28:19,333
Because I owe him one.

736
00:28:19,358 --> 00:28:23,108
Harvey, I'm just getting
back on my feet at a new firm.

737
00:28:23,132 --> 00:28:25,079
This case is winnable.

738
00:28:25,104 --> 00:28:28,320
The firm knows that it is
because I told them it is.

739
00:28:28,345 --> 00:28:29,690
I settle, I look like shit.

740
00:28:29,714 --> 00:28:31,460
I know that,
but you came to me once

741
00:28:31,485 --> 00:28:33,332
to take it easy on you
with Folsom Foods...

742
00:28:33,356 --> 00:28:35,603
Because you said if I was ever
in trouble personally...

743
00:28:35,628 --> 00:28:37,973
I am in trouble personally.

744
00:28:37,997 --> 00:28:40,144
What the hell is personal
about Robert Zane?

745
00:28:40,169 --> 00:28:41,481
You don't do this for me,

746
00:28:41,506 --> 00:28:44,578
Zane's going to put it together
about Mike Ross.

747
00:28:53,699 --> 00:28:54,700
Scottie.

748
00:28:54,702 --> 00:28:56,615
You selfish son of a bitch.

749
00:28:56,639 --> 00:28:58,051
You said you told me that

750
00:28:58,076 --> 00:29:00,357
because you didn't want to keep
lying to the people you love.

751
00:29:00,382 --> 00:29:01,393
I didn't want to.

752
00:29:01,417 --> 00:29:02,962
And now you come to me
trading on the fact

753
00:29:02,987 --> 00:29:04,198
that I know to get you
out of a jam

754
00:29:04,222 --> 00:29:05,969
for doing something
stupid and selfish

755
00:29:05,993 --> 00:29:07,071
that drove a wedge between us

756
00:29:07,096 --> 00:29:08,377
before we ever even
had a chance.

757
00:29:08,398 --> 00:29:09,642
I told you the truth.

758
00:29:09,667 --> 00:29:10,880
After it was too late.

759
00:29:10,904 --> 00:29:11,905
Scottie.

760
00:29:11,906 --> 00:29:14,587
I loved you.

761
00:29:14,612 --> 00:29:19,298
I loved you,

762
00:29:19,322 --> 00:29:23,106
and you let some stupid secret
that I would never tell anyone

763
00:29:23,131 --> 00:29:27,917
come between us because
you couldn't trust me with it.

764
00:29:27,942 --> 00:29:28,943
You're right, Scottie.

765
00:29:28,944 --> 00:29:32,493
I don't have a leg to stand on.

766
00:29:32,517 --> 00:29:36,725
But if you don't do this for me,
I am in trouble.

767
00:29:43,908 --> 00:29:47,892
I'm going to recommend
we settle with Robert Zane.

768
00:29:47,917 --> 00:29:48,918
Thank you.

769
00:29:48,919 --> 00:29:50,098
But to be clear,

770
00:29:50,123 --> 00:29:52,236
you get to ask me this once.

771
00:29:52,260 --> 00:29:54,140
And I never want to hear
the name Mike Ross again.

772
00:29:54,165 --> 00:29:55,166
Scottie...

773
00:29:55,167 --> 00:29:56,469
Once.

774
00:30:15,277 --> 00:30:17,257
You wanted it to be official.

775
00:30:17,282 --> 00:30:18,283
There it is, Louis.

776
00:30:18,284 --> 00:30:21,333
It's official.

777
00:30:21,358 --> 00:30:24,240
So that's it?

778
00:30:24,264 --> 00:30:26,411
People are just gonna walk in
here tomorrow morning

779
00:30:26,436 --> 00:30:28,918
like it's any other day
and see it or maybe not see it?

780
00:30:28,942 --> 00:30:29,943
What were you expecting?

781
00:30:29,944 --> 00:30:31,690
A ceremony and a brass band?

782
00:30:31,714 --> 00:30:32,959
We don't do that.

783
00:30:32,984 --> 00:30:35,632
Well, I'm name partner,
and I say we do now.

784
00:30:35,656 --> 00:30:37,101
Excuse me?

785
00:30:37,126 --> 00:30:38,972
You heard me.

786
00:30:38,996 --> 00:30:42,313
I want pomp and circumstance
in the form of an unveiling.

787
00:30:42,337 --> 00:30:44,184
I'm going home, Louis.

788
00:30:44,208 --> 00:30:45,652
I'm not spending
the rest of the night

789
00:30:45,677 --> 00:30:47,223
emailing invitations
to an unveiling.

790
00:30:47,248 --> 00:30:48,393
You're going home?

791
00:30:48,417 --> 00:30:50,197
Well, then I'll send them out
myself.

792
00:30:50,221 --> 00:30:52,000
Because tomorrow...

793
00:30:52,025 --> 00:30:53,137
This is happening.

794
00:30:53,161 --> 00:30:54,272
4:00 p.m. sharp.

795
00:30:54,296 --> 00:30:55,508
I have a meeting at 4:00.

796
00:30:55,533 --> 00:30:59,317
Then reschedule it.

797
00:30:59,342 --> 00:31:01,622
You don't want me to reschedule.

798
00:31:01,646 --> 00:31:04,893
What you want is
to know you've earned that.

799
00:31:04,918 --> 00:31:08,001
I have earned it,

800
00:31:08,026 --> 00:31:09,705
but I want you to know it.

801
00:31:09,729 --> 00:31:10,974
Okay, here it is.

802
00:31:10,999 --> 00:31:12,979
You got your name up there
by finding leverage

803
00:31:13,003 --> 00:31:15,050
and using it to strong-arm me
into doing something

804
00:31:15,075 --> 00:31:16,420
that I never would have done.

805
00:31:16,444 --> 00:31:17,445
See, I knew you...

806
00:31:17,446 --> 00:31:18,658
Let me finish.

807
00:31:18,683 --> 00:31:21,765
It was a stone-cold move,

808
00:31:21,790 --> 00:31:24,805
and it's exactly what Harvey
would have done.

809
00:31:24,829 --> 00:31:27,076
Now, if that doesn't tell you
that you've earned it,

810
00:31:27,101 --> 00:31:28,770
then I don't know what will.

811
00:31:32,646 --> 00:31:34,526
You still want me to reschedule
my meeting?

812
00:31:34,550 --> 00:31:35,551
Yes, I do.

813
00:31:35,552 --> 00:31:38,168
Fine. I'll be there.

814
00:31:38,193 --> 00:31:40,239
You and Harvey.

815
00:31:40,263 --> 00:31:42,476
Of course, Louis.

816
00:31:42,501 --> 00:31:45,473
We're your partners.

817
00:31:49,350 --> 00:31:50,328
Jesus, you look like shit.

818
00:31:50,352 --> 00:31:51,563
What's going on?

819
00:31:51,588 --> 00:31:54,104
Between drafting Louis's
partnership agreement

820
00:31:54,128 --> 00:31:57,576
for Jessica and Louis's
never-ending onslaught,

821
00:31:57,600 --> 00:31:59,213
I didn't get any sleep.

822
00:31:59,238 --> 00:32:00,682
Well, splash some water
on your face,

823
00:32:00,707 --> 00:32:02,319
'cause we have to go to
his debutante ball

824
00:32:02,344 --> 00:32:03,389
and look like we give a shit.

825
00:32:03,413 --> 00:32:04,558
No. I'm not going.

826
00:32:04,582 --> 00:32:05,903
What do you mean
you're not going?

827
00:32:05,919 --> 00:32:07,497
Now is not the time
to poke the bear.

828
00:32:07,522 --> 00:32:08,533
It's too late.

829
00:32:08,557 --> 00:32:09,803
The bear is an asshole,

830
00:32:09,828 --> 00:32:11,574
and he's not just taking it out
on me anymore.

831
00:32:11,598 --> 00:32:13,043
- He's taking it out on Rachel.
- What?

832
00:32:13,068 --> 00:32:14,948
Yeah, he made it clear
that he found the weak spot

833
00:32:14,972 --> 00:32:16,718
that's going to get to me,
and he's gonna keep

834
00:32:16,742 --> 00:32:19,056
pressing it and pressing it
until I can't take it anymore.

835
00:32:19,081 --> 00:32:20,828
Mike, you are not ringing
that bell.

836
00:32:20,852 --> 00:32:22,665
You're damn right
I'm not ringing that bell.

837
00:32:22,689 --> 00:32:25,204
But if I have to go raise
a glass to that son of a bitch,

838
00:32:25,228 --> 00:32:27,731
I'm gonna end up
smashing it over his head.

839
00:32:29,737 --> 00:32:31,818
Come with me.

840
00:32:31,842 --> 00:32:32,843
What are you going to do?

841
00:32:32,845 --> 00:32:35,827
Enough is enough.

842
00:32:35,851 --> 00:32:36,852
Harvey.

843
00:32:36,854 --> 00:32:38,332
You're just in time.

844
00:32:38,356 --> 00:32:39,901
Jessica's on her way down
with the partnership agreement.

845
00:32:39,926 --> 00:32:41,138
You here to be my witness?

846
00:32:41,163 --> 00:32:43,609
He's here to keep me
from ripping your face off.

847
00:32:43,634 --> 00:32:45,195
Oh, I see.
Now that big brother's here...

848
00:32:45,205 --> 00:32:46,516
Okay, that's enough.

849
00:32:46,540 --> 00:32:48,053
Louis, you got everything
you wanted,

850
00:32:48,078 --> 00:32:49,589
and you are done
taking it out on him,

851
00:32:49,614 --> 00:32:52,329
because no matter what you do,
I'm not letting him quit.

852
00:32:52,353 --> 00:32:53,898
- Then I'll just fire him.
- You can't.

853
00:32:53,923 --> 00:32:55,703
I can, and I will,

854
00:32:55,727 --> 00:32:57,507
because Jessica would rather
he be fired

855
00:32:57,532 --> 00:32:58,777
than you all go to jail.

856
00:32:58,801 --> 00:33:00,145
No one's going to jail.

857
00:33:00,170 --> 00:33:01,984
See? She knows what's what.

858
00:33:02,008 --> 00:33:04,255
I sign the agreement, he's done,

859
00:33:04,280 --> 00:33:06,082
and then I bring Katrina back
as my associate.

860
00:33:06,083 --> 00:33:07,662
And that's not going to happen.

861
00:33:07,687 --> 00:33:08,932
What are you talking about?

862
00:33:08,956 --> 00:33:10,117
Louis, I'm afraid you've made

863
00:33:10,126 --> 00:33:11,972
your last dictate to me
as name partner.

864
00:33:11,996 --> 00:33:14,043
I'm not gonna let you
take this away from me.

865
00:33:14,068 --> 00:33:15,680
I'm not taking anything away
from you.

866
00:33:15,705 --> 00:33:17,385
You are still name partner.

867
00:33:17,409 --> 00:33:19,688
Right after you sign this.

868
00:33:19,712 --> 00:33:22,828
I added a little something extra
after you finished drafting it.

869
00:33:22,853 --> 00:33:25,334
This says I'm co-conspirator
to hiring a fraud.

870
00:33:25,358 --> 00:33:26,359
You are.

871
00:33:26,360 --> 00:33:27,639
You became one

872
00:33:27,664 --> 00:33:30,110
the second you used him
to get your name on the door.

873
00:33:30,135 --> 00:33:31,180
I know I'm not a real lawyer,

874
00:33:31,204 --> 00:33:33,084
but that sounds like
he is to me.

875
00:33:33,109 --> 00:33:34,588
I am a real lawyer.

876
00:33:34,612 --> 00:33:36,992
He is.

877
00:33:37,017 --> 00:33:38,018
I'm not signing it.

878
00:33:38,020 --> 00:33:39,198
Louis, here's the thing.

879
00:33:39,222 --> 00:33:41,402
I told you not to tell anybody
about this,

880
00:33:41,427 --> 00:33:43,775
and then you went and
you shouted it to Robert Zane,

881
00:33:43,800 --> 00:33:45,411
and then you made me
tell the partners.

882
00:33:45,436 --> 00:33:47,749
And the capper is,
there are about a hundred people

883
00:33:47,773 --> 00:33:49,052
waiting to greet you

884
00:33:49,077 --> 00:33:51,224
after the unveiling
you arranged,

885
00:33:51,249 --> 00:33:54,287
which won't happen
if you don't sign that.

886
00:33:57,863 --> 00:33:59,610
I could still go to the police.

887
00:33:59,634 --> 00:34:02,582
Yeah, you could, but you won't.

888
00:34:02,606 --> 00:34:04,052
'Cause you used
that little secret

889
00:34:04,077 --> 00:34:06,224
to get where you are right now.

890
00:34:06,249 --> 00:34:09,865
It was the only bullet
in your chamber,

891
00:34:09,889 --> 00:34:11,836
and I am taking your gun away.

892
00:34:11,861 --> 00:34:12,862
You set me up.

893
00:34:12,863 --> 00:34:13,974
You set yourself up,

894
00:34:13,998 --> 00:34:15,945
just like you did
with Charles Forstman.

895
00:34:15,969 --> 00:34:17,480
And what I learned from him was,

896
00:34:17,505 --> 00:34:19,051
once you get something
that you want,

897
00:34:19,076 --> 00:34:21,857
you will do whatever it takes
to keep it.

898
00:34:21,882 --> 00:34:25,699
So why don't you go ahead
and sign

899
00:34:25,723 --> 00:34:29,197
so we can get out
to your goddamn party.

900
00:34:46,226 --> 00:34:47,738
You know, it's funny.

901
00:34:47,763 --> 00:34:51,080
We've never had a ceremony
when we've changed names before,

902
00:34:51,104 --> 00:34:55,087
but Louis Litt had the audacity
to convene us all here today.

903
00:34:55,112 --> 00:34:58,461
And as it turns out,
his first decision

904
00:34:58,485 --> 00:35:00,899
as name partner is brilliant,

905
00:35:00,924 --> 00:35:03,439
because a ceremony like this
gives us a chance

906
00:35:03,463 --> 00:35:07,480
to reevaluate where we've been
and where we're going.

907
00:35:07,505 --> 00:35:09,485
Perhaps you had a disagreement
with a colleague,

908
00:35:09,509 --> 00:35:13,326
or there's some other issue
that's been on your mind.

909
00:35:13,351 --> 00:35:17,002
The point is, with a new name
comes a new beginning.

910
00:35:17,026 --> 00:35:20,642
For me, I'm hoping
we can see this as a chance

911
00:35:20,667 --> 00:35:22,446
to wipe the slate clean.

912
00:35:22,470 --> 00:35:25,452
With that said,

913
00:35:25,477 --> 00:35:28,951
here's to our newest
name partner, Louis Litt.

914
00:35:34,898 --> 00:35:36,476
Nice speech.

915
00:35:36,501 --> 00:35:38,182
Let's hope it takes.

916
00:35:38,206 --> 00:35:39,527
It's got a better chance
of taking

917
00:35:39,542 --> 00:35:41,388
now that you made him sign
the agreement.

918
00:35:41,412 --> 00:35:43,391
That it does.

919
00:35:43,415 --> 00:35:44,594
Speaking of which,

920
00:35:44,619 --> 00:35:46,565
when exactly did you know
you were gonna do that?

921
00:35:46,589 --> 00:35:50,673
Oh, um, about 15 seconds
after Donna told me he knew.

922
00:35:50,698 --> 00:35:52,812
And you didn't feel the need
to bring me in on that plan?

923
00:35:52,837 --> 00:35:54,015
I felt the exact opposite.

924
00:35:54,039 --> 00:35:55,120
What are you talking about?

925
00:35:55,143 --> 00:35:57,322
Harvey, Louis wanted
to see you suffer.

926
00:35:57,346 --> 00:35:59,227
If I had told you,
you would have had to fake it,

927
00:35:59,251 --> 00:36:00,662
and you're a shitty actor.

928
00:36:00,687 --> 00:36:02,833
Excuse me, but I can act.

929
00:36:02,858 --> 00:36:05,874
No, everybody thinks
they can act, Harvey.

930
00:36:05,899 --> 00:36:08,481
The fact of the matter is, well,
you're just a pretty face.

931
00:36:08,505 --> 00:36:10,285
Oh, you think I'm pretty?

932
00:36:10,309 --> 00:36:12,077
Pretty stupid.

933
00:36:22,769 --> 00:36:25,250
I can't believe
it's actually up there.

934
00:36:25,274 --> 00:36:29,325
This firm is changing names
more than Prince.

935
00:36:29,350 --> 00:36:32,165
Who?

936
00:36:32,189 --> 00:36:34,602
You're kidding, right?

937
00:36:34,627 --> 00:36:35,973
Purple Rain.

938
00:36:35,998 --> 00:36:37,076
Raspberry Beret.

939
00:36:37,100 --> 00:36:38,601
I'm kidding.

940
00:36:39,806 --> 00:36:42,388
I almost had to reevaluate
our entire relationship.

941
00:36:42,412 --> 00:36:45,962
Mm-hmm, after you were gonna go
and beat Louis up for me?

942
00:36:45,986 --> 00:36:48,333
I doubt that.

943
00:36:48,358 --> 00:36:52,877
Mike, thank you.

944
00:36:52,901 --> 00:36:54,212
It just seemed right.

945
00:36:54,237 --> 00:36:55,917
After all, you stood up
to Louis for me.

946
00:36:55,941 --> 00:37:01,028
Mm-hmm, and I almost
got pummeled for it.

947
00:37:01,052 --> 00:37:02,965
That took guts.

948
00:37:02,990 --> 00:37:07,073
And that's why I love you.

949
00:37:07,098 --> 00:37:09,402
I love you too.

950
00:37:11,174 --> 00:37:13,823
I wanted to tell you
that you were right.

951
00:37:13,847 --> 00:37:16,429
I started this whole thing
by hiring Mike.

952
00:37:16,453 --> 00:37:17,697
It's my fault.

953
00:37:17,721 --> 00:37:20,269
Thank you.

954
00:37:20,294 --> 00:37:22,508
But I've been on board
long enough,

955
00:37:22,532 --> 00:37:24,746
and it's time
I accepted the fact

956
00:37:24,771 --> 00:37:27,184
that it's my secret too.

957
00:37:27,209 --> 00:37:29,056
So where do we go from here?

958
00:37:29,080 --> 00:37:31,248
We fight like
hell to protect it.

959
00:37:39,134 --> 00:37:43,018
No cake?

960
00:37:43,043 --> 00:37:46,158
What are you doing here,
Jessica?

961
00:37:46,183 --> 00:37:48,966
I know you're tired of waiting
for an explanation,

962
00:37:48,990 --> 00:37:50,870
so I'm here to give you one.

963
00:37:50,895 --> 00:37:54,311
You've given me explanations
before.

964
00:37:54,335 --> 00:37:57,183
I want the truth.

965
00:37:57,207 --> 00:37:59,454
Are you ready for the truth?

966
00:37:59,479 --> 00:38:01,926
Because it's not pretty.

967
00:38:01,951 --> 00:38:04,055
There's only one way
to find out.

968
00:38:07,163 --> 00:38:09,510
It seems like forever ago,

969
00:38:09,535 --> 00:38:12,573
but it wasn't that long ago
at all.

970
00:38:17,185 --> 00:38:21,369
Daniel Hardman embezzled money
from the firm,

971
00:38:21,394 --> 00:38:23,908
and I covered it up.

972
00:38:23,932 --> 00:38:26,046
Now, make no mistake,

973
00:38:26,070 --> 00:38:28,284
I found about it,
I confronted him,

974
00:38:28,309 --> 00:38:31,458
and I eventually made him
pay it all back.

975
00:38:31,483 --> 00:38:34,231
But I did cover it up.

976
00:38:34,255 --> 00:38:39,242
From the partners,
from the police, from everyone.

977
00:38:39,266 --> 00:38:43,818
I even adjusted our books
to hide the crime.

978
00:38:43,843 --> 00:38:45,723
And being a bloodhound
about these things,

979
00:38:45,747 --> 00:38:48,528
Louis found out

980
00:38:48,552 --> 00:38:53,806
and used it
as leverage to come back.

981
00:38:53,831 --> 00:38:55,577
As name partner.

982
00:38:55,601 --> 00:38:57,213
As name partner.

983
00:38:57,238 --> 00:39:02,158
Why couldn't you trust me
with that before?

984
00:39:02,183 --> 00:39:06,902
Because I didn't know
how you'd react,

985
00:39:06,927 --> 00:39:12,137
and I didn't want to risk losing
everything I had.

986
00:39:23,295 --> 00:39:26,444
Jessica,

987
00:39:26,469 --> 00:39:28,372
your secret is safe with me.

988
00:39:38,429 --> 00:39:39,406
You're late.

989
00:39:39,430 --> 00:39:40,709
But I come bearing gifts.

990
00:39:40,734 --> 00:39:43,013
Huh.
That doesn't look like cannoli.

991
00:39:43,037 --> 00:39:44,450
It's better than cannoli, Dad.

992
00:39:44,475 --> 00:39:46,255
It's the résumé
of your new associate.

993
00:39:46,279 --> 00:39:47,857
If this is Harvey's way of
trying to make up

994
00:39:47,882 --> 00:39:49,403
for the fact
that I didn't hire Louis...

995
00:39:49,419 --> 00:39:52,167
This isn't from Harvey.
It's from me.

996
00:39:52,191 --> 00:39:53,737
And you're going to do this
for me,

997
00:39:53,762 --> 00:39:56,008
and I am not going to owe you
a thing.

998
00:39:56,033 --> 00:39:57,836
This is what they're
teaching you at Columbia?

999
00:39:58,940 --> 00:40:00,351
Because that's not how
favors work.

1000
00:40:00,375 --> 00:40:01,620
I know how favors work.

1001
00:40:01,645 --> 00:40:03,825
You do this, and then you want
something from me someday.

1002
00:40:03,850 --> 00:40:06,532
But by then
you're going to understand

1003
00:40:06,556 --> 00:40:09,805
that right now
I'm the one doing you a favor,

1004
00:40:09,830 --> 00:40:14,482
because Katrina Bennett
is an amazing lawyer.

1005
00:40:14,506 --> 00:40:15,884
I was wrong about you.

1006
00:40:15,909 --> 00:40:19,393
You're not like your mother.

1007
00:40:19,417 --> 00:40:22,767
You're like your father.

1008
00:40:22,791 --> 00:40:24,838
Come on.

1009
00:40:24,863 --> 00:40:26,375
- Oh, that's good.
- That was a good one.

1010
00:40:26,400 --> 00:40:27,545
That was a good one.

1011
00:40:27,569 --> 00:40:29,514
Sounds just like me, baby girl.

1012
00:40:29,539 --> 00:40:31,653
I had you fooled, huh?

1013
00:40:31,677 --> 00:40:33,121
You did.

1014
00:40:33,146 --> 00:40:35,283
Now let me show you
how a lawyer cooks.

1015
00:40:42,300 --> 00:40:43,846
What do you want?

1016
00:40:43,871 --> 00:40:45,751
I just thought you'd want this.

1017
00:40:45,775 --> 00:40:47,319
The associates saved it for you.

1018
00:40:47,344 --> 00:40:48,556
No, they didn't.

1019
00:40:48,581 --> 00:40:49,993
You saved it for me
because you want to pretend

1020
00:40:50,017 --> 00:40:51,262
to be my friend again.

1021
00:40:51,287 --> 00:40:52,932
Louis, didn't you hear
Jessica's speech?

1022
00:40:52,957 --> 00:40:54,518
This is our chance
wipe the slate clean.

1023
00:40:54,528 --> 00:40:55,972
I did hear her speech,

1024
00:40:55,997 --> 00:40:59,447
and I know that she sent you
here to say that to me.

1025
00:40:59,471 --> 00:41:00,482
No one sent me here.

1026
00:41:00,506 --> 00:41:02,119
I'm here
because I want to be here.

1027
00:41:02,144 --> 00:41:05,359
You see, that's sweet.

1028
00:41:05,384 --> 00:41:08,566
But how can I ever believe
a word you say?

1029
00:41:08,591 --> 00:41:12,275
I want to know
if you ever thought once

1030
00:41:12,299 --> 00:41:15,381
to tell me the truth about Mike.

1031
00:41:15,406 --> 00:41:17,119
No, I didn't.

1032
00:41:17,143 --> 00:41:18,488
Of course you didn't.

1033
00:41:18,513 --> 00:41:20,327
- Because we're not friends.
- You're wrong.

1034
00:41:20,351 --> 00:41:21,728
We are friends,

1035
00:41:21,753 --> 00:41:24,469
but my professional loyalty
to Harvey comes above that,

1036
00:41:24,493 --> 00:41:26,340
which is why
I never told anyone...

1037
00:41:26,364 --> 00:41:30,413
Jessica, Rachel, anyone.

1038
00:41:30,438 --> 00:41:32,151
So put yourself in my position

1039
00:41:32,175 --> 00:41:34,779
and ask yourself,
what you would have done?

1040
00:41:37,521 --> 00:41:39,468
I want you to tell me
something else.

1041
00:41:39,492 --> 00:41:42,975
Yes. Anything.

1042
00:41:43,000 --> 00:41:44,312
You ever sleep with Harvey?

1043
00:41:44,336 --> 00:41:46,349
Wait. What?

1044
00:41:46,374 --> 00:41:48,989
It's not
a professional question.

1045
00:41:49,013 --> 00:41:51,093
It's a personal question.

1046
00:41:51,117 --> 00:41:53,464
Can you put our so-called
friendship high enough

1047
00:41:53,489 --> 00:41:55,669
to answer that one honestly?

1048
00:41:55,694 --> 00:41:56,772
Louis...

1049
00:41:56,796 --> 00:41:58,543
Because it's the only thing
I can think of

1050
00:41:58,567 --> 00:42:01,906
to know if I can even begin
to trust you again.

1051
00:42:04,714 --> 00:42:07,529
Once.

1052
00:42:07,553 --> 00:42:09,499
That's my way of wiping
the slate clean.

1053
00:42:09,524 --> 00:42:11,561
You can accept it or not.

1054
00:42:22,940 --> 00:42:29,447
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man

