1
00:00:00,969 --> 00:00:02,284
Previously on Suits...

2
00:00:02,285 --> 00:00:03,981
I have a list here
of the signing bonuses

3
00:00:03,982 --> 00:00:07,059
of the top three associates
who have come into this firm.

4
00:00:07,060 --> 00:00:10,039
An advance plus my salary
will cover my tuition.

5
00:00:10,063 --> 00:00:11,374
Those numbers don't add up.

6
00:00:11,398 --> 00:00:13,326
Summer associates
work as lawyers,

7
00:00:13,350 --> 00:00:15,328
and I can do the same.

8
00:00:15,352 --> 00:00:18,164
It's an offer letter.
We're investment bankers.

9
00:00:18,188 --> 00:00:20,049
Our job blows yours
out of the water.

10
00:00:20,073 --> 00:00:21,584
Harvey, Stephanie Liston
just called me.

11
00:00:21,608 --> 00:00:23,719
She said they just brought Mike
in for questioning.

12
00:00:23,743 --> 00:00:26,756
You're a dirty lawyer,
and now you're on my radar.

13
00:00:26,780 --> 00:00:29,642
I'm tired of putting the
people I care about in jeopardy.

14
00:00:29,666 --> 00:00:31,644
I called Jonathan Sidwell
this afternoon.

15
00:00:31,668 --> 00:00:33,512
I took the job.

16
00:00:33,536 --> 00:00:35,898
Mike Ross never went
to law school.

17
00:00:35,922 --> 00:00:39,819
I knew it,
and I hired him anyway.

18
00:00:39,843 --> 00:00:41,737
I still can't stay, Harvey.

19
00:00:41,761 --> 00:00:43,489
I'm sorry.

20
00:00:43,513 --> 00:00:46,031
Give me permission to go.

21
00:01:19,699 --> 00:01:22,344
Going to work or school?

22
00:01:22,368 --> 00:01:25,013
Both.

23
00:01:25,037 --> 00:01:27,005
Think you have time
for some of this?

24
00:01:28,258 --> 00:01:32,238
Maybe if you will loan me
your limo.

25
00:01:32,262 --> 00:01:35,124
Hmm.

26
00:01:35,148 --> 00:01:37,126
I'm sure
we can work something out.

27
00:01:37,150 --> 00:01:39,401
Mm-hmm.

28
00:02:13,052 --> 00:02:14,780
Thought you were
getting dressed.

29
00:02:14,804 --> 00:02:16,916
I did get dressed.

30
00:02:16,940 --> 00:02:18,584
Then you got undressed.

31
00:02:18,608 --> 00:02:21,737
I got a little hot.

32
00:02:21,761 --> 00:02:23,622
Yes.

33
00:02:23,646 --> 00:02:26,148
You did.

34
00:02:36,709 --> 00:02:39,995
Come to think of it, it is
getting a little warm in here.

35
00:03:03,970 --> 00:03:07,049
Good. Thank you.

36
00:03:07,073 --> 00:03:08,217
Mr. Gillis.

37
00:03:08,241 --> 00:03:10,052
Mike Ross. Nice to meet you.

38
00:03:10,076 --> 00:03:11,620
You should know
I'm only doing this

39
00:03:11,644 --> 00:03:13,305
as a courtesy
to Jonathan Sidwell.

40
00:03:13,329 --> 00:03:16,008
But I'll tell you right now,
the answer is no.

41
00:03:16,032 --> 00:03:18,627
- Good.
- Why good?

42
00:03:18,651 --> 00:03:19,962
Because a yes
is always so much better

43
00:03:19,986 --> 00:03:20,980
when it starts as a no.

44
00:03:21,004 --> 00:03:22,765
You're a confident young man,

45
00:03:22,789 --> 00:03:25,684
but I know what my
distribution centers are worth.

46
00:03:25,708 --> 00:03:26,936
You know
what they're worth to you.

47
00:03:26,960 --> 00:03:30,662
This is what they're worth
to me.

48
00:03:33,833 --> 00:03:35,528
This is bigger than I expected.

49
00:03:35,552 --> 00:03:37,696
I've heard that before.

50
00:03:37,720 --> 00:03:39,698
Okay, fun time's over.

51
00:03:39,722 --> 00:03:41,584
I'm not interested in selling
to someone

52
00:03:41,608 --> 00:03:42,918
who I don't know
where they're coming from.

53
00:03:42,942 --> 00:03:45,004
Let me tell you
where I'm coming from.

54
00:03:45,028 --> 00:03:46,705
I do my homework.

55
00:03:46,729 --> 00:03:49,291
These centers are a beacon
to every predator out there

56
00:03:49,315 --> 00:03:50,492
that you haven't laid
the groundwork

57
00:03:50,516 --> 00:03:51,844
to get out of the DVD business.

58
00:03:51,868 --> 00:03:53,508
Sounds to me
like where you're coming from

59
00:03:53,519 --> 00:03:54,830
is trying to scare me.

60
00:03:54,854 --> 00:03:56,348
No, no,
I'm not trying to scare you.

61
00:03:56,372 --> 00:03:59,635
I'm trying to help you.

62
00:03:59,659 --> 00:04:02,471
They're circling,
and you know it.

63
00:04:02,495 --> 00:04:03,672
You don't do this,

64
00:04:03,696 --> 00:04:05,340
you might as well send out
an invitation

65
00:04:05,364 --> 00:04:08,510
asking for a hostile takeover.

66
00:04:08,534 --> 00:04:10,362
This number can't be real.

67
00:04:10,386 --> 00:04:11,614
- It is.
- Then what the hell

68
00:04:11,638 --> 00:04:13,365
are you gonna do
with my distribution centers?

69
00:04:13,389 --> 00:04:16,541
I'll be happy to tell you that
five seconds after I buy them.

70
00:04:18,595 --> 00:04:20,539
Walter, I know you want
your people to be okay,

71
00:04:20,563 --> 00:04:22,625
and I give you my word
they will be.

72
00:04:22,649 --> 00:04:25,661
But these centers...
have become a headache.

73
00:04:25,685 --> 00:04:28,547
And you need cash for when
those predators come knocking.

74
00:04:28,571 --> 00:04:31,467
Let them knock.
I'm not answering the door.

75
00:04:31,491 --> 00:04:33,052
No, you're not hearing me.

76
00:04:33,076 --> 00:04:35,971
If you don't raise enough money,
they're coming in

77
00:04:35,995 --> 00:04:41,093
whether you answer that door
or not.

78
00:04:41,117 --> 00:04:44,235
The offer's good
for another hour.

79
00:04:51,628 --> 00:04:53,739
You are not
my hair-gelled partner in crime.

80
00:04:53,763 --> 00:04:56,158
I haven't used hair gel
since ninth grade.

81
00:04:56,182 --> 00:04:59,662
I was trying to avoid
the frizzy look.

82
00:04:59,686 --> 00:05:01,080
Where is he?

83
00:05:01,104 --> 00:05:02,397
Donna said that he had
a morning meeting

84
00:05:02,421 --> 00:05:03,415
outside of the office.

85
00:05:03,439 --> 00:05:05,084
And where is Donna?

86
00:05:05,108 --> 00:05:06,401
Right here.

87
00:05:06,425 --> 00:05:08,504
I prefer to appear
at the exact moment I'm needed.

88
00:05:08,528 --> 00:05:09,672
I wish I could say the same
for Harvey.

89
00:05:09,696 --> 00:05:11,457
- Oh, well, Harvey has a very...
- Save it.

90
00:05:11,481 --> 00:05:12,958
She may have been born
yesterday,

91
00:05:12,982 --> 00:05:15,928
but I know that morning meeting
doesn't mean "morning meeting."

92
00:05:15,952 --> 00:05:17,046
Everyone knows that.

93
00:05:17,070 --> 00:05:18,350
It's just not my place
to say it.

94
00:05:18,371 --> 00:05:19,348
Not mine either.

95
00:05:19,372 --> 00:05:21,467
He did it yesterday too.

96
00:05:21,491 --> 00:05:23,052
When he resurfaces,

97
00:05:23,076 --> 00:05:26,745
tell Specter
Pearson wants to see him.

98
00:05:29,215 --> 00:05:30,776
I used mousse in high school.

99
00:05:30,800 --> 00:05:33,028
It was the '90s. Was it?

100
00:05:33,052 --> 00:05:34,336
I heard that.

101
00:05:52,021 --> 00:05:53,716
Did you bring me lunch?

102
00:05:53,740 --> 00:05:55,217
Chen Dynasty.

103
00:05:55,241 --> 00:05:56,802
How many egg rolls are in here?

104
00:05:56,826 --> 00:05:58,637
- Two.
- You closed Gillis.

105
00:05:58,661 --> 00:06:00,122
No, I killed Gillis.

106
00:06:00,146 --> 00:06:03,175
Well, I hope you told them
no mushrooms in the lo mein.

107
00:06:03,199 --> 00:06:05,794
- You never told me that.
- I didn't think I had to.

108
00:06:05,818 --> 00:06:07,179
Aren't you supposed to be
the one taking care of me?

109
00:06:07,203 --> 00:06:09,598
Ugh, how am I
supposed to do that

110
00:06:09,622 --> 00:06:11,466
when there are mushrooms
in my lo mein?

111
00:06:11,490 --> 00:06:13,301
Why do I keep you around again?

112
00:06:13,325 --> 00:06:14,737
Deal memo
on Friedman Technologies,

113
00:06:14,761 --> 00:06:16,855
engagement letter
signed by Stillman,

114
00:06:16,879 --> 00:06:19,024
and, oh, two front-row tickets
to Daft Punk

115
00:06:19,048 --> 00:06:20,776
for you and Rachel tonight.

116
00:06:20,800 --> 00:06:24,163
But why do I keep you around?

117
00:06:24,187 --> 00:06:26,031
Mike, Sidwell's in there
waiting for you.

118
00:06:26,055 --> 00:06:28,500
Be careful, okay?
He's not in a good mood.

119
00:06:28,524 --> 00:06:30,152
It's okay. You know why?

120
00:06:30,176 --> 00:06:32,204
'Cause I killed it with Gillis.

121
00:06:32,228 --> 00:06:33,488
Hey, Amy. Yeah?

122
00:06:33,512 --> 00:06:34,823
Eat the mushrooms.
They're good for you.

123
00:06:34,847 --> 00:06:36,625
Screw you.

124
00:06:36,649 --> 00:06:39,461
- Morning.
- Where have you been?

125
00:06:39,485 --> 00:06:41,013
Oh, you know,
just getting Walter Gillis

126
00:06:41,037 --> 00:06:42,798
to sell us
all of his distribution centers.

127
00:06:42,822 --> 00:06:45,768
Oh.

128
00:06:45,792 --> 00:06:48,003
- What the hell are you doing?
- What's it look like I'm doing?

129
00:06:48,027 --> 00:06:50,222
I'm sending a message.
We're not a convent.

130
00:06:50,246 --> 00:06:51,523
We're in business to make money.

131
00:06:51,547 --> 00:06:53,225
And this deal does that.

132
00:06:53,249 --> 00:06:55,129
You did this deal
to retain those people's jobs.

133
00:06:55,134 --> 00:06:57,813
- And to make us 30%.
- We're a hedge fund.

134
00:06:57,837 --> 00:06:59,181
If we don't make 50%,

135
00:06:59,205 --> 00:07:01,366
we might as well buy time-shares
and hope for the best.

136
00:07:01,373 --> 00:07:03,068
That's bullshit.
This deal is solid.

137
00:07:03,092 --> 00:07:05,621
No, what's bullshit is you've
been here for three months.

138
00:07:05,645 --> 00:07:08,123
All you've done is hit singles,
and I need a goddamn home run.

139
00:07:08,147 --> 00:07:09,691
- Jonathan, listen.
- I don't want to hear it.

140
00:07:09,715 --> 00:07:12,044
I want you to get
your head out of your ass.

141
00:07:12,068 --> 00:07:13,662
Stop trying
to save people's jobs,

142
00:07:13,686 --> 00:07:16,715
and start making us
some real money.

143
00:07:16,739 --> 00:07:19,390
Or go back to being a lawyer.

144
00:07:25,865 --> 00:07:29,544
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪

145
00:07:29,568 --> 00:07:32,881
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪

146
00:07:32,905 --> 00:07:36,051
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪

147
00:07:36,075 --> 00:07:39,738
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪

148
00:07:39,762 --> 00:07:42,724
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪

149
00:07:42,748 --> 00:07:46,748
♪ Suits 4x01 ♪ One-Two-Three Go...
Original Air Date on June 11, 2014

150
00:07:46,752 --> 00:07:48,197
♪ all right

151
00:07:48,221 --> 00:07:53,702
♪ all that time imagine this ♪

152
00:07:53,726 --> 00:07:55,528
♪ The greenback boogie

153
00:07:55,552 --> 00:07:57,552
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man.

154
00:08:04,100 --> 00:08:05,894
I heard you wanted to see me.

155
00:08:05,918 --> 00:08:07,496
That was three hours ago.

156
00:08:07,520 --> 00:08:09,164
If you knew what I was doing
three hours ago,

157
00:08:09,188 --> 00:08:10,615
I don't think
you would've wanted to see me.

158
00:08:10,639 --> 00:08:12,751
I know what you were doing
three hours ago.

159
00:08:12,775 --> 00:08:16,254
Well, then, you should have
come on over.

160
00:08:16,278 --> 00:08:17,839
Maybe you should try having

161
00:08:17,863 --> 00:08:19,875
some morning meetings yourself.

162
00:08:19,899 --> 00:08:22,127
Don't you worry
about my mornings.

163
00:08:22,151 --> 00:08:24,679
What you need to worry about
is Logan Sanders.

164
00:08:24,703 --> 00:08:26,214
What?

165
00:08:26,238 --> 00:08:28,583
He drive one of his father's
subsidiaries into bankruptcy?

166
00:08:28,607 --> 00:08:31,353
The opposite.
Boy got his shit together.

167
00:08:31,377 --> 00:08:33,722
Max is retiring,
and Logan's taking over.

168
00:08:33,746 --> 00:08:35,390
Let me guess.
He wants a meeting.

169
00:08:35,414 --> 00:08:36,558
He's got one.

170
00:08:36,582 --> 00:08:38,894
With you, tomorrow morning,
10:00 a.m.

171
00:08:38,918 --> 00:08:41,096
Great. Push it a week.

172
00:08:41,120 --> 00:08:43,281
Harvey, this kid considers
himself a young lion.

173
00:08:43,305 --> 00:08:44,449
He's gonna want
to make his mark,

174
00:08:44,473 --> 00:08:46,201
and the easiest way
for him to do that

175
00:08:46,225 --> 00:08:47,986
is to change lawyers.

176
00:08:48,010 --> 00:08:49,621
Maybe, but the last thing
a lion wants

177
00:08:49,645 --> 00:08:52,290
is to have his dinner handed
to him on a silver platter.

178
00:08:52,314 --> 00:08:54,993
You're gonna give him a hunt.

179
00:08:55,017 --> 00:08:56,661
Did you think of that
all on your own?

180
00:08:56,685 --> 00:08:57,779
I'm extra sharp.

181
00:08:57,803 --> 00:08:59,581
I haven't worked
a minute all morning.

182
00:08:59,605 --> 00:09:01,550
See, that's funny, 'cause
I was late from all the sex.

183
00:09:01,574 --> 00:09:03,218
Get the hell out of my office.

184
00:09:03,242 --> 00:09:05,693
♪ Bow chicka bow bow

185
00:09:14,253 --> 00:09:15,564
Look what the cat dragged in.

186
00:09:15,588 --> 00:09:18,567
And you're wearing a vest.
Here it comes.

187
00:09:18,591 --> 00:09:21,103
Here what comes? Mazel tov.

188
00:09:21,127 --> 00:09:23,071
Congratulations
on your special day.

189
00:09:23,095 --> 00:09:24,806
- That's a good one.
- Harvey, leave him alone.

190
00:09:24,830 --> 00:09:26,241
He looks better than you do.

191
00:09:26,265 --> 00:09:28,410
- Thank you, Donna.
- You're welcome.

192
00:09:28,434 --> 00:09:29,811
Oh, and Mr. Peanut called,

193
00:09:29,835 --> 00:09:31,446
and he said he'd be happy
to lend you his top hat.

194
00:09:31,470 --> 00:09:34,032
- Are you two finished?
- I could go all day.

195
00:09:34,056 --> 00:09:35,417
I think the vest has had enough.

196
00:09:35,441 --> 00:09:37,119
Yeah.

197
00:09:37,143 --> 00:09:38,920
So you come all the way
down here just to let me know

198
00:09:38,944 --> 00:09:41,006
that you were right
about Walter Gillis?

199
00:09:41,030 --> 00:09:42,591
I came all the way over here
to tell you

200
00:09:42,615 --> 00:09:43,992
I am done playing
in the kiddie pool.

201
00:09:44,016 --> 00:09:45,794
- I'm listening.
- I'm going after a whale.

202
00:09:45,818 --> 00:09:47,762
I think I'm in love.
Let's go to war.

203
00:09:47,786 --> 00:09:49,831
That's the thing.

204
00:09:49,855 --> 00:09:51,332
We're not going to war.

205
00:09:51,356 --> 00:09:54,669
Mike, the second
whoever it is finds out

206
00:09:54,693 --> 00:09:56,271
that you've got 5%
of their company,

207
00:09:56,295 --> 00:09:57,722
we're going to war
whether you like it or not.

208
00:09:57,746 --> 00:10:00,442
They're not gonna find
that out because I don't own 5%.

209
00:10:00,466 --> 00:10:03,061
Do I need to give you
a tutorial on the procedure?

210
00:10:03,085 --> 00:10:04,646
You start by buying shares.

211
00:10:04,670 --> 00:10:05,947
I know what
the procedure is, Harvey.

212
00:10:05,971 --> 00:10:07,315
Well, how many shares
have you bought?

213
00:10:07,339 --> 00:10:08,900
- None.
- This phrase,

214
00:10:08,924 --> 00:10:10,185
"I know what the procedure is,"

215
00:10:10,209 --> 00:10:12,320
I don't think it means
what you think it means.

216
00:10:12,344 --> 00:10:15,123
Well, as inconceivable
as it might be to you, Harvey,

217
00:10:15,147 --> 00:10:16,791
I'm actually
not going in hostile.

218
00:10:16,815 --> 00:10:17,993
What are you talking about?

219
00:10:18,017 --> 00:10:19,294
I'm talking
about approaching someone

220
00:10:19,318 --> 00:10:21,379
to buy their company
in order to keep it alive,

221
00:10:21,403 --> 00:10:23,198
instead of selling it for parts.

222
00:10:23,222 --> 00:10:24,883
You're offering someone
hugs and rainbows.

223
00:10:24,907 --> 00:10:27,502
I'm offering someone
the chance to survive

224
00:10:27,526 --> 00:10:29,221
and banking
that they'll take that chance

225
00:10:29,245 --> 00:10:31,339
rather than give up.

226
00:10:31,363 --> 00:10:32,807
You don't have the money,
do you?

227
00:10:32,831 --> 00:10:33,975
No, I don't.

228
00:10:33,999 --> 00:10:36,011
But even if I did,
I wouldn't use it.

229
00:10:36,035 --> 00:10:38,546
Well,
welcome to what every person

230
00:10:38,570 --> 00:10:39,931
who doesn't have money
has ever said.

231
00:10:39,955 --> 00:10:42,017
Oh, I get it.

232
00:10:42,041 --> 00:10:44,352
You think this is the meeting
where you make fun of my idea.

233
00:10:44,376 --> 00:10:45,520
No, no, no, no, no, no.

234
00:10:45,544 --> 00:10:46,938
This is the meeting
where you realize

235
00:10:46,962 --> 00:10:50,859
that my idea is happening
whether you like it or not.

236
00:10:50,883 --> 00:10:52,410
Where's the fun in that meeting?

237
00:10:52,434 --> 00:10:53,828
Oh, the fun?

238
00:10:53,852 --> 00:10:56,781
It's all right over here
on this side of the table.

239
00:10:56,805 --> 00:10:58,566
Hey, I'll give you a chance
to get acquainted

240
00:10:58,590 --> 00:11:00,001
with the new reality.

241
00:11:00,025 --> 00:11:01,236
I'll be in my office.

242
00:11:01,260 --> 00:11:02,921
Get back to me
by the end of the day.

243
00:11:02,945 --> 00:11:04,122
Wow.

244
00:11:04,146 --> 00:11:07,759
Looks like our baby boy's
all growns up.

245
00:11:07,783 --> 00:11:10,178
Hey, tell me, sweetheart,
you guys validate parking?

246
00:11:10,202 --> 00:11:11,179
Oh, yeah, sure thing.

247
00:11:11,203 --> 00:11:13,632
I've got it right here.

248
00:11:13,656 --> 00:11:15,217
And how many hours
is that good for?

249
00:11:15,241 --> 00:11:16,551
What's it matter?

250
00:11:16,575 --> 00:11:18,376
We're just gonna charge it
back to you anyway.

251
00:11:21,046 --> 00:11:23,114
You know my secretary is,
like, so much younger

252
00:11:24,917 --> 00:11:26,450
did he say "fitter"?

253
00:11:28,387 --> 00:11:30,315
What did you find out?

254
00:11:30,339 --> 00:11:32,450
- Woodall's resurfacing.
- Me too. When?

255
00:11:32,474 --> 00:11:33,952
- Next week.
- Me too. Where?

256
00:11:33,976 --> 00:11:35,820
- S.E.C.
- Me too. Title?

257
00:11:35,844 --> 00:11:37,789
- Supervisor.
- Director.

258
00:11:37,813 --> 00:11:39,074
Me too. I just threw that in

259
00:11:39,098 --> 00:11:40,875
to make sure
you weren't yes-man-ing me.

260
00:11:40,899 --> 00:11:41,960
Talk to me.

261
00:11:41,984 --> 00:11:42,911
I found out the name of the man.

262
00:11:42,935 --> 00:11:44,079
Woodall's sending after us.

263
00:11:44,103 --> 00:11:46,437
Jeff Malone.

264
00:11:48,107 --> 00:11:49,467
Jeff Malone is a beast.

265
00:11:49,491 --> 00:11:50,585
Well, the only way

266
00:11:50,609 --> 00:11:53,838
to beat a beast
is with a bigger beast.

267
00:11:53,862 --> 00:11:55,223
I need to get in there
before everyone else

268
00:11:55,247 --> 00:11:57,959
and let Harvey and Jessica know
that I had the foresight

269
00:11:57,983 --> 00:11:59,477
to look for it,
the cunning to find it,

270
00:11:59,501 --> 00:12:00,679
and the balls to stop it.

271
00:12:00,703 --> 00:12:02,230
Then you take on Malone.

272
00:12:02,254 --> 00:12:04,015
Next stop: Name partner.

273
00:12:04,039 --> 00:12:06,735
- Pearson Specter Litt.
- Okay, you know what?

274
00:12:06,759 --> 00:12:10,488
Just let's not count
our chickens before they hatch.

275
00:12:10,512 --> 00:12:11,740
But just for shits and giggles,
say it one more time.

276
00:12:11,764 --> 00:12:13,275
Leave out Specter.

277
00:12:13,299 --> 00:12:16,411
Donna, I got Paul Porter's
annual restructuring proposal.

278
00:12:16,435 --> 00:12:19,414
Can you file it
under "I don't give a shit"?

279
00:12:19,438 --> 00:12:21,199
What about Mike?
You want me to have Rachel

280
00:12:21,223 --> 00:12:22,667
prepare a dog and pony show
for him?

281
00:12:22,691 --> 00:12:24,669
- That won't be necessary.
- Why not?

282
00:12:24,693 --> 00:12:26,921
Harvey, I need to talk
to you right now

283
00:12:26,945 --> 00:12:28,039
about something very important.

284
00:12:28,063 --> 00:12:29,507
Harvey, why won't it
be necessary?

285
00:12:29,531 --> 00:12:31,126
'Cause you don't beg
the girl to go out with you.

286
00:12:31,150 --> 00:12:32,294
You wait.

287
00:12:32,318 --> 00:12:34,129
She'll call. That's not even-

288
00:12:34,153 --> 00:12:37,432
Excuse me. Hold on a second.
Um, what if they don't call?

289
00:12:37,456 --> 00:12:38,850
They always call.

290
00:12:38,874 --> 00:12:40,352
Well, what about people
who aren't you?

291
00:12:40,376 --> 00:12:42,520
- You mean you?
- Yeah, of course I do.

292
00:12:42,544 --> 00:12:44,439
If they don't call,
then they don't call.

293
00:12:44,463 --> 00:12:46,191
But once they smell
your desperation,

294
00:12:46,215 --> 00:12:47,559
they won't respect you,

295
00:12:47,583 --> 00:12:49,394
and you'll never get
what you want anyway.

296
00:12:49,418 --> 00:12:51,346
I'm sorry, did you want
to talk to me about something?

297
00:12:51,370 --> 00:12:53,114
It can wait.

298
00:12:53,138 --> 00:12:54,899
Come to think of it,

299
00:12:54,923 --> 00:12:56,785
tell Rachel
when she's back from school

300
00:12:56,809 --> 00:13:00,678
she can have
the rest of the day off.

301
00:13:02,898 --> 00:13:05,076
Harvey.

302
00:13:05,100 --> 00:13:08,163
You do that, you might as well
send Mike a telegram that says,

303
00:13:08,187 --> 00:13:10,198
"I'm not putting any thought
into your idea."

304
00:13:10,222 --> 00:13:11,966
Yeah, might as well.

305
00:13:11,990 --> 00:13:14,336
Okay, are you sure that's how
you want to play this?

306
00:13:14,360 --> 00:13:15,837
Didn't I just answer that?

307
00:13:15,861 --> 00:13:19,674
You did, but this isn't about
whether or not Mike calls back.

308
00:13:19,698 --> 00:13:21,593
This is about you
not letting Mike call the shots.

309
00:13:21,617 --> 00:13:23,178
I let him call the shots,
all he's gonna do

310
00:13:23,202 --> 00:13:24,896
is shoot himself in the foot.
Maybe.

311
00:13:24,920 --> 00:13:26,714
But if this was anybody
other than Mike,

312
00:13:26,738 --> 00:13:28,316
you wouldn't be acting
like this.

313
00:13:28,340 --> 00:13:29,550
Bullshit. I don't let
Tony Gianopolous push me around.

314
00:13:29,574 --> 00:13:30,952
You think I'm gonna let
Mike Ross?

315
00:13:30,976 --> 00:13:33,188
No, of course you don't let
Tony push you around,

316
00:13:33,212 --> 00:13:35,824
but I've never seen you
mock one of his ideas.

317
00:13:35,848 --> 00:13:37,242
Yeah, because his ideas
aren't ridiculous.

318
00:13:37,266 --> 00:13:39,611
This is Mike's first big idea.

319
00:13:39,635 --> 00:13:42,113
And I just told you,
his first big idea sucks.

320
00:13:42,137 --> 00:13:44,666
And if you use Rachel
to deliver that message,

321
00:13:44,690 --> 00:13:45,667
this is gonna end badly.

322
00:13:45,691 --> 00:13:46,901
Okay, thanks, mom, but I think

323
00:13:46,925 --> 00:13:48,236
I'm gonna keep playing ball
in the house.

324
00:13:48,260 --> 00:13:50,905
Okay, act like a child
who doesn't want to be told

325
00:13:50,929 --> 00:13:52,173
what to do, but Mike's a client,

326
00:13:52,197 --> 00:13:53,625
and you need to start
treating him like one.

327
00:13:53,649 --> 00:13:55,677
Donna, the next time
I need help figuring out

328
00:13:55,701 --> 00:13:58,463
how to treat a client,
I'll let you know.

329
00:13:58,487 --> 00:14:00,571
Okay, great.

330
00:14:11,421 --> 00:14:13,349
Harvey, what can I do for you?

331
00:14:13,373 --> 00:14:15,351
There's a Jeff Malone
waiting in the conference room

332
00:14:15,375 --> 00:14:16,519
wanting to see both of us.

333
00:14:16,543 --> 00:14:18,521
Any idea who he is?

334
00:14:18,545 --> 00:14:21,474
I've run into him before.
He's a hotshot at the S.E.C.

335
00:14:21,498 --> 00:14:24,833
- What do you think he wants?
- Let's go find out.

336
00:14:27,670 --> 00:14:29,165
Ms. Pearson.

337
00:14:29,189 --> 00:14:30,583
You must be Harvey Specter.

338
00:14:30,607 --> 00:14:32,535
I'm Jeff Malone.
I know who you are.

339
00:14:32,559 --> 00:14:34,003
My question is,
why are you here?

340
00:14:34,027 --> 00:14:36,839
- You seem hostile.
- You investigate

341
00:14:36,863 --> 00:14:39,625
publicly traded companies.
We're not publicly traded.

342
00:14:39,649 --> 00:14:41,260
No, but your clients are.

343
00:14:41,284 --> 00:14:43,296
Hence his question
and our hostility.

344
00:14:43,320 --> 00:14:45,214
- Our?
- We tend to stick together

345
00:14:45,238 --> 00:14:47,517
when an uninvited guest
interrupts our dinner.

346
00:14:47,541 --> 00:14:49,936
Well, I didn't bring any wine,
but when I go,

347
00:14:49,960 --> 00:14:51,387
I hope you'll be happy
that I dropped by.

348
00:14:51,411 --> 00:14:53,356
Yeah, I doubt that.

349
00:14:53,380 --> 00:14:55,841
So why don't you tell us
which client you're here for

350
00:14:55,865 --> 00:14:57,393
and be on your way?

351
00:14:57,417 --> 00:14:59,979
All of them.

352
00:15:00,003 --> 00:15:03,399
Since when does the S.E.C.
go around intimidating law firms

353
00:15:03,423 --> 00:15:05,068
by going after their clients?

354
00:15:05,092 --> 00:15:06,452
They don't, but they will

355
00:15:06,476 --> 00:15:08,704
when Eric Woodall starts there
next week.

356
00:15:08,728 --> 00:15:10,873
He comes at our clients
after what he did,

357
00:15:10,897 --> 00:15:14,377
this time, he won't get fired,
he'll end up in jail.

358
00:15:14,401 --> 00:15:16,629
Except it won't be Woodall
who's coming.

359
00:15:16,653 --> 00:15:17,914
It'll be him.

360
00:15:17,938 --> 00:15:20,083
Exactly.

361
00:15:20,107 --> 00:15:22,835
Listen, I'm gonna be getting
a vaguely worded assignment

362
00:15:22,859 --> 00:15:24,053
with a not-so-vague agenda

363
00:15:24,077 --> 00:15:25,471
of getting up
your clients' asses

364
00:15:25,495 --> 00:15:27,540
with the full power
of the S.E.C.

365
00:15:27,564 --> 00:15:28,724
And when they ask why...

366
00:15:28,748 --> 00:15:30,726
And they always ask why...

367
00:15:30,750 --> 00:15:32,178
I'm gonna be expected
to tell them

368
00:15:32,202 --> 00:15:33,813
that it's because
they're clients of your firm.

369
00:15:33,837 --> 00:15:35,098
Why are you telling us this?

370
00:15:35,122 --> 00:15:37,683
Because he doesn't want
to work for Woodall.

371
00:15:37,707 --> 00:15:40,403
He wants to work here.

372
00:15:40,427 --> 00:15:43,906
I've always heard
how good you were.

373
00:15:43,930 --> 00:15:46,526
It's nice to see it's true.

374
00:15:46,550 --> 00:15:48,727
Anyway, here's the thing.

375
00:15:48,751 --> 00:15:51,747
I'm really tired
of being a public servant,

376
00:15:51,771 --> 00:15:53,566
and more importantly,
I've always thought

377
00:15:53,590 --> 00:15:55,901
that Eric Woodall was a, um...

378
00:15:55,925 --> 00:15:57,670
Oh, shit,
I'll just go ahead and say it.

379
00:15:57,694 --> 00:15:58,737
He's a dick.

380
00:15:58,761 --> 00:16:00,957
Finally, something
we can agree on.

381
00:16:00,981 --> 00:16:02,959
Seems to me the only thing
left for us to agree on, Harvey,

382
00:16:02,983 --> 00:16:04,177
is my starting salary.

383
00:16:04,201 --> 00:16:06,462
I'm just kidding.

384
00:16:06,486 --> 00:16:08,714
I'm sure
all your new senior partners

385
00:16:08,738 --> 00:16:10,466
get paid the same.

386
00:16:10,490 --> 00:16:11,717
Before you start picking out
floor patterns

387
00:16:11,741 --> 00:16:13,019
for your new office,

388
00:16:13,043 --> 00:16:15,388
I'd like to discuss this
with my partner first.

389
00:16:15,412 --> 00:16:18,141
I'd expect nothing less.

390
00:16:18,165 --> 00:16:20,643
Oh, uh, just one more thing.

391
00:16:20,667 --> 00:16:22,595
I haven't been formally given
this assignment yet,

392
00:16:22,619 --> 00:16:23,896
so I have no conflict.

393
00:16:23,920 --> 00:16:25,231
But in one more week I will,

394
00:16:25,255 --> 00:16:26,566
which means this offer
will be gone.

395
00:16:26,590 --> 00:16:27,733
Is that a threat?

396
00:16:27,757 --> 00:16:28,985
I would never threaten someone

397
00:16:29,009 --> 00:16:31,103
that I want to be
in business with, Jessica.

398
00:16:31,127 --> 00:16:34,063
It's just the truth.

399
00:16:37,567 --> 00:16:38,934
I like him.

400
00:16:41,971 --> 00:16:44,000
How did it go with Harvey?

401
00:16:44,024 --> 00:16:47,420
Didn't.

402
00:16:47,444 --> 00:16:49,505
What do you mean "it didn't"?

403
00:16:49,529 --> 00:16:52,458
You're the only man here
who can take on Jeff Malone.

404
00:16:52,482 --> 00:16:55,127
How could he not see that?
I didn't bring it up.

405
00:16:55,151 --> 00:16:57,763
Louis, winter is coming.

406
00:16:57,787 --> 00:16:59,315
I know,
and I'm the night's watch.

407
00:16:59,339 --> 00:17:02,268
But right now
we need to be patient.

408
00:17:02,292 --> 00:17:05,738
Patience
is not your strong suit.

409
00:17:05,762 --> 00:17:07,156
Well, today it is.

410
00:17:07,180 --> 00:17:08,691
Because if there's one thing
that I've always known,

411
00:17:08,715 --> 00:17:10,943
it's that you do not call
the pretty girl.

412
00:17:10,967 --> 00:17:12,612
You wait for her to call you.

413
00:17:12,636 --> 00:17:14,864
Louis, I'm seeing someone.

414
00:17:14,888 --> 00:17:16,332
I'm happy for you,

415
00:17:16,356 --> 00:17:17,617
though I have no idea why
you're saying that right now.

416
00:17:17,641 --> 00:17:19,035
Katrina, trust me.

417
00:17:19,059 --> 00:17:21,204
They're gonna find out
about Jeff Malone soon enough

418
00:17:21,228 --> 00:17:22,588
'cause he's gonna come calling.

419
00:17:22,612 --> 00:17:25,508
And when he does, they're gonna
come right over to me.

420
00:17:25,532 --> 00:17:27,677
Like him all you want.
I'm not hiring him.

421
00:17:27,701 --> 00:17:29,262
- Why not?
- Why do you think?

422
00:17:29,286 --> 00:17:30,663
Because you don't like
making decisions

423
00:17:30,687 --> 00:17:32,348
staring down the barrel
of a shotgun.

424
00:17:32,372 --> 00:17:33,966
Jessica Pearson.
Nice to meet you.

425
00:17:33,990 --> 00:17:35,834
Jessica, the man walked in here

426
00:17:35,858 --> 00:17:37,353
and offered to fight for us.

427
00:17:37,377 --> 00:17:38,938
If it's not him,
who's it gonna be?

428
00:17:38,962 --> 00:17:41,774
The guy in the office next door.

429
00:17:41,798 --> 00:17:43,142
Louis?

430
00:17:43,166 --> 00:17:45,278
Harvey, Louis knows
everything there is to know

431
00:17:45,302 --> 00:17:46,279
about the S.E.C.

432
00:17:46,303 --> 00:17:48,114
He's damn good, and you know it.

433
00:17:48,138 --> 00:17:50,199
This guy isn't damn good.
He's a killer.

434
00:17:50,223 --> 00:17:52,535
And he's a prosecutor.
We need a defender.

435
00:17:52,559 --> 00:17:53,953
If I'm in a dark alley,

436
00:17:53,977 --> 00:17:55,621
I'd take the killer
over the defender

437
00:17:55,645 --> 00:17:56,822
seven days a week.

438
00:17:56,846 --> 00:17:59,742
And Eric Woodall's gonna put us
in a dark alley.

439
00:17:59,766 --> 00:18:01,160
Louis is a known quantity.

440
00:18:01,184 --> 00:18:03,246
And right now Jeff Malone's
biggest selling point

441
00:18:03,270 --> 00:18:04,997
is telling us
that Woodall is coming.

442
00:18:05,021 --> 00:18:06,299
Louis sure as hell didn't,

443
00:18:06,323 --> 00:18:08,084
which means
he either didn't know

444
00:18:08,108 --> 00:18:09,585
or he wasn't man enough
to come in here

445
00:18:09,609 --> 00:18:11,721
and take the job for himself.

446
00:18:11,745 --> 00:18:14,890
Harvey, do you know why
I don't like being strong-armed

447
00:18:14,914 --> 00:18:16,342
into decisions?

448
00:18:16,366 --> 00:18:19,478
Because I'll never be able
to trust the person who did it.

449
00:18:19,502 --> 00:18:21,731
Then figure out a way
to get someone as good

450
00:18:21,755 --> 00:18:24,567
or hire this guy
and come to terms with it.

451
00:18:24,591 --> 00:18:25,901
Because if it's Louis
against Malone

452
00:18:25,925 --> 00:18:28,877
in a street fight,
I'm picking that dude.

453
00:18:36,853 --> 00:18:39,064
Oh, thank you.

454
00:18:39,088 --> 00:18:40,128
Hey, how'd your meeting go

455
00:18:40,140 --> 00:18:41,367
with the mysterious
Harvey Specter?

456
00:18:41,391 --> 00:18:43,619
Being a dick
doesn't make him mysterious.

457
00:18:43,643 --> 00:18:45,621
Well, then I guess
you're an open book.

458
00:18:45,645 --> 00:18:47,806
You know, I was gonna give you
those Daft Punk tickets,

459
00:18:47,814 --> 00:18:50,343
but now after that,
I think I'll give them to Edna.

460
00:18:50,367 --> 00:18:52,628
Okay, first of all, Edna
was 63 when Daft Punk was born.

461
00:18:52,652 --> 00:18:54,513
Really? With that skin?

462
00:18:54,537 --> 00:18:55,581
You know what, I worked hard
to get you those things.

463
00:18:55,605 --> 00:18:56,632
Why aren't you going?

464
00:18:56,656 --> 00:18:57,967
I dropped the hammer on Harvey,

465
00:18:57,991 --> 00:19:00,085
which means Rachel's
gonna be working all night.

466
00:19:00,109 --> 00:19:02,305
Hey, what are you doing here?

467
00:19:02,329 --> 00:19:04,307
Donna texted me
when I was at Columbia...

468
00:19:04,331 --> 00:19:05,424
Mmhmm.

469
00:19:05,448 --> 00:19:07,092
And told me that Harvey gave me

470
00:19:07,116 --> 00:19:09,595
the rest of the day off
because I'm kicking ass.

471
00:19:09,619 --> 00:19:11,564
He's giving you
the rest of the day off?

472
00:19:11,588 --> 00:19:12,931
Mmhmm, so I figured

473
00:19:12,955 --> 00:19:16,986
we could celebrate over dinner
before the concert.

474
00:19:17,010 --> 00:19:19,205
What, are you jealous 'cause
he never did that for you?

475
00:19:19,229 --> 00:19:21,657
Um, no. That's great.

476
00:19:21,681 --> 00:19:23,793
You pick a place.
I'll meet you there.

477
00:19:23,817 --> 00:19:26,245
I got to set up some meetings
for tomorrow first.

478
00:19:26,269 --> 00:19:27,330
What about the little owl?

479
00:19:27,354 --> 00:19:30,305
- Yeah.
- Okay.

480
00:19:39,532 --> 00:19:42,094
Mike, what are you doing here?

481
00:19:42,118 --> 00:19:45,788
You delivered a message,
so now I'm delivering one.

482
00:19:47,924 --> 00:19:50,770
Pearson Specter
is formally in review.

483
00:19:50,794 --> 00:19:52,571
What did you just say to me?

484
00:19:52,595 --> 00:19:55,274
You want my business,
you're gonna have to earn it.

485
00:19:55,298 --> 00:19:57,493
- I have earned it.
- By shit-ing on my plan?

486
00:19:57,517 --> 00:19:58,911
You don't have a plan.

487
00:19:58,935 --> 00:20:00,196
You're running into a wall.

488
00:20:00,220 --> 00:20:01,330
It's not my job
to crash into it with you.

489
00:20:01,354 --> 00:20:02,665
Crash into it?

490
00:20:02,689 --> 00:20:04,200
You didn't even ask me
who I'm going after.

491
00:20:04,224 --> 00:20:06,318
I didn't have to
because it doesn't matter.

492
00:20:06,342 --> 00:20:08,022
But go ahead. Who is it?
Gillis industries.

493
00:20:08,027 --> 00:20:10,089
That's not a whale.
That's a monster.

494
00:20:10,113 --> 00:20:13,509
A man like Walter Gillis isn't
gonna listen to a guy like you

495
00:20:13,533 --> 00:20:15,795
offering to save him
with sunshine and rainbows.

496
00:20:15,819 --> 00:20:18,163
That's exactly
what you said to me

497
00:20:18,187 --> 00:20:20,132
before I got him to sell me
his distribution centers.

498
00:20:20,156 --> 00:20:21,717
Congratulations.
You got to walk his dog.

499
00:20:21,741 --> 00:20:24,220
That doesn't mean he's gonna
let you marry his daughter.

500
00:20:24,244 --> 00:20:26,839
Listen to me.
You want to be my guy?

501
00:20:26,863 --> 00:20:28,441
You stop telling me
why I can't do this,

502
00:20:28,465 --> 00:20:30,643
and you start figuring out
how I can.

503
00:20:30,667 --> 00:20:31,944
I already told you how you can.

504
00:20:31,968 --> 00:20:33,779
You get some money,
start buying some shares,

505
00:20:33,803 --> 00:20:35,648
and you walk in there
with a club

506
00:20:35,672 --> 00:20:36,949
and the balls to use it
if you have to.

507
00:20:36,973 --> 00:20:38,951
Harvey, when I told you
my plan's happening

508
00:20:38,975 --> 00:20:40,536
whether you like it or not,
I meant it.

509
00:20:40,560 --> 00:20:42,187
I'm interviewing law firms
tomorrow.

510
00:20:42,211 --> 00:20:44,323
You show up with a better
attitude and another move,

511
00:20:44,347 --> 00:20:47,215
or you just lost a client.

512
00:20:51,964 --> 00:20:53,519
You want talk about it?

513
00:20:54,808 --> 00:20:56,586
Talk about what?

514
00:20:56,610 --> 00:21:00,646
About whatever's going on
with you and Harvey.

515
00:21:03,116 --> 00:21:05,011
Why does everybody think
that I was born yesterday?

516
00:21:05,035 --> 00:21:07,130
I tell you that he gives me
the rest of the day off work,

517
00:21:07,154 --> 00:21:09,154
you vanish until dinner,
and then you're pissed off

518
00:21:09,156 --> 00:21:10,416
for the rest of the night,

519
00:21:10,440 --> 00:21:12,385
so it doesn't take
a rocket scientist.

520
00:21:12,409 --> 00:21:14,187
Clearly.

521
00:21:14,211 --> 00:21:16,689
I meant "I love you."

522
00:21:16,713 --> 00:21:18,558
Mmhmm, nice recovery.

523
00:21:18,582 --> 00:21:20,310
Doesn't get you
out of answering my question.

524
00:21:20,334 --> 00:21:21,327
You really want to know?

525
00:21:21,351 --> 00:21:23,146
I'll tell you.

526
00:21:23,170 --> 00:21:25,865
Harvey was Michael Jordan.

527
00:21:25,889 --> 00:21:29,619
Now it's Lebron's time,
and he can't take it.

528
00:21:29,643 --> 00:21:32,322
That's a pretty big accusation
to make.

529
00:21:32,346 --> 00:21:34,741
Well, there's more
to the story than you know.

530
00:21:34,765 --> 00:21:36,292
- What?
- Right, so come on.

531
00:21:36,316 --> 00:21:38,661
I said I didn't want to get
between you two.

532
00:21:38,685 --> 00:21:40,069
What?

533
00:21:42,773 --> 00:21:45,218
Let's just say
that you kicking ass for him

534
00:21:45,242 --> 00:21:48,327
isn't the reason
you got the day off.

535
00:21:53,834 --> 00:21:55,261
I thought
you had law school today.

536
00:21:55,285 --> 00:21:58,264
I do right after this.

537
00:21:58,288 --> 00:22:00,316
He told you.

538
00:22:00,340 --> 00:22:02,018
Did you think he wouldn't?

539
00:22:02,042 --> 00:22:03,820
Look, if you want to send
a message to Mike,

540
00:22:03,844 --> 00:22:05,021
go right ahead.

541
00:22:05,045 --> 00:22:06,472
If you want me to send
a message to Mike,

542
00:22:06,496 --> 00:22:09,075
tell me when and where, but...

543
00:22:09,099 --> 00:22:12,645
Please don't ever use me
like that again.

544
00:22:12,669 --> 00:22:15,531
You're right.

545
00:22:15,555 --> 00:22:18,001
I'm what now?

546
00:22:18,025 --> 00:22:19,919
I shouldn't have done that.
I'm sorry.

547
00:22:19,943 --> 00:22:21,621
Is it April fools' day?

548
00:22:21,645 --> 00:22:23,256
No, but don't ever
let it be said

549
00:22:23,280 --> 00:22:24,424
that I can't admit
when I'm wrong.

550
00:22:24,448 --> 00:22:26,009
Then I will stop saying that.

551
00:22:26,033 --> 00:22:27,627
Didn't you say
you have class today?

552
00:22:27,651 --> 00:22:30,162
I'm on my way.

553
00:22:30,186 --> 00:22:31,931
What was that all about?

554
00:22:31,955 --> 00:22:32,999
Just some administrative stuff.

555
00:22:33,023 --> 00:22:35,852
Administrative stuff.
You and Rachel.

556
00:22:35,876 --> 00:22:37,353
I don't want to talk about it.

557
00:22:37,377 --> 00:22:38,771
You mean about how everything
I said would happen happened,

558
00:22:38,795 --> 00:22:40,890
and now you realize I was right
the whole time?

559
00:22:40,914 --> 00:22:42,141
No one likes a gloater, Donna.

560
00:22:42,165 --> 00:22:43,359
Well, then I guess

561
00:22:43,383 --> 00:22:44,560
the Harvey Specter University
of gloating

562
00:22:44,584 --> 00:22:45,862
is gonna have to shut down.

563
00:22:45,886 --> 00:22:49,866
I can still give lectures
on the weekend.

564
00:22:49,890 --> 00:22:51,284
You want to hear it?

565
00:22:51,308 --> 00:22:53,259
You were right.

566
00:22:54,511 --> 00:22:55,705
Call Ray.

567
00:22:55,729 --> 00:22:58,074
I'm gonna go let Mike know
I'm his lawyer.

568
00:22:58,098 --> 00:23:01,694
You're gonna push
a meeting with me?

569
00:23:01,718 --> 00:23:04,881
Harvey, Logan Sanders
is here to see you.

570
00:23:04,905 --> 00:23:07,133
First of all, I don't appreciate

571
00:23:07,157 --> 00:23:08,968
you stomping into my office
with an attitude.

572
00:23:08,992 --> 00:23:10,720
Yeah, well, I don't appreciate
being put off,

573
00:23:10,744 --> 00:23:12,138
especially when I know
that you never pushed a meeting

574
00:23:12,162 --> 00:23:13,473
with my father.

575
00:23:13,497 --> 00:23:14,924
Your father
never went to Jessica

576
00:23:14,948 --> 00:23:16,509
to set a meeting with me.

577
00:23:16,533 --> 00:23:18,978
Then I assume that next time
I call you directly,

578
00:23:19,002 --> 00:23:20,346
you'll pick up the phone.

579
00:23:20,370 --> 00:23:24,517
Logan, let me give you
the ABCs of me.

580
00:23:24,541 --> 00:23:27,153
I don't take meetings.
I set them.

581
00:23:27,177 --> 00:23:29,772
And my respect isn't demanded.
It's earned.

582
00:23:29,796 --> 00:23:32,658
That's only two things.
What's "C"?

583
00:23:32,682 --> 00:23:35,111
"C" is for people who show me
they know "A" and "B."

584
00:23:35,135 --> 00:23:38,031
Well, since we're quoting
Jerry Maguire,

585
00:23:38,055 --> 00:23:39,999
all I want is for you
to show me the money.

586
00:23:40,023 --> 00:23:43,336
You just took step number one
towards earning my respect.

587
00:23:43,360 --> 00:23:45,254
And I dig that about you. Great.

588
00:23:45,278 --> 00:23:48,124
Would it be too much trouble for
me to discuss my business now?

589
00:23:48,148 --> 00:23:50,743
Well, I was gonna move on
to Crimson Tide,

590
00:23:50,767 --> 00:23:52,095
but, yeah, go ahead.

591
00:23:52,119 --> 00:23:53,746
Knock yourself out.

592
00:23:53,770 --> 00:23:55,681
You ever hear of a family
called the Winwards?

593
00:23:55,705 --> 00:23:58,184
No. Should I?

594
00:23:58,208 --> 00:23:59,469
In 1950, they were worth
the equivalent

595
00:23:59,493 --> 00:24:01,721
of a billion dollars.

596
00:24:01,745 --> 00:24:04,807
By 1988, one of them owned
a couple of dry cleaners.

597
00:24:04,831 --> 00:24:06,258
And it didn't happen
because they squandered it.

598
00:24:06,282 --> 00:24:08,561
It happened
because they stayed a dinosaur.

599
00:24:08,585 --> 00:24:09,985
You don't want to become
a dinosaur.

600
00:24:10,003 --> 00:24:11,197
No.

601
00:24:11,221 --> 00:24:14,700
I like to think of myself
as a shark.

602
00:24:14,724 --> 00:24:16,536
Keep moving forward or die.

603
00:24:16,560 --> 00:24:18,204
You're talking hostile takeover.

604
00:24:18,228 --> 00:24:20,439
You think I'd be here
if I wasn't?

605
00:24:20,463 --> 00:24:22,575
You just took step number two
towards earning my respect.

606
00:24:22,599 --> 00:24:23,776
What's the company?

607
00:24:23,800 --> 00:24:26,963
Gillis Industries,
and I already own 4.9%.

608
00:24:26,987 --> 00:24:29,465
Logan, we have to end
this conversation right now.

609
00:24:29,489 --> 00:24:30,583
What are you talking about?

610
00:24:30,607 --> 00:24:32,118
I thought I just earned
your respect.

611
00:24:32,142 --> 00:24:33,302
You did, but we have a conflict.

612
00:24:33,326 --> 00:24:34,720
What do you mean,
you have a conflict?

613
00:24:34,744 --> 00:24:36,055
I mean we have a conflict.

614
00:24:36,079 --> 00:24:38,057
What are you gonna do about it?

615
00:24:38,081 --> 00:24:40,176
I'm gonna go and resolve it.

616
00:24:40,200 --> 00:24:43,429
Well, you better do it fast,
because I am in on this.

617
00:24:43,453 --> 00:24:45,648
And that means you're either
with me or against me.

618
00:24:45,672 --> 00:24:49,158
That includes all $1 billion
of my business.

619
00:24:59,386 --> 00:25:01,364
Hey. Prunie?

620
00:25:01,388 --> 00:25:03,783
- What is that?
- It's a prune smoothie.

621
00:25:03,807 --> 00:25:05,284
I invented it myself.

622
00:25:05,308 --> 00:25:06,502
Rain check.

623
00:25:06,526 --> 00:25:10,923
Louis, guess who
stopped by yesterday

624
00:25:10,947 --> 00:25:12,925
for an impromptu meeting
with Jessica and Harvey.

625
00:25:12,949 --> 00:25:14,760
Please tell me
it was Dick Cheney.

626
00:25:14,784 --> 00:25:16,712
Why would you want it
to be Dick Cheney?

627
00:25:16,736 --> 00:25:19,048
Why wouldn't I want it
to be Iron Dick?

628
00:25:19,072 --> 00:25:20,600
Holy shit, I think I know
who you were talking about.

629
00:25:20,624 --> 00:25:22,501
I think you do too.

630
00:25:22,525 --> 00:25:23,853
Is it a certain S.E.C. beast

631
00:25:23,877 --> 00:25:26,522
whose name happens to rhyme
with schmeff schmalone?

632
00:25:26,546 --> 00:25:28,975
Schmess it is,
and schmess it does.

633
00:25:28,999 --> 00:25:30,476
Well, schmuck me.

634
00:25:30,500 --> 00:25:32,278
Louis, we have a problem.

635
00:25:32,302 --> 00:25:34,369
What's the problem?
As if I didn't know.

636
00:25:37,924 --> 00:25:41,737
I just got out of a meeting
with Logan Sanders.

637
00:25:41,761 --> 00:25:43,873
Logan Sanders?

638
00:25:43,897 --> 00:25:46,292
This isn't about... about what?

639
00:25:46,316 --> 00:25:48,360
Then-never mind.

640
00:25:48,384 --> 00:25:49,795
What's the problem?

641
00:25:49,819 --> 00:25:50,796
He wants to go
after the same company

642
00:25:50,820 --> 00:25:52,165
that Mike pitched me first.

643
00:25:52,189 --> 00:25:53,666
So what's the problem?
Mike brought it to you first.

644
00:25:53,690 --> 00:25:55,001
You're obligated
to stick with him.

645
00:25:55,025 --> 00:25:58,004
The problem is Mike formally
put us in review.

646
00:25:58,028 --> 00:26:00,756
Holy shit.
That's why you're coming to me.

647
00:26:00,780 --> 00:26:02,341
You're gonna lose Mike,

648
00:26:02,365 --> 00:26:03,893
and you want to know
if there's any way around it?

649
00:26:03,917 --> 00:26:06,378
- Is there?
- No, Harvey.

650
00:26:06,402 --> 00:26:09,338
I'm sorry, but you're
gonna have to drop Mike.

651
00:26:21,502 --> 00:26:23,103
- What happened with Harvey?
- Nothing.

652
00:26:23,121 --> 00:26:25,683
He had an emergency with Mike.

653
00:26:25,707 --> 00:26:29,520
Fine, but don't you think now
is the time to act for yourself?

654
00:26:29,544 --> 00:26:31,505
No, we have a good plan,
and we're sticking to it.

655
00:26:31,529 --> 00:26:34,241
They're stewing on Malone,
and the more they stew...

656
00:26:34,265 --> 00:26:36,977
The more leverage we have.

657
00:26:37,001 --> 00:26:38,312
Name partner.

658
00:26:38,336 --> 00:26:41,448
And as I've said,
all we need to do is be patient.

659
00:26:41,472 --> 00:26:45,536
Well, patience may be
one of your virtues,

660
00:26:45,560 --> 00:26:47,561
but it is not one of mine.

661
00:26:53,201 --> 00:26:54,494
I didn't want to jinx it.

662
00:26:54,518 --> 00:26:56,987
You didn't.

663
00:27:04,462 --> 00:27:06,607
Katrina, this is
one of the sweetest things

664
00:27:06,631 --> 00:27:07,975
anyone's ever done for me.

665
00:27:07,999 --> 00:27:10,010
I want to make sure
you don't waste your opportunity

666
00:27:10,034 --> 00:27:12,946
to get this.

667
00:27:12,970 --> 00:27:15,972
I promise I won't.

668
00:27:24,599 --> 00:27:26,994
What are you doing here?

669
00:27:27,018 --> 00:27:28,695
We shouldn't be seen together.

670
00:27:28,719 --> 00:27:30,080
You had no problem walking
into my place of business.

671
00:27:30,104 --> 00:27:31,965
Why should I have a problem
walking into yours?

672
00:27:31,989 --> 00:27:34,368
Because unless you're here
to tell me that I have the job,

673
00:27:34,392 --> 00:27:36,837
then you're putting
my position here in jeopardy.

674
00:27:36,861 --> 00:27:38,088
How do you think I felt

675
00:27:38,112 --> 00:27:39,539
when I found the man
that I'm sleeping with

676
00:27:39,563 --> 00:27:42,226
standing in my conference room?

677
00:27:42,250 --> 00:27:43,710
Jessica, will you please
lower your voice?

678
00:27:43,734 --> 00:27:44,711
Not only that,
but you stood there

679
00:27:44,735 --> 00:27:46,313
with a shit-eating grin
on your face

680
00:27:46,337 --> 00:27:48,715
and tried to strong-arm me
into giving you a job.

681
00:27:48,739 --> 00:27:51,735
Are you as turned on
as I am right now?

682
00:27:51,759 --> 00:27:54,521
You're not funny.

683
00:27:54,545 --> 00:27:56,573
Why didn't you come to me first
with this?

684
00:27:56,597 --> 00:27:58,725
Because if I had come to you
with this first,

685
00:27:58,749 --> 00:28:01,195
you would have thought I was
trading on our relationship.

686
00:28:01,219 --> 00:28:02,780
- Aren't you?
- No.

687
00:28:02,804 --> 00:28:03,997
And if we weren't together,

688
00:28:04,021 --> 00:28:05,449
I would have gone
to both of you, all right?

689
00:28:05,473 --> 00:28:06,950
So I went to both of you.

690
00:28:06,974 --> 00:28:09,736
Now it may not
have been perfect, but...

691
00:28:09,760 --> 00:28:11,505
There was no perfect way
of doing it,

692
00:28:11,529 --> 00:28:12,623
unless I hadn't done it.

693
00:28:12,647 --> 00:28:14,291
Now that sounds
pretty perfect to me.

694
00:28:14,315 --> 00:28:15,292
What are you so afraid of?

695
00:28:15,316 --> 00:28:16,593
Do I have to draw you a picture?

696
00:28:16,617 --> 00:28:17,795
I'm not the one
that made up the saying

697
00:28:17,819 --> 00:28:19,263
"you don't shit where you eat."

698
00:28:19,287 --> 00:28:21,849
Am I the shit or the food in
this little painting of yours?

699
00:28:21,873 --> 00:28:23,250
Because if we're just a fling,

700
00:28:23,274 --> 00:28:24,351
then what difference
does it make

701
00:28:24,375 --> 00:28:26,053
whether I work with you or not?

702
00:28:26,077 --> 00:28:27,938
I didn't say we're just a fling.

703
00:28:27,962 --> 00:28:29,807
Then if there really
is a chance for us,

704
00:28:29,831 --> 00:28:31,141
then why not go for both?

705
00:28:31,165 --> 00:28:34,261
Because I've seen what happens
when things go south

706
00:28:34,285 --> 00:28:35,729
between partners,

707
00:28:35,753 --> 00:28:37,698
and I'm not willing to put
my business in jeopardy.

708
00:28:37,722 --> 00:28:38,932
Your business.

709
00:28:38,956 --> 00:28:42,202
Yes, my business.

710
00:28:42,226 --> 00:28:45,122
The one that I have fought
tooth and nail to keep together,

711
00:28:45,146 --> 00:28:48,325
the same business that
you strolled into with a shotgun

712
00:28:48,349 --> 00:28:53,113
and said, "marry me,
or I'll start shooting."

713
00:28:53,137 --> 00:28:55,249
Jess, if you want me
to apologize

714
00:28:55,273 --> 00:28:57,000
for the way that I asked,
then I will.

715
00:28:57,024 --> 00:28:59,753
But I don't ask for things
that I don't want.

716
00:28:59,777 --> 00:29:02,339
And what I want is to work
at Pearson Specter

717
00:29:02,363 --> 00:29:05,125
and to keep seeing you.

718
00:29:05,149 --> 00:29:09,263
Those two things
are not both gonna happen.

719
00:29:09,287 --> 00:29:11,148
Then I guess you have to decide

720
00:29:11,172 --> 00:29:12,850
what's more important to you...

721
00:29:12,874 --> 00:29:17,043
What we have or what you have.

722
00:29:23,518 --> 00:29:24,978
Hey, Mike.

723
00:29:25,002 --> 00:29:26,246
There's another prospect here
to see you,

724
00:29:26,270 --> 00:29:27,915
but he's late,
and his tie's too fat.

725
00:29:27,939 --> 00:29:29,032
Should I let him in?

726
00:29:29,056 --> 00:29:30,650
You tell her to say
all that garbage?

727
00:29:30,674 --> 00:29:32,319
He didn't need to,
Johnnie fat tie.

728
00:29:32,343 --> 00:29:34,254
Yeah, I guess I have time
for one more meeting.

729
00:29:34,278 --> 00:29:35,956
- Mike, I need to talk to you.
- Although, I'm sorry, sir.

730
00:29:35,980 --> 00:29:38,175
You've missed the pastries.
I can call you some up.

731
00:29:38,199 --> 00:29:39,676
Listen to me.

732
00:29:39,700 --> 00:29:41,378
I came down here
because I wanted to tell you

733
00:29:41,402 --> 00:29:43,297
if you want to run
through this wall,

734
00:29:43,321 --> 00:29:44,298
I'm ready to run through it
with you.

735
00:29:44,322 --> 00:29:45,299
Good.

736
00:29:45,323 --> 00:29:47,968
But I can't.

737
00:29:47,992 --> 00:29:48,969
What?

738
00:29:48,993 --> 00:29:50,187
What I can do is tell you

739
00:29:50,211 --> 00:29:51,522
I'm ready
to run through another one.

740
00:29:51,546 --> 00:29:52,973
What the hell
are you talking about?

741
00:29:52,997 --> 00:29:55,309
- We have a conflict.
- Bullshit.

742
00:29:55,333 --> 00:29:57,561
Who is it? It's not bullshit.

743
00:29:57,585 --> 00:29:58,645
Then who is it?

744
00:29:58,669 --> 00:29:59,980
You know I can't tell you that.

745
00:30:00,004 --> 00:30:01,014
No, what I know
is that it's very convenient

746
00:30:01,038 --> 00:30:02,449
that you suddenly
have a conflict

747
00:30:02,473 --> 00:30:04,902
the day after you tell me
that my idea isn't good enough.

748
00:30:04,926 --> 00:30:06,286
I don't find it convenient
at all,

749
00:30:06,310 --> 00:30:07,454
but you put us in review,

750
00:30:07,478 --> 00:30:09,323
and now I have to go
with the other client.

751
00:30:09,347 --> 00:30:11,358
I put you in review because
you refused to get on board.

752
00:30:11,382 --> 00:30:12,543
And I just told you,

753
00:30:12,567 --> 00:30:14,027
I want to run
through another wall with you,

754
00:30:14,051 --> 00:30:16,914
and we still can
if you drop this.

755
00:30:16,938 --> 00:30:19,199
And why should I be the one
to drop it?

756
00:30:19,223 --> 00:30:22,169
Because they're not going to,
and I have to stick with them.

757
00:30:22,193 --> 00:30:23,804
And I'm telling you,
you're gonna lose.

758
00:30:23,828 --> 00:30:24,888
What, because
you're on the other side?

759
00:30:24,912 --> 00:30:26,206
Because their plan is better.

760
00:30:26,230 --> 00:30:27,558
Says
the professional bullshit-er

761
00:30:27,582 --> 00:30:30,210
who has a brand-new vested
interest in me bowing out.

762
00:30:30,234 --> 00:30:32,045
I'm gonna let that go.

763
00:30:32,069 --> 00:30:33,514
But if you don't let this go,

764
00:30:33,538 --> 00:30:38,652
I can't represent you
on anything until it's over.

765
00:30:38,676 --> 00:30:42,879
Then I guess we're done here.

766
00:30:59,597 --> 00:31:02,009
You cook?

767
00:31:02,033 --> 00:31:04,177
You come home to this
in your kitchen,

768
00:31:04,201 --> 00:31:06,380
and that's what you're going
to ask me?

769
00:31:06,404 --> 00:31:07,548
Well, I was gonna ask you

770
00:31:07,572 --> 00:31:08,882
how the hell you got
into my apartment,

771
00:31:08,906 --> 00:31:11,969
but I knew
you weren't gonna tell me.

772
00:31:11,993 --> 00:31:13,270
Do you remember when you told me

773
00:31:13,294 --> 00:31:16,329
I should think about taking
some morning meetings?

774
00:31:19,050 --> 00:31:21,278
I can't say that
it's never crossed my mind,

775
00:31:21,302 --> 00:31:22,696
but you really think
it's a good idea...

776
00:31:22,720 --> 00:31:23,780
Jeff Malone.

777
00:31:23,804 --> 00:31:26,766
Well, he's not my type.

778
00:31:26,790 --> 00:31:27,868
You gotta be kidding me.

779
00:31:27,892 --> 00:31:29,102
Why didn't you tell me
yesterday?

780
00:31:29,126 --> 00:31:30,704
Because I wasn't gonna
hire him yesterday,

781
00:31:30,728 --> 00:31:32,539
so it was none of your business.

782
00:31:32,563 --> 00:31:35,609
But today I might, so now it is.

783
00:31:35,633 --> 00:31:37,794
And you want to know
how I feel about it.

784
00:31:37,818 --> 00:31:39,162
You're my partner.

785
00:31:39,186 --> 00:31:41,415
Well, I already told you
how I feel about hiring him.

786
00:31:41,439 --> 00:31:42,466
This doesn't change that.

787
00:31:42,490 --> 00:31:45,636
Good to know.

788
00:31:45,660 --> 00:31:50,173
Seems like something else
is on your mind.

789
00:31:50,197 --> 00:31:52,759
He doesn't
just want to work together.

790
00:31:52,783 --> 00:31:55,012
He wants us
to keep seeing each other.

791
00:31:55,036 --> 00:31:57,014
And you don't want to risk
the one to have the other.

792
00:31:57,038 --> 00:32:00,150
No. I don't.

793
00:32:00,174 --> 00:32:01,685
I've been there.

794
00:32:01,709 --> 00:32:03,320
I know.

795
00:32:03,344 --> 00:32:08,525
Then you need to figure out
which is more important.

796
00:32:08,549 --> 00:32:11,801
I guess I do.

797
00:32:14,639 --> 00:32:17,317
So you two have, um...

798
00:32:17,341 --> 00:32:19,870
Yes.

799
00:32:19,894 --> 00:32:22,839
So he's seen you naked?

800
00:32:22,863 --> 00:32:25,899
That's usually
how these things work.

801
00:32:29,570 --> 00:32:34,518
Are you picturing me naked
right now?

802
00:32:34,542 --> 00:32:36,503
Maybe.

803
00:32:36,527 --> 00:32:38,271
Yes.

804
00:32:38,295 --> 00:32:40,880
Go wash your hands.

805
00:32:45,035 --> 00:32:47,364
Don't spend too much time
in that bathroom.

806
00:32:47,388 --> 00:32:49,199
Let me get this straight.

807
00:32:49,223 --> 00:32:50,901
You come to me
with a killer idea,

808
00:32:50,925 --> 00:32:52,486
and all of a sudden
you don't want to do it anymore

809
00:32:52,510 --> 00:32:54,020
'cause you lost your BFF?

810
00:32:54,044 --> 00:32:56,657
I don't want to do it because
it's not a killer idea anymore.

811
00:32:56,681 --> 00:32:58,825
- Why the hell not?
- Because Harvey has a conflict,

812
00:32:58,849 --> 00:33:00,911
which means somebody already
has a dog in the fight.

813
00:33:00,935 --> 00:33:02,379
- Who gives a shit?
- I do.

814
00:33:02,403 --> 00:33:05,382
'Cause whoever it is
is already buying shares.

815
00:33:05,406 --> 00:33:06,967
You didn't come in here
to give up.

816
00:33:06,991 --> 00:33:08,552
You came in here
to get my money.

817
00:33:08,576 --> 00:33:09,720
You're damn right I did.

818
00:33:09,744 --> 00:33:11,555
I give you my money,
now I have downside.

819
00:33:11,579 --> 00:33:13,056
Jonathan, look.

820
00:33:13,080 --> 00:33:15,509
You said you wanted a home run.

821
00:33:15,533 --> 00:33:16,710
You gotta pull out
your checkbook,

822
00:33:16,734 --> 00:33:18,055
'cause I can't compete
without it.

823
00:33:18,068 --> 00:33:19,896
- You could yesterday.
- Now it's today.

824
00:33:19,920 --> 00:33:21,398
And you're still going in there

825
00:33:21,422 --> 00:33:22,599
another banker in a suit,

826
00:33:22,623 --> 00:33:25,318
hoping he'll trust you
based on nothing.

827
00:33:25,342 --> 00:33:29,106
I've got more than nothing.

828
00:33:29,130 --> 00:33:31,558
What the hell
are you talking about?

829
00:33:31,582 --> 00:33:33,360
Trust me.

830
00:33:33,384 --> 00:33:35,829
I did my homework.

831
00:33:35,853 --> 00:33:37,487
Batter up.

832
00:33:43,967 --> 00:33:45,224
What are you doing here?

833
00:33:45,369 --> 00:33:46,596
I said I'd tell you

834
00:33:46,620 --> 00:33:47,680
what we were gonna do
with your centers

835
00:33:47,704 --> 00:33:49,015
five seconds after we closed.

836
00:33:49,039 --> 00:33:51,634
When did we close?

837
00:33:51,658 --> 00:33:53,736
About three seconds ago.

838
00:33:53,760 --> 00:33:56,012
I guess we better hurry.

839
00:33:58,098 --> 00:34:00,743
All right, what's going
to happen to my employees?

840
00:34:00,767 --> 00:34:02,478
We're going to sell
your distribution centers

841
00:34:02,502 --> 00:34:04,664
to a pharmaceutical company

842
00:34:04,688 --> 00:34:06,249
as distribution centers.

843
00:34:06,273 --> 00:34:07,483
They use your workers.

844
00:34:07,507 --> 00:34:10,286
They hit the ground running.
Win-win.

845
00:34:10,310 --> 00:34:12,611
You're a man of your word.

846
00:34:14,147 --> 00:34:17,710
But that's not why you're here.

847
00:34:17,734 --> 00:34:20,346
No, it isn't.

848
00:34:20,370 --> 00:34:22,632
I'm not interested
in selling my business.

849
00:34:22,656 --> 00:34:24,851
I know that, because I know why

850
00:34:24,875 --> 00:34:26,636
you've thrown your whole life
into this company

851
00:34:26,660 --> 00:34:29,222
and why you chose the movie
business in the first place.

852
00:34:29,246 --> 00:34:31,357
What's your point?

853
00:34:31,381 --> 00:34:34,310
Phillip.

854
00:34:34,334 --> 00:34:36,529
Your son.

855
00:34:36,553 --> 00:34:39,148
You loved watching movies
together.

856
00:34:39,172 --> 00:34:40,867
That's why you started
this company

857
00:34:40,891 --> 00:34:42,852
and why you won't let go
of what it's become

858
00:34:42,876 --> 00:34:43,953
for any amount of money.

859
00:34:43,977 --> 00:34:46,289
How do you know that?

860
00:34:46,313 --> 00:34:48,458
I told you.

861
00:34:48,482 --> 00:34:51,484
I do my homework.

862
00:34:53,854 --> 00:34:55,164
You lost him,

863
00:34:55,188 --> 00:34:56,716
and you needed an outlet,

864
00:34:56,740 --> 00:35:01,137
and that's what this company
is to you now...

865
00:35:01,161 --> 00:35:02,138
Your family.

866
00:35:02,162 --> 00:35:04,424
I told you, I'm not selling.

867
00:35:04,448 --> 00:35:06,309
And I told you,
they're coming after you

868
00:35:06,333 --> 00:35:08,428
whether you like it or not.

869
00:35:08,452 --> 00:35:10,379
And the difference
between me and them

870
00:35:10,403 --> 00:35:11,881
is they want to tear
your company apart,

871
00:35:11,905 --> 00:35:13,149
and I want to keep it together.

872
00:35:13,173 --> 00:35:15,601
You don't have the resources
to do that.

873
00:35:15,625 --> 00:35:17,737
Yes.

874
00:35:17,761 --> 00:35:21,056
I do.

875
00:35:21,080 --> 00:35:23,109
As of an hour ago,
I started investing.

876
00:35:23,133 --> 00:35:27,113
So by this time next week,
I will own 4.9%.

877
00:35:27,137 --> 00:35:29,532
I didn't have to tell you that.

878
00:35:29,556 --> 00:35:33,275
And that's supposed
to make me trust you?

879
00:35:36,596 --> 00:35:41,076
I lost both of my parents
when I was 11 years old,

880
00:35:41,100 --> 00:35:45,181
so I know a little something
about needing family.

881
00:35:45,205 --> 00:35:48,434
Walter...

882
00:35:48,458 --> 00:35:51,637
I can't guarantee you we'll win,

883
00:35:51,661 --> 00:35:54,797
but I can guarantee you
that I will never sell you out.

884
00:35:58,385 --> 00:35:59,969
All right, I'm in.

885
00:36:06,810 --> 00:36:08,821
Listen, Zane,
I want that goddamn filing

886
00:36:08,845 --> 00:36:10,573
on my desk nine seconds ago,
or you can forget

887
00:36:10,597 --> 00:36:11,707
you ever worked here.

888
00:36:11,731 --> 00:36:13,042
Now excuse me.

889
00:36:13,066 --> 00:36:14,610
I've got to go be a dick
to someone.

890
00:36:14,634 --> 00:36:16,685
Sit down.

891
00:36:19,072 --> 00:36:20,883
Is this about you and Mike?

892
00:36:20,907 --> 00:36:23,285
Listen to me...
This is gonna be a street fight,

893
00:36:23,309 --> 00:36:26,139
and there's only gonna be
one man standing when it's over.

894
00:36:26,163 --> 00:36:27,890
So I'm only gonna
ask you this once.

895
00:36:27,914 --> 00:36:28,891
You don't need to.

896
00:36:28,915 --> 00:36:31,394
I don't want out. I want in.

897
00:36:31,418 --> 00:36:33,479
And when I said, "you want me
to send a message to Mike?"

898
00:36:33,503 --> 00:36:34,730
I meant it.

899
00:36:34,754 --> 00:36:36,732
I was just gonna ask
if you were comfortable

900
00:36:36,756 --> 00:36:38,017
getting me coffee
in the mornings.

901
00:36:38,041 --> 00:36:40,135
I'm serious.

902
00:36:40,159 --> 00:36:42,321
I didn't back down
from a fight with my dad,

903
00:36:42,345 --> 00:36:44,857
and I'm not going to back down
from one with Mike.

904
00:36:44,881 --> 00:36:47,360
Good.

905
00:36:47,384 --> 00:36:49,695
Now, I actually am
gonna get coffee.

906
00:36:49,719 --> 00:36:51,581
Great.
One sugar, a splash of cream,

907
00:36:51,605 --> 00:36:54,116
and don't skimp on the hazelnut.

908
00:36:54,140 --> 00:36:56,419
Too soon.

909
00:36:56,443 --> 00:36:58,538
Instead of failing
to be charming,

910
00:36:58,562 --> 00:37:00,590
why don't you do
something useful and get moving

911
00:37:00,614 --> 00:37:02,925
on drawing up a tender offer
for Logan Sanders?

912
00:37:02,949 --> 00:37:05,294
Logan? No, you mean Max Sanders.

913
00:37:05,318 --> 00:37:07,162
I keep forgetting that you're
in law school half the time.

914
00:37:07,186 --> 00:37:08,664
Max is retired.

915
00:37:08,688 --> 00:37:11,624
It's Logan's show now.

916
00:37:17,047 --> 00:37:18,191
You wanted to see me?

917
00:37:18,215 --> 00:37:20,443
We need to move up our timeline.

918
00:37:20,467 --> 00:37:22,945
Well, I'm buying shares
as fast as I can.

919
00:37:22,969 --> 00:37:24,179
I'm talking
about a tender offer.

920
00:37:24,203 --> 00:37:25,848
The plan is shock and awe.

921
00:37:25,872 --> 00:37:27,733
If we rush a tender offer,
we won't have enough leverage

922
00:37:27,757 --> 00:37:29,202
to force people to vote with us.

923
00:37:29,226 --> 00:37:30,319
It's fine to have shock and awe

924
00:37:30,343 --> 00:37:31,487
when you're the only one
in the game,

925
00:37:31,511 --> 00:37:32,521
but Walter Gillis
knows we're coming,

926
00:37:32,545 --> 00:37:35,374
and he got himself an ally.

927
00:37:35,398 --> 00:37:36,459
How do you know that?

928
00:37:36,483 --> 00:37:38,578
Because I do.

929
00:37:38,602 --> 00:37:40,329
Your conflict... who is it?

930
00:37:40,353 --> 00:37:43,049
- I can't talk about it.
- Well, when the hell can you?

931
00:37:43,073 --> 00:37:45,658
In another hour.

932
00:37:49,496 --> 00:37:52,041
You have it for me?

933
00:37:52,065 --> 00:37:54,209
Harvey, you know you can still
get out of this if you want to.

934
00:37:54,233 --> 00:37:56,512
Mike's not gonna sign that thing
if you tell him not to.

935
00:37:56,536 --> 00:37:57,563
It's too late for that.

936
00:37:57,587 --> 00:37:59,315
Oh, my God.

937
00:37:59,339 --> 00:38:01,067
Hey, just the woman
I wanted to see.

938
00:38:01,091 --> 00:38:02,652
Donna, would you happen to have
the measurements

939
00:38:02,676 --> 00:38:03,653
to Hardman's old office?

940
00:38:03,677 --> 00:38:04,687
Louis, get out of my way.

941
00:38:04,711 --> 00:38:07,156
Whoa. What's going on, Donna?

942
00:38:07,180 --> 00:38:09,325
What's going on?

943
00:38:09,349 --> 00:38:10,576
That bullshit Harvey told you

944
00:38:10,600 --> 00:38:12,828
about waiting
for the girl to call,

945
00:38:12,852 --> 00:38:14,413
it's bullshit.

946
00:38:14,437 --> 00:38:17,589
He waited,
and now it's too late.

947
00:38:24,197 --> 00:38:25,791
Change of plans.
Cancel anything you have.

948
00:38:25,815 --> 00:38:26,876
We're staying here all night.
What for?

949
00:38:26,900 --> 00:38:28,210
The S.E.C.'s coming,

950
00:38:28,234 --> 00:38:29,629
Jessica's hiring one person
to fight 'em,

951
00:38:29,653 --> 00:38:30,880
and first thing tomorrow,

952
00:38:30,904 --> 00:38:32,505
we need to convince her
that person's me.

953
00:38:34,541 --> 00:38:36,469
Hey.

954
00:38:36,493 --> 00:38:38,744
I see you have the movies.
Mmhmm.

955
00:38:40,880 --> 00:38:42,257
I guess that means
you've decided

956
00:38:42,281 --> 00:38:44,310
which relationship
you want us to have.

957
00:38:44,334 --> 00:38:47,563
I have.

958
00:38:47,587 --> 00:38:50,506
But it's not
what you might think.

959
00:38:53,727 --> 00:38:56,205
If you still want the job,

960
00:38:56,229 --> 00:38:58,931
it starts tomorrow.

961
00:39:00,934 --> 00:39:04,297
I do.

962
00:39:04,321 --> 00:39:07,950
Then tonight is our last night.

963
00:39:07,974 --> 00:39:10,452
We'll see if you still
think that in four hours.

964
00:39:10,476 --> 00:39:12,254
Oh, you want to go three times?

965
00:39:12,278 --> 00:39:14,223
Oh, I was including
one of the movies.

966
00:39:14,247 --> 00:39:17,116
- No.
- No.

967
00:39:36,970 --> 00:39:38,647
Finally got yourself an office.

968
00:39:38,671 --> 00:39:42,168
Maybe you forgot,
but I had an office before.

969
00:39:42,192 --> 00:39:43,586
I just gave it back.

970
00:39:43,610 --> 00:39:46,822
I remember,
as a show of loyalty.

971
00:39:46,846 --> 00:39:49,732
Yeah, well, that was then.
This is now.

972
00:39:53,620 --> 00:39:55,831
What you got there, Harvey?

973
00:39:55,855 --> 00:39:57,133
You think you could meet
with Walter Gillis

974
00:39:57,157 --> 00:39:58,684
and I wouldn't find out?

975
00:39:58,708 --> 00:40:00,436
No, I knew you'd find out.

976
00:40:00,460 --> 00:40:03,606
I just didn't care.

977
00:40:03,630 --> 00:40:05,474
Then maybe you won't mind
signing this.

978
00:40:05,498 --> 00:40:08,527
Let me guess.

979
00:40:08,551 --> 00:40:10,696
You want me to waive
the conflict that you still have

980
00:40:10,720 --> 00:40:12,398
after hearing my plan first.

981
00:40:12,422 --> 00:40:15,724
I sure didn't come here
to see your shit-y office.

982
00:40:17,727 --> 00:40:18,821
Aren't you supposed to be nice

983
00:40:18,845 --> 00:40:20,656
to the person
you need something from?

984
00:40:20,680 --> 00:40:23,492
They're still coming
whether you sign it or not.

985
00:40:23,516 --> 00:40:28,381
If I don't sign it,
they won't be coming with you.

986
00:40:28,405 --> 00:40:30,299
True.

987
00:40:30,323 --> 00:40:33,502
Of course, if you don't sign it,

988
00:40:33,526 --> 00:40:36,756
it may cause some people to say
you're afraid of me.

989
00:40:36,780 --> 00:40:39,842
And by "some people," I mean me.

990
00:40:39,866 --> 00:40:41,594
Of course, if I sign it
just because you said that,

991
00:40:41,618 --> 00:40:44,814
then it might cause some people
to say you baited me.

992
00:40:44,838 --> 00:40:47,600
But I knew you were coming

993
00:40:47,624 --> 00:40:50,319
the second I went to see
Walter Gillis,

994
00:40:50,343 --> 00:40:52,321
so...

995
00:40:52,345 --> 00:40:56,391
I went ahead
and signed one for you.

996
00:40:56,415 --> 00:40:59,412
- I guess it's on.
- I guess it is.

997
00:40:59,436 --> 00:41:02,164
You think we need to lay out
some ground rules?

998
00:41:02,188 --> 00:41:03,922
Rules? In a knife fight?

999
00:41:05,358 --> 00:41:07,536
I guess somebody ought to yell,
"one, two, three, go."

1000
00:41:07,560 --> 00:41:10,762
One, two, three, go.

1001
00:41:12,431 --> 00:41:14,293
You know, usually
when someone gets a new office,

1002
00:41:14,317 --> 00:41:17,412
you're supposed to bring them
something, right?

1003
00:41:17,436 --> 00:41:21,517
Like an orchid or something?

1004
00:41:21,541 --> 00:41:23,185
No?

1005
00:41:23,209 --> 00:41:26,128
Nothing?

1006
00:41:34,337 --> 00:41:36,198
You signed the waiver,
didn't you?

1007
00:41:36,222 --> 00:41:37,783
You know I did.

1008
00:41:37,807 --> 00:41:40,402
Not gonna back down from Harvey.
Mm.

1009
00:41:40,426 --> 00:41:44,990
And I suppose you got Gillis
on board with your plan?

1010
00:41:45,014 --> 00:41:49,211
I wouldn't have needed
to sign the waiver if I didn't.

1011
00:41:49,235 --> 00:41:50,663
Hey.

1012
00:41:50,687 --> 00:41:53,632
Hey, it's gonna be okay.

1013
00:41:53,656 --> 00:41:54,783
This thing
between me and Harvey...

1014
00:41:54,807 --> 00:41:56,919
It doesn't have to affect us.

1015
00:41:56,943 --> 00:42:00,723
We won't let it.

1016
00:42:00,747 --> 00:42:02,725
I didn't know that Logan Sanders

1017
00:42:02,749 --> 00:42:05,460
took over his father's company
until today.

1018
00:42:05,484 --> 00:42:07,229
What does that have to do
with anything?

1019
00:42:07,253 --> 00:42:10,839
- He's Harvey's client.
- Yeah, so?

1020
00:42:12,926 --> 00:42:16,972
Do you remember
when I told you that I...

1021
00:42:16,996 --> 00:42:20,142
That I once had an affair
with a married man?

1022
00:42:20,166 --> 00:42:23,469
It was him.

1023
00:42:23,493 --> 00:42:28,493
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man

