1
00:00:02,755 --> 00:00:05,169
So I sign this and the bribery
allegations are gone?

2
00:00:05,193 --> 00:00:06,838
And no one ever knows a thing.

3
00:00:06,863 --> 00:00:09,544
You never let me tell you
what the money was for.

4
00:00:09,569 --> 00:00:11,749
You didn't listen to me
when I told you I don't care.

5
00:00:11,773 --> 00:00:13,585
Well, do you care
that after Mike grilled me,

6
00:00:13,610 --> 00:00:16,358
I was so impressed with him that
I wonder why I'd forgotten him?

7
00:00:16,383 --> 00:00:21,000
But I couldn't find any record
of him ever being in my class.

8
00:00:21,024 --> 00:00:23,104
Just like they're not gonna
find any record of you

9
00:00:23,129 --> 00:00:24,975
accepting a bribe
from a student.

10
00:00:25,000 --> 00:00:27,737
Jessica, your secret
is safe with me.

11
00:00:28,873 --> 00:00:30,819
I told him you found out

12
00:00:30,844 --> 00:00:33,591
that I covered up
Daniel Hardman's embezzlement.

13
00:00:33,616 --> 00:00:35,830
And now you want me to protect
another one of your secrets.

14
00:00:35,854 --> 00:00:38,068
It's the same secret, Louis,

15
00:00:38,093 --> 00:00:40,038
and you have just as much
invested in it as I do.

16
00:00:40,063 --> 00:00:42,276
You want me to kiss the ring,
Louis, after what you did?

17
00:00:42,300 --> 00:00:43,679
You're damn right I do,

18
00:00:43,703 --> 00:00:45,615
because I don't care
how it got up there.

19
00:00:45,640 --> 00:00:50,114
My name is on that wall
whether you like it or not.

20
00:00:59,634 --> 00:01:07,642
♪

21
00:01:08,787 --> 00:01:11,333
- Hey.
- Hey.

22
00:01:11,357 --> 00:01:13,537
What do you think of this tie?

23
00:01:13,562 --> 00:01:15,274
I think...

24
00:01:15,298 --> 00:01:18,513
I want to tie you up with it.

25
00:01:18,538 --> 00:01:24,425
Really?
And what brought that on?

26
00:01:24,450 --> 00:01:26,898
Okay, well,

27
00:01:26,922 --> 00:01:30,104
then let's make

28
00:01:30,128 --> 00:01:33,243
that happen.

29
00:01:33,267 --> 00:01:34,712
Wait.

30
00:01:34,737 --> 00:01:35,916
Is this to do things to me

31
00:01:35,940 --> 00:01:37,518
or just to get control
of the remote?

32
00:01:37,543 --> 00:01:39,155
Why can't it be both?

33
00:01:39,179 --> 00:01:41,859
Rachel, if you think I'm gonna
let you watch Game of Thrones

34
00:01:41,884 --> 00:01:43,429
while sexually dominating me,

35
00:01:43,454 --> 00:01:46,459
then you are absolutely right.

36
00:01:48,998 --> 00:01:52,113
Seriously, what's got you
feeling so good?

37
00:01:52,138 --> 00:01:53,550
Oh, it just feels like
such a weight off

38
00:01:53,574 --> 00:01:54,819
now that Louis doesn't...

39
00:01:54,843 --> 00:01:56,488
- Despise me?
- Mm-hmm.

40
00:01:56,513 --> 00:01:58,583
Ah, you know what else
would feel like a weight off?

41
00:02:01,056 --> 00:02:03,103
- Oh...
- No. No, no, no.

42
00:02:03,127 --> 00:02:04,939
Nobody ever calls
the landline except my parents.

43
00:02:04,963 --> 00:02:06,608
- What if something's wrong?
- It's fine.

44
00:02:06,633 --> 00:02:07,644
Mike.

45
00:02:07,668 --> 00:02:10,015
Okay, okay, okay.

46
00:02:10,040 --> 00:02:11,419
Hello.

47
00:02:11,443 --> 00:02:13,412
Yeah, this is him.

48
00:02:16,052 --> 00:02:18,633
Yeah, of course
I can come meet you.

49
00:02:18,657 --> 00:02:21,906
Can I ask what this is... hello?

50
00:02:21,931 --> 00:02:22,975
Who was it?

51
00:02:22,999 --> 00:02:24,445
Professor Gerard.

52
00:02:24,469 --> 00:02:26,014
He wants me to go meet him.

53
00:02:26,039 --> 00:02:27,250
Did he say what it was about?

54
00:02:27,274 --> 00:02:28,887
No, he hung up.

55
00:02:28,912 --> 00:02:30,490
When does he want you
to meet him?

56
00:02:30,514 --> 00:02:31,649
Right now.

57
00:02:34,055 --> 00:02:38,338
- Professor Gerard.
- Thanks for coming.

58
00:02:38,362 --> 00:02:40,274
I wouldn't have bothered you
if it wasn't important.

59
00:02:40,299 --> 00:02:42,313
It's not a problem.
What can I help you with?

60
00:02:42,337 --> 00:02:44,082
It's not me.

61
00:02:44,107 --> 00:02:47,457
A former employee at
Liberty Rail reached out to me.

62
00:02:47,481 --> 00:02:49,059
He claims he was fired
because he knows

63
00:02:49,084 --> 00:02:50,896
the real reason for the crash.

64
00:02:50,921 --> 00:02:53,802
And what was the real reason?

65
00:02:53,827 --> 00:02:55,172
He wouldn't tell me.

66
00:02:55,196 --> 00:02:56,374
Well, what did he tell you?

67
00:02:56,398 --> 00:02:58,612
Enough for me to know
it would be unethical

68
00:02:58,637 --> 00:03:02,019
if somebody didn't
look into this.

69
00:03:02,043 --> 00:03:05,225
But you can't, so you want me
to get Harvey to.

70
00:03:05,249 --> 00:03:07,497
Well, you convinced him
to look into my case

71
00:03:07,522 --> 00:03:08,733
when he didn't want to,
didn't you?

72
00:03:08,757 --> 00:03:11,104
This is different.
We don't take cases like this.

73
00:03:11,128 --> 00:03:14,143
Maybe,

74
00:03:14,167 --> 00:03:17,115
but I believe a man
who can convince Harvey

75
00:03:17,140 --> 00:03:18,985
to hire someone
who never went to law school

76
00:03:19,010 --> 00:03:21,847
could convince him
to make an exception for this.

77
00:03:23,819 --> 00:03:26,534
What?

78
00:03:26,559 --> 00:03:28,394
He didn't tell you I know.

79
00:03:30,934 --> 00:03:32,179
No, he didn't.

80
00:03:32,204 --> 00:03:34,507
Well, I do.

81
00:03:36,412 --> 00:03:40,328
But what I'm asking you to do
and me knowing

82
00:03:40,353 --> 00:03:42,489
have nothing
to do with each other.

83
00:03:45,262 --> 00:03:46,707
I appreciate that.

84
00:03:46,731 --> 00:03:49,813
Does that mean that you're
gonna tell him to take the case?

85
00:03:49,837 --> 00:03:51,406
I have a better idea.

86
00:03:56,952 --> 00:03:58,498
Got a second?

87
00:03:58,522 --> 00:04:00,768
Of course. What do you need?

88
00:04:00,792 --> 00:04:03,597
I'd like you to sign off
on my vacation request.

89
00:04:05,937 --> 00:04:07,682
Paris.

90
00:04:07,706 --> 00:04:09,284
I've never heard you
talk about Paris.

91
00:04:09,309 --> 00:04:12,726
No, but I have heard you
talk about it,

92
00:04:12,751 --> 00:04:14,719
which is why I'm taking you.

93
00:04:15,923 --> 00:04:18,303
Are you asking me
to go to Paris with you?

94
00:04:18,327 --> 00:04:19,572
I believe I just did.

95
00:04:19,596 --> 00:04:20,642
Jeff, do you have any idea

96
00:04:20,667 --> 00:04:22,078
how much is on my plate
right now?

97
00:04:22,102 --> 00:04:23,247
Actually, I do, all of which

98
00:04:23,271 --> 00:04:25,584
Harvey has agreed to cover.

99
00:04:25,609 --> 00:04:27,488
You went to Harvey with this.

100
00:04:27,512 --> 00:04:28,924
Well, I would have
come to you first,

101
00:04:28,949 --> 00:04:31,820
but then it really
wouldn't be a surprise.

102
00:04:34,225 --> 00:04:35,804
I'll think about it.

103
00:04:35,829 --> 00:04:37,909
Take all the time you need.

104
00:04:37,933 --> 00:04:39,278
But in the meantime,

105
00:04:39,302 --> 00:04:42,249
I'll be thinking about
who else around here I can take.

106
00:04:42,274 --> 00:04:43,820
Really?

107
00:04:43,845 --> 00:04:45,992
Well, you're awfully
sure of yourself.

108
00:04:46,016 --> 00:04:48,596
You think I haven't seen
the way Norma looks at me?

109
00:04:48,621 --> 00:04:50,489
Calls me the Black Stallion.

110
00:04:56,837 --> 00:04:58,639
Norma.

111
00:05:01,880 --> 00:05:02,891
Taking a case.

112
00:05:02,915 --> 00:05:04,294
What kind of case?

113
00:05:04,319 --> 00:05:05,598
What does it matter?

114
00:05:05,622 --> 00:05:07,500
Because you wouldn't be
announcing it like that

115
00:05:07,525 --> 00:05:08,970
if there wasn't something wrong.

116
00:05:08,994 --> 00:05:11,976
It's a case that came
from Professor Gerard.

117
00:05:12,000 --> 00:05:13,078
What?

118
00:05:13,102 --> 00:05:14,348
A man who used to work
at Liberty Rail

119
00:05:14,373 --> 00:05:16,385
says the real cause
of the crash was covered up.

120
00:05:16,409 --> 00:05:17,687
Then refer him to a firm

121
00:05:17,711 --> 00:05:19,457
that takes whistle-blower cases,
because we don't.

122
00:05:19,482 --> 00:05:20,560
Yeah, I'm not gonna do that.

123
00:05:20,584 --> 00:05:22,095
Then don't, but there's a reason

124
00:05:22,120 --> 00:05:24,434
lawyers who take whistle-blower
cases don't work here,

125
00:05:24,458 --> 00:05:25,936
and it's because corporations

126
00:05:25,960 --> 00:05:27,706
don't appreciate
shakedown artists.

127
00:05:27,731 --> 00:05:29,092
And what if
this isn't a shakedown?

128
00:05:29,101 --> 00:05:30,246
And how do you know it isn't?

129
00:05:30,270 --> 00:05:31,882
What I know is that
innocent people died...

130
00:05:31,906 --> 00:05:34,420
Mothers and fathers
and sons and daughters...

131
00:05:34,445 --> 00:05:36,792
And if somebody's covering up
why that happened

132
00:05:36,816 --> 00:05:38,361
and I can stop it,
then I'm going to.

133
00:05:38,386 --> 00:05:39,765
And I said you're not.

134
00:05:39,789 --> 00:05:41,668
Well, but you also said
that Professor Gerard

135
00:05:41,693 --> 00:05:43,494
didn't know my secret.

136
00:05:44,865 --> 00:05:47,145
Harvey, I know,
I know he'll never tell anyone,

137
00:05:47,169 --> 00:05:49,350
but someday, someone's
gonna find out who will,

138
00:05:49,374 --> 00:05:50,375
and I'll be done.

139
00:05:50,376 --> 00:05:51,421
Mike, he's not...

140
00:05:51,445 --> 00:05:53,156
Harvey, I got
into this whole thing

141
00:05:53,181 --> 00:05:56,464
so that I could try
to help people,

142
00:05:56,488 --> 00:05:58,200
and I don't know
how much time I have left,

143
00:05:58,225 --> 00:06:02,409
so please,

144
00:06:02,433 --> 00:06:05,438
let me try
and help these people.

145
00:06:09,213 --> 00:06:10,792
Then you better make damn sure

146
00:06:10,817 --> 00:06:13,821
this whistle-blower
isn't full of sh...

147
00:06:19,333 --> 00:06:22,782
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪

148
00:06:22,807 --> 00:06:26,257
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪

149
00:06:26,281 --> 00:06:29,429
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪

150
00:06:29,454 --> 00:06:32,969
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪

151
00:06:32,993 --> 00:06:36,109
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪

152
00:06:36,133 --> 00:06:40,117
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪

153
00:06:40,141 --> 00:06:41,575
♪ All right

154
00:06:41,577 --> 00:06:43,149
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪

155
00:06:43,150 --> 00:06:47,154
♪ Suits 4x14 ♪ Derailed Original
Air Date on February 18, 2015

156
00:06:47,155 --> 00:06:48,534
♪ The greenback boogie

157
00:06:48,536 --> 00:06:52,540
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man.

158
00:06:52,541 --> 00:06:53,953
Bonjour, madame.

159
00:06:53,977 --> 00:06:56,258
Oh, I'm so glad you started
with that French bullshit,

160
00:06:56,283 --> 00:06:57,927
because that's what
I want to talk to you about.

161
00:06:57,951 --> 00:06:59,230
I know.

162
00:06:59,255 --> 00:07:01,569
Never thought I'd have
someone ask my permission

163
00:07:01,593 --> 00:07:02,871
to take you to Paris.

164
00:07:02,895 --> 00:07:04,830
You know damn well
that's not what Jeff did.

165
00:07:06,636 --> 00:07:08,849
Jessica, what exactly
do you want to talk about?

166
00:07:08,873 --> 00:07:11,154
I want to know
why you cleared my schedule.

167
00:07:11,179 --> 00:07:12,757
Because Jeff asked me to,

168
00:07:12,781 --> 00:07:14,626
and I can't remember the last
time you took a vacation.

169
00:07:14,651 --> 00:07:16,363
When's the last time
you took a vacation?

170
00:07:16,388 --> 00:07:18,334
I'm not the one
in a serious relationship.

171
00:07:18,359 --> 00:07:19,771
Oh, so you're playing matchmaker
for me now?

172
00:07:19,795 --> 00:07:21,007
Oh, I'm not playing anything,

173
00:07:21,032 --> 00:07:22,576
and you were the one
who said you had to choose

174
00:07:22,600 --> 00:07:25,616
between hiring him
and continuing to see him.

175
00:07:25,640 --> 00:07:26,952
And then I changed my mind.

176
00:07:26,977 --> 00:07:28,856
And I don't want you
to make the same mistake I did.

177
00:07:28,881 --> 00:07:32,396
What are you talking about?

178
00:07:32,420 --> 00:07:33,999
I should have taken
some time with Scottie.

179
00:07:34,024 --> 00:07:35,769
Jeff and I are not
you and Scottie.

180
00:07:35,794 --> 00:07:37,240
Jessica, take a vacation.

181
00:07:37,264 --> 00:07:38,675
Don't take a vacation.

182
00:07:38,700 --> 00:07:40,079
The man came in here,

183
00:07:40,103 --> 00:07:42,415
asking me for help because
he wants to go away with you,

184
00:07:42,439 --> 00:07:45,511
and I said yes because I'm not
gonna be the reason he can't.

185
00:07:55,767 --> 00:07:59,239
Pearson Specter,
how may I direct your call?

186
00:08:02,981 --> 00:08:06,219
Pearson Specter,
how may I direct your call?

187
00:08:11,096 --> 00:08:13,443
- Louis, do you have a minute?
- No, I don't.

188
00:08:13,468 --> 00:08:16,316
Okay. What are you doing?

189
00:08:16,341 --> 00:08:18,587
Pearson Specter,
how may I direct your call?

190
00:08:18,611 --> 00:08:20,959
Pearson Specter,
how may I direct your call?

191
00:08:20,983 --> 00:08:22,461
You hear...

192
00:08:22,486 --> 00:08:24,032
Pearson Specter,
how may I direct your call?

193
00:08:24,056 --> 00:08:28,139
Hello? Pearson Specter...

194
00:08:28,163 --> 00:08:29,675
You hear that?

195
00:08:29,700 --> 00:08:31,412
Where's the Litt?

196
00:08:31,437 --> 00:08:33,249
Every call is like a slap
in the face.

197
00:08:33,274 --> 00:08:35,488
Louis, it's standard practice
for a law firm

198
00:08:35,512 --> 00:08:36,757
to shorten their name
on the phone.

199
00:08:36,781 --> 00:08:38,726
So blatant disrespect
is standard practice now?

200
00:08:38,751 --> 00:08:40,263
It's not disrespect. It's just...

201
00:08:40,288 --> 00:08:42,335
You're telling me
that your father doesn't

202
00:08:42,359 --> 00:08:43,403
have them answer the phone,

203
00:08:43,427 --> 00:08:45,139
"Rand, Kaldore, Zane"?

204
00:08:45,164 --> 00:08:46,510
Actually, no, he doesn't,

205
00:08:46,534 --> 00:08:50,016
and I think you'd agree
that people respect my father.

206
00:08:50,041 --> 00:08:51,285
Unless you want to go back
to telling me

207
00:08:51,309 --> 00:08:52,521
that he's a shady lawyer.

208
00:08:52,545 --> 00:08:54,426
Come on, Rachel,
that was when I was mad at you.

209
00:08:54,448 --> 00:08:58,589
Which is actually why I wanted
to come and talk to you.

210
00:08:59,826 --> 00:09:02,808
I want to thank you
for forgiving Mike.

211
00:09:02,832 --> 00:09:06,347
It... it means a lot to me.

212
00:09:06,372 --> 00:09:08,051
Now, can you stop
obsessing over the phone

213
00:09:08,076 --> 00:09:10,524
long enough to hear that?

214
00:09:10,548 --> 00:09:11,759
I'm sorry, Rachel,

215
00:09:11,784 --> 00:09:13,162
but I can't,

216
00:09:13,186 --> 00:09:15,065
and now I have to go rip
that receptionist a new ass...

217
00:09:15,090 --> 00:09:18,105
Louis, if one of your first acts
as name partner

218
00:09:18,129 --> 00:09:20,910
is to rip the receptionist
to shreds,

219
00:09:20,935 --> 00:09:23,182
you'll regret that
for the rest of your life.

220
00:09:23,206 --> 00:09:25,052
Just let it go.

221
00:09:25,077 --> 00:09:26,355
Let it go.

222
00:09:26,379 --> 00:09:29,627
Things will run their course.

223
00:09:29,652 --> 00:09:31,631
You know what, Rachel?
You're right.

224
00:09:31,656 --> 00:09:35,663
And by the way, I'm glad
that we're friends again.

225
00:09:45,883 --> 00:09:47,886
Pearson Specter...

226
00:09:51,128 --> 00:09:54,410
Harvey, what are you doing
at 3:30 this afternoon?

227
00:09:54,435 --> 00:09:55,779
Why?

228
00:09:55,803 --> 00:09:58,050
I have some news, and I don't
want you to overreact.

229
00:09:58,074 --> 00:09:59,075
What is it?

230
00:09:59,076 --> 00:10:02,493
Jeffrey Bender
wants to meet with you.

231
00:10:02,518 --> 00:10:04,062
He heard we're taking
a whistle-blower case,

232
00:10:04,086 --> 00:10:07,067
and he wants us to drop it.

233
00:10:07,091 --> 00:10:10,341
Relax, I'll take care
of Jeffrey Bender.

234
00:10:10,366 --> 00:10:11,477
Wait a second,
you're not gonna try

235
00:10:11,501 --> 00:10:13,280
to cut Mike's legs
out from under him

236
00:10:13,305 --> 00:10:14,650
- before he even gets started?
- What's the point?

237
00:10:14,674 --> 00:10:17,144
He'd just bother me
until I agreed not to anyway.

238
00:10:19,950 --> 00:10:21,796
I can't believe it.

239
00:10:21,821 --> 00:10:24,235
You have no idea what to say.

240
00:10:24,260 --> 00:10:26,474
What's the date today?
I want to write this down.

241
00:10:26,498 --> 00:10:28,277
You know what?

242
00:10:28,302 --> 00:10:29,880
It's the seventh of kiss my ass,

243
00:10:29,904 --> 00:10:33,019
and tomorrow is the eighth of
set your own goddamn meetings.

244
00:10:33,044 --> 00:10:34,355
Is that the Mayan calendar?

245
00:10:34,379 --> 00:10:36,426
Nope, that's the Donna calendar.

246
00:10:36,450 --> 00:10:39,221
I got you.
For the record, I got you.

247
00:10:42,262 --> 00:10:44,609
All right, take me
through it one more time.

248
00:10:44,633 --> 00:10:46,714
It's simple.

249
00:10:46,738 --> 00:10:50,020
There are axles on all the cars
in all the trains,

250
00:10:50,045 --> 00:10:53,027
and those axles have sensors to
make sure they don't overheat.

251
00:10:53,051 --> 00:10:54,495
So you're saying
that the train crashed

252
00:10:54,519 --> 00:10:55,832
because the heat sensors failed.

253
00:10:55,857 --> 00:10:58,270
I'm saying
that all the heat sensors

254
00:10:58,294 --> 00:11:00,807
on the entire fleet were faulty,

255
00:11:00,832 --> 00:11:02,211
and they knew about it.

256
00:11:02,235 --> 00:11:03,813
Then why didn't you
come forward with this before?

257
00:11:03,838 --> 00:11:06,185
You mean before they fired me
for coming forward with it?

258
00:11:06,209 --> 00:11:07,722
Which brings me
to my next question.

259
00:11:07,747 --> 00:11:10,227
You've had four different jobs
in the last six years.

260
00:11:10,251 --> 00:11:11,252
What are you getting at?

261
00:11:11,253 --> 00:11:13,433
I want to know why.

262
00:11:13,457 --> 00:11:14,636
I move around.

263
00:11:14,661 --> 00:11:16,005
It's not uncommon
in my business.

264
00:11:16,029 --> 00:11:18,510
Move around or keep failing?

265
00:11:18,535 --> 00:11:20,815
I got fired
for blowing the whistle,

266
00:11:20,839 --> 00:11:22,285
not for messing up on the job.

267
00:11:22,309 --> 00:11:24,270
That's not what your last
performance review says.

268
00:11:24,279 --> 00:11:26,090
I don't give a shit
what it says.

269
00:11:26,115 --> 00:11:28,195
They used that as an excuse
to fire me,

270
00:11:28,219 --> 00:11:30,767
and my reviews
before I came forward

271
00:11:30,792 --> 00:11:32,470
passed with flying colors.

272
00:11:32,495 --> 00:11:33,573
I'm a solid worker.

273
00:11:33,597 --> 00:11:34,942
How the hell do you think
I got this?

274
00:11:34,966 --> 00:11:36,745
I know your reviews are stellar.

275
00:11:36,770 --> 00:11:38,749
What I need to know is
if there's anything out there

276
00:11:38,774 --> 00:11:40,921
that we don't have, because
they are gonna come at us

277
00:11:40,945 --> 00:11:43,292
any way they can,
and when they do,

278
00:11:43,317 --> 00:11:44,829
it's not gonna
be about heat sensors.

279
00:11:44,853 --> 00:11:46,365
It's gonna be about you.

280
00:11:46,390 --> 00:11:49,338
Yeah, I don't care if
I'm the worst guy in the world.

281
00:11:49,363 --> 00:11:51,810
I know I'm not the only guy
in that company

282
00:11:51,834 --> 00:11:53,970
that knows
those sensors are faulty.

283
00:11:56,075 --> 00:11:57,987
What are you talking about?

284
00:11:58,012 --> 00:11:59,757
What do you mean,
there's a report?

285
00:11:59,782 --> 00:12:02,931
Done after the crash
that showed a defective part

286
00:12:02,955 --> 00:12:05,369
was the real cause,
not engineer error.

287
00:12:05,394 --> 00:12:06,538
Says the whistle-blower.

288
00:12:06,562 --> 00:12:09,443
Says these.

289
00:12:09,468 --> 00:12:11,047
That's a memo
ordering the report

290
00:12:11,072 --> 00:12:13,853
and another email
acknowledging its existence.

291
00:12:13,877 --> 00:12:15,189
We got 'em.

292
00:12:15,214 --> 00:12:16,859
- We do.
- Set a meeting.

293
00:12:16,883 --> 00:12:18,930
Let them do the talking,
then drop the hammer,

294
00:12:18,955 --> 00:12:20,267
and stick a settlement
down their throat

295
00:12:20,291 --> 00:12:21,268
before they know what hit them.

296
00:12:21,293 --> 00:12:22,871
I appreciate the advice, Harvey,

297
00:12:22,896 --> 00:12:24,874
but this time I'm going in
with the hammer in my hand,

298
00:12:24,899 --> 00:12:26,577
and I am coming out swinging.

299
00:12:26,601 --> 00:12:28,447
Okay, big talker,
how much you asking for?

300
00:12:28,472 --> 00:12:30,218
40 million.

301
00:12:30,243 --> 00:12:31,554
Are you kidding me?

302
00:12:31,578 --> 00:12:33,992
They'll pay ten times that
without even trying.

303
00:12:34,017 --> 00:12:35,362
Not when I tell them
they're gonna have to admit

304
00:12:35,386 --> 00:12:36,664
what they did.

305
00:12:36,688 --> 00:12:38,467
- Are you nuts?
- No, I am not.

306
00:12:38,492 --> 00:12:39,904
We are not sealing
this settlement,

307
00:12:39,929 --> 00:12:42,343
and before you say another word,
this is my case.

308
00:12:42,367 --> 00:12:43,578
I don't care whose case it is.

309
00:12:43,602 --> 00:12:45,348
They're never going to admit
what they did.

310
00:12:45,373 --> 00:12:47,018
Pick a higher number
and let them seal it.

311
00:12:47,043 --> 00:12:49,290
Harvey, you told me to prove
this wasn't a shakedown.

312
00:12:49,314 --> 00:12:51,627
Now you want me to take money
to cover things up?

313
00:12:51,652 --> 00:12:53,397
You know what that is?
A shakedown!

314
00:12:53,421 --> 00:12:56,102
A shakedown is when
your case has no merit.

315
00:12:56,127 --> 00:12:57,405
This is the way things work.

316
00:12:57,429 --> 00:12:58,907
Not to mention,
if we quietly settle,

317
00:12:58,932 --> 00:13:01,080
we don't have to worry
about scaring away our clients.

318
00:13:01,104 --> 00:13:02,782
That's why
it's the way things work.

319
00:13:02,807 --> 00:13:04,887
Harvey, people died
in this crash!

320
00:13:04,911 --> 00:13:07,525
And they're not coming back, no
matter what Liberty Rail admits.

321
00:13:07,550 --> 00:13:09,496
You are such a cold,
heartless son of a bitch.

322
00:13:09,521 --> 00:13:11,300
And this isn't
about your parents,

323
00:13:11,324 --> 00:13:13,269
so back them
into whatever corner you want,

324
00:13:13,294 --> 00:13:15,207
but when they refuse
to admit what they did,

325
00:13:15,232 --> 00:13:17,968
you are not going to trial.

326
00:13:21,678 --> 00:13:23,681
Stay out of my case.

327
00:13:35,360 --> 00:13:37,406
Something smells delicious.

328
00:13:37,430 --> 00:13:41,681
I'm making us dinner, but it
won't be ready for a while.

329
00:13:41,705 --> 00:13:43,384
Good, that means we have time

330
00:13:43,409 --> 00:13:45,923
to go over
my proposed itinerary.

331
00:13:45,947 --> 00:13:48,160
I don't recall saying yes.

332
00:13:48,185 --> 00:13:50,399
I thought that we would start

333
00:13:50,423 --> 00:13:53,137
with a private tour
of the Rodin.

334
00:13:53,162 --> 00:13:54,573
Oh, the Rodin.

335
00:13:54,597 --> 00:13:58,213
God, I must have visited that
sculpture garden a dozen times.

336
00:13:58,238 --> 00:14:00,017
Then I'm so glad that I arranged
for us to have a picnic

337
00:14:00,042 --> 00:14:01,453
while we're there,

338
00:14:01,477 --> 00:14:02,522
and during that picnic,

339
00:14:02,546 --> 00:14:05,962
we can reminisce
about the week before,

340
00:14:05,987 --> 00:14:08,834
where we danced the night away
in the Latin Quarter.

341
00:14:08,859 --> 00:14:10,271
We did?

342
00:14:10,295 --> 00:14:13,076
Mm, or we'll talk
about how we'll end the trip

343
00:14:13,101 --> 00:14:15,581
in the Loire Valley,

344
00:14:15,605 --> 00:14:19,756
where we will sip wine
along the Seine.

345
00:14:19,781 --> 00:14:23,431
♪

346
00:14:23,455 --> 00:14:26,335
Jeff, this trip is perfect.
How did you know?

347
00:14:26,360 --> 00:14:29,599
I know you've always
loved Paris, so I started there.

348
00:14:30,736 --> 00:14:32,783
And then I called your sister.

349
00:14:32,807 --> 00:14:34,185
You did that for me?

350
00:14:34,209 --> 00:14:36,088
I did.

351
00:14:36,113 --> 00:14:39,451
So what do you say?

352
00:14:41,390 --> 00:14:43,604
I say,

353
00:14:43,629 --> 00:14:47,512
if you knew what I was cooking,

354
00:14:47,537 --> 00:14:49,371
you'd already know my answer.

355
00:14:54,417 --> 00:14:57,598
- Looks French.
- Mm-hmm.

356
00:14:57,622 --> 00:14:59,435
So you let me go through
all that even though

357
00:14:59,460 --> 00:15:01,507
you knew you were gonna
say yes the entire time?

358
00:15:01,531 --> 00:15:02,975
Mm-hmm.

359
00:15:02,999 --> 00:15:05,347
Aren't you glad I did?

360
00:15:05,372 --> 00:15:07,508
Yes, Jessica.

361
00:15:08,811 --> 00:15:10,657
Yes, I am.

362
00:15:10,682 --> 00:15:18,690
♪

363
00:15:23,474 --> 00:15:24,651
Donna, what are you doing here?

364
00:15:24,675 --> 00:15:27,423
I'm here
because I can't take it anymore.

365
00:15:27,448 --> 00:15:28,759
What?

366
00:15:28,783 --> 00:15:31,932
This place has no life,
and I can't take it anymore.

367
00:15:31,957 --> 00:15:33,503
And that's gonna add life?

368
00:15:33,527 --> 00:15:34,848
If I gave you
something too needy,

369
00:15:34,862 --> 00:15:36,942
it would intimidate you,
and you would let it die.

370
00:15:36,967 --> 00:15:39,781
You expect me to believe
that's why you're really here?

371
00:15:39,805 --> 00:15:41,183
Of course not.

372
00:15:41,208 --> 00:15:42,320
I'm here to stop you from doing

373
00:15:42,344 --> 00:15:43,989
what you're gonna do in an hour:

374
00:15:44,014 --> 00:15:45,259
Crash Mike's meeting.

375
00:15:45,283 --> 00:15:47,396
Donna, I can't have him
risking our other business.

376
00:15:47,420 --> 00:15:49,099
It was one client,
and you covered it.

377
00:15:49,124 --> 00:15:50,469
And if he drags this to trial,

378
00:15:50,493 --> 00:15:51,571
it will be every client.

379
00:15:51,595 --> 00:15:53,073
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do.

380
00:15:53,098 --> 00:15:55,112
Then trust him
to accept that on his own.

381
00:15:55,136 --> 00:15:56,414
Donna...

382
00:15:56,438 --> 00:15:58,519
Harvey, when are you gonna
let him be his own man?

383
00:15:58,543 --> 00:16:00,689
His own man?
He's out of control.

384
00:16:00,714 --> 00:16:02,761
He's identifying these people
with his parents.

385
00:16:02,785 --> 00:16:04,164
And you're out of control
because you can't

386
00:16:04,188 --> 00:16:05,499
separate yourself from him.

387
00:16:05,523 --> 00:16:06,934
Okay, you need
to stay out of it.

388
00:16:06,959 --> 00:16:09,140
And I will, but you said
you made a mistake

389
00:16:09,164 --> 00:16:12,146
not trusting Mike
with Gillis Industries.

390
00:16:12,170 --> 00:16:15,175
I'm telling you,
don't make that mistake again.

391
00:16:23,993 --> 00:16:25,661
♪

392
00:16:28,301 --> 00:16:30,715
Pearson Specter,
how may I direct your call?

393
00:16:30,740 --> 00:16:37,061
♪

394
00:16:37,085 --> 00:16:38,086
Uh...

395
00:16:38,087 --> 00:16:46,095
♪

396
00:16:51,515 --> 00:16:53,494
Rand, Kaldore, Zane.

397
00:16:53,519 --> 00:16:55,521
Son of a bitch!

398
00:16:57,559 --> 00:17:00,274
Hello, liar.

399
00:17:00,299 --> 00:17:02,379
- Excuse me?
- Rand, Kaldore, Zane.

400
00:17:02,403 --> 00:17:03,814
You know what that is?

401
00:17:03,838 --> 00:17:06,452
That's how they answer the phone
at Rand, Kaldore, Zane.

402
00:17:06,477 --> 00:17:08,222
- Louis, I'm sorry.
- Oh, save your sorrys.

403
00:17:08,247 --> 00:17:09,559
Do you know the receptionist
at the front desk?

404
00:17:09,583 --> 00:17:11,228
Yes, her name is Elise.

405
00:17:11,253 --> 00:17:13,367
Good, you can use her name
when you fire her.

406
00:17:13,391 --> 00:17:15,405
I don't have the authority
to fire people,

407
00:17:15,429 --> 00:17:17,073
but I did just talk to her.

408
00:17:17,098 --> 00:17:18,177
- You did?
- Mm-hmm.

409
00:17:18,201 --> 00:17:19,178
To set her straight.
That's good.

410
00:17:19,203 --> 00:17:20,247
No, not good.

411
00:17:20,271 --> 00:17:21,617
She came to see me.

412
00:17:21,641 --> 00:17:24,454
She said that
you've been harassing her.

413
00:17:24,479 --> 00:17:25,925
What happened?

414
00:17:25,950 --> 00:17:29,065
She said that you called and
hung up on her over 50 times.

415
00:17:29,089 --> 00:17:30,201
What?
How did she even know it was me?

416
00:17:30,225 --> 00:17:31,703
Because you called
from your office.

417
00:17:31,727 --> 00:17:33,539
Well, it wasn't harassment
because it wasn't sexual.

418
00:17:33,564 --> 00:17:36,111
Well, she also said that
you were leering at her

419
00:17:36,136 --> 00:17:37,181
when you stepped
off the elevator.

420
00:17:37,205 --> 00:17:38,383
I wasn't leering!

421
00:17:38,407 --> 00:17:39,819
I was mad about
how she answered the phone.

422
00:17:39,844 --> 00:17:41,022
Louis, it doesn't matter
why you did it.

423
00:17:41,046 --> 00:17:42,558
She felt violated.

424
00:17:42,582 --> 00:17:44,762
Well, you know what,
you tell her it's not like that,

425
00:17:44,787 --> 00:17:48,270
and then you violate her ass
out the door.

426
00:17:48,294 --> 00:17:52,177
Louis, is this really the kind
of name partner you want to be?

427
00:17:52,202 --> 00:17:53,803
No, I want to be
the kind of name partner

428
00:17:53,805 --> 00:17:55,750
that has his name
said on the goddamn phone.

429
00:17:55,775 --> 00:17:57,587
Okay, well, in order to fire her

430
00:17:57,612 --> 00:17:59,057
without getting sued
for harassment,

431
00:17:59,081 --> 00:18:00,559
you'd have to fire
the entire support staff,

432
00:18:00,584 --> 00:18:04,835
and you and I both know that
that's never going to happen.

433
00:18:04,859 --> 00:18:07,207
We are not firing
all of our support staff.

434
00:18:07,231 --> 00:18:09,076
Well, it's easy for you to say,
being that your name is first.

435
00:18:09,101 --> 00:18:10,102
What are you talking...

436
00:18:10,103 --> 00:18:11,916
Jessica, I am talking
about respect.

437
00:18:11,941 --> 00:18:15,623
R-e-s-p-e-c-t,
find out what it means to me.

438
00:18:15,648 --> 00:18:16,927
But I guess
I'll just find my own way

439
00:18:16,951 --> 00:18:19,197
to be treated how I deserve.

440
00:18:19,221 --> 00:18:21,166
I know I'm gonna regret
asking this.

441
00:18:21,191 --> 00:18:24,796
Louis, tell me specifically
what it is you're talking about.

442
00:18:28,239 --> 00:18:30,118
They are answering the phones,
"Pearson Specter,"

443
00:18:30,142 --> 00:18:31,854
not "Pearson Specter Litt."

444
00:18:31,879 --> 00:18:33,091
Louis...

445
00:18:33,115 --> 00:18:34,893
You don't believe me?
Check it yourself.

446
00:18:34,918 --> 00:18:36,264
I'm not harassing
our support staff.

447
00:18:36,289 --> 00:18:37,600
It's not harassment,
God damn it!

448
00:18:37,624 --> 00:18:38,970
Louis!

449
00:18:38,994 --> 00:18:41,341
Jessica, it's like they've
been specifically instructed

450
00:18:41,366 --> 00:18:42,743
to leave my name off.

451
00:18:42,767 --> 00:18:43,912
Now you're just being paranoid.

452
00:18:43,936 --> 00:18:45,515
I am not paranoid.
They're in lockstep.

453
00:18:45,540 --> 00:18:47,620
I'm telling you,
someone paid them off.

454
00:18:47,644 --> 00:18:49,757
Louis, that's insane,

455
00:18:49,781 --> 00:18:51,895
but if you want them
to say your name,

456
00:18:51,919 --> 00:18:53,888
I will get them
to say your name.

457
00:19:01,304 --> 00:19:03,485
Jessica, what can I do for you?

458
00:19:03,509 --> 00:19:05,923
You can explain to me
why you paid our reception staff

459
00:19:05,948 --> 00:19:08,428
not to say Louis' name
when they answer the phone.

460
00:19:08,452 --> 00:19:10,465
- Who says I did that?
- They do.

461
00:19:10,489 --> 00:19:12,235
God damn it.

462
00:19:12,260 --> 00:19:13,804
I paid them good money
to keep Louis

463
00:19:13,829 --> 00:19:15,042
from finding out
for at least a month.

464
00:19:15,066 --> 00:19:16,310
He hasn't found out.

465
00:19:16,334 --> 00:19:18,313
It wasn't him who got them
to crack, it was me.

466
00:19:18,338 --> 00:19:20,184
Even still,
I'm asking for a refund.

467
00:19:20,209 --> 00:19:22,812
Jeff, I'm serious about this.

468
00:19:24,685 --> 00:19:27,366
I know you're pissed about
how he got his name on the door,

469
00:19:27,390 --> 00:19:29,870
but I need you
to bury the hatchet.

470
00:19:29,895 --> 00:19:31,840
- Well, I'm not gonna do that.
- Why not?

471
00:19:31,865 --> 00:19:33,946
Because every single time
I see his rat face,

472
00:19:33,970 --> 00:19:35,347
I think about him
blackmailing you,

473
00:19:35,371 --> 00:19:36,583
and it makes me want
to walk over to him

474
00:19:36,608 --> 00:19:37,953
and rip his arms off his body,

475
00:19:37,977 --> 00:19:41,359
and that little phone prank
was just my way

476
00:19:41,383 --> 00:19:44,532
of keeping myself
from doing something like that.

477
00:19:44,557 --> 00:19:46,002
I understand,

478
00:19:46,026 --> 00:19:48,207
and I do appreciate it,

479
00:19:48,231 --> 00:19:50,677
but I'm not asking you
to do it for him.

480
00:19:50,702 --> 00:19:52,705
I'm asking you to do it for me.

481
00:20:01,123 --> 00:20:03,336
Mr. Ross.

482
00:20:03,361 --> 00:20:04,906
All I can say about your filing
is that I think

483
00:20:04,930 --> 00:20:07,111
you might have a career
writing fiction.

484
00:20:07,135 --> 00:20:09,181
And if you don't hand over
that report we're requesting,

485
00:20:09,206 --> 00:20:10,885
you're gonna
have a career behind bars.

486
00:20:10,909 --> 00:20:12,320
You're not here for that report.

487
00:20:12,345 --> 00:20:14,660
You're here to strong arm
my client into a big, fat check.

488
00:20:14,684 --> 00:20:16,062
I'm sorry to be the one
to tell you this,

489
00:20:16,086 --> 00:20:18,933
but a big, fat check
isn't gonna get you out of this.

490
00:20:18,958 --> 00:20:20,436
- Is that a fact?
- Sure as hell is,

491
00:20:20,461 --> 00:20:21,807
because we both know that report

492
00:20:21,831 --> 00:20:24,211
says you're responsible
for this accident,

493
00:20:24,236 --> 00:20:26,349
and we're not settling anything
without you admitting it.

494
00:20:26,373 --> 00:20:29,377
And we're not admitting
something we didn't do.

495
00:20:30,948 --> 00:20:32,126
What the hell is this?

496
00:20:32,151 --> 00:20:33,429
Well, you wanted the report.

497
00:20:33,453 --> 00:20:35,066
Here it is.

498
00:20:35,091 --> 00:20:36,936
Your client wasn't lying
about its existence.

499
00:20:36,961 --> 00:20:38,873
He was just lying
about everything else.

500
00:20:38,898 --> 00:20:40,877
We ran repeated tests
on our heat sensors,

501
00:20:40,902 --> 00:20:42,637
and they passed every one.

502
00:20:44,675 --> 00:20:45,687
This is bullshit.

503
00:20:45,711 --> 00:20:46,789
The only thing that's bullshit

504
00:20:46,814 --> 00:20:48,359
is Joe Henderson.

505
00:20:48,383 --> 00:20:49,962
He doesn't care
about the accident.

506
00:20:49,987 --> 00:20:51,665
All he's trying to do
is shake us down,

507
00:20:51,689 --> 00:20:54,360
exactly like he did
at his last four jobs.

508
00:20:57,802 --> 00:20:59,147
What the hell is that?

509
00:20:59,171 --> 00:21:01,685
His last four lawsuits.

510
00:21:01,710 --> 00:21:03,188
Did you think we wouldn't
find out about them

511
00:21:03,212 --> 00:21:04,791
just because the records
were sealed?

512
00:21:04,816 --> 00:21:06,896
Mr. Ross,
your client's been playing

513
00:21:06,920 --> 00:21:09,000
the whistle-blower lottery
for years.

514
00:21:09,024 --> 00:21:10,470
He's never won before.

515
00:21:10,494 --> 00:21:12,362
He's not going to win today.

516
00:21:22,552 --> 00:21:24,431
You son of a bitch,
you tried to blow the whistle

517
00:21:24,456 --> 00:21:28,472
at every job you've ever had,
and now they know it!

518
00:21:28,496 --> 00:21:30,943
Keep your voice down.

519
00:21:30,967 --> 00:21:32,613
You...
No, I'll keep my voice down

520
00:21:32,638 --> 00:21:33,982
when you stop bullshit-ing me.

521
00:21:34,006 --> 00:21:36,321
Those claims were
supposed to be sealed.

522
00:21:36,346 --> 00:21:38,057
I don't care what they were
supposed to be.

523
00:21:38,081 --> 00:21:40,995
They found them, and you were
supposed to tell me about them.

524
00:21:41,020 --> 00:21:42,933
And what would you
have done if I did?

525
00:21:42,958 --> 00:21:44,270
I would've said what they said,

526
00:21:44,295 --> 00:21:46,140
that you don't give a shit
about what they did!

527
00:21:46,164 --> 00:21:47,543
You're just looking to get rich.

528
00:21:47,568 --> 00:21:49,346
You think I would've
risked my job

529
00:21:49,371 --> 00:21:51,818
and everything that I have
for nothing?

530
00:21:51,842 --> 00:21:52,854
Excuse me?

531
00:21:52,878 --> 00:21:54,857
I said, I don't see you

532
00:21:54,882 --> 00:21:56,560
working out of the goodness
of your heart

533
00:21:56,585 --> 00:21:58,632
in your $1,000 suit.

534
00:21:58,656 --> 00:22:01,838
You have no idea
who I am or why I do things.

535
00:22:01,862 --> 00:22:04,911
And I told you, you don't have
to be concerned about my history

536
00:22:04,935 --> 00:22:07,917
because what
I'm telling you is true.

537
00:22:07,941 --> 00:22:09,719
Not according to this.

538
00:22:09,744 --> 00:22:12,125
That's the report that you said
gave us all the leverage

539
00:22:12,150 --> 00:22:14,129
and they say
proves them innocent.

540
00:22:14,154 --> 00:22:15,900
That report is bullshit,

541
00:22:15,925 --> 00:22:18,571
because I'm telling you,
those sensors didn't work,

542
00:22:18,595 --> 00:22:20,174
and that was the cause
of that accident.

543
00:22:20,199 --> 00:22:21,477
Well, I might have
a leg to stand on

544
00:22:21,501 --> 00:22:23,615
if you had
any credibility at all.

545
00:22:23,639 --> 00:22:25,484
How the hell am I supposed
to get a jury to believe you

546
00:22:25,509 --> 00:22:27,512
when I'm not even sure I do?

547
00:22:36,331 --> 00:22:37,710
What are you doing here?

548
00:22:37,735 --> 00:22:39,480
I'm here to tell you
to call the front desk.

549
00:22:39,504 --> 00:22:41,450
Oh, let me guess.

550
00:22:41,475 --> 00:22:43,285
Jessica told you
they won't say my name

551
00:22:43,310 --> 00:22:44,656
and you thought
it was hilarious.

552
00:22:44,681 --> 00:22:45,859
You're right, I did.

553
00:22:45,883 --> 00:22:46,927
Why don't you get the hell
out of my office

554
00:22:46,951 --> 00:22:49,031
and go laugh somewhere else?

555
00:22:49,055 --> 00:22:50,534
Oh, you want to hit me now?

556
00:22:50,558 --> 00:22:52,537
Yeah, well, why don't you go
ask Mike Ross about my headlock?

557
00:22:52,563 --> 00:22:54,733
'Cause it's a goddamn vice.

558
00:23:00,077 --> 00:23:01,054
Pearson Specter Litt,

559
00:23:01,079 --> 00:23:03,082
how may I direct your call?

560
00:23:08,160 --> 00:23:09,161
It was you.

561
00:23:09,162 --> 00:23:10,541
Yes, it was me,

562
00:23:10,566 --> 00:23:13,146
but I fixed it, so...

563
00:23:13,170 --> 00:23:15,082
you can stop worrying
if everybody at the firm

564
00:23:15,107 --> 00:23:18,179
respects you, because they do.

565
00:23:22,188 --> 00:23:24,191
Everyone except you.

566
00:23:30,772 --> 00:23:32,484
No, Louis, including me.

567
00:23:32,509 --> 00:23:35,057
Listen, I may not like how
you got your name on the wall,

568
00:23:35,081 --> 00:23:37,617
but that doesn't mean
it shouldn't be up there.

569
00:23:39,857 --> 00:23:42,871
Congratulations, Louis.

570
00:23:42,895 --> 00:23:45,709
Thanks, Jeff.

571
00:23:45,734 --> 00:23:48,538
Hey, maybe we can even
get drinks this week.

572
00:23:49,842 --> 00:23:53,125
- Name partner buys.
- Deal.

573
00:23:53,150 --> 00:23:54,751
Done.

574
00:24:00,197 --> 00:24:02,118
You can leave the coffee,
but I'm not getting up.

575
00:24:02,135 --> 00:24:04,482
Mike, you've been working
for seven hours straight.

576
00:24:04,506 --> 00:24:05,984
You need a break.

577
00:24:06,009 --> 00:24:07,621
I've been working for seven
hours because if I tell Harvey

578
00:24:07,645 --> 00:24:09,090
what's going on
before I have a fix,

579
00:24:09,115 --> 00:24:10,360
he is gonna pull the plug.

580
00:24:10,384 --> 00:24:12,095
Well, then maybe the plug
needs to be pulled.

581
00:24:12,120 --> 00:24:13,833
Rachel, just because
Joe Henderson is

582
00:24:13,858 --> 00:24:14,936
a bullshit plaintiff
doesn't mean

583
00:24:14,960 --> 00:24:16,138
they didn't cover things up.

584
00:24:16,162 --> 00:24:18,910
It doesn't mean that they did.

585
00:24:18,935 --> 00:24:20,446
Okay, fine.

586
00:24:20,470 --> 00:24:21,582
Why would he ask for that report

587
00:24:21,606 --> 00:24:24,286
if he knew
it would hurt our case?

588
00:24:24,311 --> 00:24:25,657
- I don't know.
- I don't know either,

589
00:24:25,682 --> 00:24:27,293
which is why I need more time.

590
00:24:27,317 --> 00:24:29,397
Well, then you need to convince
Harvey to let you keep going,

591
00:24:29,421 --> 00:24:31,000
because if you don't
and he finds out...

592
00:24:31,025 --> 00:24:32,470
He is not gonna find out.

593
00:24:32,494 --> 00:24:35,408
Mike, he's not gonna
find out from me,

594
00:24:35,433 --> 00:24:37,681
but if I've learned one thing
in the last six months

595
00:24:37,706 --> 00:24:41,822
of working here, it's that if
he finds out from somebody else,

596
00:24:41,846 --> 00:24:44,316
you're gonna regret it.

597
00:24:50,062 --> 00:24:51,708
You come here to tell me
you're taking that vacation?

598
00:24:51,733 --> 00:24:53,578
I came by to ask
when Mike Ross started taking

599
00:24:53,603 --> 00:24:54,604
whistle-blower cases.

600
00:24:54,605 --> 00:24:55,606
Jessica...

601
00:24:55,607 --> 00:24:56,919
I want you
to put the brakes on him

602
00:24:56,943 --> 00:24:58,121
before this gets out of control.

603
00:24:58,145 --> 00:25:00,091
Well, I'm not gonna do that.

604
00:25:00,116 --> 00:25:01,794
- Harvey.
- Jessica, it's one case.

605
00:25:01,819 --> 00:25:04,333
He asked me to trust him,
and I'm gonna do it,

606
00:25:04,358 --> 00:25:06,571
and if you're ever gonna
be able to enjoy a vacation,

607
00:25:06,595 --> 00:25:09,744
you're gonna have to trust me.

608
00:25:09,768 --> 00:25:13,083
All right. Good night.

609
00:25:13,107 --> 00:25:15,454
Bon voyage.

610
00:25:15,479 --> 00:25:17,559
You do know
that doesn't mean "good night."

611
00:25:17,583 --> 00:25:18,795
Of course I do.

612
00:25:18,819 --> 00:25:20,798
Do you know how to say
"good night" in French?

613
00:25:20,823 --> 00:25:23,403
What, do you think
I'm some kind of Neanderthal?

614
00:25:23,428 --> 00:25:26,778
You don't know one word
of French, do you?

615
00:25:26,802 --> 00:25:27,946
Ménage à trois.

616
00:25:27,970 --> 00:25:29,806
You're an idiot.

617
00:25:31,144 --> 00:25:33,357
Ménage à quatre.

618
00:25:33,381 --> 00:25:35,184
Ménage à cinq.

619
00:25:36,887 --> 00:25:38,856
Can I come in?

620
00:25:43,468 --> 00:25:46,082
What's going on?

621
00:25:46,107 --> 00:25:47,108
We have a problem.

622
00:25:47,109 --> 00:25:49,155
I'm listening.

623
00:25:49,179 --> 00:25:52,094
Liberty Rail's report
directly contradicts our claim.

624
00:25:52,119 --> 00:25:53,531
That's a big damn problem.

625
00:25:53,555 --> 00:25:55,100
I believe my client, Harvey.

626
00:25:55,125 --> 00:25:56,303
Based on what, your gut?

627
00:25:56,327 --> 00:25:58,106
No, I found the guy
who wrote the report.

628
00:25:58,131 --> 00:26:00,511
He's on indefinite leave
in Australia,

629
00:26:00,535 --> 00:26:02,114
where we can't subpoena him.

630
00:26:02,139 --> 00:26:04,017
So it's our word against theirs.

631
00:26:04,042 --> 00:26:05,710
Which is why I'm here.

632
00:26:07,716 --> 00:26:11,332
Joe Henderson made four other
claims in the last six years.

633
00:26:11,356 --> 00:26:12,601
- You're shit-ing me.
- Harvey...

634
00:26:12,626 --> 00:26:14,807
That's it. I'm pulling the plug.

635
00:26:14,831 --> 00:26:16,109
I knew it.

636
00:26:16,133 --> 00:26:17,845
I knew you would bail on me
the second this thing

637
00:26:17,870 --> 00:26:18,948
hit the smallest bump.

638
00:26:18,972 --> 00:26:20,151
Bail on you?

639
00:26:20,175 --> 00:26:22,154
I backed you because you told me
you had a case.

640
00:26:22,179 --> 00:26:24,859
I do have a case.
I told you they got to this guy.

641
00:26:24,884 --> 00:26:25,929
And you got no proof of that.

642
00:26:25,953 --> 00:26:26,998
And if this were your case,

643
00:26:27,022 --> 00:26:28,967
you would be begging me
for help to get it.

644
00:26:28,992 --> 00:26:30,504
It's not my case. It's yours.

645
00:26:30,529 --> 00:26:32,073
And now you're asking a jury

646
00:26:32,097 --> 00:26:34,478
to believe these guys
fabricated a report

647
00:26:34,503 --> 00:26:36,650
based on the word
of a career whistle-blower.

648
00:26:36,674 --> 00:26:38,420
No, I'm asking you
to believe it.

649
00:26:38,445 --> 00:26:39,923
It doesn't matter
what I believe.

650
00:26:39,947 --> 00:26:41,859
This guy is
a goddamn shakedown artist,

651
00:26:41,884 --> 00:26:42,885
and I'm pulling the plug.

652
00:26:42,886 --> 00:26:44,131
I don't care what he is.

653
00:26:44,155 --> 00:26:47,237
I'm not
a goddamn shakedown artist!

654
00:26:47,262 --> 00:26:48,641
Mike...

655
00:26:48,665 --> 00:26:53,651
Harvey, you told me that
those people weren't my parents,

656
00:26:53,675 --> 00:26:55,811
but they are somebody's parents.

657
00:26:58,485 --> 00:27:00,319
Please.

658
00:27:01,858 --> 00:27:03,861
You got 24 hours.

659
00:27:21,524 --> 00:27:23,804
You know it's against the law
to litter, don't you?

660
00:27:23,828 --> 00:27:25,239
What do you want, Donna?

661
00:27:25,264 --> 00:27:26,465
I know you went to see Harvey.

662
00:27:26,467 --> 00:27:27,912
You know that
he wants me to fail.

663
00:27:27,937 --> 00:27:29,248
That's not true.

664
00:27:29,272 --> 00:27:31,251
I don't have anything,
and he only gave me a day.

665
00:27:31,276 --> 00:27:32,355
And if he wanted you to fail,

666
00:27:32,379 --> 00:27:35,193
he wouldn't have given you
another second.

667
00:27:35,218 --> 00:27:37,655
You know he thinks
this is about my parents, right?

668
00:27:40,963 --> 00:27:42,797
Is it?

669
00:27:46,674 --> 00:27:49,388
Maybe it is,

670
00:27:49,412 --> 00:27:51,726
but what these people did
is a million times worse

671
00:27:51,751 --> 00:27:53,997
because they knew
it could happen.

672
00:27:54,021 --> 00:27:55,500
Wait a second...
They knew this could happen,

673
00:27:55,524 --> 00:27:56,836
and they didn't fix it before?

674
00:27:56,861 --> 00:27:58,907
Yeah, Donna, and then they...
They rolled the dice.

675
00:27:58,931 --> 00:28:00,009
Well, what about now?

676
00:28:00,033 --> 00:28:01,144
Are those trains
still messed up?

677
00:28:01,168 --> 00:28:02,581
Because that would
make them monsters.

678
00:28:02,606 --> 00:28:04,451
They are monsters, but that
would also make them idiots,

679
00:28:04,476 --> 00:28:05,554
and they're not idiots.

680
00:28:05,578 --> 00:28:06,723
Well, what are you
talking about?

681
00:28:06,747 --> 00:28:08,258
Well, they must have
fixed the sensors by now;

682
00:28:08,282 --> 00:28:10,094
Otherwise if it happened again,
they'd all go to jail.

683
00:28:10,119 --> 00:28:11,698
Well, if they fixed the sensors,
then there has to be

684
00:28:11,723 --> 00:28:12,901
- a paper trail.
- Of course there is.

685
00:28:12,925 --> 00:28:14,437
Then all you have to do
is get it.

686
00:28:14,462 --> 00:28:16,475
What do you think I've been
trying to figure out all night?

687
00:28:16,499 --> 00:28:18,278
What's to figure out?
Subpoena it.

688
00:28:18,302 --> 00:28:21,518
Yeah, there's only one problem.
Harvey only gave me 24 hours.

689
00:28:21,543 --> 00:28:22,654
But now that
you've come up with this,

690
00:28:22,678 --> 00:28:24,223
maybe Harvey
will change his mind.

691
00:28:24,248 --> 00:28:26,495
Donna, I have a theory that
I can't prove and an opposition

692
00:28:26,519 --> 00:28:28,197
that's shown they're willing
to alter evidence.

693
00:28:28,222 --> 00:28:30,937
He's not gonna change his mind,
and you know it.

694
00:28:30,961 --> 00:28:32,539
There's got to be another way.

695
00:28:32,564 --> 00:28:35,712
Donna, look, I appreciate
what you're doing,

696
00:28:35,736 --> 00:28:38,584
but unless you have this other
way in your pocket, please,

697
00:28:38,609 --> 00:28:41,457
just leave me alone
and let me try

698
00:28:41,482 --> 00:28:44,119
and think this thing through.

699
00:29:02,856 --> 00:29:04,835
No! I don't care what he says.

700
00:29:04,861 --> 00:29:06,340
It's an active
goddamn investigation,

701
00:29:06,364 --> 00:29:07,341
and I'm not gonna stand around...

702
00:29:07,366 --> 00:29:08,378
You can't talk on that here.

703
00:29:08,402 --> 00:29:09,679
Hang on a second, Charlie.

704
00:29:09,703 --> 00:29:11,783
I'm sorry, we got off
on the wrong foot.

705
00:29:11,808 --> 00:29:13,488
Is your name Danielle?

706
00:29:13,512 --> 00:29:15,224
That's what it says
on the plate, isn't it?

707
00:29:15,249 --> 00:29:17,228
Well, Danielle, I'm here
to pick up the documents

708
00:29:17,253 --> 00:29:19,415
I ordered an hour ago,
and if you don't give them to me

709
00:29:19,424 --> 00:29:20,601
in the next 15 seconds,

710
00:29:20,625 --> 00:29:22,103
today's gonna be your last day.

711
00:29:22,128 --> 00:29:23,173
You didn't talk to me.

712
00:29:23,197 --> 00:29:25,878
I said hold on, damn it.

713
00:29:25,903 --> 00:29:29,185
Look, I don't have time
to play "who spoke To who."

714
00:29:29,209 --> 00:29:31,456
I am up from DC because,
as it is, these documents

715
00:29:31,480 --> 00:29:33,125
weren't sent
when they were promised.

716
00:29:33,150 --> 00:29:34,429
I'm sorry.
What is it you need again?

717
00:29:34,453 --> 00:29:36,633
Oh, Jesus Christ.

718
00:29:36,658 --> 00:29:39,472
All the maintenance work orders
from the past six months.

719
00:29:39,496 --> 00:29:41,677
I can't let you have that
without authorization.

720
00:29:41,702 --> 00:29:43,882
Well, then by all means,
let's call your supervisor,

721
00:29:43,906 --> 00:29:46,619
and we can tell him
how you'd rather play Farmville

722
00:29:46,644 --> 00:29:48,445
than cooperate with me.

723
00:29:52,221 --> 00:29:53,800
Who did you say
you're with again?

724
00:29:53,825 --> 00:29:56,830
Have you heard of the National
Transportation Safety Board?

725
00:30:00,438 --> 00:30:02,441
They'll give you
what you need in the back.

726
00:30:19,709 --> 00:30:21,354
What did you do?

727
00:30:21,379 --> 00:30:23,291
I didn't do anything.
What did you do?

728
00:30:23,316 --> 00:30:24,317
Don't give me that.

729
00:30:24,318 --> 00:30:26,064
This makes my entire case,

730
00:30:26,089 --> 00:30:28,235
but I can't use it if
I don't know where it came from.

731
00:30:28,259 --> 00:30:30,306
Oh, that looks like
it came from Liberty Rail.

732
00:30:30,330 --> 00:30:32,844
Oh, oh, yeah,
it just happened to walk itself

733
00:30:32,868 --> 00:30:34,915
over from their secure facility.

734
00:30:34,939 --> 00:30:36,885
Well, it's possible that
somebody went over there

735
00:30:36,910 --> 00:30:38,854
and released it
from their secure facility.

736
00:30:38,879 --> 00:30:41,394
Donna, if I go to Harvey
with this and tell him

737
00:30:41,419 --> 00:30:42,630
what I know happened, he...

738
00:30:42,654 --> 00:30:44,166
You don't know. You think.

739
00:30:44,191 --> 00:30:47,105
Don't lawyer me.
He'll never let me use it.

740
00:30:47,130 --> 00:30:49,344
Well, then don't tell him
what you think happened,

741
00:30:49,368 --> 00:30:52,517
because if you do,
he'll make you drop the case.

742
00:30:52,541 --> 00:30:55,411
Okay, right now,
I don't care about the case.

743
00:30:56,783 --> 00:30:58,662
I care about you.

744
00:30:58,686 --> 00:31:02,269
Mike, I didn't steal anything.

745
00:31:02,294 --> 00:31:04,172
I talked my way in,
and that's what happened.

746
00:31:04,197 --> 00:31:05,243
Did you tell them
this was discovery

747
00:31:05,267 --> 00:31:06,268
for a case against them?

748
00:31:06,269 --> 00:31:07,245
No.

749
00:31:07,270 --> 00:31:08,548
Then it's not admissible
in court.

750
00:31:08,572 --> 00:31:10,017
Well, then you
have to figure out a way

751
00:31:10,042 --> 00:31:13,324
to use it not in court,

752
00:31:13,348 --> 00:31:14,861
but don't ask me
for my help on that.

753
00:31:14,886 --> 00:31:16,889
I have done enough.

754
00:31:28,112 --> 00:31:29,657
Hey.

755
00:31:29,682 --> 00:31:31,728
Heard you wanted to see me.

756
00:31:31,752 --> 00:31:34,199
I take it you patched things up
with Louis Litt.

757
00:31:34,223 --> 00:31:35,368
How do you know?

758
00:31:35,393 --> 00:31:37,674
Oh, he wanted to know
if you were a sports bar guy

759
00:31:37,698 --> 00:31:39,142
or a wine bar guy.

760
00:31:39,166 --> 00:31:41,180
Did you tell him I'm more
of a strip club kind of guy?

761
00:31:41,204 --> 00:31:43,484
You really want to go
to a strip club with Louis Litt?

762
00:31:43,509 --> 00:31:46,692
I don't really want to go
to a strip club with anyone,

763
00:31:46,716 --> 00:31:48,027
but I do have a meeting
in 10 minutes,

764
00:31:48,051 --> 00:31:49,052
and it's 15 minutes away.

765
00:31:49,053 --> 00:31:50,264
Oh, I just wanted to tell you

766
00:31:50,289 --> 00:31:52,704
that I appreciate you
patching things up with him.

767
00:31:52,728 --> 00:31:54,573
There's no need to thank me.

768
00:31:54,598 --> 00:31:57,603
I would do anything
for the woman that I love...

769
00:31:59,675 --> 00:32:01,678
Even get a drink
with Louis Litt.

770
00:32:13,234 --> 00:32:15,314
You here to talk
about Anderton Software?

771
00:32:15,338 --> 00:32:17,753
Because your 24-hour
Liberty Rail pass is up.

772
00:32:17,777 --> 00:32:18,855
Then I guess it's a good thing

773
00:32:18,879 --> 00:32:20,892
that just came
in the mail for me.

774
00:32:20,917 --> 00:32:21,918
What is it?

775
00:32:21,919 --> 00:32:23,097
Maintenance records showing

776
00:32:23,121 --> 00:32:24,966
they replaced the heat sensors
on all of their trains

777
00:32:24,991 --> 00:32:27,439
within six weeks
after the derailment.

778
00:32:27,463 --> 00:32:29,743
Now, why would they do that if
they never failed a safety test?

779
00:32:29,767 --> 00:32:31,012
They wouldn't.

780
00:32:31,037 --> 00:32:32,783
Which means Joe Henderson
was telling the truth.

781
00:32:32,808 --> 00:32:34,084
I can think
of three different ways

782
00:32:34,108 --> 00:32:35,487
they'll explain this away.

783
00:32:35,511 --> 00:32:39,562
Not if we can get them on record
before they know we have it.

784
00:32:39,586 --> 00:32:41,498
And why don't they know
we have it?

785
00:32:41,523 --> 00:32:42,902
The same way I didn't know
they got

786
00:32:42,927 --> 00:32:44,171
Joe Henderson's sealed records.

787
00:32:44,195 --> 00:32:45,676
Which means you did
something sketchy.

788
00:32:45,699 --> 00:32:48,313
Harvey, do you want to spend
all night asking me exactly

789
00:32:48,337 --> 00:32:49,515
what I did or did not do,

790
00:32:49,539 --> 00:32:51,909
or do you want
to help me right a wrong?

791
00:32:54,248 --> 00:32:57,598
Donna?

792
00:32:57,623 --> 00:32:59,502
Set a deposition
with Liberty Rail,

793
00:32:59,527 --> 00:33:02,609
and tell them this time
it won't just be Mike.

794
00:33:02,633 --> 00:33:04,434
I'm on it.

795
00:33:13,406 --> 00:33:15,987
Who the hell is that?

796
00:33:16,011 --> 00:33:17,555
That's the CEO of Liberty Rail.

797
00:33:17,580 --> 00:33:19,694
Yeah, I know who he is.
Who is she?

798
00:33:19,718 --> 00:33:21,364
That's their lawyer.

799
00:33:21,389 --> 00:33:23,166
Why didn't you tell me
she was hot?

800
00:33:23,190 --> 00:33:24,603
Because it's not relevant.

801
00:33:24,628 --> 00:33:26,139
- It is to me.
- Why?

802
00:33:26,163 --> 00:33:27,876
Because she's hot.

803
00:33:27,901 --> 00:33:29,981
You must be
the infamous Harvey Specter.

804
00:33:30,005 --> 00:33:32,118
- You must be...
- Evan Smith.

805
00:33:32,142 --> 00:33:33,787
Have to admit,
when I saw your name was Evan,

806
00:33:33,812 --> 00:33:35,625
I thought you were a man.

807
00:33:35,650 --> 00:33:37,194
And I have to admit,
when I saw your name was Harvey,

808
00:33:37,219 --> 00:33:38,532
I thought you were a man.

809
00:33:38,556 --> 00:33:40,535
- I think I'm in love.
- I think you are too.

810
00:33:40,560 --> 00:33:42,138
Okay, can we get this over with?

811
00:33:42,163 --> 00:33:43,675
We sure can.

812
00:33:43,699 --> 00:33:45,544
I don't even know how you
have any questions at all,

813
00:33:45,569 --> 00:33:46,647
given our last meeting.

814
00:33:46,671 --> 00:33:48,105
We just have a few.

815
00:33:52,515 --> 00:33:54,327
Mr. McIntyre,
before the derailment,

816
00:33:54,352 --> 00:33:57,368
Liberty Rail conducted tests on
the heat sensors on its trains.

817
00:33:57,392 --> 00:33:58,571
Is that correct?

818
00:33:58,595 --> 00:34:00,116
- Of course we did.
- And why was that?

819
00:34:00,131 --> 00:34:03,413
We run tests on all our systems.

820
00:34:03,437 --> 00:34:04,749
It's routine.

821
00:34:04,773 --> 00:34:06,118
And the finding of that report

822
00:34:06,143 --> 00:34:08,290
is that there were no problems
with the heat sensors.

823
00:34:08,314 --> 00:34:09,726
Are you going to just
ask questions

824
00:34:09,750 --> 00:34:10,860
that you already
know the answers to?

825
00:34:10,885 --> 00:34:12,363
It's routine.

826
00:34:12,387 --> 00:34:14,033
There weren't any problems
with the sensors.

827
00:34:14,058 --> 00:34:17,006
And do you routinely
replace the heat sensors?

828
00:34:17,031 --> 00:34:18,375
Yes.

829
00:34:18,399 --> 00:34:19,845
We replace them every five years

830
00:34:19,870 --> 00:34:21,782
as part of our regularly
scheduled maintenance.

831
00:34:21,807 --> 00:34:23,786
And when was the last
regularly scheduled maintenance?

832
00:34:23,811 --> 00:34:25,356
That would be two years ago.

833
00:34:25,380 --> 00:34:27,622
And you wouldn't fix something
that wasn't broken, right?

834
00:34:28,755 --> 00:34:30,935
Of course not.

835
00:34:30,959 --> 00:34:33,106
I'm not in the business
of wasting money, gentlemen.

836
00:34:33,130 --> 00:34:35,409
I'm a bit confused.

837
00:34:35,433 --> 00:34:37,580
If you're not in the business
of wasting money

838
00:34:37,605 --> 00:34:39,351
and there was nothing wrong
with those sensors,

839
00:34:39,375 --> 00:34:41,354
then why did you just
replace all of them?

840
00:34:41,379 --> 00:34:42,957
They didn't replace all of them.

841
00:34:42,982 --> 00:34:45,419
I think we'd like your client
to answer that question.

842
00:34:47,592 --> 00:34:49,304
You're in a bit
of a pickle, Richard.

843
00:34:49,328 --> 00:34:51,174
You don't know whether to say
you did or you didn't.

844
00:34:51,199 --> 00:34:53,010
Of course, you could roll
the dice with your own life

845
00:34:53,035 --> 00:34:54,447
just like you did
with other people's.

846
00:34:54,472 --> 00:34:56,318
The truth is, it doesn't matter,

847
00:34:56,343 --> 00:34:57,821
because you already
said on camera

848
00:34:57,845 --> 00:34:59,023
you didn't replace
those sensors.

849
00:34:59,047 --> 00:35:01,050
And we have these.

850
00:35:11,505 --> 00:35:12,684
Where'd you get these?

851
00:35:12,708 --> 00:35:14,420
I'll tell you
what I told Joe Henderson.

852
00:35:14,445 --> 00:35:16,792
It doesn't matter
where they came from.

853
00:35:16,816 --> 00:35:19,731
It just matters
that they're here.

854
00:35:19,756 --> 00:35:21,267
I need to talk to my client.

855
00:35:21,292 --> 00:35:22,738
That's a good idea.

856
00:35:22,762 --> 00:35:24,073
You should discuss
how many zeros

857
00:35:24,098 --> 00:35:25,476
you're gonna write
on that check.

858
00:35:25,500 --> 00:35:26,612
And one more thing.

859
00:35:26,636 --> 00:35:27,813
You're not only gonna
write a check.

860
00:35:27,837 --> 00:35:28,982
You're gonna
write a public admission

861
00:35:29,006 --> 00:35:31,386
because people died
in that crash.

862
00:35:31,411 --> 00:35:32,857
That's not how this works.

863
00:35:32,881 --> 00:35:38,700
It's how it works today.

864
00:35:38,725 --> 00:35:40,471
You're really gonna force
them to make a public admission?

865
00:35:40,496 --> 00:35:41,875
Damn right, I am.

866
00:35:41,900 --> 00:35:44,180
- Who are you, Mahatma Gandhi?
- Somebody has to be.

867
00:35:44,204 --> 00:35:46,150
You were too busy
demanding a bunch of zeros.

868
00:35:46,175 --> 00:35:47,653
Well, I was just
looking out for you.

869
00:35:47,677 --> 00:35:49,288
Those suits don't pay
for themselves.

870
00:35:49,313 --> 00:35:50,391
No, they don't.

871
00:35:50,415 --> 00:35:53,831
Mike, great job.
You really stepped it up.

872
00:35:53,856 --> 00:35:55,601
Thanks, Harvey.

873
00:35:55,625 --> 00:35:58,630
I think you might be starting
to come into your own too.

874
00:36:06,413 --> 00:36:07,958
Really?

875
00:36:07,983 --> 00:36:09,594
Every single game?

876
00:36:09,619 --> 00:36:12,000
No, just the playoffs.

877
00:36:12,024 --> 00:36:13,703
- Two sips?
- Two sips.

878
00:36:13,728 --> 00:36:16,209
- No more, no less.
- Any beer?

879
00:36:16,233 --> 00:36:17,878
Oh, no, not any beer.

880
00:36:17,903 --> 00:36:19,471
Miller Lite.

881
00:36:21,042 --> 00:36:23,021
Miller Lite? What?

882
00:36:23,046 --> 00:36:24,091
But she's a queen.

883
00:36:24,115 --> 00:36:26,195
What can I tell you?
She got it from her dad.

884
00:36:26,219 --> 00:36:28,131
Look, if the Giants
are in the playoffs

885
00:36:28,156 --> 00:36:29,935
and Jessica doesn't take
two sips of Miller Lite

886
00:36:29,960 --> 00:36:31,072
after every single first down,

887
00:36:31,096 --> 00:36:32,207
she thinks they're gonna lose,

888
00:36:32,231 --> 00:36:33,509
and there's no talking her
out of it.

889
00:36:33,534 --> 00:36:36,314
And those happen a lot, right?
First downs?

890
00:36:36,339 --> 00:36:37,517
They sure do.

891
00:36:37,541 --> 00:36:40,089
So what is she like
when she's drunk?

892
00:36:40,113 --> 00:36:42,126
Well, that's a conversation
for another time.

893
00:36:42,150 --> 00:36:44,163
Ooh.

894
00:36:44,187 --> 00:36:45,522
I so feel you, bro.

895
00:36:50,467 --> 00:36:52,915
You know, I got to say, Louis,

896
00:36:52,939 --> 00:36:55,852
I almost feel bad
about pulling that prank on you.

897
00:36:55,877 --> 00:36:58,758
Don't feel bad.

898
00:36:58,783 --> 00:37:00,495
It was a pretty good prank.

899
00:37:00,520 --> 00:37:04,804
Okay. One more?

900
00:37:04,828 --> 00:37:07,375
Only if you tell me more about
what Jessica's like at home.

901
00:37:07,400 --> 00:37:08,812
No, screw that,
I want you to tell me

902
00:37:08,836 --> 00:37:11,884
what she was like back
when it was Pearson Hardman.

903
00:37:11,908 --> 00:37:14,522
Done.

904
00:37:14,547 --> 00:37:15,625
- Hey.
- Hey.

905
00:37:15,649 --> 00:37:16,761
You're heading out
for the night?

906
00:37:16,785 --> 00:37:18,331
- In a few minutes.
- Want to grab a drink?

907
00:37:18,356 --> 00:37:19,467
Celebrate?

908
00:37:19,491 --> 00:37:20,970
- I can't.
- Why not?

909
00:37:20,995 --> 00:37:22,573
Not that it's
any of your concern,

910
00:37:22,597 --> 00:37:24,676
but I'm having drinks
with Evan Smith.

911
00:37:24,700 --> 00:37:26,545
What? You got her number?

912
00:37:26,570 --> 00:37:27,949
No, she called me.

913
00:37:27,974 --> 00:37:29,252
Oh, she asked for your number?

914
00:37:29,276 --> 00:37:31,790
No, she didn't have to.
You gave it to her.

915
00:37:31,815 --> 00:37:33,027
It was on that subpoena.

916
00:37:33,051 --> 00:37:34,863
I know what's gonna
be on your subpoena.

917
00:37:34,888 --> 00:37:37,168
- What does that even mean?
- You know what it means.

918
00:37:37,192 --> 00:37:38,994
Sure as hell do.

919
00:37:40,432 --> 00:37:42,244
- You wanted to see me?
- I did.

920
00:37:42,269 --> 00:37:44,315
I take it you heard
about Liberty Rail.

921
00:37:44,339 --> 00:37:45,517
- I did.
- See?

922
00:37:45,541 --> 00:37:48,890
No harm, no foul,
no mass exodus of clients.

923
00:37:48,915 --> 00:37:50,727
I'm glad.

924
00:37:50,752 --> 00:37:52,097
What's on your mind, Jessica?
You don't seem...

925
00:37:52,121 --> 00:37:54,691
I know you told Scottie
about Mike Ross.

926
00:38:02,709 --> 00:38:03,754
How'd you know?

927
00:38:03,778 --> 00:38:06,359
I didn't till just now.

928
00:38:06,383 --> 00:38:08,195
- Jessica...
- I'm not mad.

929
00:38:08,220 --> 00:38:10,867
I just want to know
what made you want to tell her.

930
00:38:10,892 --> 00:38:12,337
What difference does that make?

931
00:38:12,361 --> 00:38:14,608
Because I want to tell Jeff
the truth about Mike Ross too.

932
00:38:14,633 --> 00:38:16,279
What changed between now

933
00:38:16,303 --> 00:38:18,382
and when you fed him
that Louis bullshit?

934
00:38:18,407 --> 00:38:20,186
Nothing's changed.

935
00:38:20,210 --> 00:38:23,525
I just don't want
to lie to him anymore.

936
00:38:23,550 --> 00:38:25,687
He told you he loved you,
didn't he?

937
00:38:27,191 --> 00:38:29,829
When the hell did you start
figuring shit like that out?

938
00:38:31,132 --> 00:38:33,646
I didn't till just now.

939
00:38:33,671 --> 00:38:34,882
Then answer my question.

940
00:38:34,906 --> 00:38:36,819
What made you decide
to tell Scottie?

941
00:38:36,844 --> 00:38:39,959
That's not what
you really want to know.

942
00:38:39,983 --> 00:38:43,733
What you want to know
is if I wish I told her sooner.

943
00:38:43,758 --> 00:38:45,559
Do you?

944
00:38:47,799 --> 00:38:49,634
Yes, I do.

945
00:39:00,824 --> 00:39:02,235
Hey.

946
00:39:02,260 --> 00:39:05,476
Hey, Rachel,
what can I do for you?

947
00:39:05,500 --> 00:39:09,283
I just wanted to come by
and say thank you.

948
00:39:09,308 --> 00:39:12,056
- For what?
- Oh, come on, Donna.

949
00:39:12,081 --> 00:39:15,129
Mike told me you saved the day.

950
00:39:15,153 --> 00:39:16,631
Oh, well, you know,

951
00:39:16,655 --> 00:39:18,501
after I saved those kids
from that burning building,

952
00:39:18,526 --> 00:39:20,338
I had a little extra time, so...

953
00:39:20,363 --> 00:39:22,209
Well, then maybe you should
take the rest of the night off.

954
00:39:22,234 --> 00:39:23,444
And why is that?

955
00:39:23,468 --> 00:39:27,274
Because that's what
superheroes do.

956
00:39:30,315 --> 00:39:38,323
♪

957
00:39:52,125 --> 00:39:54,405
Macallan 18.

958
00:39:54,430 --> 00:39:56,577
You got great taste.

959
00:39:56,601 --> 00:39:57,980
Surprised I called?

960
00:39:58,004 --> 00:40:00,484
Like I said, you got great
taste, but let me be clear.

961
00:40:00,509 --> 00:40:01,687
You want to talk settlement,

962
00:40:01,711 --> 00:40:03,758
I can't do it without Mike Ross.

963
00:40:03,782 --> 00:40:05,896
I'm definitely not here
to talk settlement.

964
00:40:05,920 --> 00:40:09,869
Good, because there are things
I can do without him,

965
00:40:09,894 --> 00:40:11,696
exceptionally.

966
00:40:13,668 --> 00:40:16,283
I want to show you
a little video.

967
00:40:16,308 --> 00:40:18,487
What, did you dig up footage

968
00:40:18,511 --> 00:40:19,756
from my high school
championship?

969
00:40:19,780 --> 00:40:21,783
Because that'll make this
too easy.

970
00:40:22,886 --> 00:40:25,701
Afraid not.

971
00:40:25,726 --> 00:40:29,107
That's your secretary
unlawfully gathering evidence,

972
00:40:29,132 --> 00:40:33,139
which means there will be
no settlement of any kind.

973
00:40:39,787 --> 00:40:43,871
And tomorrow, I'm sending this
to the district attorney.

974
00:40:43,896 --> 00:40:45,975
Enjoy your drink, handsome.

975
00:40:45,999 --> 00:40:54,007
♪

976
00:41:13,687 --> 00:41:14,899
Jessica.

977
00:41:14,923 --> 00:41:17,670
Jeff, there's something
I need to tell you.

978
00:41:17,695 --> 00:41:19,731
There's something
I need to tell you too.

979
00:41:22,438 --> 00:41:23,782
What's going on?

980
00:41:23,807 --> 00:41:26,021
What's going on is
I just had drinks with Louis,

981
00:41:26,045 --> 00:41:27,824
you know, as a favor to you.

982
00:41:27,849 --> 00:41:31,465
Turns out he's not so great
at holding his liquor.

983
00:41:31,490 --> 00:41:34,338
- What did he do?
- No, he didn't do anything.

984
00:41:34,362 --> 00:41:36,675
- You did.
- I don't...

985
00:41:36,700 --> 00:41:37,911
You see, we were
actually bonding

986
00:41:37,935 --> 00:41:39,746
when I suddenly remembered
what he had done to you,

987
00:41:39,771 --> 00:41:42,086
and I...
Well, I wanted to make sure

988
00:41:42,110 --> 00:41:44,256
that no one
ever did that to you again.

989
00:41:44,281 --> 00:41:45,726
So I asked him how he found out

990
00:41:45,750 --> 00:41:47,529
about Daniel Hardman's
embezzlement,

991
00:41:47,554 --> 00:41:49,066
and he started with the words,

992
00:41:49,090 --> 00:41:51,404
"It was two years ago."

993
00:41:51,429 --> 00:41:52,773
Jeff, I can explain.

994
00:41:52,797 --> 00:41:54,043
You can always explain,

995
00:41:54,067 --> 00:41:56,248
but that just means
your whole story

996
00:41:56,273 --> 00:41:59,254
about how Louis got his name
on the door is bullshit.

997
00:41:59,278 --> 00:42:00,891
And I came here
to tell you the truth.

998
00:42:00,915 --> 00:42:02,493
More bullshit!

999
00:42:02,518 --> 00:42:03,996
Then let me tell you now.

1000
00:42:04,020 --> 00:42:05,332
Don't you get it?
We're past that now.

1001
00:42:05,357 --> 00:42:06,902
- I don't want to know!
- Jeff...

1002
00:42:06,926 --> 00:42:08,938
In fact, I never really
wanted to know, I just...

1003
00:42:08,962 --> 00:42:10,975
I just wanted you to tell me.

1004
00:42:11,000 --> 00:42:12,812
But now, no matter
what you tell me,

1005
00:42:12,836 --> 00:42:15,317
I won't ever believe
it's the truth.

1006
00:42:15,342 --> 00:42:16,654
Jeff, let me in.

1007
00:42:16,678 --> 00:42:17,856
It's over, Jessica.

1008
00:42:17,880 --> 00:42:19,883
It's done.

1009
00:42:25,629 --> 00:42:27,632
We're done.

1010
00:42:30,429 --> 00:42:36,935
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man

