Previously on
Suits...
It's going up
on the wall tomorrow...
And this is your way
of getting me on your side.
I don't want you
on my side.
I want us to be
on the same side.
I get
Ava Hessington acquitted.
Darby backs me
for managing partner.
I'm here to tell you
I don't want it anymore.
Get out of my sight.
Let me spell it out
for you, okay?
You don't work my case
without me.
And since you seem to be
having trouble
understanding that,
you don't work my case at all.
You and Stephen.
It bothers me.
I didn't know
you're a cat man.
Do I have brains
in my head?
Do I have a heart
in my chest?
Who is this stunning creature?
Mikado.
The Hong Kong office
urgently requires me
for a few weeks.
I'm sure there is a suitable
luxury feline hotel.
- Don't play games, okay?
- So you'll do it?
Nyes.
Can I have her?
What do you want, Stephen?
I heard Cameron
got a witness.
He did?
What do you want?
I'm just checking to see
if there's anything
I can do to help.
- There isn't.
- No way.
If you didn't have
Mariga yesterday,
you don't have him today.
Why don't you ask your friend
Stephen Huntley?
He's the one who led me
right to him.
You know, you might just be
the perfect man.
You're just coming
to realize that now?
Mmhmm.
Donna.
I need a minute alone
with Stephen.
Is it just a minute?
Or do I need to get a cab?
It won't take long.
But the rest is up to you.
Well, I'm guessing you're not
here to join us for dessert.
You called Colonel Mariga.
Yeah.
I called him.
Called him to find out what
Cameron Dennis had offered him
and to suggest
that he could do better.
You mean you called him
to offer him a bribe.
Doesn't matter.
Dennis was bluffing.
He never had him
in the first place.
He didn't
but he does now
because of you.
You're saying
he traced my call?
You're damn right I am.
And you're angry with me?
You're supposed to be
looking out for Ava.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd think
that you were working
for Cameron Dennis.
And by the way,
the man is in hiding.
His own country can't find him.
How the hell did you?
Same way you would.
You know people here.
I know people everywhere.
Well, calling those people
just screwed us.
I called them, Harvey,
because you were doing nothing.
I was doing nothing
because he had nothing.
And then I had the tape
thrown out
and he had less than nothing.
Then he threw a hail Mary
and you just caught it.
If he found Mariga
by tapping my phones,
the judge
will throw him out.
You think we're gonna be able
to prove
that that's how
he found him?
You wanna carry on
yelling at me?
Or should we fix this?
You know, I have had
about enough
of your fixer crap, okay?
You didn't fix shit.
You broke it wide open.
Then what the hell
are you doing here?
I'm here to tell you
that if I hear your name
around my case again,
I am gonna beat the shit
outta you.
You told him you were gonna
beat the shit out of him?
Yeah, and that's
the last time
I'm gonna tell him anything.
What?
You think I wouldn't
do it?
No, I'm not sure
you could do it.
What's he going
to hit me with, his ascot?
Harvey, the man plays rugby.
That's no joke.
How do you even
know that?
It's on the Darby
international website.
I don't give you
enough work.
And I'm gonna change that
right now.
Cameron's not denying us access
to Mariga,
which means he's gonna sing
any song Cameron wants
to avoid a firing squad--
So I need to find anything
I can
to take Mariga apart.
What the hell is this?
I'll tell you what it is.
It's a witness list
from Cameron Dennis
with Colonel Mariga on it.
And he's giving us access,
which means he's not bluffing.
I know.
You told me
he didn't have him.
He didn't.
Then how the hell
did he get him?
Stephen.
He was trying to fix it.
Are you telling me
you let Stephen Huntley
lead Cameron directly
to the star witness?
I didn't let Stephen
do shit.
He did it on his own.
He's your guy.
You aligned with him.
I did not.
Okay, he's Edward Darby's guy.
You made a deal
with Darby.
That makes him your guy.
You really wanna do this
right now?
Are you telling me
he doesn't know?
You know I know.
You and I had
this conversation once.
And you know
where my loyalties lie.
And as for your point,
Stephen is only here at all
because you made a deal
with Darby in the first place.
And I told you,
I don't want mine anymore.
Then I guess
I'm still in charge.
And since I've now been drafted
onto this case,
no one tells Edward Darby
or Stephen Huntley
a goddamn thing.
Does anyone in this room
have a problem with that?
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ Suits 3x07 ♪
She's Mine
Original Air Date on August 27, 2013
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ the greenback boogie
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
What'd you get me?
This isn't the first time
Mariga lied
to get out of prosecution.
Other murders?
Murder. Extortion.
Embezzlement.
You want someone
to commit a crime
and blame it on someone else,
he's your guy.
You got the questions
lined up?
Right here.
But I think you know
what my biggest question is.
What do you want me
to say?
I changed my mind about Darby.
I told Jessica.
And I didn't get a chance
to tell you
because we had bigger fish
to fry.
I understand why you didn't
get a chance to tell me.
What I don't get is
why you told her.
If I can't trust her
to get over it after I tell her,
I might as well have stuck
with Darby in the first place.
Doesn't look like
she's over it.
Because she knows
what we know.
Right now,
we got bigger fish to fry.
Are you kidding me?
Norma?
I've told you a million
goddamn times.
2% of Mikado's afternoon milk.
She's gonna taste
the extra skim.
And who do you think
she's gonna take it out on?
Me.
Oh, and find out
what the holdup is
on my trademark claim
on "Litt Up."
Nigel, you're back a week early.
I was gonna holiday
an extra week.
But I was rejuvenated
after only two days
in the native clays
at Guangzhou.
You're glowing.
And I can't wait
to see Mikado.
The lovely lass is here,
I see.
Uh, no, she's not here.
Then who's that for?
That's for me.
It's my afternoon milk.
Hits the spot.
Gotta run.
Louis.
Where is she?
At the best cat spa
in the city,
getting her nails buffed
and her paws polished.
You spoil her.
- She spoils me.
- Call me when she's back.
I will.
Rachel, Louis.
Code Red.
Did anybody see you
leave my office?
- Norma gave me a look.
- She's on our side.
Rachel, concentrate.
I don't even know
if I'm on your side.
This isn't right.
She wants to be my cat.
No.
You want her to be your cat.
You don't understand.
This past week has been the best
week of my life, ever since--
Bruno, I understand.
But you can't keep Mikado.
She's Nigel's cat.
- Well said.
- Ah, Nigel, how did you--
By doing what any
self-respecting cat owner
would do:
Equipping her with an RFID.
A radio-frequency-identifier
integrated circuit.
Why would you hide
my prize possession?
Is that what she is to you?
A possession?
What she is to me
is between me and her.
You're right.
He's right.
I'm sorry.
I'm not ready.
Louis.
He was supposed to be gone
for two weeks.
We had a verbal contract I would
have custody for two weeks.
It was
a baby-sitting arrangement.
One that I was
mentally, emotionally,
and physically prepared for.
And accordingly,
I am legally entitled
to Mikado
for one more week.
That is not the law.
There's actually precedent.
Warminsky v. Mitchell, 1974.
I have a meeting,
after which I will collect
what is rightfully mine.
- That was genius.
- No, Louis.
That was a stall
because the truth is
Nigel's right.
She's not your cat.
You've gotta let her go.
Hey, do you wanna talk
about last night?
No, Donna, I don't.
Harvey, you said my being
with Stephen bothered you.
And I just wanna
make sure that--
That what he did deserved
interrupting your date?
- Did it?
- I don't know, Donna.
You tell me.
I mean, we had this entire case
locked up.
I mean, your boyfriend
gave Cameron
a Get-Out-Of-Jail-Free card
after I told him to stay
the hell out of it.
What'd he do?
He tracked down Mariga
and led Cameron
right to him.
- Harvey, I'm--
- You know what?
Instead of discussing Stephen
shit-ing the bed,
right now,
I have to try to clean it up.
Gwambaa.
Makaiwa.
Port Eefa.
40 people killed.
Are you here to answer
questions or ask them?
Are you familiar
with these photos?
I'm responsible
for these photos.
You seem proud of yourself.
I am a military man
in a violent country.
I do what needs to be done.
That doesn't make me
a murderer.
Because you kill people
under orders
from your government.
Precisely.
Isn't that exactly
what you did
on Hessington Oil's land?
No, I killed those people
because I was paid
by your client.
Well, that does make you
a murderer.
And you're only saying
that Ava knew about it
because your precious government
is no longer in power
to protect you.
That is not true.
And what exactly is
the penalty
if you're found guilty of murder
in your country?
Death.
And why is it you haven't
been sent back there?
I'll take this one.
He cut a deal with me.
Because I care more about
the person who ordered this
than the person
who carried it out.
There's only one problem.
He only met with Ava once.
And your only proof
of that meeting is inadmissible.
Wrong.
He didn't only talk
to Ava once.
I told your client
about what needed to be done
when we spoke
on the phone.
Ah.
Ms. Hessington didn't tell you
about that.
She didn't tell us about that
because that never happened.
What'd you expect her
to do?
Come to you
and say "I did it?"
A record of the call
from Ava's private, secure line.
A call in which we discussed
the impediments
to the pipeline,
the six leaders
who stood in its way,
and the cost
for their removal.
$3 million,
which she admitted paying
in the admission
you had her sign.
I don't need the tape because
I have everything I need,
including the fact that she lied
about that phone call.
Hey.
What happened to you
last night?
I think you know
what happened.
I saw you two yelling
at each other
and I didn't want any part
of it.
Well, believe me, I didn't
want any part of it either.
Well, what did you think
he was gonna do
when he found out
you screwed up his case?
I think you know that I wasn't
trying to screw it up.
But you did.
And he specifically told you
to stay away.
And you told me not
to discuss you with him.
So why are you discussing him
with me?
Because I have a relationship
with him
that's a lot longer
than a few weeks.
And when you mess with him,
you mess with me.
Donna, I wasn't trying
to mess with him.
I was trying to help him.
And as long as we're on
the subject,
I'm sure he mentioned if
it wasn't for my previous help,
he wouldn't still have Ava
as a client.
You know, he might've
mentioned something about that.
Then can we get back
to not discussing him?
As long as you promise
not to do anything
to make us not discuss him
ever again.
I promise.
Good boy.
I'm gonna ask you once.
Is he telling
the truth?
Yes.
We had a conversation
on the phone
but not about murder.
You didn't think we needed
to know?
I didn't remember.
That lie won't play well
in court.
I told you about
the meeting.
I didn't think to tell you
about the call
where we agreed to meet.
That's all it was.
When? Where?
How much money?
Not even that.
That was settled beforehand.
It was a formality
Nick arranged.
Nick Howell?
Your former protege?
He dealt with these people.
He knew what's expected.
It was a social nicety
so insignificant,
I didn't remember
until you brought it up.
They brought it up.
And now, they're gonna point out
that you didn't.
I understand
it looks bad.
But Edward said that this man
is a murderer.
And there's no need for me
to be concerned--
Edward Darby says
a lot of things
you want to believe
but shouldn't.
You don't believe me.
Hiding a conversation
and then coming clean
about it later
tends to get in the way
of trust.
- Jessica--
- It makes you disingenuous.
It makes you look guilty.
I'm not.
Do you find that people
usually kill your enemies
for you without your asking?
- Jessica.
- Ava, you'll have to excuse us.
We have to come up
with another plan
because the one we had
just went to shit.
I can't help but notice
you've come empty-handed.
Not exactly.
You're suing me for ownership
of Mikado.
On what grounds?
On the grounds that I provide
a better home
because you're constantly flying
around the world.
Mary Poppins doesn't
get custody
of the children
in her care.
The Von Trapp children
fell in love with Maria.
She became their mother.
Because their mother was dead.
There's no legal basis
for this.
You're confident
in that fact?
Most assuredly.
Then let's put it
to our own jury.
You're suggesting
a mock trial.
You get to prove you're
the better man
in front
of our associates.
You agree to hand her back
the moment the verdict is in?
I agree to let you say
good-bye to her
the moment
that you're defeated.
Whatever the hell
that means.
Glad to see you haven't lost
your touch with the clients.
I don't have to be
nice to her.
I just have to clean up
after her bullshit.
She didn't lie.
She just made a mistake.
We still have
to clean it up.
And she just handed us
a road map.
You wanna go after
Nick Howell.
He's reasonable doubt
staring us right in the face.
It's a bad idea.
He admitted to the bribe,
he set up the call,
and he was her man
on the ground.
Laying it on Nick
would be admitting
Hessington Oil paid Mariga
to kill those people.
We already admitted
that Ava paid him.
And Mariga already admitted
to the murders.
This is exactly why
we should stick to the plan
to destroy Mariga's testimony.
Not wanting to be shot
is a hell of an incentive
to lie.
And an easy thing for a jury
to understand.
Let me spell this out
for you.
You don't just show
that your client didn't do it
when you can point to someone
who did.
But you're never gonna
convince a jury
the number one didn't know
what the number two was up to.
You have the balls
to say that to me?
I'm not saying--
I don't care
what you're saying.
I'm the one in charge
of this case.
And believe me,
I can convince anyone
of the fact
that a number two
can betray a number one
behind her back.
Out.
- You still hiding from Nigel?
- What?
No, I'm looking
for Katrina.
She just left
for Barcelona.
Sorry? She what?
The training program.
- Nesbitt.
- Why would he send her away?
Because he knew I'd pick her
to represent me
at Mikado's custody hearing.
You're suing for custody?
Louis, that's insane.
- Rachel, he abandoned her.
- He went on a business trip.
- Okay, whose side are you on?
- Yours.
But the law is not
with you.
What, you think
when you become a lawyer,
you're gonna be
trying cases
where the law
is always on your side?
- Louis.
- Rachel.
You need to tell me
which associate
is least loyal
to Nigel now.
- Kaufman.
- No, too green.
Corcoran.
The guy owned a hamster
as a child.
He'll view a cat
as a predator.
- Donahue?
- D-D-D-D-D-Donahue?
I'll not only lose custody,
I may end up in jail.
- For what?
- Rachel, I stole the man's cat.
And I need someone
who understands why.
Then who, Louis?
You.
- I'm not a lawyer, Louis.
- You're gonna be soon enough.
You run circles around
those clowns.
And Nigel holds no sway
over you.
Okay.
You are asking me to help you
steal Nigel's cat.
Rachel, you know how tough
it's been for me this year.
I lost the associates.
Mike made a fool of me.
I saw Harvey's name go up
on the wall.
And I went home.
But you know
what happened?
Mikado saw my pain.
And she brought me
a mouse.
Louis, we have a murder trial
going on.
A trial that I have nothing
to do with.
Rachel, I love her.
Now, I once fought valiantly
for your dream.
And even though I lost...
I'm asking you.
Fight for mine?
Jessica!
You have something for me
on Nick Howell?
Nick Howell
didn't do this.
Yeah, what the hell does
that have to do with anything?
Look, Harvey's problem
with going after Nick
is that it might backfire
on Ava, right?
But even if it doesn't,
we're still putting
an innocent man
in the cross hairs.
An innocent man.
He sold out Ava the second
he had a chance.
And I sat there
and watched him do it.
Cameron had him backed
against a wall.
He just did what he had
to do.
And now, we're backed up
against a wall.
And I don't give a shit
about Ava's number two.
He can rot in hell
for all I care.
I just have
one question.
Are you going after him
because he tried to sell Ava out
or because Harvey
tried to sell you out?
What did you just say
to me?
I just wanna make sure
we're not potentially
throwing a man's
life away
just because you're mad
at someone else.
Instead of you coming
down here
and telling me
who to be mad at,
why don't you do
your job?
And find out what the hell
Cameron has on Nick Howell
that had him turn on Ava
in the first place
because if you think all it was
was that tape,
then you don't know
what the hell you're doing.
They wanna talk settlement
and they sent you?
No, they didn't.
So you're going rogue?
Bullshit.
I don't buy it--
You can buy whatever you want.
The fact is you, Harvey,
and Jessica
are so busy trying
to beat each other,
you can't see you all have
your heads up your asses.
Cocky, I get it.
Harvey taught you well.
No, what Harvey taught me
is to help my client.
Now, look.
I can't guarantee you
that we'll agree to anything.
But Ava deserves
an offer.
I spelled out my offer
a week ago.
Yeah, an offer based on
a bluff.
Huh, now,
I've got the real deal.
It was 9.
Now, it's 12.
Your real deal is
a confessed murderer
and a vindictive ex-employee.
I've got one saying
that Ava paid for it.
And another saying she knew
what she was paying for.
Great, then get me
a goddamn offer under nine,
and I'll get you
a deal.
This negotiation
is over, Junior.
Take your ball
and go home.
You really are a dick.
- What did you say?
- I said you're a dick.
And you can take your offer
and shove it up your ass.
I am so sorry.
You little piss ant.
I can't believe
this shit.
Who the hell do you think
you're dealing with?
You know, I could have
you locked up
for assault right now?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
You know, I just--
I lost my head.
Please.
I-I was just trying
to do my job.
Take your mediation and get
the hell out of my office.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Litt,
how would you describe
Mikado's well-being
when she came under your care?
Well, Mikado's physical needs
were taken care of.
But there's more to a cat
than its physical condition.
They're highly
emotional creatures.
And were her emotional needs
tended to?
Calls for speculation.
He's not the cat whisperer.
He can't testify
to Mikado's thoughts,
which you should've
objected to.
- Sorry, sir.
- Very well.
Mr. Litt,
without speaking for Mikado,
would you describe
for the court
her emotional condition?
When Mikado first entered
my home,
she was aloof
and standoffish.
She's a cat.
Sorry.
I'll wait my turn.
She was listless,
you know?
Like, I would take her out
to see a bird
or a dog.
And there'd just
be nothing.
You know what I think?
Hm?
I think that she was
the victim of neglect
due to the absence
of a consistent father figure
because he's traveling
all the time.
- I object.
- To what?
To you letting him talk
about my cat that way.
You changed the rules
to get Ms. Zane.
I'm changing the rules.
I'm gonna represent myself.
- But--
- You're dismissed.
Getting hot in here, Nesbitt?
Mr. Litt, I'll ask you
not to address
the defendant directly.
I'm not the defendant.
This isn't
a criminal trial.
Well, it should be.
Where were we?
You were describing
the deplorable condition
in which you found
Mr. Nesbitt's cat.
Oh, yeah.
Jessica, I've been expecting
your call.
You aren't expecting
this call.
It was pointed out
to me
that I had misplaced
some of my anger.
So I've decided to place
some of it on you.
Then this is the call
I was expecting.
You've heard about Stephen?
I heard about you.
And your deal
with Harvey.
I was wondering
when you'd find out.
Save it.
I thought when I got rid
of Daniel Hardman,
I was done with partners
I couldn't trust.
I assume you're referring
to Harvey
because I'm not the one
who proposed that deal.
Him asking isn't the same
as you accepting.
No, it isn't,
but he was going to quit
because of you.
And that deal
made him stay.
And as you said yourself,
he is essential to the firm.
Not more essential
than me.
And as for your deal
with Harvey,
it doesn't exist because
he doesn't want it anymore.
Which was my hope
from the beginning.
You are a saint,
aren't you?
I'm not sure
I fully understand
the purpose of this call.
I want
Stephen Huntley gone.
I won't allow him to do
any more damage.
When you have a problem,
you turn to Harvey.
Stephen fills that role
for me.
You want him gone?
Win the case.
He'll be on the next
flight out.
Edward, Harvey and I
are going to win this case.
And then you and I are going
to have a conversation
about the future
of this merger.
Ah, now I understand.
What?
By telling you about my part
in his deal,
he's turned you
against the very merger
he never wanted
in the first place.
Harvey had nothing to do
with this.
Hadn't he?
Goodbye, Edward.
You have portrayed yourself
as the kindhearted savior
of this feline soul.
Is that correct?
Yeah.
I believe I've brought out
the best in her.
So you have a way
with your charges?
A velvet glove,
so to speak?
I guess you could say
I'm built that way.
So you're a good parent?
Um, a role model?
No one could
say otherwise.
So if one of your charges
were to say you were hostile,
cruel, prone to kicking
the proverbial dog,
would that be a lie?
My treatment of felines is
what's of issue here.
I thought it was
your parenting skills,
your ability to mold
and shape gently.
But that's not--
This jury knows all about
your parenting skills,
which involve
berating, belittling,
screaming, sadism--
Objection!
You can object
all you like.
But as I said,
this jury knows
that that man is not
what he portrays himself to be.
And what about you?
You think molding and shaping
is accomplished
by abandoning your charges
and sending
the occasional memo
while you're off mudding
in the Yangtze?
I'd like to call
my next witness.
Oh, really?
What witness?
You didn't declare
a witness.
He's a hostile witness.
And I'm afraid he's hostile
to you.
I call Harold Gunderson
to the stand.
Holy shit.
We're in trouble.
We need
a ten-minute recess.
Ah, uh, no, no, Rachel,
I'm sorry,
but I can't talk
right now.
I am typing up Cameron's files
from memory.
Mike, I am going to lose
my first case...
- Uh-huh.
- A mock case...
- Okay.
- About a cat.
Okay, that,
I have a couple of minutes for.
Nigel dug up Harold.
What? He's gonna throw Louis
under the bus.
Which is why I need
your help.
I need you to remember
anything good he said
about Louis.
- I can't.
- What are you talking about?
You were just referring
to your amazing memory.
No, it's not
that I can't remember it.
It's that he never said
anything good.
Oh, my God.
I'm screwed.
I'm so sorry, Rachel,
but I have to go.
What> Are you kidding?
You've got--you've got nothing?
What I have is complete faith
in you.
So say hi to Harold
for me
before you figure out a way
to screw him.
Huh.
Jessica was right.
There's dirt on Nick.
Where'd you get this?
It's courtesy
of Cameron Dennis.
I actually went in there--
Holy shit.
I know, there's enough there
to point the finger at him.
There's enough here to make me
think that he really did it.
So what do
you wanna do?
Go tell Jessica
she was right
and then get Nick Howell
in here.
And make sure he doesn't have
an answer for this
before we get to court.
On it.
Mr. Gunderson,
you are currently
an associate at Bratton Gould.
At what firm
did you previously work?
I worked here.
And who was
your supervisor?
That man, Louis Litt.
Really, Harold?
Let the record show
that Mr. Gunderson
indicated Mr. Litt.
Tell me about
Mr. Litt's guidance.
Louis believes
in teaching by fear.
Your Honor, I'd just like
to state for the record
that the witness is speaking
into an imaginary microphone.
You're speaking into
an imaginary microphone.
- That's what I mean.
- You know what?
Fine, I'm done.
Proceed.
Would you characterize him
as a-a screamer?
A tyrant?
Petty and vindictive?
All of the above.
He didn't try to gently sculpt
your future like blown glass?
He called me an idiot,
an imbecile,
and an embarrassment
to the legal profession.
That sounds harsh.
My therapist says
that I have scars on my psyche.
- Hearsay.
- I could call said therapist.
Oh, that'd be lovely,
except it still has nothing
to do with the cat.
Uh, bear with me.
I'm getting there.
Uh, tell me about Bruno.
He was Louis' cat.
I was made to take care
of him.
- He didn't do it himself?
- No.
Do you like cats, Harold?
No.
I'm allergic.
I don't even know
what to do with them.
But he left this cat,
his cat,
in your care?
What happened?
Hey, you know what?
This would be a good time
to object.
I can't, Louis, it's a valid
line of questioning.
What happened,
Mr. Gunderson?
He died a day later.
And what did he say to you
prior to that day?
He said he might as well
have left his cat
with Michael Vick.
I didn't realize
she'd be here.
Didn't want to look me
in the eye?
Ava, I'm sorry.
I'm glad I can help you
as a character witness.
I had no idea admitting
to the bribe
would lead
to this nonsense.
Solicitation of murder
is nonsense?
You know what I meant,
that Ava would never do that.
Oh, we agree.
We don't think she would.
We think you would.
What? You're trying
to blame the murders on me?
You met with Mariga
before Ava did.
You made the arrangements.
You agreed on the payments.
You know all this.
But we didn't
know this.
Mr. Howell is being shown
a record of deposits
into a numbered
Swiss bank account
opened one week
after the murders.
- How did you get this?
- Are you saying it's not yours?
It's not what it seems.
Then tell us
what it is
because what it looks like
is a split of the take.
How much did Mariga
cut you in for?
- These are bonuses.
- Bonuses?
Part of my deal,
incentive payments
for getting the job done
under hardship conditions.
The only hardship you had
was finding someone
to kill those people.
You split the take with Mariga
then hid your share.
This money didn't come
from Colonel Mariga.
It came from Hessington Oil
and she knows it.
You can't keep pointing
the finger at Ava.
You acted alone on this.
I have emails
asking for her authorization
to make bonus payments.
Those emails didn't mention
Swiss bank accounts.
Because I knew you wouldn't
want them to.
Bullshit.
It didn't mention
Swiss bank accounts
because you went to Mariga
and arranged everything.
I didn't even
know Mariga.
He came to me.
He laid out a bribe.
I accepted it.
And Ava knew everything I did.
- That's a lie.
- She knew.
She just didn't know
the specifics.
And now, you're acting
like this means
that I ordered the killing
of those people.
Well, I didn't.
And if you try to make it look
like I did
without her knowledge,
no jury's ever going
to believe it
because it's not true.
Mr. Gunderson,
your tenure at this law firm
wasn't very successful,
was it?
I worked very hard.
Is it true that you once
failed to deliver
a motion to the court
because you thought
they were closed
due to inclement weather?
Someone told me
that it was a snow day.
Did you ever give
opposing counsel
a copy
of our trial strategy?
I thought it was part
of disclosure.
Did you leave a zero off
the Hopkins settlement,
nearly costing
the client $900,000?
No one was supposed to know
about that.
Because Louis covered
for you.
- He berated me.
- No.
He kept it private.
And he allowed you to go back
and fix it.
Did he not?
He did.
Which allowed you to learn
from your mistakes.
Did it not?
I guess.
You testified that you now
work at Bratton Gould.
Is that correct?
Yes.
And when
they hired you,
did they know you'd been trained
by Louis Litt?
It came up.
So they knew
that you were nurtured by Louis.
They hired you.
And now,
are you happy?
Yes.
So with Louis' nurturance,
your mistakes were covered,
you landed another job,
and you're happy.
Isn't that correct?
But he was mean
to me.
No, this isn't about how
he treated you, Harold.
This is about how he treated
his cat.
And isn't the truth
that he loved that cat
and cared for him
with all of his heart?
Harold, you're under oath.
No, I'm not.
Harold.
Yes, he loved Bruno
with all of his heart.
I have
no further questions.
Hey.
What a lovely surprise.
And I come bearing gifts.
Oh, you didn't have
to do that.
Oh, well,
it's only right.
You've given me
so many things.
And I've never
given you anything.
Well, anything like this.
What is it?
I'm surprised
you don't recognize it.
It's a copy
of Colonel Mariga's deposition.
My copy count didn't reconcile
with the machine.
It was off
by seven pages,
the exact amount of that.
You thought
I wouldn't notice.
I would.
- You spied on me.
- Oh, no.
I trusted you.
- Donna...
- Don't Donna me.
You looked me in the face
and you made me a promise.
I also made a promise
to Edward Darby.
And I made a promise
to Harvey.
And I wouldn't make
another one
if I knew I could only
keep one.
So you're choosing
what you don't have with him
over something that you do have
with me?
This has nothing to do
with him.
I don't care if you said
you'd stay out
of Norma's business
and you went back on it.
You lied to me.
We're done.
Oh.
And by the way,
you're welcome.
For what?
For not telling Harvey
about this.
Because if he found out,
he would beat the shit
outta you.
Watch what you're doing.
I wasn't actually moving.
Yeah, well,
I don't actually care.
- Donna, are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Hey, Donna.
I don't wanna talk
about it, okay?
You'll tell Harvey.
He'll get furious--
I won't tell Harvey.
Yeah, another promise.
Donna.
He just couldn't keep his nose
out of it.
Who couldn't keep his nose
out of what?
Stephen got
Mariga's deposition.
You know what?
It doesn't matter.
I'm done with him anyway.
I'm so sorry.
Rachel that was amazing.
- Thank you, Louis.
- We're gonna win.
You did win.
Don't worry.
I'm not going to take your cat.
I am a man of honor.
Well, that's very gracious
of you.
In fact, I'm glad
we had this trial
because you and I both know
you didn't win
on the merits
of the case.
You won because
the associates prefer
your tough love
to my light touch.
- Yeah, they do.
- But Mikado belongs with me.
And this trial showed me
there's something
you care about
more than her.
- Nothing.
- Yes.
The associates.
I'm offering you
a settlement.
No.
You get back
the associates.
I get back my cat.
No.
II need a moment to confer
with my client.
Of course.
I do love her, you know?
Louis, as your attorney,
I need to say this...
Please don't
make me choose.
She's Nigel's cat.
You were right.
No one's ever going
to believe
that Ava didn't know
what her number two was up to.
It was worth trying.
It was worth trying
because she really didn't know.
And no one's ever going
to believe it
because she should've known.
Jessica, Ava and Nick
are not the same as you and me.
I know.
They're not.
She didn't wanna know what was
happening under her nose.
I do.
And the only reason
why I didn't see it
this time
is because I never thought
you'd do that to me.
- I didn't do it to you.
- You put it in motion.
And then I stopped it.
And then I told you about it.
What I wanna know
is why.
You coulda just
let it go,
never said a word.
I told you
because enough was enough
and I didn't want anymore
secrets between us.
No, when you cheat on someone
and tell them about it,
it's not to make them
feel better.
It's to make yourself
Yeah, unless you think
there's a chance
that they're gonna
find out.
Or you think
telling them
is going to make them
wanna get out of their merger.
I guess we've stopped
with the cheating analogy.
Yes, we have.
Now, did you come clean
to heal our relationship
or to make me want out
of the merger?
Like I just
told you,
I did it because I didn't want
to keep anymore secrets.
But I have never kept it
a secret
that I want out
of this merger.
You didn't answer
the question.
Okay, if you're asking
if I knew
that coming clean about Darby
would make you furious with him,
I'd be lying
if I didn't say
it crossed my mind.
So you set me up.
No, all I did
is what you've taught me to do
for a long time.
And it didn't change
your mind.
It just put you in touch
with what you already felt.
You really could be
managing partner.
But I'm not.
And I don't
wanna be.
So...
What are we gonna do
about this trial?
As much as Mikado
means to you,
I know the associates
mean more.
No, not more.
The needs of the many outweigh
the needs of one.
- What philosopher said that?
- Spock.
The Wrath of Khan?
I will take her back
to Nigel for you.
Well, thanks for doing this
for me, Rachel.
But I want to do something
for you first,
a reward of sorts
for your victory.
See, I was right to pick you
to be my lawyer.
And as it turns out,
Columbia Law School agrees.
Louis, what--
I saw it on mail cart
this morning.
I wanted to save it
for you.
Congratulations, Rachel.
You're gonna be a lawyer.
A real lawyer.
- Donna, where's Harvey?
- He's with Jessica.
Where?
They're not in her office.
- They're on the roof.
- Okay.
Get them down here
right now.
- Mike, what's wrong?
- I said now.
Mike.
What's wrong?
I know why Stephen needed
to know
what Mariga said
in his deposition.
Why?
He was afraid that Mariga
would tell the truth.
Stephen was the one
who ordered those killings.
Emmanuel Mariga
20 years ago
at the University of Cape Town
as an Econ major.
Always had a head
for business.
He was also
on the rugby team.
You know who else played rugby?
Stephen Huntley.
Stephen's record
from Cambridge included
a semester abroad
at the University of Cape Town.
That year's team.
They had
a hell of a season.
They're still
a team.
Darby was clear.
Whenever he has
a problem,
Stephen's the one
he sends in to fix it.
And Ava's problem
was his problem.
So when she came to him
to get her pipeline built--
He went to Stephen.
And you wanna know
what it took
to set up
those murders?
One phone call
to Mariga,
from the offices
of Darby International,
from Stephen Huntley's
London office.
From there, Mariga calls Nick,
Nick calls Ava,
and the whole thing is set
in motion.
They thought they were paying
for a bribe.
But they were actually paying
for murder.
And they never knew
the connection.
And when Ava's about to be
charged for murder,
Stephen shows up to make sure
we'd never find out.
I'm so sorry, harvey.
Harvey.
Harvey, what are
you gonna do?
Ah!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man