I'm looking at a bribe,
plain as day.
That's exactly
what it is.
Tony Gianopolous got a hold
of that video somehow.
I think he's trying
to take over the company.
You son of a bitch,
you leaked it.
Ava Hessington
is Hessington Oil.
- Not for long.
- Excuse me?
- This is my call.
- I'm afraid it isn't.
You'd like her to remove
herself from management?
I'm not going to stand
for losing this takeover.
Then don't,
but Ava isn't going anywhere.
I just got voted
out of my own company.
I stand by my decision,
and I'd do it again.
Don't tell me it doesn't
have to do with Darby.
You're the one who gave him
the 51% in the first place.
You can't stand
being number two.
Please tell me
you're calling me
because you've been kidnapped.
I'm not the one
who disappeared.
I told you I had a thing.
At 1:00.
It's 1:45.
And it's called
a lunch hour, Harvey.
60 whole minutes,
which my teeth deserve.
You fit the dentist in
at lunch?
He can be
surprisingly quick,
yet remarkably thorough.
Donna, Judge Atkins
is ready to hear
my motion for summary judgment,
which she won't do
if there aren't
two copies of that motion
in my hands
in ten minutes.
All right,
here's what you're gonna do.
Go to my computer
and press "print."
Pick the motions up
off the printer,
then walk over to the corner,
throw everything in the trash,
because there's already
two copies
on your desk
at this very moment.
So the trash can's
in the corner then?
Bye.
You had "a thing"?
Well...
Two things.
But who's counting?
What did he want anyway?
I thought we agreed
not to talk about work at lunch.
Yeah, we did, but we also
agreed to have lunch at lunch.
Yeah, you're right.
It's just that, uh,
I've always made it my business
knowing about things.
And you're good
at your business.
Mmm, business is good.
Ooh,
some might say booming.
Listen, we've only
got 15 minutes left,
so I'll endeavor
to be surprisingly quick.
As long as you continue
to be remarkably thorough.
Your Honor, you said
you would dismiss this case
if he couldn't
produce evidence
beyond the bribery tape.
Well, he couldn't.
We found five witnesses
that tied the man
that Ava Hessington bribed
on that tape to the murders.
And those witnesses
refused to come forward.
If we can't confront them,
then their statements
are inadmissible.
Just because
they won't come forward
doesn't mean
they don't exist.
He's right, their statements
may be inadmissible,
but I can't ignore the fact
that they were made.
Well, in that case,
we move for an expedited trial.
Ten seconds ago,
he was moving for a dismissal.
And in the ten seconds since,
public opinion of my client
has gone down even further.
She's a murderer.
How much lower can it go?
Well, you tell me.
You leaked evidence
to Tony Gianopolous
that lost her
her company.
You might leak it
to anyone.
Your Honor, we've been
down this road before.
It's called
bullshit highway.
All dragging this out does
is delay Ava Hessington
the opportunity
to vindicate herself.
It also conveniently gives me
less time to build my case.
But the case you just argued
was solid enough to go to trial.
You're letting your mini-me
make your arguments for you now?
Are you letting
your moustache--
Enough.
The trial starts
a week from Monday.
Get out.
You still haven't told
Harvey about Stephen?
I went to tell him,
but he was in a bad mood,
and then somehow
I ended up telling him
that I made some copies
for Stephen,
and he got
really pissed.
What's he gonna do
when he finds out about this?
Whoa, but I thought you said
that you two had never--
So?
So I get why he doesn't want
to share you here.
You're his everything here.
But what you're doing
with Stephen isn't here,
it's there.
Two completely different things.
Then why did you tell me
I had to tell him?
To let him know
that your there and his here
can coexist
in the same place.
I liked it better when
we talked about you and Mike.
I'm sure you did.
So are you two
going to keep--
Yes, it is some
of the best damn...
Yoga I've had
in a long time.
Well, sooner or later,
he's gonna find out,
because it is
all over your face.
Oh, please,
you're a woman.
Men are oblivious.
There's something
different about you.
What is it?
Yes, please tell the man
what it is.
Nothing, Louis.
I'm just--
been doing some yoga.
No, that's not it.
You're practically glowing.
Tell me your secret.
Ii don't think
that it's your cup of tea.
For that glow,
I'd tea.
I'm gonna have to keep this
to myself, Louis.
Okay, well, promise me
you'll keep doing
whatever it is you're doing.
I think she can do that.
No, I'm serious, Donna.
Morning, noon, and night.
Five times a day
if necessary.
I will do my best.
Mm.
- Well, we did our best.
- Our best?
Wait a minute,
you never expected this case
to get dismissed.
Then why would I ask for it?
Because she was more likely
to grant an expedited trial
after saying no
to a dismissal.
And now, Cameron's
got a shitty case to try
with no evidence and less
than two weeks to get any more.
Wait a second.
What if they didn't just have
to scramble for new evidence?
What if they had to scramble
for a whole new lawyer?
Any lawyer who got
assigned this case
with only two weeks to go
would drop the whole thing.
Unless they had
a personal beef with you,
which they wouldn't.
There's only one way
to get Cameron
thrown off this case.
Prove he colluded
with Gianopolous.
Turn bullshit highway into...
fact highway.
Fact highway?
Yeah, you know,
it's right next
to "I don't want to talk
about this anymore" lane.
We're gonna have to talk
about how to prove they colluded
because we have a chance
to get rid of this murder charge
once and for all.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ Suits 3x05 ♪
Shadow of a Doubt
Original Air Date on August 13, 2013
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ the greenback boogie
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Trina said
you wanted to see me.
Hey, Simon, come on in.
I have a question for you.
Come on, you need
to see this.
Look at this.
This is so funny.
Is that
some sort of joke?
Nominal
in the first paragraph,
pagination
on the left-hand side,
Times New Roman's
stupid little feet
walking
all across the page.
And what's that word?
- "Shall"?
- Mm.
At this firm, we instruct,
we advise, we order,
we must,
but we do not "shall."
- That's not really a--
- Why must we "must"?
Because we thrust,
we don't parry.
Rewrite this.
I can't.
Excuse me?
Mr. Nesbitt has clearly
instructed us--
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
This was Nigel's doing?
Per his most recent memo.
He's communicating
with you through memos?
You've been left adrift
on lady law's fickle ocean
with no rudder,
no captain?
He hasn't been
in the office
since he took over
the program,
if that's
what you're asking.
No, I think
I was perfectly clear
in what I was asking,
Simon.
Am I supposed
to respond to that?
Yeah, by going back
to your desk right now
and doing it correctly.
But--
Simon,
a memo from Nigel
is not gonna stick
its boot in your ass.
A memo from me will.
Get out.
I told you,
not at the office.
You mean I can't see Harvey
at the office?
'Cause that's what
I'm here to do.
- Oh.
- What?
- You know what.
You haven't told him yet.
It's none
of his business.
He and I are here,
and you and I are...there.
I wish we were there.
I just told you,
not here.
Donna, what's going on
out there?
I think he means
out here.
You have a walk-in.
What are you doing here?
What I've always
been doing here,
representing
Edward Darby's wishes.
I lost Ava her company.
I assume my deal
with Edward is dead.
Well, Edward doesn't
see it like that.
You may have failed,
but Jessica took a shot
at her own team.
And the consequences of that
are what?
Deal stays in place
as long as you win
her murder trial.
What if my plan is
to not even have a murder trial?
Well, as long
as you don't accomplish that
by having Ava plead guilty,
you'll be
the next managing partner.
Good, because I'm going
to accomplish it
by getting Cameron Dennis
thrown off this case
for colluding
with Tony Gianopolous.
And how are you
going to accomplish that?
By suing
Tony Gianopolous.
For what?
For this...
or this...
And/or that.
- Yeah, that's good.
- Mm-hmm.
- It is.
- Yeah.
- But I can do better.
- No way.
$5,000 says I can.
$10,000 says you can't.
Excellent.
What's your idea?
Well, it requires you
to take me with you
to see Mr. Gianopolous.
Mike?
- Yeah.
- You're off the case.
What? You're gonna let him
get away with that?
I have to.
I just took a bet.
There's no going back
on a bet.
Okay, what if I bet him
that my idea's better?
Then can I come?
You gonna pony up
$10,000?
Best of luck, guys.
Hope it works out.
So you're off the case?
Yeah,
thanks to Stephen Huntley.
Well, doesn't he have his hand
in a lot of cookie jars?
- What does that mean?
- Nothing.
Wait a second,
"nothing" never means nothing.
Sometimes
it means something.
Ah, do you want me
to force it out of you?
I may or may not need
plausible deniability.
- Rachel.
- Donna slept with Stephen.
Holy shit.
You cannot let her know
that you know.
- Does Harvey know?
- No, not yet.
Don't you dare tell him.
Yeah, like I'm gonna
touch that with a 10-foot pole.
But he's gonna care
that she didn't tell him.
So how are you gonna
get back on that case?
Um, I got
a different case.
Graham Stenton.
The accountant
who embezzled
$30 million from our client?
Yep.
And our job is to get
the money back, quietly.
Our job
as in Pearson Darby?
as in you and me.
I'm interviewing
his associate this afternoon,
and I need your help.
You want me to be the Mike
to your Harvey.
I do want you to be
the Mike to my Harvey.
Yeah, well,
it's not really a thing.
It can be.
- Huh.
I get to ask
half the questions.
Oh, Harvey doesn't let Mike
ask half the questions.
Fine, 1/3.
Harvey doesn't
negotiate with Mike.
Mike doesn't have sex
with Harvey.
1/3 of the questions
seems reasonable to me.
Could you possibly keep
your thwacking to yourself?
This is a private club.
With a sister club
in London.
Courtesy mudding
privileges.
And, yes,
it's Turkish.
Outside mud is a clear
violation of club policy.
There are rules,
Nigel.
Just as there are rules
forbidding interference
with my associates.
Yeah, well, you don't give
a rat's ass about them.
How dare you?
You know, let me tell you
something you may not know.
Associates,
they're like grains of sand.
They need pressure
and heat
to shape them
into Chihuly glass.
Memos from a distant land
don't shape shit into shit.
Nonsense.
I attended boarding school
from the tender age of four,
during which time
I received weekly memos
from my father.
Yeah, and look
how you turned out.
Graduating summa cum laude
from both Cambridge
and Harvard
is quite the failure.
Your parents' choice
to "homeschool," much better.
Okay, that was only
till I was ten,
and my mother's science fair
was legendary.
You must be so proud of
your uncontested blue ribbons.
Okay, you know what,
I'm not gonna let you
shatter the glass
that I spent years blowing.
And I'm certainly not gonna
let the likes of you
tell me who I can
and cannot blow.
He's not gonna come.
He will.
You pushed his assistant?
I charmed her.
You didn't.
He's right,
you didn't.
She was irritated.
But I was curious.
Works for me.
You know what they say
about curiosity.
I get it.
I come after Hessington Oil,
you come after me.
Well, bring it on, boys.
I got a team of lawyers
just itching
to take your lunch money.
Well, unfortunately, you're
not gonna be able to use them.
He's not gonna
sue you here.
He's gonna sue you
in London,
where you have
countless holdings.
Where the burden of proof
isn't on the plaintiff.
It's on the defendant.
So instead of us
having to prove you're guilty,
you'll have to prove
you're innocent.
Doesn't look
very innocent.
So you guys think
I'm gonna run scared
at the prospect of losing
a little money.
I'm a corporate raider.
This is a $50,000 bond.
You see, I'm not in
this business for the money.
Money's just
about keeping score.
I'm in this business
to win.
Well, here's the thing,
Tony.
This trial's
gonna take a while.
You'll be going
to hearing after hearing,
deposition
after deposition.
You won't be able
to enjoy your business at all.
So even if you win,
you lose.
Or?
Well, I...
I could withdraw the suit.
And all that'll cost you
is the truth,
that you colluded
with Cameron Dennis.
Ah, but I didn't
collude shit.
Yes, you did,
when you let him leak you
that video of Ava Hessington,
then tried to use it
to take over Hessington Oil.
All right,
so how do we celebrate?
Celebrate what?
Our first case
as a couple.
We should go
to that French place you like,
get a bottle of wine,
a couple of things that
I don't know how to pronounce,
and then go back
to my place and celebrate.
That's what we're calling it
these days?
Well, "victory sex"
seemed less romantic.
- Well, I can't tonight.
- Why not?
I have dinner
with my parents.
Maybe I could
come with you.
Um...Yeah, I--
Unless you don't
want me there.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, wait a minute.
You don't want me there.
Of course I do.
You don't look
like you do.
Is it because I'm white?
- That's not funny.
- Empirically it is.
No, it's not, and you're
acting like it's nothing.
Rachel, come on, look,
I know it's something,
but you're acting
like it's everything.
It is everything.
Wait a second.
Do you not want me to meet them
tonight or at all?
I don't want them
to find out your secret.
They're not
gonna find out.
- How do you know that?
- Because no one finds out.
You, Donna, Jessica,
you were all told.
Besides, I met your dad.
He didn't figure it out.
He met you as someone
that he wouldn't give
a second thought to,
Mike.
As my boyfriend,
he is going to put you
under the microscope.
- I can pass inspection.
- Well, what about me?
Because you might be experienced
at lying to the world,
but I'm not.
And it's not the world,
it's my family.
Okay, Rachel, you and I
have told each other
that we love
each other, right?
Did we mean that
or not?
If we did,
then at some point,
I am gonna have to meet
your parents.
Interview's in 20 minutes.
We should go.
Make yourself at home.
I wanted to talk to you
in here.
- Is this about your--
- No, no.
You don't even know
what I was gonna say.
How'd it go
with Gianopolous?
Well,
he's not a pushover,
but I think we have
a good plan.
- So it went well?
- Yeah, it went well.
And since when are you--
I'm sleeping with Stephen.
I can see that.
You can see that?
That's all you have
to say?
Do you want me
to say more?
It depends
on what you would say.
I'd say, "when?"
Three days ago.
Why didn't
you tell me before?
I was going to,
but you got so upset
when you thought
I was working for him.
Because you work for me.
Well, I'm not working
for him.
Good.
So you're not upset.
No.
What you're doing with him
is personal.
- And this isn't?
- Donna,
I don't wanna make this a thing.
I don't either.
I just want to make sure
that it doesn't become a thing.
It won't as long as you
don't let that affect this.
Okay.
Miss Clark, do you know
Graham Stenton well?
We've worked together
for a while.
And you handle the books
for his accounts,
is that right?
Yes, that's right.
We just need to know
when exactly you became aware
that Mr. Stenton
was manipulating the numbers.
I don't believe he was.
Well,
the auditors disagree.
Well, I disagree with them.
Graham's a good person.
I'm sure Bernie Madoff's
friends all said the same thing.
That isn't fair.
And Graham
isn't the only person
who had access
to those accounts.
Mr. Oxnard, Mr. Dipetro,
several individuals
from the controller's office.
I just have
one question for you.
How long have you
been sleeping with him?
What?
You smiled when you started
talking about him.
You called him "Graham."
You've referred to everyone else
as "mister" or "individual."
And when my colleague asked
you about sleeping with him,
you didn't seem offended,
you seemed caught.
I had nothing
to do with this.
That doesn't mean
you don't know anything.
Look, Miss Clark, we're trying
to make this go away quietly,
but if we can't, we're gonna
make it go away loudly,
which means putting you
on the stand.
Beth, you won't be able
to take the fifth
because you won't be
testifying against yourself.
And if you lie on the stand,
that's perjury.
Look, if you really
want to protect him,
just get him to give us
the money back now,
while we can still
take care of this quietly.
I can't.
That's it,
I'm calling the D.A.
I think we should give her
some time to think about it.
- I don't think so.
- Mike, it's a hard decision.
Fine.
She has until tomorrow.
Oh, what's going on?
Nothing.
Simon.
Mr. Nesbitt
gave us all gifts.
And they're funny?
I think
they're meant to be.
Well, you know,
he has trouble connecting,
but he's making an effort.
Maybe he took
my words to heart.
What'd you say to him?
Ah.
Turned out quite well.
- You crossed a line.
- I did no such thing.
You took a private feud,
and you made it public.
After you tried
to undermine my authority.
Because you don't know
what you're doing.
I knew what I was doing
when I took them from you
like biscuits
from a schoolboy.
All right,
you son of a bitch.
You better get yourself ready,
'cause I'm about to kick--
I know it's generally
against regulations,
but her nanny
fell ill, and--
No, no, no, no.
Say no more.
A father's love
knows no rule.
I didn't know
you were a cat man.
Do I have brains
in my head?
Do I have a heart
in my chest?
Who is
this stunning creature?
Her moniker
is "Mikado."
So does that mean
she enjoys--
Yes, whenever we travel,
I make sure she has
some Gilbert and Sullivan
playing in her sherpa.
Uh, do be careful,
she doesn't normally like--
My God.
What?
Oh.
Does she prefer
the left side?
She doesn't normally
let anyone touch her except me.
I happen to have a way with
those of the feline persuasion.
Do you have any cream?
You wanted to see me?
Yes.
I had some free time.
Oakwood Foods canceled
our 10:00 a.m. meeting,
as did Omni Holdings at noon
and Dunbar Securities at 4:00.
Sounds like you need
to work on your people skills.
You need to work
on your people skills.
Those meetings were canceled
because we just got fired.
And why is that
my fault?
They're not my clients.
I've never even met them.
No, but evidently,
you have met
their new owner,
Tony Gianopolous,
who bought them
for the sole purpose
of firing us.
Good.
I pissed him off.
That means it's working.
Oh, you mean
that plan of yours
you didn't think
to tell me about.
Oh, I thought about it,
and then I thought
you'd just go behind my back
and undo it.
So you went behind my back
and went to Stephen Huntley.
I told you,
I trust him.
Well,
you're the one
who likes to throw
Darby's name around.
So why don't
you and Stephen call him
and let him know that
you single-handedly lost us
more business in a day
than you've ever gotten
in a month.
And feel free
to use my phone.
Since you freed up
my afternoon,
I'm taking
the rest of the day off.
Did you see the look
on her face?
Are you kidding?
We put that look on her face.
- Ah.
- Good cop, bad cop.
- Uh, Mike, Harvey.
- So I guess it is a thing.
So we should have the money
back by this weekend,
and then,
we can celebrate.
I was thinking that we could
celebrate tonight...
After dinner
with my parents.
Do you want me to come?
That look
on Beth's face,
it didn't just say
that they slept together.
She loves him.
I told you I love you,
and I meant it.
That's not something
I want to hide from my family.
I actually made plans,
so I'm not gonna be able to--
Bad joke?
- No, terrible timing.
- Bad timing.
Okay.
I guessed.
I need your help
with Gianopolous.
Relax,
if he's making another run
at Hessington Oil,
that's not gonna happen.
- Well, how can you know that?
- Because you just restructured,
and he can't force
another takeover vote
for at least six months.
Then why is he driving
my stock into the ground?
- What?
- He's been dumping it all day.
I'll take care of it.
What did you do?
We picked a fight
with him.
We've just finished
a fight with him
that ended with me
losing control of my company,
so why in God's name
would you pick another?
To get you out of these
murder charges once and for all,
and after I do,
we'll figure out a way
to get you back in charge.
You see that you do,
because I would rather rot
in a cell
than let that man
take over my company.
So I tell her, it's not
my fault she might be early.
Man, I'm in the middle
of closing arguments.
And I tell him that if he's
not with me when she arrives,
the next case he'll try
is his own murder.
Then I walk in the room,
and she sees that I was right
outside the door the whole time.
I was not amused.
You weren't amused?
You actually didn't go
into labor for another week.
I lost that case.
Robert, you've had
enough potatoes.
She's trying to make me eat
that foodie bullshit.
Oh, I find that
hard to believe.
Made me a smoothie
this morning,
I got all excited.
It was green.
That's what healthy
looks like.
Thank you, Rachel.
- You're not alone.
- What was that?
I'm bonding
with your father here.
- Speaking of which--
- Robert.
What? You don't even know
what I'm gonna say.
I know the next six things
you're gonna say,
and you're not gonna say them,
because I told you,
Rachel doesn't want you
grilling this poor young man.
- What?
- Mom.
You're not taking it easy
on me, are you?
- A little.
- You told me to rein him in.
I also told you
not to tell him.
That's not how we do things
in this family.
I'm not keeping things
from your father.
You kept it from me
when you scratched the car.
Robert,
eat your potatoes.
What's so funny?
She's not consistent
with the potatoes.
with anything.
Okay, you're not getting
any potatoes.
Now what's so funny?
Uh, I see
where she gets it from.
Gets what?
You better shut up
and eat your potatoes.
Mmhmm.
She actually said
she'd prefer to rot in a cell?
Well, you've gotta give her
credit for that.
You do,
and she's right.
It's not making any sense.
If he's not making a run,
why is he dumping her shares?
- He's reacting.
- He's overreacting.
He may have money to burn,
but this isn't
tens of thousands,
it's tens of millions.
It's completely
out of proportion.
- Not exactly.
- What are you talking about?
I subpoenaed his daughter.
You what?
He fired our client,
so I struck back.
And you didn't think
to run that by me?
No, I didn't think
you'd say no.
I'd say no
because I'm not an idiot.
Idiot?
We need this man
to help us.
You just made him
a permanent enemy.
Me?
We did this together.
- Don't put this on me.
- You're putting it on me.
Because you
goddamn did it!
You were going to go after him
no matter what I said.
I attacked his business.
You went after his family.
Don't tell me you've never
done the same thing,
and what's the difference
between me doing it,
other than
the fact that--
ah.
I see.
This isn't about me getting
personal with Gianopolous.
This is about me
getting personal with Donna.
I'm gonna pretend
you didn't just say that.
Is that
because she's listening?
I don't give a shit
if she hears it or not.
You crossed a line
with Gianopolous,
and you just crossed
another one with me.
You know, you've had it
in for me from the start.
And you've only been
with Donna for three days,
that should tell you
something.
Let me spell it out
for you, okay?
You don't work my case
without me,
and since you seem to be having
trouble understanding that,
you don't work my case
at all.
Now get out of my office.
- So, Michael--
- Mike.
So now you're gonna tell me
what to call you?
No, I-I--it's--
people usually call me--
I'm just messing
with you.
So where are you from?
I grew up in Brooklyn.
Brothers, sisters?
Only child.
Parents still there?
They both died
when I was a kid.
Nah,
you're messing with me.
I just asked an orphan
about his dead parents
and made a joke about it,
didn't I?
Does he like apple
or blueberry?
Mom, shh, I'm trying to hear
what they're saying.
Rachel, relax,
he can handle your father.
How do you know?
Because you wouldn't have
brought him here if he couldn't.
Besides, what are you so afraid
they're gonna say?
You're right.
Nothing.
Honey, what is it?
You don't have
to tell me.
But just tell me this,
do you love him?
As long as he hasn't killed
someone, it'll all work out.
Come on.
I thought you were taking
the day off.
That was the day,
this is the night,
and my name is
still on the door.
It is.
- What do you want, Harvey?
- You were right.
We've had a lot
of disagreements lately.
Which one
are you referring to?
I'm not entirely sure
Stephen Huntley's judgment
is better than yours.
He went behind my back.
Going behind someone's back
doesn't seem like something
you have a problem with.
Maybe, but he hit Gianopolous
below the belt,
and now we have
a problem.
We have a problem?
You said your name
was still on the door.
I'm coming to you
for help.
What's our problem?
He's dumping
Hessington Oil shares
just to drive her
into the ground.
Well,
if we can come together,
maybe they
can come together.
- I'm listening.
- Tony Gianopolous
wants to own
Hessington Oil.
Ava wants to control it.
She sells him her shares,
he gives her
the voting rights.
And he gives up
Cameron Dennis.
They get what they want,
and so do we.
You think
he'll still go for it?
He'll know we're coming to him
because he won.
He won't be the problem.
Ava said she'd rather rot
than see him
take over her company.
I'll take care of Ava.
Look, it seems like
you two get along,
and I like you.
So I'm gonna
ask you this straight.
She's worked her ass off
to become a lawyer.
I know.
Well, I don't want anything
to stand in her way.
I would never do that.
So what happens
when she gets into Stanford?
You didn't know
she applied there.
Looks like you two
have something to talk about.
You're awfully
quiet this morning.
- Just tired.
- Still?
I mean, you went home
right after dinner last night.
Yeah,
trouble sleeping.
Is something wrong?
Hey, who the hell
do you think you are?
Mr. Stenton, I guess
you got our message.
Oh, I did,
and now I've got one for you.
Beth and I got married
this morning.
You married a woman
to protect yourself?
I married her
because I love her.
But you did it
to make any conversation
that the two of you had
privileged.
Says the lawyer
who threatened her.
Well, now you take this
to trial, she won't testify.
Well, it's too bad
spousal privilege
doesn't apply
to bullshit marriages.
Yeah, good luck
arguing that.
We offered the two of you
a chance to give back the money
and walk away, but
after we prove you did this--
Oh, you can't prove
I did a thing.
And now, you can't force her
to prove it for you either.
You never returned my call
last night.
Well, what could be different
about last night
than the night before?
Hmm?
Maybe the fact
that you went to Harvey
and you threw me
in his face.
Um, I was just telling it
how it was.
He's already
got it in for us anyway.
Well, that's my business
with him, not yours.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
I never wanted to make things
awkward for you and Harvey.
You made things awkward
for you and me.
- Donna--
- I like you, Stephen,
and I have enjoyed
our short-term arrangement,
but I don't enjoy
complications.
I don't either,
but it seems we have one.
Now, I'm affected by you
more than I thought,
and I'm finding I'd like
to extend our term.
I'll take your offer
under advisement.
I am not selling my shares
to that man.
I don't know you
that well, Ava,
and I won't pretend
that I do,
but we do have something
in common.
What is that?
I merged
with Edward Darby
to save my firm
from being hijacked
by my piece of shit
ex-partner.
And what exactly
does that give us in common?
I know what it's like
to prefer rotting in the ground
than letting my enemy
take what's mine.
I said,
"rotting in a cell."
I wasn't
up on murder charges.
And you'd rather
have died?
I was speaking metaphorically,
as I'm sure you were.
Was I?
You won't be able
to run your company from a cell.
My point is,
I didn't want to merge,
but I did what I had to do
to keep my company mine.
And how is that
working out for you?
It has
its ups and downs,
but I wouldn't be
standing here in front of you
if I hadn't done it.
Not exactly
a ringing endorsement.
Ava...
Do this.
Get free of your murder charges.
Nobody is saying we can't try
to get you
out of this deal later.
I don't care what it takes,
I'm not losing to that guy.
We need to find a way
around spousal privilege.
I don't see how we can.
Stupid goddamn law.
Excuse me.
It's not entirely stupid.
Oh, what, so now,
you're on his side?
No, privilege exists
for a reason.
You don't want
to have to worry
about what you trust
your partner with.
That's assuming your partner
even trusts you
in the first place.
What is that even
supposed to mean?
It means, when were you gonna
tell me you applied to Stanford?
Okay, so that's why you've
barely said three words to me
since last night.
My dad told you.
No, no, he didn't tell me,
he asked me how I felt about it
because he assumed I knew,
like I know
about all the East Coast schools
that you applied to.
- Mike--
- First you didn't want me
to meet your parents,
and now this?
Yeah, and I changed my mind
about you meeting my parents,
which I'm now
beginning to regret.
Oh, why, because I found out
you hid something from me?
Like you never
hid anything from me.
I hid something from you,
it kept us apart.
What brought us together
was me telling you everything.
- I was going to tell you.
- When?
Before I went,
on Friday.
You're going there?
I got an interview.
I'm sorry.
I just didn't know
how to tell you, mi--
- I don't know, how about,
"hey, Mike,
I might go to law school
3,000 miles away"?
I don't even know
if I'm gonna get in,
which is exactly why I didn't
want to have this conversation.
No, you didn't want to have it
because you might go there
and you're too afraid
to say it.
Okay.
I might want to go there.
I've said it.
You may enter.
I'm afraid I've got
a bit of a sticky wicket.
That sounds uncomfortable.
The Hong Kong office urgently
requires me for a few weeks.
Normally,
I'd bring Mikado, but--
Whoa, wait,
are you asking me to--
I can't get her papers
in time.
She'd be facing quarantine.
She'd sooner die.
You already
understand her so well.
I do, yet a request
of this magnitude--
No, you're probably right,
it's too much to ask.
I'm sure there is
a suitable luxury feline hotel.
Don't play games, okay?
We both know there isn't.
- So you'll do it?
- N--yes, can I have her?
Do you have a minute?
I don't really feel like
talking about us right now.
It's not about that.
Our discussion gave me an idea.
Our discussion?
Can we please not fight
about what to call our fight?
What's the idea?
We don't do good cop,
bad cop anymore.
We do bad cop, bad cop.
The way I'm feeling right now,
yeah, I can do bad cop.
Since when
do you come out here?
Since they added
Asiago cheese.
Your reward of choice
for a job well done.
You remember that story?
First story you ever told me.
You think I'd forget?
That wasn't
the point of the story.
- I assume you got Ava to agree.
- Yes, I did.
Should I be buying you
an Asiago bagel?
Poppy seed.
The "good news, bad news"
bagel.
Gianopolous agreed
to the deal.
He gave up
Cameron Dennis.
What's the bad news?
Cameron
protected himself.
He never explicitly told
Gianopolous about the tape
and never actually
showed him the tape.
So what's
the good news?
He never explicitly
said anything,
but he left Gianopolous alone
in the room with that tape.
Late night?
No sleep at all.
The ulcer?
No, Nigel's cat.
You slept at Nigel's?
No, he's out of town.
I'm cat-sitting.
Mikado won't drink her cream
unless it's precisely
5.5 degrees celsius,
she turned her nose up
at Bruno's origami collection,
and she won't use her litter box
unless it's facing London.
Hate that damn thing.
You're loving every second
with her, aren't you?
All 86,400 of them.
By the way, you don't have
that glow today, Donna.
You stop yoga?
I took
a couple nights off.
Is this
because of Harvey?
'Cause I don't care
what he says, Donna,
you can't let work
get in the way of that glow.
You know what, Louis,
you're right.
I'm gonna schedule
an extra long session tonight.
Ooh, can I come?
Harvey,
what are you doing here?
I'm here to tell you
that you lost.
I didn't lose.
I may not have much time,
but I still got--
That tape?
Not anymore,
unless you want to dispute
Tony Gianopolous'
sworn statement
that you left him alone
with it.
I can fight this.
Chain of custody
is something
I know a little bit about,
thanks to you.
That tape is gone,
and so are you.
- I'm not going anywhere.
- Admit it, Cameron, I beat you.
Save yourself the embarrassment,
and cancel this trial.
If you think
I would ever do that,
I taught you
even less than I thought.
This case was 50/50.
All you did was make it 80/20.
99 to 1.
It could be a million to one
for all I care.
We're in the ring, I'm still
standing, and this isn't done.
Now get out of my face.
I got a trial to prepare for.
- What do you want?
- This is a request
for charges to be filed
against Graham Stenton
for stealing $30 million.
The penalty for which
is 15 years in a federal prison.
If you had proof of that,
you wouldn't have
come after me
in the first place.
We have proof that you knew
something was wrong
and you didn't notify
your employer.
Which is why
this is a request for charges
to be filed against you
as an accessory after the fact.
The penalty for which is
five years in a federal prison.
But you can avoid that
by testifying against him.
Even if I was willing to,
I can't.
We're married.
He'd stop me from testifying.
In New York,
not in Connecticut.
Which is where the charges
will be filed.
You're asking me
to turn against the man I love.
Then go to jail
and trust him.
I'm guessing he's not gonna
be there when you get out.
Beth,
even if he waits for you,
he did this, and the fear
of him getting caught
is going to cast a shadow
over every moment
of the rest of your life
together.
He may not be able to see that,
but I know you can.
I'll get you
the money back.
What are you doing?
Just leaving a note.
By the way,
congratulations.
I hear you got the tape
thrown out
and Ava reinstated
as the CEO.
- In spite of you.
- Yeah, I know.
You went to Jessica
for help.
- You have a problem with that?
- No.
I just think it's ironic
that she doesn't realize
she just helped me
dig her own grave.
It's me.
Money got wired
into the account.
Congratulations.
I don't think
she would've caved
if you hadn't broken script
and gone all good cop on me.
Look, I'm sorry--
I'm sorry-
Rachel--
No, Mike.
We're in a fight
because I made the mistake
of not telling you that I was
considering going to Stanford,
but we're really
in a fight
because I'm considering
going to Stanford.
What you said to Beth,
was that really about me?
- Mike, come on.
- Because you said
the fear of him getting caught
was gonna cast a shadow
over every minute of the rest
of their life together.
If you're asking
if it's occurred to me
that going to Stanford
could be a fresh start...
Yeah.
It has,
but the truth is
I may or may not
get into Yale or Columbia,
and you were the one
that told me
that it'd be stupid
if I didn't just cover my bases,
so I just need to go
and see if I even get in or not.
I get it.
I get all of it.
I just can't stop thinking
about what will happen
if you do.
You came to the decision
to let me in on your secret
on your own,
and I just need you
to give me the freedom
to come to this decision
on my own.
I'm not one
for sentimental gestures,
but I was thinking
about when Hardman came back
and you and I got into it.
You got me
my tea set back.
You here to thank me
for that?
I'm here with a gesture
of my own.
This isn't a tea set.
It's going up on the wall
tomorrow.
I asked for that
a while ago.
You said I wasn't ready.
I also said
I wasn't just going to slap
someone else's name up there
next to mine, but I did.
And now you regret it.
And you're playing chess
again.
What does that mean?
It means, I want to know
if this is a gesture
or if it's a move.
What it is,
is my way of showing you
that Darby's treating me
the same way I treated you,
and I understand
how you felt.
You don't like it,
and this is your way
of getting me on your side.
Harvey, I can't make you
believe me,
but I don't want you
on my side.
I want us to be
on the same side.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man