1
00:00:00,146 --> 00:00:01,333
Previously on Suits...

2
00:00:01,334 --> 00:00:05,346
I want you to decide if you
love me more than you hate

3
00:00:05,348 --> 00:00:10,186
what I did, and if you do,
then I want you to come home.

4
00:00:10,321 --> 00:00:12,199
The only they'll definitely
find if they get a look at

5
00:00:12,223 --> 00:00:14,024
those files,
is that you embezzled money.

6
00:00:14,143 --> 00:00:17,529
Listen to me, God damn it.
We need to undo this deal.

7
00:00:17,647 --> 00:00:20,126
- We have nothing to hide.
- No, no, this is a ploy.

8
00:00:20,151 --> 00:00:22,285
He's trying to get me on
record stating that we have

9
00:00:22,437 --> 00:00:24,455
everything,
and if I find nothing,

10
00:00:24,607 --> 00:00:26,908
he's gonna file malicious
prosecution charges.

11
00:00:27,077 --> 00:00:30,130
Actually, Sean, I'm filing
those charges right now.

12
00:00:30,282 --> 00:00:31,633
Harvey went to court
this morning,

13
00:00:31,751 --> 00:00:34,085
and agreed to hand over
every single document

14
00:00:34,221 --> 00:00:37,317
on the Gillis takeover,
including Forstman.

15
00:00:37,341 --> 00:00:40,288
Shit!

16
00:00:40,313 --> 00:00:41,764
Then it's only a matter of time

17
00:00:41,931 --> 00:00:43,459
before I'm marched
out of here in handcuffs.

18
00:00:43,484 --> 00:00:45,128
If he did make
a dirty deal with Forstman,

19
00:00:45,152 --> 00:00:46,753
it wouldn't have been
in those documents.

20
00:00:46,772 --> 00:00:48,082
It would've been in...
The documents

21
00:00:48,107 --> 00:00:50,002
we just told the court
we're happy to turn over.

22
00:00:50,026 --> 00:00:51,109
What are you going to do?

23
00:00:51,245 --> 00:00:54,448
I'm gonna find out
what the hell Louis did.

24
00:00:56,585 --> 00:00:58,203
I made a huge mistake.

25
00:01:05,998 --> 00:01:07,266
What's going on?

26
00:01:07,383 --> 00:01:08,717
Louis, I want you to tell Harvey

27
00:01:08,853 --> 00:01:10,854
exactly what you just told me,
or I will.

28
00:01:11,005 --> 00:01:12,139
He doesn't have to.

29
00:01:12,274 --> 00:01:13,724
He made a dirty deal
with Forstman.

30
00:01:13,843 --> 00:01:15,527
Harvey, I can explain.

31
00:01:15,646 --> 00:01:17,156
Explain what, that you
put the firm in jeopardy

32
00:01:17,180 --> 00:01:18,541
all because you had
to be the hero?

33
00:01:18,650 --> 00:01:19,867
I didn't do it to be the hero.

34
00:01:20,017 --> 00:01:21,034
I didn't even know

35
00:01:21,186 --> 00:01:22,426
I was gonna do it at all. What?

36
00:01:22,521 --> 00:01:25,374
The deal was closed, and
you were so happy we won.

37
00:01:25,526 --> 00:01:28,329
Then I went back that night,
Forstman said if I didn't

38
00:01:28,464 --> 00:01:30,414
funnel the money overseas,
the deal was off,

39
00:01:30,550 --> 00:01:32,584
so I did it.

40
00:01:35,055 --> 00:01:36,439
There's more.

41
00:01:36,575 --> 00:01:38,809
How do you know there's more?

42
00:01:38,911 --> 00:01:41,681
Because with Forstman
there's always more.

43
00:01:44,252 --> 00:01:48,289
He made me take a million
dollars out of the deal

44
00:01:48,391 --> 00:01:51,695
so I couldn't turn on him later.

45
00:01:51,796 --> 00:01:54,164
- Jesus Christ.
- I had no choice!

46
00:01:54,299 --> 00:01:55,666
Bullshit, you had no choice!

47
00:01:55,785 --> 00:01:57,763
You could've said no at any
goddamn point along the way,

48
00:01:57,788 --> 00:02:00,206
but you didn't, because all
you cared about was yourself.

49
00:02:00,342 --> 00:02:01,782
Okay, if I care
about myself so much,

50
00:02:01,910 --> 00:02:04,054
how come I'm in here telling
you that I'm gonna confess?

51
00:02:04,079 --> 00:02:05,324
You want to confess?
Be my guest!

52
00:02:05,349 --> 00:02:09,102
Harvey, that's enough.

53
00:02:09,220 --> 00:02:14,693
Louis... the problem with
that is that we're innocent.

54
00:02:14,811 --> 00:02:17,447
Cahill's plan is to throw mud
against the wall

55
00:02:17,598 --> 00:02:18,625
and see what sticks.

56
00:02:18,650 --> 00:02:20,318
You tell him about what you did,

57
00:02:20,453 --> 00:02:23,934
and all of a sudden,
everything sticks.

58
00:02:23,958 --> 00:02:26,242
Okay.

59
00:02:26,378 --> 00:02:28,212
But I have to do something
to help.

60
00:02:28,331 --> 00:02:32,518
You will, when the time comes.

61
00:02:32,653 --> 00:02:34,987
Right now, I need
to talk to Harvey.

62
00:02:45,638 --> 00:02:47,155
I can't believe
you're taking this

63
00:02:47,306 --> 00:02:48,306
as well as you are.

64
00:02:48,325 --> 00:02:49,669
I'm not taking this well at all.

65
00:02:49,693 --> 00:02:52,111
Then what the hell are
you being so nice to him for?

66
00:02:52,247 --> 00:02:53,808
Did you hear?

67
00:02:53,833 --> 00:02:55,010
He was going to confess.

68
00:02:55,034 --> 00:02:56,501
I had to calm him down.

69
00:02:56,620 --> 00:02:58,481
So you're not
gonna stand by him?

70
00:02:58,506 --> 00:02:59,840
Stand by him?

71
00:02:59,958 --> 00:03:01,258
The second this thing is over,

72
00:03:01,377 --> 00:03:04,847
I'm gonna fire his goddamn ass.

73
00:03:07,936 --> 00:03:09,387
How was your shower?

74
00:03:09,504 --> 00:03:10,638
It was great.

75
00:03:10,807 --> 00:03:12,484
Rachel, you don't
have to clean up for me.

76
00:03:12,508 --> 00:03:13,692
I live here.

77
00:03:13,844 --> 00:03:17,174
I know, I just... I want
everything to be perfect.

78
00:03:17,198 --> 00:03:20,702
It is.

79
00:03:20,854 --> 00:03:22,905
Is this my parents' photo album?

80
00:03:23,041 --> 00:03:26,327
Oh, yeah, it was in
the back of the closet.

81
00:03:26,462 --> 00:03:29,331
Yeah, I know where it was.
Why is it out here?

82
00:03:29,499 --> 00:03:35,506
Because I was looking for
pictures of you.

83
00:03:38,729 --> 00:03:41,064
What do you want to do
for dinner tonight?

84
00:03:41,182 --> 00:03:42,209
I was thinking
maybe we could hit

85
00:03:42,233 --> 00:03:43,651
that little Mexican spot.

86
00:03:43,769 --> 00:03:45,854
No. You just got back here.

87
00:03:46,023 --> 00:03:47,273
I don't want to go anywhere.

88
00:03:47,390 --> 00:03:49,910
I don't either, but we
don't have anything to eat.

89
00:03:50,061 --> 00:03:51,578
- Don't we?
- Well, I know for a fact

90
00:03:51,730 --> 00:03:53,581
we don't have any bean
and cheese burritos.

91
00:03:53,700 --> 00:03:55,394
Mm, then why are there
six of them in the fridge

92
00:03:55,419 --> 00:03:58,289
right now?

93
00:04:05,182 --> 00:04:06,799
You hate them.

94
00:04:06,935 --> 00:04:09,721
I do, but you love them,
and I wanted you

95
00:04:09,855 --> 00:04:12,475
to have them here
when you came home.

96
00:04:12,592 --> 00:04:14,527
And what if I
didn't come home tonight?

97
00:04:14,645 --> 00:04:19,033
Then I would have bought
fresh ones again tomorrow.

98
00:04:19,152 --> 00:04:22,155
Thanks, Rachel.

99
00:04:22,289 --> 00:04:24,457
It's good to have you home.

100
00:04:24,576 --> 00:04:28,580
It's good to be home.

101
00:04:33,005 --> 00:04:35,641
What happened?

102
00:04:35,792 --> 00:04:37,787
I thought you had a date.

103
00:04:37,811 --> 00:04:39,762
I canceled it,
and I asked you a question.

104
00:04:39,931 --> 00:04:41,108
I don't want to talk about it,

105
00:04:41,133 --> 00:04:42,460
because I know what
you're going to say.

106
00:04:42,484 --> 00:04:44,329
Harvey, I don't even
know what exactly Louis did.

107
00:04:44,354 --> 00:04:46,271
He broke the law
to close Forstman.

108
00:04:46,440 --> 00:04:48,993
He broke it or Forstman
made him break it?

109
00:04:49,111 --> 00:04:50,171
- What's the goddamn difference?
- Harvey...

110
00:04:50,195 --> 00:04:51,662
You don't have to say it, Donna,

111
00:04:51,814 --> 00:04:53,054
I've heard it a thousand times.

112
00:04:53,117 --> 00:04:54,784
Louis only did this
to get my approval.

113
00:04:54,918 --> 00:04:56,586
And you know what,
I don't give a shit

114
00:04:56,704 --> 00:04:58,122
that I agreed to be
his best man.

115
00:04:58,257 --> 00:05:00,208
He put you, me, and every one
of us in jeopardy

116
00:05:00,342 --> 00:05:01,376
to get what he wanted.

117
00:05:01,511 --> 00:05:02,795
Well, I was gonna say that,

118
00:05:02,964 --> 00:05:04,131
but instead I'll say this:

119
00:05:04,265 --> 00:05:05,715
You put us all in jeopardy too.

120
00:05:05,834 --> 00:05:07,301
When the hell did I do that?

121
00:05:07,436 --> 00:05:09,637
The day you hired Mike,
and by the way,

122
00:05:09,773 --> 00:05:11,473
I'm guessing he wouldn't
even be back here

123
00:05:11,642 --> 00:05:13,143
if Louis hadn't done
what he did.

124
00:05:13,311 --> 00:05:15,947
Then tell that to Jessica,
'cause when it's over,

125
00:05:16,065 --> 00:05:19,035
she's gonna fire him.

126
00:05:24,193 --> 00:05:27,463
They keep this
place open late for you?

127
00:05:27,581 --> 00:05:29,215
Ownership has its privileges.

128
00:05:31,170 --> 00:05:32,670
What do you want, Harvey?

129
00:05:32,805 --> 00:05:34,449
I want you to undo
the dirty deal you made

130
00:05:34,474 --> 00:05:35,641
with Louis Litt.

131
00:05:35,759 --> 00:05:38,279
Dirty deal.
Doesn't sound like me at all.

132
00:05:38,380 --> 00:05:40,097
How does prison sound?

133
00:05:40,232 --> 00:05:42,016
Because the S.E.C.
is gonna get a record

134
00:05:42,151 --> 00:05:43,852
of the shit you pulled
tomorrow morning.

135
00:05:43,987 --> 00:05:47,524
There is no record,
'cause I didn't do anything.

136
00:05:47,659 --> 00:05:49,220
Louis Litt came to me,

137
00:05:49,245 --> 00:05:51,246
and he's the one
who embezzled money.

138
00:05:51,397 --> 00:05:53,282
And your grudge
isn't with Louis.

139
00:05:53,417 --> 00:05:56,871
It's with me, so let him go.

140
00:05:57,039 --> 00:05:58,623
Live to fight me another day.

141
00:05:58,758 --> 00:06:03,346
If I let him off, I let you off,

142
00:06:03,465 --> 00:06:05,182
and I don't think
I want to do that.

143
00:06:05,300 --> 00:06:07,802
Then you're forcing me to
turn you in for what you did

144
00:06:07,938 --> 00:06:11,108
12 years ago.

145
00:06:11,259 --> 00:06:14,112
No way.
You're not gonna do that,

146
00:06:14,263 --> 00:06:15,947
because you did it too, pal.

147
00:06:16,099 --> 00:06:18,735
You're right, I did.
But if you did it to Louis

148
00:06:18,903 --> 00:06:22,156
and you did it to me, you
did it to a hundred others.

149
00:06:22,274 --> 00:06:24,325
And if you don't
do what I'm asking,

150
00:06:24,460 --> 00:06:26,378
I'll just have to find
the one in a hundred

151
00:06:26,497 --> 00:06:28,308
that's in a position
to turn on you.

152
00:06:28,333 --> 00:06:30,584
I'll take my chances, Harvey.

153
00:06:30,720 --> 00:06:32,470
Now, get out of my face.

154
00:06:32,588 --> 00:06:35,825
Let me finish my cigar in peace.

155
00:06:39,665 --> 00:06:43,235
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪

156
00:06:43,354 --> 00:06:46,574
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪

157
00:06:46,692 --> 00:06:49,745
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪

158
00:06:49,862 --> 00:06:53,449
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪

159
00:06:53,585 --> 00:06:56,481
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪

160
00:06:56,505 --> 00:07:00,426
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪

161
00:07:00,545 --> 00:07:01,878
♪ All right ♪

162
00:07:01,996 --> 00:07:05,997
♪ Suits 4x09 ♪ Gone Original
Air Date on August 13, 2014

163
00:07:07,503 --> 00:07:09,188
♪ the greenback boogie ♪

164
00:07:09,213 --> 00:07:15,215
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man.

165
00:07:17,571 --> 00:07:20,374
- You know?
- Of course I do.

166
00:07:20,510 --> 00:07:22,404
- I never meant to...
- Louis...

167
00:07:22,428 --> 00:07:24,713
I understand why you did
what you did.

168
00:07:24,882 --> 00:07:27,718
- You do?
- Yes. You went down a path

169
00:07:27,853 --> 00:07:28,969
with the best intentions,

170
00:07:29,105 --> 00:07:30,889
and then it just got
worse and worse

171
00:07:31,058 --> 00:07:32,892
until it was too late.

172
00:07:34,779 --> 00:07:37,425
- Feel like shit.
- And you should.

173
00:07:37,449 --> 00:07:39,868
What?

174
00:07:39,986 --> 00:07:42,321
But you just said...
I understand? I do.

175
00:07:42,456 --> 00:07:44,624
But I don't think you
understand that every

176
00:07:44,776 --> 00:07:46,994
other time you screwed up,
it was a mistake,

177
00:07:47,130 --> 00:07:49,248
and this time, it was a choice!

178
00:07:49,383 --> 00:07:50,416
That's what Harvey said.

179
00:07:50,552 --> 00:07:51,646
Of course
that's what Harvey said.

180
00:07:51,670 --> 00:07:53,030
And just because I get
what happened,

181
00:07:53,055 --> 00:07:54,366
it doesn't mean that you
deserve to be let off the hook,

182
00:07:54,390 --> 00:07:56,091
so if you've come
in here to ask me

183
00:07:56,226 --> 00:07:57,927
to go to him for
the millionth time, I'm...

184
00:07:58,062 --> 00:07:59,429
No, I'm not here for that.

185
00:07:59,597 --> 00:08:01,398
Then... then what
are you here for?

186
00:08:01,517 --> 00:08:05,487
I'm here to ask you
if I'm gonna get fired.

187
00:08:05,606 --> 00:08:06,667
What?

188
00:08:06,691 --> 00:08:08,108
I saw how he looked
at me, Donna.

189
00:08:08,277 --> 00:08:09,610
I know he trusts you,

190
00:08:09,778 --> 00:08:14,700
but I need to know if Harvey's
planning on firing me.

191
00:08:14,835 --> 00:08:16,346
No, Louis.

192
00:08:16,371 --> 00:08:17,755
To my knowledge,

193
00:08:17,872 --> 00:08:23,179
Harvey isn't planning
to fire you.

194
00:08:23,331 --> 00:08:26,184
Thank you, Donna.

195
00:08:26,335 --> 00:08:29,188
I knew I could count on you.

196
00:08:37,867 --> 00:08:40,035
Can't remember the last time
I saw you in here.

197
00:08:40,154 --> 00:08:43,073
I can't remember the last time
this firm faced prosecution.

198
00:08:43,192 --> 00:08:45,160
Ava Hessington.

199
00:08:45,294 --> 00:08:46,305
And after that, we said
it would never come

200
00:08:46,330 --> 00:08:47,340
to this again.

201
00:08:47,364 --> 00:08:48,497
How the hell did it?

202
00:08:48,633 --> 00:08:50,277
We stepped into the ring
with Charles Forstman.

203
00:08:50,301 --> 00:08:52,219
I'm guessing he didn't
budge last night.

204
00:08:52,371 --> 00:08:53,721
He didn't.

205
00:08:53,873 --> 00:08:55,993
He sheltered himself, and
he'd rather laugh in my face

206
00:08:56,010 --> 00:08:59,263
than be 100% protected
against the S.E.C.

207
00:08:59,398 --> 00:09:00,575
You have a plan "B"?

208
00:09:00,600 --> 00:09:02,067
He doesn't, but I do.

209
00:09:02,218 --> 00:09:03,685
What the hell is it?

210
00:09:03,821 --> 00:09:05,521
What would you do
if you were Cahill?

211
00:09:05,690 --> 00:09:07,358
Go through every
one of these boxes,

212
00:09:07,492 --> 00:09:08,692
and start deposing us.

213
00:09:08,828 --> 00:09:11,079
Okay, so what if
while he's doing that,

214
00:09:11,231 --> 00:09:14,835
we start deposing him?

215
00:09:19,092 --> 00:09:21,237
Did you come here to
personally deliver my files?

216
00:09:21,262 --> 00:09:23,129
I came here to
personally deliver this.

217
00:09:23,265 --> 00:09:24,776
Well, if it's an invitation
to your birthday party,

218
00:09:24,800 --> 00:09:27,111
I think I'm busy that day.
That's too bad.

219
00:09:27,136 --> 00:09:29,536
I promised the children a clown.
You've got to be kidding me.

220
00:09:29,640 --> 00:09:32,025
You got Judge Hopkins
to let you start depositions

221
00:09:32,143 --> 00:09:33,671
on your malicious
prosecution bullshit?

222
00:09:33,696 --> 00:09:35,063
He didn't think it was bullshit,

223
00:09:35,197 --> 00:09:36,518
which is why
he's letting me start

224
00:09:36,533 --> 00:09:37,760
with your boyfriend
Eric Woodall.

225
00:09:37,784 --> 00:09:39,902
You trying to take
my eye off the ball, Harvey?

226
00:09:40,038 --> 00:09:41,288
This is the ball, Sean.

227
00:09:41,440 --> 00:09:45,210
It's a wrecking ball,
and it's headed your way.

228
00:09:52,672 --> 00:09:54,840
Louis, where the hell
have you been?

229
00:09:54,975 --> 00:09:56,759
Those documents are
on their way over.

230
00:09:56,895 --> 00:09:58,145
Katrina, relax.

231
00:09:58,264 --> 00:09:59,791
Relax?

232
00:09:59,815 --> 00:10:01,850
The last time I saw you,
you were worried

233
00:10:01,985 --> 00:10:03,046
about going to prison.

234
00:10:03,070 --> 00:10:04,937
What did you decide to do?

235
00:10:05,060 --> 00:10:06,060
I went to Harvey and Jessica,

236
00:10:06,085 --> 00:10:07,085
and I told them everything.

237
00:10:07,109 --> 00:10:08,326
What?

238
00:10:08,478 --> 00:10:10,529
Jessica said that
I made a mistake,

239
00:10:10,664 --> 00:10:12,248
and they're working
on a way out.

240
00:10:12,366 --> 00:10:15,669
Louis, have you seen
any mafia movie ever made?

241
00:10:15,788 --> 00:10:17,289
I'm not really
a fan of the genre.

242
00:10:17,423 --> 00:10:19,017
I find it to be a little
offensive to Italians...

243
00:10:19,042 --> 00:10:20,393
Shut up, and listen.

244
00:10:20,511 --> 00:10:23,630
She's telling you to your
face she'll let you live,

245
00:10:23,799 --> 00:10:26,829
but behind your back, she's
making plans to whack you.

246
00:10:26,853 --> 00:10:28,804
Holy shit, I'm living
on borrowed time.

247
00:10:28,973 --> 00:10:30,891
Unless you fix this,
because if you don't,

248
00:10:31,009 --> 00:10:34,313
even if Jessica manages
to keep you out of prison,

249
00:10:34,447 --> 00:10:37,317
she'll be coming to fire you.

250
00:10:42,625 --> 00:10:44,743
Jessica, I was just thinking

251
00:10:44,861 --> 00:10:46,662
about our dinner plans tonight,

252
00:10:46,831 --> 00:10:48,165
and I think that...

253
00:10:48,300 --> 00:10:49,300
What's wrong?

254
00:10:49,418 --> 00:10:50,752
We're going after Eric Woodall.

255
00:10:50,887 --> 00:10:54,391
Harvey moved up the time line.

256
00:10:54,542 --> 00:10:57,061
And since this is
Harvey's case now...

257
00:10:57,212 --> 00:10:58,679
Why are you talking to me?

258
00:10:58,815 --> 00:11:02,068
'Cause I need you to find
out every dirty thing

259
00:11:02,219 --> 00:11:06,357
Eric Woodall has ever done,
condoned, or been part of.

260
00:11:06,492 --> 00:11:08,527
Jessica, I really
don't feel comfortable

261
00:11:08,695 --> 00:11:11,365
participating in blackmail
without knowing why.

262
00:11:11,533 --> 00:11:13,534
It's not blackmail,
it's evidence,

263
00:11:13,702 --> 00:11:14,953
and I'll tell you why.

264
00:11:15,087 --> 00:11:17,205
Because malicious prosecution
is easier to prove

265
00:11:17,340 --> 00:11:18,474
when there's a track record.

266
00:11:18,609 --> 00:11:20,220
Yeah, there's only
one problem with that.

267
00:11:20,244 --> 00:11:23,074
You see, just yesterday, we
agreed to hand over our files

268
00:11:23,098 --> 00:11:24,382
because we had nothing to hide,

269
00:11:24,551 --> 00:11:26,718
and now, you want me
to go after the S.E.C.,

270
00:11:26,854 --> 00:11:28,388
which means we do. Jeff-

271
00:11:28,523 --> 00:11:31,059
Jessica, hide it
from them all you want, okay?

272
00:11:31,227 --> 00:11:32,571
But we talked about this,
and you said

273
00:11:32,595 --> 00:11:34,595
that I shouldn't be treated
like any other partner,

274
00:11:34,731 --> 00:11:37,149
so don't come in here
hiding it from me.

275
00:11:37,285 --> 00:11:39,096
You want a straight answer.

276
00:11:39,121 --> 00:11:40,905
I'll give you a straight answer.

277
00:11:41,041 --> 00:11:43,577
Harvey did not collude
with Mike Ross,

278
00:11:43,711 --> 00:11:45,912
but Sean Cahill doesn't
give a shit about that.

279
00:11:46,081 --> 00:11:48,667
So I need you to do
whatever you have to

280
00:11:48,801 --> 00:11:51,588
and get me something
on these guys.

281
00:11:59,784 --> 00:12:02,620
Hey, how did Cahill
handle our surprise?

282
00:12:02,771 --> 00:12:03,882
Actually, I got
to hand it to him.

283
00:12:03,907 --> 00:12:06,660
He handled it pretty damn well.

284
00:12:06,794 --> 00:12:08,245
What? You guys had

285
00:12:08,380 --> 00:12:09,547
your whole Wonder Twins riff,

286
00:12:09,665 --> 00:12:11,025
and now you're
giving him respect?

287
00:12:11,050 --> 00:12:13,185
What's next: A time share
in the Florida Keys?

288
00:12:13,320 --> 00:12:14,320
Easy, tiger.

289
00:12:14,422 --> 00:12:15,532
Just saying, I got
two words for you:

290
00:12:15,556 --> 00:12:17,807
Bro-Mance.

291
00:12:17,959 --> 00:12:20,261
Before you order us
a gift off our registry,

292
00:12:20,363 --> 00:12:21,623
let me tell you
what he's been up too.

293
00:12:21,648 --> 00:12:24,435
He had Judge Hopkins sign
off on his depositions,

294
00:12:24,602 --> 00:12:27,655
meaning he's coming at us
the same time we go after him.

295
00:12:27,806 --> 00:12:29,668
- We can handle it.
- Can Rachel?

296
00:12:29,693 --> 00:12:31,410
What?

297
00:12:31,529 --> 00:12:33,173
Take a look.

298
00:12:33,198 --> 00:12:34,916
She's first on the list.

299
00:12:35,033 --> 00:12:36,784
And you want me
to tell her it's coming.

300
00:12:36,920 --> 00:12:38,160
I want you to do more than that.

301
00:12:38,171 --> 00:12:39,421
I want you to prep her.

302
00:12:39,540 --> 00:12:41,841
Harvey, that's not a good idea.

303
00:12:41,993 --> 00:12:43,771
Yes, it is... you're
the best person for the job.

304
00:12:43,796 --> 00:12:45,180
I am the worst
person for the job.

305
00:12:45,331 --> 00:12:46,331
And you're only saying it

306
00:12:46,467 --> 00:12:48,028
because it makes you
feel uncomfortable.

307
00:12:48,135 --> 00:12:50,015
How do you think Cahill's
gonna make Rachel feel

308
00:12:50,021 --> 00:12:53,057
when he gets her under oath?

309
00:13:02,655 --> 00:13:05,542
Usually, people don't
start by washing their hands.

310
00:13:05,659 --> 00:13:08,579
Usually, people aren't
here to talk about Louis.

311
00:13:08,697 --> 00:13:11,801
- Donna.
- Jessica, he made a mistake.

312
00:13:11,919 --> 00:13:15,005
"Mistake" implies that he
did something by accident.

313
00:13:15,173 --> 00:13:16,757
Louis made a choice.

314
00:13:16,892 --> 00:13:18,520
And you're making
the choice to fire him

315
00:13:18,545 --> 00:13:20,095
when this is over.

316
00:13:20,230 --> 00:13:22,598
And how the hell is that
any of your business?

317
00:13:22,733 --> 00:13:25,770
I just thought if Louis
could help get you out of it...

318
00:13:25,888 --> 00:13:27,022
Help get me out of it?

319
00:13:27,156 --> 00:13:28,607
He's the one
that got me into it.

320
00:13:28,742 --> 00:13:29,742
And if this were Harvey,

321
00:13:29,893 --> 00:13:31,304
you'd let him try
to make up for it.

322
00:13:31,329 --> 00:13:32,613
And if this were Harvey,

323
00:13:32,730 --> 00:13:35,450
I'd have the confidence
that he would.

324
00:13:35,585 --> 00:13:38,371
Jessica, Louis did all of this

325
00:13:38,540 --> 00:13:41,175
because he is dying
for your approval.

326
00:13:41,293 --> 00:13:42,760
You never have
confidence in him,

327
00:13:42,878 --> 00:13:44,439
and you never treat him
the way you treat Harvey.

328
00:13:44,464 --> 00:13:45,598
So this is my fault?

329
00:13:45,748 --> 00:13:47,600
I'm saying
Harvey's made mistakes,

330
00:13:47,718 --> 00:13:49,769
and you've forgiven him.

331
00:13:49,921 --> 00:13:51,889
I've made mistakes,
and you've forgiven me.

332
00:13:52,025 --> 00:13:54,894
You're right, Donna,
you did make a mistake once,

333
00:13:55,062 --> 00:13:58,949
and I did forgive you,
but first I fired you.

334
00:13:59,101 --> 00:14:00,952
And if you don't back off me
right now,

335
00:14:01,104 --> 00:14:04,908
I will do it again.

336
00:14:05,043 --> 00:14:08,413
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have a deposition to get to.

337
00:14:11,919 --> 00:14:14,114
Please state your full name
for the record.

338
00:14:14,139 --> 00:14:15,556
Eric ignatius Woodall.

339
00:14:15,674 --> 00:14:18,119
- Ignatius?
- Like the Saint.

340
00:14:18,144 --> 00:14:19,261
I doubt that.

341
00:14:19,430 --> 00:14:21,431
And how long have you
worked for the S.E.C.?

342
00:14:21,600 --> 00:14:22,610
Two months.

343
00:14:22,634 --> 00:14:23,834
And where were you before that?

344
00:14:23,853 --> 00:14:25,820
I worked at
the U.S. attorneys' office.

345
00:14:25,939 --> 00:14:28,575
Until I got you fired
for malicious prosecution.

346
00:14:28,693 --> 00:14:29,860
You didn't get me fired.

347
00:14:29,977 --> 00:14:32,112
You slandered me
to a person in power,

348
00:14:32,247 --> 00:14:34,198
which caused me to leave
a job I loved.

349
00:14:34,334 --> 00:14:35,618
To avoid getting fired.

350
00:14:35,752 --> 00:14:38,072
You have no proof of that,
and he has no knowledge of that.

351
00:14:38,089 --> 00:14:41,926
Does he have any knowledge
of his feelings towards me?

352
00:14:42,045 --> 00:14:43,962
I don't have any feelings
for you, Mr. Specter,

353
00:14:44,131 --> 00:14:46,850
and for your information,
I landed on my feet.

354
00:14:46,968 --> 00:14:48,602
Yes, we know, at the S.E.C.,

355
00:14:48,721 --> 00:14:50,365
but we don't want
to talk about that.

356
00:14:50,389 --> 00:14:52,701
We want to talk
about Jim Pembry.

357
00:14:52,726 --> 00:14:56,480
You don't seem
too comfortable anymore, Eric.

358
00:14:56,615 --> 00:14:59,201
Who's Jim Pembry?

359
00:14:59,352 --> 00:15:01,232
I worked with Jim
at the U.S. attorneys' office.

360
00:15:01,355 --> 00:15:02,956
On the Arthur Cohen prosecution?

361
00:15:03,074 --> 00:15:04,457
I believe he did
some work for me.

362
00:15:04,576 --> 00:15:06,210
You believe? You sent him

363
00:15:06,362 --> 00:15:09,082
over 1,200 emails on that case
over four years.

364
00:15:09,199 --> 00:15:10,560
If you say so.

365
00:15:10,584 --> 00:15:12,104
Actually, your
computer records say so,

366
00:15:12,220 --> 00:15:13,671
and I could read them all,

367
00:15:13,839 --> 00:15:15,807
but I'd rather start
with my favorite.

368
00:15:15,926 --> 00:15:18,144
"I don't care what we
get Arthur Cohen on.

369
00:15:18,261 --> 00:15:20,764
"Tax evasion, insider trading,
jaywalking if we have to,

370
00:15:20,899 --> 00:15:23,078
but we're putting that
piece of shit behind bars."

371
00:15:23,102 --> 00:15:24,212
Where the hell did you get that?

372
00:15:24,237 --> 00:15:25,531
It's not important
where we got it,

373
00:15:25,555 --> 00:15:26,565
but that we got it.

374
00:15:26,590 --> 00:15:27,590
Emails get heated.

375
00:15:27,692 --> 00:15:28,719
It was the middle of a case.

376
00:15:28,744 --> 00:15:29,754
The problem is, Eric,

377
00:15:29,778 --> 00:15:31,362
this was dated two years before

378
00:15:31,497 --> 00:15:32,641
you even brought your big case.

379
00:15:32,665 --> 00:15:34,366
- Do you have a question?
- I sure do.

380
00:15:34,501 --> 00:15:35,895
You decide someone's guilty,

381
00:15:35,920 --> 00:15:37,371
then you find the crime
to fit them.

382
00:15:37,505 --> 00:15:38,956
Isn't that true? No.

383
00:15:39,091 --> 00:15:41,069
You want me to get
you for perjury too?

384
00:15:41,094 --> 00:15:42,878
You tried to get
Arthur on one thing.

385
00:15:43,013 --> 00:15:44,847
Instead, you got him
on another, didn't you?

386
00:15:44,966 --> 00:15:46,433
- Don't answer him.
- Yes.

387
00:15:46,585 --> 00:15:48,396
And that's exactly what you
want to do with me, isn't it?

388
00:15:48,421 --> 00:15:49,498
That's enough. Stop typing.

389
00:15:49,522 --> 00:15:50,722
We're done here.

390
00:15:50,724 --> 00:15:52,274
- To answer your question...
- Don't...

391
00:15:52,426 --> 00:15:55,112
You're damn right it is.

392
00:15:55,263 --> 00:15:57,091
That's okay.
It may not be on record,

393
00:15:57,116 --> 00:16:01,037
but I got what I wanted.

394
00:16:09,000 --> 00:16:10,584
You're not my usual guy.

395
00:16:10,752 --> 00:16:12,586
I'm not a usual anything.

396
00:16:12,721 --> 00:16:18,595
No, you're not.

397
00:16:18,730 --> 00:16:20,014
Thanks to Jim Pembry.

398
00:16:20,148 --> 00:16:22,399
I'm not here to celebrate
with Jim Pembry.

399
00:16:24,738 --> 00:16:26,082
Jessica, we may have
landed the first punch,

400
00:16:26,107 --> 00:16:27,991
but we're next up.

401
00:16:28,142 --> 00:16:29,503
And Cahill's gonna
be brutal on us.

402
00:16:29,612 --> 00:16:31,863
- No, he isn't.
- What do you mean?

403
00:16:31,998 --> 00:16:33,342
We're going to court tomorrow,

404
00:16:33,366 --> 00:16:35,367
and with any luck, we're
gonna get this whole thing

405
00:16:35,503 --> 00:16:37,788
tossed before he even
has a chance to depose us.

406
00:16:37,923 --> 00:16:40,018
Well, then, maybe
we should go to dinner.

407
00:16:40,043 --> 00:16:42,044
I have a better idea.

408
00:16:42,162 --> 00:16:45,132
Let's order in.

409
00:16:53,846 --> 00:16:56,147
Miss Zane, do you
live with Michael Ross,

410
00:16:56,283 --> 00:16:58,284
the lawyer on the other
side of this takeover?

411
00:16:58,402 --> 00:17:00,036
Yes.

412
00:17:00,187 --> 00:17:02,372
And, uh, and at any point
during the takeover,

413
00:17:02,491 --> 00:17:03,852
did you discuss business
with him?

414
00:17:03,877 --> 00:17:04,877
No.

415
00:17:04,878 --> 00:17:06,929
You expect me to believe that?

416
00:17:07,064 --> 00:17:08,308
I don't care whether
you believe it or not,

417
00:17:08,332 --> 00:17:10,333
because it's the truth.

418
00:17:10,502 --> 00:17:14,055
The truth.

419
00:17:14,207 --> 00:17:20,014
Did you discuss Logan Sanders
with Mr. Ross?

420
00:17:20,182 --> 00:17:21,983
- Yes.
- I'm confused.

421
00:17:22,102 --> 00:17:23,746
You just said that
you didn't discuss business

422
00:17:23,771 --> 00:17:25,689
with Mr. Ross,
yet now you're saying

423
00:17:25,823 --> 00:17:28,168
that you discussed the man on
the other side of the takeover.

424
00:17:28,193 --> 00:17:30,004
How can one of those be
true and not the other?

425
00:17:30,029 --> 00:17:32,893
- That wasn't about business.
- Then what was it about?

426
00:17:32,917 --> 00:17:35,836
It was about the fact
that I used to be involved

427
00:17:35,955 --> 00:17:38,624
with Logan Sanders.

428
00:17:38,759 --> 00:17:40,209
And did you assure Mr. Ross

429
00:17:40,377 --> 00:17:41,404
that you wouldn't
become involved

430
00:17:41,429 --> 00:17:42,713
with Logan Sanders again?

431
00:17:42,881 --> 00:17:43,941
What does that have to do with...

432
00:17:43,966 --> 00:17:45,967
- Answer my question.
- Yes, I did.

433
00:17:46,102 --> 00:17:47,703
And yet, over the course
of the takeover,

434
00:17:47,721 --> 00:17:49,365
you did become involved
with him again, didn't you?

435
00:17:49,390 --> 00:17:50,724
No, I didn't.

436
00:17:50,858 --> 00:17:52,786
You had no physical contact
of a sexual nature at all...

437
00:17:52,811 --> 00:17:54,739
- Mike, please, I don't...
- Just answer my question.

438
00:17:54,764 --> 00:17:56,899
We kissed once, and that was it.

439
00:17:57,034 --> 00:17:59,931
- Did you sleep with him?
- He is not going to ask me...

440
00:17:59,955 --> 00:18:01,682
You just lied.
You said you weren't involved,

441
00:18:01,707 --> 00:18:02,991
and then you said
you kissed him.

442
00:18:03,125 --> 00:18:04,292
So I'm gonna ask you again:

443
00:18:04,444 --> 00:18:06,078
Did you sleep with Logan Sanders

444
00:18:06,214 --> 00:18:08,465
after you assured the man
that you supposedly love

445
00:18:08,617 --> 00:18:10,178
that you wouldn't
become involved again?

446
00:18:10,285 --> 00:18:11,646
I'm not gonna answer that,

447
00:18:11,671 --> 00:18:13,616
because it doesn't have anything
to do with collusion.

448
00:18:13,641 --> 00:18:14,935
It goes to credibility.
It goes to

449
00:18:14,959 --> 00:18:17,488
what you're capable of,
whether a jury should trust you.

450
00:18:17,512 --> 00:18:18,833
- A jury or you?
- What difference

451
00:18:18,848 --> 00:18:20,482
does that make?
The difference is

452
00:18:20,600 --> 00:18:22,461
you're the one that's doing it,
because you don't trust me.

453
00:18:22,486 --> 00:18:25,022
- Because Harvey needs me to.
- It is vicious, and it's cruel.

454
00:18:25,156 --> 00:18:26,450
- I am doing my job.
- Mike, I thought

455
00:18:26,475 --> 00:18:28,827
you were over this.
Well, I'm goddamn not!

456
00:18:36,589 --> 00:18:39,626
I didn't sleep with Logan.

457
00:18:44,267 --> 00:18:48,805
I kissed him,
and I hate myself for it.

458
00:18:51,010 --> 00:18:54,480
Mike, I'm so sorry.

459
00:18:54,648 --> 00:18:58,201
And I can apologize to you
every day

460
00:18:58,319 --> 00:18:59,486
for the rest of my life,

461
00:18:59,621 --> 00:19:02,073
but I-I...

462
00:19:02,208 --> 00:19:04,660
I don't know what else to do,

463
00:19:04,829 --> 00:19:07,498
other than to tell you that...

464
00:19:07,632 --> 00:19:08,916
You mean more to me

465
00:19:09,052 --> 00:19:14,201
than anything in the world,
and I need you to believe me.

466
00:19:14,225 --> 00:19:16,427
I need you to believe me
so that we can move on

467
00:19:16,562 --> 00:19:19,432
and live our lives.

468
00:19:24,223 --> 00:19:27,926
Think that's enough
questions for tonight.

469
00:19:37,583 --> 00:19:39,260
Louis, what the
hell are you doing here?

470
00:19:39,285 --> 00:19:41,053
I read
the Eric Woodall deposition,

471
00:19:41,172 --> 00:19:42,199
and I thought I could help.

472
00:19:42,223 --> 00:19:43,340
Help what?

473
00:19:43,474 --> 00:19:44,935
You're here
to shut down Sean Cahill,

474
00:19:44,960 --> 00:19:46,154
and he's not gonna give up
without a fight.

475
00:19:46,179 --> 00:19:47,513
Louis, I don't
have time for this.

476
00:19:47,647 --> 00:19:49,408
So take your arguments
and get the hell out of here.

477
00:19:49,433 --> 00:19:50,460
Please, Jessica, I want to help.

478
00:19:50,484 --> 00:19:51,684
I don't need your help.

479
00:19:51,820 --> 00:19:53,270
We're about to put
this thing to bed.

480
00:19:53,405 --> 00:19:56,324
- And I feel responsible.
- You are responsible.

481
00:19:56,476 --> 00:19:58,505
You are the entire
reason we are in jeopardy,

482
00:19:58,530 --> 00:20:01,499
and you want to sit your
stupid face in front of Cahill?

483
00:20:01,650 --> 00:20:04,620
You may as well wear a sign
that says "depose me next."

484
00:20:04,755 --> 00:20:07,958
And if he does that, you will
tumble like a House of Cards,

485
00:20:08,092 --> 00:20:09,960
because you are ruled
by your emotions,

486
00:20:10,095 --> 00:20:12,848
and that is the reason
why we are in this situation

487
00:20:12,999 --> 00:20:15,769
in the first place.

488
00:20:15,886 --> 00:20:17,353
Can I at least sit
in the gallery?

489
00:20:17,505 --> 00:20:18,889
I don't care where you sit,

490
00:20:19,025 --> 00:20:20,335
but Cahill's gonna be here
in 30 seconds,

491
00:20:20,359 --> 00:20:24,707
so it better be
far away from me.

492
00:20:24,732 --> 00:20:25,826
What the hell is he doing here?

493
00:20:25,850 --> 00:20:27,044
The important thing is

494
00:20:27,069 --> 00:20:29,905
is that he's not sitting
here anymore.

495
00:20:32,243 --> 00:20:35,046
Mr. Cahill, this email
makes a strong case

496
00:20:35,197 --> 00:20:36,547
that Eric Woodall
has a propensity

497
00:20:36,699 --> 00:20:37,916
for malicious prosecution.

498
00:20:38,051 --> 00:20:39,061
Yes, it does, Your Honor,

499
00:20:39,086 --> 00:20:40,720
but I'm the one pursuing
this case,

500
00:20:40,871 --> 00:20:42,222
not Eric Woodall,

501
00:20:42,373 --> 00:20:44,341
and I don't have a propensity
for anything.

502
00:20:44,477 --> 00:20:46,394
I'm a simple man
trying to do my job.

503
00:20:46,546 --> 00:20:48,898
You expect us to believe
that the guy you came up with

504
00:20:49,050 --> 00:20:52,353
at the Department of Justice
comes over to the S.E.C.,

505
00:20:52,488 --> 00:20:54,583
and you immediately
start coming after us,

506
00:20:54,608 --> 00:20:55,991
and it's a coincidence?

507
00:20:56,110 --> 00:20:58,071
Doesn't take much to connect
the dots here, Your Honor.

508
00:20:58,095 --> 00:20:59,423
Well, as long as
we're connecting dots,

509
00:20:59,448 --> 00:21:00,948
I can connect a few too.

510
00:21:01,084 --> 00:21:02,261
Let's start with Jeff Malone.

511
00:21:02,285 --> 00:21:03,702
A man who used to work
at the S.E.C.

512
00:21:03,871 --> 00:21:06,289
Now conveniently works
at Pearson Specter.

513
00:21:06,424 --> 00:21:08,052
It's not against
the law to change jobs.

514
00:21:08,076 --> 00:21:09,760
Yes, but why did he change jobs?

515
00:21:09,912 --> 00:21:11,630
Because he was instructed
to come after us

516
00:21:11,748 --> 00:21:13,216
on behalf of the S.E.C.

517
00:21:13,383 --> 00:21:14,433
So he says.

518
00:21:14,585 --> 00:21:15,746
I think it's because
he wanted to work

519
00:21:15,770 --> 00:21:19,390
with his girlfriend
Jessica Pearson.

520
00:21:19,526 --> 00:21:20,609
Excuse me?

521
00:21:20,727 --> 00:21:21,944
Ms. Pearson hired Mr. Malone,

522
00:21:22,096 --> 00:21:23,874
because if you're planning
to break some rules,

523
00:21:23,899 --> 00:21:25,460
you need someone
to navigate them for you.

524
00:21:25,484 --> 00:21:26,744
Who better to do that
than your boyfriend

525
00:21:26,769 --> 00:21:27,796
who works at the S.E.C.?

526
00:21:27,820 --> 00:21:29,431
That's ridiculous.

527
00:21:29,456 --> 00:21:31,017
Do you have any proof
of this allegation?

528
00:21:31,041 --> 00:21:33,744
Right here.

529
00:21:33,913 --> 00:21:35,830
I can call you up to the stand,

530
00:21:35,965 --> 00:21:39,635
or we can do this right now.

531
00:21:39,787 --> 00:21:42,674
Were you seeing Jeff Malone

532
00:21:42,791 --> 00:21:46,495
during the time
that he worked for the S.E.C.?

533
00:21:50,986 --> 00:21:54,606
Please let the record reflect
Ms. Pearson said yes.

534
00:21:54,742 --> 00:21:56,303
Well, a romantic relationship
isn't proof

535
00:21:56,328 --> 00:21:58,863
of a conspiracy,
but it's not irrelevant.

536
00:21:58,998 --> 00:22:01,199
I'll allow you to move
forward with depositions.

537
00:22:03,871 --> 00:22:05,422
I don't care what we have to do.

538
00:22:05,540 --> 00:22:07,507
I'm not losing
to that son of a bitch.

539
00:22:11,498 --> 00:22:13,618
Despite what we just proved,
you're not losing to him,

540
00:22:13,719 --> 00:22:14,769
you're losing to me.

541
00:22:14,886 --> 00:22:16,971
And as far as depositions go,

542
00:22:17,140 --> 00:22:19,976
now it's our turn.

543
00:22:28,873 --> 00:22:30,991
Louis.

544
00:22:31,160 --> 00:22:33,494
Is there something
I can help you with?

545
00:22:33,663 --> 00:22:37,500
I was just thinking
things were so much simpler

546
00:22:37,668 --> 00:22:38,668
when I was in here.

547
00:22:38,804 --> 00:22:40,921
Yeah, Louis...

548
00:22:41,039 --> 00:22:43,234
I know about you and Jessica.

549
00:22:43,259 --> 00:22:44,370
What?

550
00:22:44,395 --> 00:22:46,740
It came out in court.

551
00:22:46,765 --> 00:22:49,985
See, I thought you were
using me to get ahead,

552
00:22:50,102 --> 00:22:53,406
when you really just wanted
to spend more time with Jessica.

553
00:22:53,556 --> 00:22:56,109
What are you doin'
in here, Louis?

554
00:22:56,228 --> 00:22:58,196
I'm here to apologize.

555
00:22:58,364 --> 00:23:00,531
You wanted to be my friend,
and I rejected you

556
00:23:00,667 --> 00:23:04,137
because you were
trying to protect her.

557
00:23:04,272 --> 00:23:08,110
You must've felt so alone.

558
00:23:08,211 --> 00:23:09,311
And believe me,

559
00:23:09,446 --> 00:23:12,216
I know what it's like
to feel alone.

560
00:23:12,350 --> 00:23:14,953
- You're not alone.
- Oh, I am.

561
00:23:15,087 --> 00:23:17,522
Jessica said that I'm
responsible for everything

562
00:23:17,658 --> 00:23:20,277
that's happening,
and she was right.

563
00:23:20,395 --> 00:23:22,980
No one made me make that
dirty deal with Forstman,

564
00:23:23,115 --> 00:23:24,399
and now she won't forgive me.

565
00:23:24,534 --> 00:23:27,704
I'm alone.

566
00:23:27,822 --> 00:23:30,324
And you want me to
talk to her for you.

567
00:23:30,459 --> 00:23:34,079
You're the only
one I can go to, Jeff.

568
00:23:34,214 --> 00:23:37,634
And you're
the closest person she has.

569
00:23:39,422 --> 00:23:41,222
Sure, Louis.

570
00:23:41,341 --> 00:23:44,227
I'll talk to Jessica for you.

571
00:23:51,405 --> 00:23:52,405
Hey.

572
00:23:52,523 --> 00:23:53,523
Hey.

573
00:23:53,640 --> 00:23:54,951
You're off the hook with Cahill.

574
00:23:54,976 --> 00:23:57,713
He's gonna start with me
and Harvey in the morning.

575
00:23:57,814 --> 00:23:58,880
Am I?

576
00:23:58,982 --> 00:24:01,852
- Are you what?
- Off the hook.

577
00:24:01,986 --> 00:24:05,924
Rachel...

578
00:24:06,041 --> 00:24:09,211
I didn't mean
for what happened to happen.

579
00:24:09,347 --> 00:24:12,383
- But it did.
- I know.

580
00:24:14,187 --> 00:24:15,738
- Mike...
- I still haven't gotten

581
00:24:15,872 --> 00:24:17,890
a full night's sleep
since you told me.

582
00:24:18,025 --> 00:24:21,562
I know that you're
not completely over it.

583
00:24:23,901 --> 00:24:25,701
But things are gonna
come up, and I...

584
00:24:25,852 --> 00:24:29,406
Want me to not be
vicious and cruel.

585
00:24:29,542 --> 00:24:31,993
Do you think that's possible?

586
00:24:32,162 --> 00:24:34,390
I hope so.

587
00:24:34,415 --> 00:24:37,418
I hope so too.

588
00:24:39,589 --> 00:24:42,536
If it means anything,

589
00:24:42,560 --> 00:24:44,177
I haven't gotten
a good night's sleep

590
00:24:44,312 --> 00:24:47,899
since any of this
happened either.

591
00:24:48,050 --> 00:24:51,521
Maybe we can both
give it a shot tonight.

592
00:25:00,334 --> 00:25:02,285
Let's start with one
for you, Mr. Ross.

593
00:25:02,421 --> 00:25:07,209
Were you on good terms
with him when you left?

594
00:25:07,344 --> 00:25:09,212
- Yes.
- Oh.

595
00:25:09,347 --> 00:25:10,608
Well, then, why weren't
you representing him

596
00:25:10,632 --> 00:25:12,349
on the Gillis Industries
takeover?

597
00:25:12,468 --> 00:25:13,829
Because he wasn't
technically our client

598
00:25:13,854 --> 00:25:15,137
at the time.

599
00:25:15,272 --> 00:25:16,639
Well, if you're
on such good terms,

600
00:25:16,757 --> 00:25:17,757
why wasn't he a client?

601
00:25:17,775 --> 00:25:20,478
Because sometimes
brothers fight.

602
00:25:20,596 --> 00:25:23,499
And sometimes
they pretend to fight.

603
00:25:23,633 --> 00:25:24,950
What are you getting at?

604
00:25:25,102 --> 00:25:26,953
I'm getting at the fact
that you supposedly

605
00:25:27,105 --> 00:25:28,433
were fighting when
this thing started,

606
00:25:28,457 --> 00:25:30,959
yet you claim that you
weren't fighting when it ended.

607
00:25:31,110 --> 00:25:32,878
Who says we weren't
fighting when it ended?

608
00:25:32,997 --> 00:25:34,497
You did,
when you hired him back.

609
00:25:34,616 --> 00:25:37,335
Yeah, and the cowboys
signed Deion Sanders,

610
00:25:37,470 --> 00:25:38,480
even though they were rivals.

611
00:25:38,504 --> 00:25:39,754
You want to know why?

612
00:25:39,923 --> 00:25:41,367
'Cause he was awesome,
and they were tired of him

613
00:25:41,392 --> 00:25:42,893
intercepting their passes.

614
00:25:43,011 --> 00:25:44,678
He didn't intercept passes
for you.

615
00:25:44,813 --> 00:25:45,813
He fumbled the ball.

616
00:25:45,931 --> 00:25:47,375
Bullshit. He hit
it out of the park.

617
00:25:47,400 --> 00:25:48,934
What park are you playing at?

618
00:25:49,070 --> 00:25:52,406
He sides with Walter Gillis,
buys a ton of shares,

619
00:25:52,524 --> 00:25:53,608
then ditches poor Walter,

620
00:25:53,742 --> 00:25:55,286
and then walks away
from the whole thing.

621
00:25:55,311 --> 00:25:57,172
Why would you even want
a guy like this on your team?

622
00:25:57,197 --> 00:25:58,448
What am I missing?

623
00:25:58,616 --> 00:26:00,260
You're missing the fact
that he kicked ass

624
00:26:00,285 --> 00:26:03,171
his first time out, and anybody
would be lucky to have him.

625
00:26:03,322 --> 00:26:05,290
Then why didn't
anybody take him?

626
00:26:05,425 --> 00:26:06,626
What?

627
00:26:06,761 --> 00:26:08,962
I checked with every
major law firm in the city,

628
00:26:09,098 --> 00:26:11,215
and not one of them
received a resume from you.

629
00:26:11,351 --> 00:26:13,997
Why is that?
Because it's clear as day.

630
00:26:14,021 --> 00:26:16,306
You're hiding something,
and I'll tell you what it is.

631
00:26:16,441 --> 00:26:18,693
It's because you always
knew that he was coming back

632
00:26:18,844 --> 00:26:21,364
because you and he were in
this together the whole time.

633
00:26:21,482 --> 00:26:23,616
The problem with your
theory is neither one of us

634
00:26:23,734 --> 00:26:25,368
got a nickel from
this alleged collusion,

635
00:26:25,520 --> 00:26:26,870
and you've got no proof we did.

636
00:26:27,022 --> 00:26:28,050
Yeah, and you're
never gonna find any,

637
00:26:28,074 --> 00:26:31,077
because it doesn't exist.

638
00:26:31,211 --> 00:26:33,139
So you're both insisting
that neither one of you

639
00:26:33,164 --> 00:26:34,364
got any money?

640
00:26:34,500 --> 00:26:35,500
Damn right.

641
00:26:35,501 --> 00:26:38,804
That tells me
that someone else did.

642
00:26:41,008 --> 00:26:43,143
Thank you, gentlemen.

643
00:26:43,261 --> 00:26:45,523
I believe you showed me where
I should focus my manpower.

644
00:26:45,548 --> 00:26:48,601
Somewhere in those files
there's a payment

645
00:26:48,736 --> 00:26:51,438
from somewhere to someone,
and I'm gonna find it,

646
00:26:51,574 --> 00:26:54,660
because you can't hide
money from the S.E.C.

647
00:27:01,107 --> 00:27:03,660
Son of a bitch.

648
00:27:04,627 --> 00:27:06,761
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Tell you what?

649
00:27:06,913 --> 00:27:09,098
About Louis making
a dirty deal with Forstman.

650
00:27:09,250 --> 00:27:11,601
- He told you.
- He thought I already knew.

651
00:27:11,753 --> 00:27:13,521
He found out we were together,

652
00:27:13,639 --> 00:27:16,225
and unlike you, he assumed
that people in relationships

653
00:27:16,393 --> 00:27:17,393
share shit like that.

654
00:27:17,394 --> 00:27:19,445
Goddamn ticking time bomb.

655
00:27:19,564 --> 00:27:21,532
Do you hear yourself?

656
00:27:21,651 --> 00:27:23,985
I'm coming to you with
a problem between you and me,

657
00:27:24,121 --> 00:27:25,905
and you're focused on Louis.

658
00:27:26,039 --> 00:27:28,074
I'm focused on Louis
because right now his actions

659
00:27:28,209 --> 00:27:29,470
threaten this entire firm.

660
00:27:29,495 --> 00:27:31,746
Which brings me right
back to where we started.

661
00:27:31,882 --> 00:27:33,259
Why didn't you tell me
about Louis

662
00:27:33,283 --> 00:27:36,386
when I asked you what
the dirt on Woodall was for?

663
00:27:36,505 --> 00:27:38,923
I didn't tell you
because I didn't want you

664
00:27:39,058 --> 00:27:43,096
in the position of having
to lie for me in a deposition.

665
00:27:43,230 --> 00:27:48,236
Is that "focused
on you and me "enough?

666
00:27:48,354 --> 00:27:50,155
Jessica...

667
00:27:50,307 --> 00:27:51,741
When are you gonna understand

668
00:27:51,859 --> 00:27:54,278
that I can handle
crossing lines,

669
00:27:54,413 --> 00:27:56,531
but I won't
handle you lying to me?

670
00:27:59,086 --> 00:28:00,366
Now, how much trouble are we in?

671
00:28:00,487 --> 00:28:03,457
That's what I'm gonna find out.

672
00:28:08,599 --> 00:28:10,600
- Louis, did you see this?
- No, what is it?

673
00:28:10,719 --> 00:28:14,306
It's Cahill's deposition
with Harvey and Mike.

674
00:28:14,441 --> 00:28:18,362
Skip to the end.

675
00:28:18,512 --> 00:28:21,115
Jesus Christ, he's honing in
like a bloodhound.

676
00:28:21,233 --> 00:28:22,817
It's only a matter of time.

677
00:28:22,986 --> 00:28:24,597
There's got to be a way
we can get this filed...

678
00:28:24,622 --> 00:28:25,632
There isn't.

679
00:28:25,656 --> 00:28:27,657
- Louis.
- I'm done.

680
00:28:31,465 --> 00:28:33,833
I'm done.

681
00:28:36,004 --> 00:28:37,388
And if I don't do something now,

682
00:28:37,506 --> 00:28:40,092
so are Harvey and Mike.

683
00:28:40,227 --> 00:28:43,540
- Where are you going?
- To finish what I started.

684
00:28:43,564 --> 00:28:44,848
- You know what I think?
- What?

685
00:28:45,017 --> 00:28:46,661
I think we both could've
used a better lawyer

686
00:28:46,686 --> 00:28:47,903
in that deposition.

687
00:28:48,054 --> 00:28:50,072
- You think this is funny?
- No, I don't.

688
00:28:50,224 --> 00:28:51,608
Then help me figure a way out,

689
00:28:51,743 --> 00:28:54,423
because if we don't, they're
gonna find out about Louis,

690
00:28:54,447 --> 00:28:56,531
and everything Cahill's
been saying about us

691
00:28:56,700 --> 00:28:58,468
is gonna start looking true.

692
00:28:58,602 --> 00:29:00,722
We have to stop Cahill from
going through those files.

693
00:29:00,738 --> 00:29:02,350
- We tried that.
- We have to try again.

694
00:29:02,375 --> 00:29:04,877
We have to prove that Cahill
is only on this investigation

695
00:29:05,012 --> 00:29:06,345
because Woodall hates you.

696
00:29:06,464 --> 00:29:09,217
The problem is we don't
have a link between them.

697
00:29:09,385 --> 00:29:11,302
And they have a link
between Jessica and Malone.

698
00:29:11,438 --> 00:29:13,772
So we'd have to convince
Judge Hopkins

699
00:29:13,923 --> 00:29:16,787
their relationship has nothing
to do with this whole thing,

700
00:29:16,812 --> 00:29:19,958
which...
We'll never be able to do.

701
00:29:19,982 --> 00:29:22,094
How do they even know
about Jessica and Malone?

702
00:29:22,119 --> 00:29:24,320
I don't know.
Someone at the S.E.C. must've

703
00:29:24,439 --> 00:29:26,300
seen them together while
Malone was still working there.

704
00:29:26,324 --> 00:29:27,645
You think
they were holding hands?

705
00:29:27,660 --> 00:29:29,604
Come on, Harvey, this is
Jessica we're talking about.

706
00:29:29,629 --> 00:29:31,247
Talking about me, what?

707
00:29:31,381 --> 00:29:32,665
Holy shit, you're right.

708
00:29:32,783 --> 00:29:35,112
She was married,
and I didn't even know it.

709
00:29:35,137 --> 00:29:37,088
Cahill had us followed
without authorization.

710
00:29:37,223 --> 00:29:38,567
And there's no way
he had authorization

711
00:29:38,591 --> 00:29:40,759
to follow a government official.

712
00:29:40,895 --> 00:29:42,178
You need to pay
that man a visit.

713
00:29:42,297 --> 00:29:44,900
I need to pay that man a visit.

714
00:29:48,689 --> 00:29:51,325
Yep.

715
00:29:51,477 --> 00:29:52,754
Oh, sorry, maybe you
didn't hear the news.

716
00:29:52,778 --> 00:29:54,529
Jeff Malone doesn't
work here anymore.

717
00:29:54,664 --> 00:29:56,092
And I'm guessing you know
exactly where he is,

718
00:29:56,116 --> 00:29:57,796
since you've been
following him for months.

719
00:29:57,818 --> 00:29:59,263
I haven't been
following him at all.

720
00:29:59,288 --> 00:30:00,555
I've been following you.

721
00:30:00,689 --> 00:30:02,333
Well, it doesn't really
matter who you followed,

722
00:30:02,358 --> 00:30:04,560
since there's no way
you got authorization.

723
00:30:04,695 --> 00:30:06,546
You think Judge Hopkins
is going to look into

724
00:30:06,664 --> 00:30:08,015
those dreamy brown eyes of yours

725
00:30:08,166 --> 00:30:09,767
and drop the case
because of that?

726
00:30:09,886 --> 00:30:12,137
No, I think
you're gonna drop it.

727
00:30:12,306 --> 00:30:14,190
- Hmm.
- 'Cause if you don't,

728
00:30:14,342 --> 00:30:16,193
it's no longer
malicious prosecution.

729
00:30:16,344 --> 00:30:17,838
It's abuse of power.

730
00:30:17,863 --> 00:30:20,148
You did it to Mike Ross,
you did it to me,

731
00:30:20,283 --> 00:30:22,234
and we're gonna find out
who else you did it to.

732
00:30:22,370 --> 00:30:23,547
Take a shot.

733
00:30:23,571 --> 00:30:24,998
It'll take you two years
to make a case,

734
00:30:25,023 --> 00:30:27,208
and even if it sticks,
I'll get a slap on the wrist,

735
00:30:27,360 --> 00:30:29,996
but Harvey Specter
will already be in prison.

736
00:30:30,131 --> 00:30:31,391
You dirty son of a bitch.

737
00:30:31,415 --> 00:30:33,216
Dirty?

738
00:30:33,368 --> 00:30:34,502
I may bend the rules,

739
00:30:34,637 --> 00:30:36,532
but I'm doing it
because you are guilty.

740
00:30:36,557 --> 00:30:38,007
That's exactly
what Eric Woodall said

741
00:30:38,175 --> 00:30:40,009
before we got his ass fired.

742
00:30:40,145 --> 00:30:41,539
Well, I'll tell you
what I told Harvey.

743
00:30:41,564 --> 00:30:42,847
I'm not Eric Woodall,

744
00:30:42,982 --> 00:30:44,493
and sending
some guy named Louis Litt

745
00:30:44,518 --> 00:30:46,569
to confess to some
fabricated bullshit

746
00:30:46,720 --> 00:30:48,605
isn't gonna make me stop.

747
00:30:48,739 --> 00:30:51,609
It's gonna make me
come at you harder.

748
00:30:58,253 --> 00:31:01,873
Maybe no news is good news.

749
00:31:02,009 --> 00:31:03,570
All right, maybe
no news means bad news.

750
00:31:05,013 --> 00:31:07,882
When it comes to Jessica,
no news is no news.

751
00:31:08,017 --> 00:31:09,851
Harvey, you have a minute?

752
00:31:09,970 --> 00:31:11,581
What do you want, Louis?

753
00:31:11,606 --> 00:31:13,273
I'd prefer to tell you alone.

754
00:31:13,391 --> 00:31:15,752
Mike knows everything,
so spit it out.

755
00:31:15,777 --> 00:31:18,229
Okay, um, but I think
you both should know

756
00:31:18,364 --> 00:31:19,959
that whatever happens to me,

757
00:31:19,984 --> 00:31:22,570
I had the dignity to come to you
and tell you like a man.

758
00:31:22,704 --> 00:31:24,121
- What did you do?
- He did exactly

759
00:31:24,273 --> 00:31:25,707
what I told him not to do.

760
00:31:25,825 --> 00:31:27,936
He went to the S.E.C.,
and he confessed.

761
00:31:27,961 --> 00:31:28,961
Wait, Jessica, please.

762
00:31:29,113 --> 00:31:30,664
Please what? Don't kill you?

763
00:31:30,798 --> 00:31:32,466
Because one thing is for sure.

764
00:31:32,585 --> 00:31:35,221
When all this is over, I'm gonna
fire the shit out of you.

765
00:31:35,338 --> 00:31:37,423
Fire me?

766
00:31:37,558 --> 00:31:38,758
You should be thanking me.

767
00:31:38,926 --> 00:31:40,343
I read the transcript.

768
00:31:40,479 --> 00:31:42,813
Cahill knows
about the hidden payment.

769
00:31:42,965 --> 00:31:44,933
I went there to save all of you!

770
00:31:45,069 --> 00:31:47,520
And I told you
the second you did that,

771
00:31:47,639 --> 00:31:49,773
these two go from being
probably innocent

772
00:31:49,909 --> 00:31:51,443
to definitely guilty.

773
00:31:51,578 --> 00:31:54,281
- Goddamn idiot.
- Wait a second. We...

774
00:31:54,415 --> 00:31:56,783
Louis, if you confessed,
then why are you here?

775
00:31:56,952 --> 00:31:58,836
- They sent me home.
- What?

776
00:31:58,987 --> 00:32:00,232
What exactly did you
say to Cahill?

777
00:32:00,257 --> 00:32:01,257
I didn't talk to Cahill.

778
00:32:01,258 --> 00:32:02,852
I mean, I was in his office,

779
00:32:02,877 --> 00:32:05,178
but then Eric Woodall comes in,
takes me down the hall.

780
00:32:05,330 --> 00:32:06,330
I confessed to him.

781
00:32:06,348 --> 00:32:08,432
You told the head of the S.E.C.

782
00:32:08,551 --> 00:32:10,646
you committed a federal crime,
and he sent you on your way?

783
00:32:10,671 --> 00:32:11,998
- Yes.
- And he didn't try to get you

784
00:32:12,023 --> 00:32:13,607
to implicate Harvey?
No, in fact,

785
00:32:13,725 --> 00:32:15,202
he didn't seem to care at all.

786
00:32:15,227 --> 00:32:17,656
And you specifically told him
about your deal with Forstman?

787
00:32:17,681 --> 00:32:19,248
Yeah. He said
they're not interested

788
00:32:19,350 --> 00:32:20,484
in little fish like me.

789
00:32:20,618 --> 00:32:21,828
You might be
a little fish to him,

790
00:32:21,853 --> 00:32:23,821
but Forstman is a goddamn whale.

791
00:32:23,956 --> 00:32:24,989
It doesn't matter.

792
00:32:25,158 --> 00:32:26,678
Woodall hates me:
I'm the one he wants.

793
00:32:26,794 --> 00:32:29,245
But why not use Forstman
to reel you in

794
00:32:29,381 --> 00:32:31,082
and get two
for the price of one?

795
00:32:31,199 --> 00:32:32,416
Unless for some reason.

796
00:32:32,552 --> 00:32:35,805
Woodall doesn't want to drag
Forstman into this.

797
00:32:35,939 --> 00:32:38,041
Because they're in bed together.

798
00:32:38,176 --> 00:32:39,910
That's a big leap.

799
00:32:40,046 --> 00:32:41,123
Harvey, you said
you told Forstman

800
00:32:41,147 --> 00:32:42,491
the S.E.C. was on his ass,
and he acted

801
00:32:42,516 --> 00:32:44,050
like he was wearing
a teflon suit.

802
00:32:44,185 --> 00:32:45,619
He acted the same way with me.

803
00:32:45,753 --> 00:32:47,654
And when assholes
act invincible,

804
00:32:47,790 --> 00:32:49,424
it's because
they think they are.

805
00:32:49,526 --> 00:32:51,443
It's the only
thing that makes sense.

806
00:32:51,561 --> 00:32:53,412
You two find the link
between those two,

807
00:32:53,564 --> 00:32:56,500
and find it tonight.

808
00:33:09,458 --> 00:33:11,326
This could be something.

809
00:33:11,460 --> 00:33:13,294
Look.

810
00:33:13,413 --> 00:33:15,497
In April of last year,

811
00:33:15,666 --> 00:33:17,884
Charles Forstman made huge
contributions

812
00:33:18,003 --> 00:33:20,806
to these three senators.

813
00:33:20,923 --> 00:33:22,941
So what? He's got money to burn.

814
00:33:23,077 --> 00:33:24,427
Yeah, but four weeks later,

815
00:33:24,562 --> 00:33:26,023
these same senators
helped appoint Eric Woodall

816
00:33:26,047 --> 00:33:27,898
to head the New York office
of the S.E.C.

817
00:33:28,050 --> 00:33:29,328
That doesn't prove a direct link

818
00:33:29,353 --> 00:33:30,903
between Forstman and Woodall.

819
00:33:31,054 --> 00:33:33,489
- It's still a link, Harvey.
- And it's how this shit works.

820
00:33:33,608 --> 00:33:35,803
It's totally legal, and it's
not gonna do a thing for us.

821
00:33:35,828 --> 00:33:36,888
Well, what do you want?

822
00:33:36,913 --> 00:33:38,793
A picture of him handing Woodall
a bag of money?

823
00:33:38,915 --> 00:33:40,059
Because we're never
gonna get that.

824
00:33:40,084 --> 00:33:42,252
Maybe we don't need it.

825
00:33:42,404 --> 00:33:45,290
You better be here
with something good.

826
00:33:49,012 --> 00:33:51,347
I am.

827
00:33:51,466 --> 00:33:53,600
Charles Forstman made me take
a million dollars

828
00:33:53,752 --> 00:33:55,113
to keep from turning on him.

829
00:33:55,138 --> 00:33:57,691
What if he made Woodall
take a taste too?

830
00:33:57,809 --> 00:33:59,192
You think we don't know that?

831
00:33:59,311 --> 00:34:00,661
That's the "bag of money"
problem.

832
00:34:00,763 --> 00:34:01,973
It wouldn't be a bag of money,

833
00:34:01,998 --> 00:34:03,119
because if it's untraceable,

834
00:34:03,233 --> 00:34:04,577
he wouldn't have leverage
over Woodall.

835
00:34:04,602 --> 00:34:06,453
That's great,
but we can't get access

836
00:34:06,603 --> 00:34:07,714
to Woodall's bank accounts.

837
00:34:07,739 --> 00:34:09,073
We can't.

838
00:34:09,208 --> 00:34:10,375
But Cahill can.

839
00:34:10,493 --> 00:34:11,993
Okay, what good
does that do us, huh?

840
00:34:12,129 --> 00:34:16,133
They're together.
What if they're not?

841
00:34:16,284 --> 00:34:18,446
I told you,
I went to see Cahill.

842
00:34:18,471 --> 00:34:19,921
He wasn't there.

843
00:34:20,056 --> 00:34:21,841
Five minutes later,
Eric Woodall shows up.

844
00:34:21,959 --> 00:34:23,527
I say two words:
"Charles Forstman."

845
00:34:23,661 --> 00:34:25,372
He hustles me outta there
like I'm his mistress

846
00:34:25,397 --> 00:34:26,931
with his wife
coming up the driveway.

847
00:34:27,066 --> 00:34:29,936
Why would he not wait
for Cahill?

848
00:34:30,070 --> 00:34:32,606
You want us to get Cahill
to turn on Woodall.

849
00:34:32,741 --> 00:34:35,610
- Wouldn't you?
- Maybe Louis is right.

850
00:34:35,745 --> 00:34:37,756
Maybe there are lines that
Woodall's willing to cross

851
00:34:37,781 --> 00:34:38,791
that Cahill won't.

852
00:34:38,815 --> 00:34:40,116
That's a big "maybe."

853
00:34:40,251 --> 00:34:42,119
You have a better idea?

854
00:34:42,254 --> 00:34:44,790
No, I don't.

855
00:34:44,925 --> 00:34:46,759
Look, guys, we all know

856
00:34:46,878 --> 00:34:50,348
that Jessica's gonna
fire me after this.

857
00:34:50,499 --> 00:34:52,383
I just want to help,

858
00:34:52,519 --> 00:34:54,553
make things right.

859
00:34:57,058 --> 00:34:58,692
Get your coat.

860
00:35:06,321 --> 00:35:08,990
You really looking through
those all by yourself?

861
00:35:09,158 --> 00:35:10,802
Are the Witches of Eastwick
here to tell me

862
00:35:10,827 --> 00:35:12,495
how to run my department?

863
00:35:12,663 --> 00:35:14,191
We're here to make
things easier for you.

864
00:35:14,216 --> 00:35:15,333
Oh.

865
00:35:15,501 --> 00:35:19,221
Buried in one of these boxes
is a copy of this.

866
00:35:19,373 --> 00:35:20,507
It proves collusion.

867
00:35:20,641 --> 00:35:22,141
Not between me and Mike.

868
00:35:22,260 --> 00:35:25,347
Between him
and Charles Forstman.

869
00:35:25,481 --> 00:35:26,909
And you're just
gonna give this to me?

870
00:35:26,934 --> 00:35:27,994
Yup.

871
00:35:28,018 --> 00:35:29,028
And you're gonna
give it to Woodall,

872
00:35:29,052 --> 00:35:30,486
and we're gonna
see what he says.

873
00:35:30,605 --> 00:35:32,550
And what he's gonna say is
that he doesn't give a shit

874
00:35:32,575 --> 00:35:33,691
about Charles Forstman,

875
00:35:33,859 --> 00:35:35,504
just like he told me
when I confessed to him.

876
00:35:35,529 --> 00:35:36,745
What exactly are you implying?

877
00:35:36,897 --> 00:35:38,114
We're not implying anything.

878
00:35:38,232 --> 00:35:40,192
We're telling you that
after Woodall lost his job,

879
00:35:40,202 --> 00:35:42,370
Forstman got him installed
at the S.E.C.,

880
00:35:42,505 --> 00:35:45,208
and all he had to do
in return was protect Forstman.

881
00:35:45,342 --> 00:35:46,403
Where's the proof?

882
00:35:46,427 --> 00:35:47,961
In Eric Woodall's bank accounts.

883
00:35:48,096 --> 00:35:50,130
Oh, so you want me to go
through his bank accounts

884
00:35:50,266 --> 00:35:51,550
based on your word.

885
00:35:51,717 --> 00:35:53,385
You followed us
based on his bullshit.

886
00:35:53,520 --> 00:35:54,760
Based on the word of my friend.

887
00:35:54,856 --> 00:35:56,534
Why don't you ask your
friend if he has a problem

888
00:35:56,558 --> 00:35:58,058
giving you access
to his accounts?

889
00:35:58,160 --> 00:35:59,440
If he doesn't, then we're wrong,

890
00:35:59,563 --> 00:36:01,497
and we've just handed you
the smoking gun.

891
00:36:01,631 --> 00:36:03,482
And if you're right,
you want me to let him

892
00:36:03,618 --> 00:36:05,068
off the hook for what he did.

893
00:36:05,203 --> 00:36:07,238
Woodall already
said he's a little fish.

894
00:36:07,373 --> 00:36:09,791
We're asking you to
throw him back in the water.

895
00:36:09,943 --> 00:36:11,104
What the hell's
going on in here?

896
00:36:11,128 --> 00:36:12,138
Hey, Eric.

897
00:36:12,163 --> 00:36:13,330
It's good to see you again.

898
00:36:13,465 --> 00:36:14,775
Sean, isn't this great
that we're all together?

899
00:36:14,800 --> 00:36:16,778
Did you see me come in?

900
00:36:16,803 --> 00:36:17,970
Afraid of what I'd say?

901
00:36:18,121 --> 00:36:20,339
I have no idea what
you're talking about.

902
00:36:20,458 --> 00:36:21,619
Eric, these gentlemen
came in here

903
00:36:21,643 --> 00:36:23,143
with these wild accusations

904
00:36:23,295 --> 00:36:25,480
that you and Charles Forstman
are in bed together.

905
00:36:25,632 --> 00:36:29,129
A bed filled
with Forstman's money.

906
00:36:29,153 --> 00:36:31,772
Yes, Charles Forstman
gave me millions of dollars.

907
00:36:31,941 --> 00:36:33,525
That's why I drive a Subaru.

908
00:36:33,660 --> 00:36:35,621
Yeah, I didn't spend
the money he gave me either.

909
00:36:35,646 --> 00:36:37,223
That doesn't mean he
didn't make me take it.

910
00:36:37,248 --> 00:36:39,166
I don't give a shit.
I'm not you.

911
00:36:39,285 --> 00:36:41,005
Eric, obviously these
allegations are crazy.

912
00:36:41,153 --> 00:36:42,921
Of course they are.

913
00:36:43,040 --> 00:36:45,291
So just...

914
00:36:45,426 --> 00:36:48,630
Prove it to 'em
you've got nothing to hide.

915
00:36:52,503 --> 00:36:53,603
This is ridiculous.

916
00:36:53,721 --> 00:36:56,974
I... am not gonna dignify...

917
00:37:01,866 --> 00:37:05,236
I'm your boss.

918
00:37:05,371 --> 00:37:07,155
Gentlemen, give me a minute.

919
00:37:07,290 --> 00:37:08,407
Yep.

920
00:37:10,244 --> 00:37:14,632
And by a minute,
he means 10 to 15 years.

921
00:37:14,751 --> 00:37:16,395
In about a half an hour,
you're gonna need

922
00:37:16,419 --> 00:37:17,920
a really good lawyer.

923
00:37:18,055 --> 00:37:20,340
And when that happens,

924
00:37:20,475 --> 00:37:24,062
don't call me.

925
00:37:34,495 --> 00:37:36,096
Which lawyer do you
think Woodall called?

926
00:37:36,114 --> 00:37:38,092
Well, if he was smart,
he would call Daniel Hardman.

927
00:37:38,117 --> 00:37:40,501
The best person to defend
a criminal is a criminal.

928
00:37:40,620 --> 00:37:43,038
And Hardman's a much better
lawyer than you anyways.

929
00:37:43,174 --> 00:37:45,458
Oh, very funny.

930
00:37:45,594 --> 00:37:47,128
Thank you.

931
00:37:47,263 --> 00:37:50,550
Thank you, Louis.

932
00:37:59,564 --> 00:38:01,698
Please.

933
00:38:01,817 --> 00:38:03,201
I'll try.

934
00:38:10,712 --> 00:38:12,392
Donna told me she
already said this to you,

935
00:38:12,498 --> 00:38:15,478
but I want you to
hear it from me.

936
00:38:15,502 --> 00:38:19,840
I wouldn't be back here
if it wasn't for Louis.

937
00:38:19,958 --> 00:38:22,845
I'll take care of it.

938
00:38:29,472 --> 00:38:32,742
Woodall's taken care of,
and so is everything else.

939
00:38:32,860 --> 00:38:35,028
- Not everything.
- Jessica...

940
00:38:35,163 --> 00:38:37,883
Harvey, I've already
made up my mind.

941
00:38:38,017 --> 00:38:40,953
You weren't there.
He helped get us out of this.

942
00:38:41,088 --> 00:38:42,555
After he put us goddamn in it.

943
00:38:42,690 --> 00:38:44,491
And I put us in it just as much,

944
00:38:44,627 --> 00:38:45,960
the day I hired Mike Ross.

945
00:38:46,095 --> 00:38:48,129
Are you looking to save Louis,

946
00:38:48,298 --> 00:38:50,026
or to get yourself fired too?

947
00:38:50,051 --> 00:38:51,885
I'm saying he did some bad shit,

948
00:38:52,020 --> 00:38:54,472
but so have I, and so have you.

949
00:38:54,641 --> 00:38:56,775
You and I don't mess shit up.

950
00:38:56,894 --> 00:38:57,977
We fix it.

951
00:38:58,112 --> 00:38:59,229
Which is what he did today.

952
00:38:59,364 --> 00:39:00,915
You want to talk
about what he did?

953
00:39:01,049 --> 00:39:03,985
I told him not to confess,
and he went straight down

954
00:39:04,120 --> 00:39:06,321
to the S.E.C.,
and he sang like a canary,

955
00:39:06,490 --> 00:39:08,885
after he did the same
thing with Jeff Malone.

956
00:39:08,910 --> 00:39:10,204
- That doesn't...
- Doesn't what?

957
00:39:10,229 --> 00:39:12,731
That's just the tip
of the iceberg.

958
00:39:12,833 --> 00:39:15,368
Let's talk about
his greatest hits.

959
00:39:15,503 --> 00:39:18,606
Last year, he blew up
our merger negotiations

960
00:39:18,740 --> 00:39:20,474
because of a cat.

961
00:39:20,610 --> 00:39:24,514
This year, he led Mike Ross
straight to Charles Forstman.

962
00:39:24,649 --> 00:39:26,994
He unwound the Wexler shares
after I specifically told him

963
00:39:27,019 --> 00:39:29,437
not to, and to top it all off,

964
00:39:29,556 --> 00:39:32,359
he took a million-dollar
payout to commit tax fraud

965
00:39:32,527 --> 00:39:35,163
that could've landed
you ten years in jail.

966
00:39:35,281 --> 00:39:37,665
And he didn't tell us about
that until it was too late,

967
00:39:37,784 --> 00:39:40,035
and he only did that
because he had to.

968
00:39:40,171 --> 00:39:41,504
I'm still not doin' it.

969
00:39:41,622 --> 00:39:42,756
I tell him to do something,

970
00:39:42,908 --> 00:39:46,545
and he never goddamn does it.

971
00:39:46,679 --> 00:39:49,716
Now, I told myself
I'm gonna do something.

972
00:39:49,885 --> 00:39:52,721
And I'm gonna goddamn do it.

973
00:39:56,560 --> 00:39:58,527
Then let me do it.

974
00:40:03,119 --> 00:40:04,403
Why you and not me?

975
00:40:04,538 --> 00:40:06,823
Because you want
to deliver the message

976
00:40:06,959 --> 00:40:09,628
"his services
are no longer needed,"

977
00:40:09,779 --> 00:40:11,607
and I want to tell him
"good-bye."

978
00:40:11,631 --> 00:40:13,916
You're really going to do this?

979
00:40:28,521 --> 00:40:31,274
Harvey,
this place is all he has.

980
00:40:31,442 --> 00:40:33,109
I know.

981
00:40:35,314 --> 00:40:38,167
I'm coming with you.

982
00:40:46,430 --> 00:40:48,297
Dear Harvey and Jessica,

983
00:40:48,433 --> 00:40:50,027
there comes a time

984
00:40:50,052 --> 00:40:51,997
when a man must
look at himself in the mirror,

985
00:40:52,022 --> 00:40:53,605
to judge himself

986
00:40:53,723 --> 00:40:56,810
instead of waiting
to be judged by others.

987
00:40:56,979 --> 00:41:00,482
And for me, that time is now.

988
00:41:00,650 --> 00:41:02,534
You both know
I came to Pearson Specter

989
00:41:02,653 --> 00:41:05,205
right out of law school,
but what you may not know is

990
00:41:05,356 --> 00:41:08,493
this is the only place
I've ever worked.

991
00:41:08,627 --> 00:41:12,331
It's the only place
I've ever wanted to work.

992
00:41:12,467 --> 00:41:14,862
It is my life...

993
00:41:14,887 --> 00:41:17,473
It is my home...

994
00:41:17,590 --> 00:41:21,371
And the people that work here
are my family.

995
00:41:21,395 --> 00:41:23,313
You're like my parents.

996
00:41:23,432 --> 00:41:25,566
And the partners,
they're like my brothers,

997
00:41:25,718 --> 00:41:28,738
and associates under my care
are like my children.

998
00:41:28,856 --> 00:41:30,690
And I'm ashamed
to admit it, but...

999
00:41:30,859 --> 00:41:34,245
I put all of you in jeopardy
for my own personal gain.

1000
00:41:34,396 --> 00:41:36,197
I told myself
it was for the greater good,

1001
00:41:36,333 --> 00:41:38,167
but the truth is
I just wanted to feel

1002
00:41:38,286 --> 00:41:41,839
on the same level
as both of you, I...

1003
00:41:41,957 --> 00:41:43,875
I can deny that no longer.

1004
00:41:44,010 --> 00:41:46,679
I can excuse
my actions no longer.

1005
00:41:46,797 --> 00:41:48,965
Although we've had our
differences over the years,

1006
00:41:49,084 --> 00:41:52,804
there are no two people
I respect more.

1007
00:41:52,940 --> 00:41:55,776
Your names are on the wall
for a reason,

1008
00:41:55,927 --> 00:41:58,813
and mine is not for a reason.

1009
00:41:58,948 --> 00:42:00,815
And I refuse to put
either one of you

1010
00:42:00,934 --> 00:42:03,369
through the pain
of having to fire me.

1011
00:42:03,488 --> 00:42:05,205
So effective immediately,

1012
00:42:05,324 --> 00:42:08,577
I, Louis Litt,

1013
00:42:08,745 --> 00:42:11,881
am resigning
from Pearson Specter.

1014
00:42:11,999 --> 00:42:13,275
Please take care of my home.

1015
00:42:13,280 --> 00:42:19,282
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man

