Previously on
Suits...
This is a copy of the letter
you wrote a copy
to the district attorney
when you threatened
expose me.
You ever do send that letter,
you're in the same boat as me.
You want to move in here?
I've only ever
been here twice,
and both times
were with you.
You beat me
on the dissolution negotiation,
you get your name
on the door.
If you think you're gonna win
this time,
you've got another thing
coming.
You ready to use
your relationship with Rachel
to get her father to turn?
Doesn't matter,
because I'm not gonna do that.
Folsom Foods.
This is about Harvey Specter,
Jessica Pearson,
and their divorce negotiations,
and you don't go to the one
you didn't marry
to stick it
to the one you did.
It's a check
from Folsom Foods.
It's the remainder
of what they owe us.
If you crush me,
I'll have nothing.
He was bullying me.
So you used me
to bully him back.
If you don't want
to live with me,
why don't you just tell me?
I just need some time.
- Hessington Oil just fired us.
- Scottie betrayed me.
I gave you my word,
and I honored it.
Something dropped
from the sky,
tilted everything in your favor
right after I cut you a break?
I am not going to dissolve
this merger.
You already signed
the agreement.
Then sue me.
Scottie didn't get us fired.
Ava Hessington did.
She's suing all of us.
I got into Stanford.
You have something
to say to me?
I'm sorry, Scottie.
I didn't believe you,
but you were telling the truth.
Why does it always
have to be so--
- I said I was sorry.
- You didn't mean it.
I meant it.
But just because I was wrong
about you betraying me
doesn't mean I was wrong
to think you might have done it.
See, this is what I mean,
Harvey.
If you thought anything of me,
you'd know I'd never do that.
I do think something
of you,
which is why I'm going to
tell you this: Get out.
Honor the dissolution agreement
and move on.
You've got to be
kidding me.
You want me to put
all the liability on Edward?
The liability
belongs on Edward.
So when you say that you think
something of me,
what you actually mean is
you want me to help you
to bail
on Darby International.
Scottie,
when this lawsuit's over,
there's not going to be
a Darby International.
- You don't know that.
- What I know is
you have a chance
to get another job
before everything hits the fan.
You won't in another week.
I won't need another job
when I right the ship.
You're not going to right
the ship.
If you were on that jury,
the only question you'd ask
is how many zeroes
to put on the check.
You want me to turn my back
on the man
that I've been in the foxhole
with for the last ten years.
Would you do the same?
If that man turned out
to have sanctioned murder
without my knowledge and let me
take the hit, I would.
Hmm.
Well...like it or not,
you're in the foxhole with me.
So order a glass
of your Macallan 20-pretentious,
and let's figure out how we're
going to fight this together.
You haven't said a word
all night.
Are we going to talk
about this or not?
What is there
to talk about?
This is why you didn't want
to decide
whether to live with me
or not, right?
Well, it isn't,
actually,
but you knew that I was
applying to Stanford,
and you said that you'd support
whatever decision I made.
I did, but then
you got into Columbia,
so I thought
that wouldn't matter anymore.
Because Stanford's
in California,
and Columbia's here.
And because Columbia
is an amazing school
and we said we love each other.
Yeah, but it's not
that simple.
It sounds that simple to me.
What I mean is
I'm not built
the same as you.
I need to decide
what school is better for me
before factoring in you or us
or anything else.
And how exactly
do you plan on doing that?
The same way that I make
all the important decisions
in my life,
by weighing the pros and cons
of both schools.
And where does not being
with me rank on that list?
You're missing the point.
I am trying to figure out
which school is best for me
in a vacuum.
No, you're missing the point.
You're trying to figure out
what school is best for you
as though I didn't exist,
but I do.
- Mike--
- Rachel, I'm not saying
that you have to
go to Columbia.
We're adults.
We're together.
At some point, you're going to
have to factor that in too.
- She go for it?
- No, she didn't.
Then if Scottie won't
separate from us amicably,
we'll make her do it
forcibly.
Jessica, I don't want to start
another war with her.
- Then what's your idea?
- My idea is
we act like lawyers
and we fight the lawsuit.
On its merits?
Edward Darby sanctioned murder.
We don't stand a chance.
- Jessica--
- Harvey, you know I'm right,
and it's what you told
Scottie--
it's the truth, and just because
she can't see it
doesn't mean
we have to live with it.
No, we don't.
I need you to get in a room
with Ava
and offer our testimony
against Edward
in exchange for taking our names
off the lawsuit.
What about when Scottie
finds out?
Thanks.
11:08.
For being late
to a settlement conference.
Tanner, what the hell are you
doing here, and how the hell
did you insinuate yourself
with Ava Hessington?
- Jealous?
- No, I just thought Hessington
was in the oil business,
not the snake oil business.
Ha ha.
They diversified.
- Where's Ava?
- Ava's not here,
because she's not interested
in your offer
to testify
against Edward Darby.
I'm not the one
who did this to her.
Aren't you? Didn't you pull
your typical bullshit
to get the original attorney
thrown off this case?
- To win the damn case.
- Well, instead of winning it,
it led to Ava being charged
with murder.
A charge I got her off of
by finding the people
who were actually responsible.
Sorry, Harv,
but that's not enough,
and Ava has no intention
of letting you off the hook.
Ava or you?
We both know
you tracked her down
because of your lifelong,
never-gonna-happen dream
to beat me.
I never heard
of Ava Hessington until
she walked through my door.
Bullshit.
You have a subscription
to Harvey Specter monthly,
and I know it.
Okay, you got me.
I knew exactly who she was
the second she walked
through my door--
my chance to take
your lunch money.
Well, let me make you
an advance payment.
Why don't you use this
to call your mom and tell her
to get the tissues ready,
because you're 0-2
against me,
and the 0 isn't the number
that's going to change.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ Suits 3x10 ♪
Stay
Original Air Date on September 17, 2013
♪ Y'all step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ The Greenback Boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
We should have known
Tanner was behind
this whole thing.
According to Tanner,
Ava went to him,
not the other way around.
- You believe that shit?
- Not for a second.
Who am I putting
in the cross hairs,
Tanner or Ava?
At the moment, no one.
Tanner's going to depose me,
then we'll see what we see.
Come on, Harvey,
you got to give me one of them.
You've got to be
kidding me.
You got girlfriend troubles,
don't you?
Okay, I'm just asking
for an assignment, that's all.
Don't tell me, quarterback
asked her to the prom?
Okay, first of all,
I specifically haven't
bothered you with any of this.
Until now.
I was just asking
for an assignment.
Captain Pinstripe's the one
who brought up the girlfriend,
and second of all,
people actually had girlfriends
after high school,
which you wouldn't know,
because emotionally,
you never graduated.
Well, I guess
you're the expert,
because the only thing you
graduated from is high school.
Why you got to go there,
man?
This predicts
a candidate's success rate,
and then this
cross-references it
with your firm's
employment needs.
Wait a second, you're running
two programs at the same time?
Yeah, I don't bend over
backwards for just anyone.
Hold on to that thought.
In the meantime, I need you
to put this guy on the list.
Uhhuh.
I already did.
Would you
look at this place?
I mean, it's like a war room
in here.
Mmhmm.
Speaking of wartime,
I'm in the mood
to do battle in the bedroom.
- Not now!
- Oh.
Muddles my mind.
I need to focus.
I get it, you want
to keep looking at candidates.
Yeah.
Check out this bad boy
right here.
- Where'd you get this?
- Harvard archives.
Think this guy's
partner material?
I'm ready to go
to the other room.
Thought
that'd do the trick.
We should bring this in,
tape it to the wall.
There's already 50
taped to the ceiling.
You won't be
looking at the ceiling.
You want this guy
to join us?
- We're running out of time.
- Oh.
Tanner's deposing Harvey.
We need to talk about it.
- Who's going to handle it?
- I am.
I don't want to step
on your toes,
but don't we want to consider
outside counsel?
We've gone
down that road before.
Turns out Harvey doesn't
play well with others.
Don't I know it.
But I still think
it's a good idea
to have outside counsel
in that room.
I don't think
it's a good idea
to have anyone else
in that room.
So you brought me in here
to tell me
that you don't want me
to be a part of it?
I brought you in here
to tell you to keep your cool.
I appreciate the condescending
words of wisdom, but I've sat in
on about 1,000 depositions
and I've never broken a sweat.
You've never sat in one
with Travis Tanner.
You're gonna need
a thick skin,
'cause he's gonna try
to get under it.
- I'm not the one being deposed.
- Doesn't matter.
Last time he deposed Harvey,
it ended with Harvey
punching him in the face.
That's Harvey, not me.
And if Harvey hadn't done it,
I might have.
What are you talking about?
Tanner knew
all about Harvey's mother.
Came with a whole story
about how I'm Harvey's mother
and what Harvey wants to do
to his mother,
and that story was bullshit.
I get it.
He's not going to need
a bullshit story with me.
Stanford class schedule
and a list of every flight
from here
to Northern California.
I would get a lot of time off,
and it's really not that far.
So I guess this means
you've made your decision.
Mike, I need you
to listen to me.
I love you.
That's over here.
I need to decide
where I want to go to school.
That's over here.
But I want to be with you
no matter what,
and that's in here.
I'm onboard with that,
Rachel,
there's just one problem.
If you say that long-distance
relationships don't work--
I know,
you don't want to hear it.
Because we're not
most people.
I don't know anyone
that has ever
made a long-distance
relationship work.
Do you?
Mike, I need
to be able to breathe
to make this decision.
I'm not the one
that's making it that you can't.
The facts are, but the facts
aren't going to change.
You choose to go to Stanford,
most likely it means we're done.
I don't think you could be
any better than that.
It's like you read my mind.
I have a reward for you.
Oh, please, if it's a picture
of me as an astronaut,
I can't right now.
Brian Galloway.
Top of his class, Law Review,
and one cutthroat mother--
Oh, my God,
he's perfect.
You were hiding him
from me?
I've been saving him
for you.
Now, Louis, let's you and I
take the rest of the day off.
- The rest of the day?
- Yeah, we can play hooky.
It'll be fun.
There's a Mastodon exhibit
on loan from Bangkok.
Sheila!
You know that I can't
be unfaithful to my firm
like that.
I mean, it's bad enough
we took a 77-minute break
to do what we just did.
I understand.
You're dedicated
to your work.
It's one of the things
that I admire about you.
Thank you.
In fact, unless you have
any other candidates for me,
I really have to go.
Thank you.
Donna.
Oh, he's not here.
Is there something
that I can help you with?
Come to think of it,
I'm not one for office gossip,
but I have to know.
Are Briscoe and Linhart dating?
Oh, my God,
big time,
and it is drama
with a capital "D."
I knew it.
What about van Giessen
and Schwarz?
Oh, they were,
but it's done-zo.
Van Giessen thinks Schwarz
got too cozy with Boone.
- Tax law Boone?
- Bankruptcy Boone.
- I thought she was gay.
- No, she's not.
What?
I knew you'd know.
I always do.
How long have Mike Ross
and Rachel Zane been dating?
Um, a few months.
- So it's not casual?
- No, it's not.
Which means
he told Robert Zane's daughter
his secret.
Jessica, I know
what you're thinking--
You have no idea
what I'm thinking.
But for now, I'm thinking
that you're not going to say
anything about this
to either one of them.
And that's not a request.
I won't say a word.
Jesus, you look like shit.
I was up all night.
I couldn't sleep.
I told you I didn't need
anything on Tanner yet.
I'm not here to talk
about Tanner
or the lawsuit or the merger,
I just...
I want to know
how you do it.
How I do what?
Not let people in.
I need to know.
You don't know
what I do and don't do.
What I know is that
you seem to have relationships
again and again
and they don't eat you up
or spit you out
or seem to affect you at all.
I have a picture
of Dorian Gray
hanging in my closet.
It's not funny.
I wasn't joking.
I was trying to get you to leave
so I could have my morning
without you judging me.
Harvey,
I'm not judging you, all right?
I'm just--I just need to know
what your mind-set is.
My mind-set is,
I don't talk about it.
I don't want
to talk about it.
I keep my personal here
and my business over there.
I'm happy
that's working for you,
but it doesn't seem
to be working for me.
I wasn't giving you advice.
I was answering your question.
You want advice,
call Dr. Phil.
Harvey, I'm not trying
to attack you here, okay?
I'm struggling with something.
I just--
I'm trying to get
your take on it.
And I'm not trying to be
defensive, I'm just telling you
I don't know everything
about everything.
Look Mike, you want to know
how to be a lawyer,
I'm your man.
You want to know
how to deal with love,
That's not my area.
There's coffee made
and bagels in the fridge.
Why don't you
take the morning off?
I've got the deposition.
I got to go.
What the hell happened?
Brian Galloway's weighing offers
from seven different firms.
Eight if you count yours.
Why would you
do that to me?
Is this about
the Mastodon exhibit?
No, you're committed
to your work
as I'm committed to mine,
and unless I'm mistaken,
we never made a professional
commitment to each other.
Sheila,
I don't need a commitment
to know that what we have
is special and unique.
It's not special,
and it's definitely not unique.
Okay, well, then I'm going to
ask you a question,
and I'm only
going to ask it once.
Do you war room
with other firms?
You're a lawyer, Louis.
Don't ask questions
you don't want the answers to.
I'm sorry
you feel that way,
but if you can't handle me
seeing other firms,
then maybe you're not the man
that I thought you were,
and maybe you don't deserve
Brian Galloway.
Deserve him?
You don't get to make
that determination.
Yes, I do.
I'm Sheila Amanda Sazs,
and if I say
you don't deserve him,
you don't get to have him.
I don't care who you are.
If I want him,
I can have him,
and I'm going to take him
six ways from Sunday
and there's nothing you can do
to stop me.
Yes, there is,
because when I'm done
talking to him,
there's no way on earth he'll
end up at Pearson Darby Specter
or whatever bullshit name
you guys are calling yourselves
this week.
Now, get out of my way.
I have a plane to catch.
- You're early.
- So are you.
I should have known
something like this was coming
when you left
without saying a word.
What did you expect,
a fruit basket
for getting me out of a crime
your firm committed?
Ava, I know Travis Tanner
fed you a line
to get your business, but--
Mr. Tanner
didn't feed me anything.
This is the result
of your actions.
Wait a second,
you really did go to him?
I looked into you
when I was deciding to hire you.
You think I wouldn't do
the same thing again
when I decided
to come after you?
When you looked into me,
you found out
that whatever I do
I do it to win, and that's all
I ever did for you.
What you did
was intimidate people
and what it did
was backfire onto me.
Well, now I've found someone
you can't intimidate,
and it's backfiring
onto you.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I don't need to be here
for this.
So you came here
just to vent at me?
I came here to see
if you were at all sorry
about the way
you handled my case.
I see that you aren't.
Though I imagine you will be
once Mr. Tanner
gets through with you.
Feels like old times.
Lot of good memories
in this room.
Bring back the taste of blood
in your mouth?
Oh, I'm a shark, Harvey.
I love the taste of blood.
Speaking of which,
when you accepted this case,
did you make a side deal
with Edward Darby
where he agreed to make you
managing partner
over Jessica Pearson if you won?
Yes, I did,
but that isn't a side deal.
That's an incentive.
What it is
is a conflict of interest.
That is not true.
If anything, it made Harvey
work harder for Ava.
Whatever gets you
through the night.
The truth is, Edward Darby
doesn't make that deal
unless you have leverage.
You knew Darby couldn't lose
because Stephen Huntley's
murders would be discovered.
Isn't that correct?
No, it isn't.
So prior to her trial
starting, you didn't know
that Stephen Huntley
orchestrated those murders?
- No, I didn't.
- What if I told you
I have evidence that you did?
I'd say you're full of shit.
And whether he knew or not
is irrelevant,
since Edward Darby
stipulated that he knew,
making Mr. Specter liable
anyway.
Oh, it's relevant,
because two days ago,
Mr. Specter tried to cut a deal
to split off from Edward Darby
behind your back.
Oh, I see.
Harvey didn't tell you.
If Harvey had told me,
it wouldn't be going
behind my back,
and I'm not going to blame him
for doing what's in his nature
any more than I'd blame you
for being an asshole.
Ooh.
Feisty and hot.
Now I get why he can't
stay away from you.
Tanner, last time,
Harvey knocked you out.
You don't start acting
like a human being this time,
you're gonna have to deal
with me.
Hey, I'm not the one
who screwed my old girlfriend
while she was engaged.
Kind of a dick move, Harv.
That's enough.
Wait a second.
How come she jumped in,
and you didn't?
She didn't tell you
she was engaged.
Can't trust the hot ones.
Come after me, Tanner.
That's what you're here for.
Oh. I get it.
You actually care about her.
I think I've gotten
everything I need right now,
but since it was so much fun,
I'm going to go ahead
and reserve the right
to do this again.
- Hey, do you have a minute?
- Of course.
Just wondering if maybe
you had a copy
of Harvey's deposition.
Can't you just
get one from Harvey?
I could, but then I wouldn't
be able to show you
how I'm letting you
have all your space.
- This is space?
- Yeah, I mean,
I'm all the way over here,
being all space-giving
and adorable.
As opposed to what
you really want to be doing,
which is looking
at my pros and cons list
for Columbia and Stanford.
No, it actually isn't.
That list is for you.
It's part of your process,
and I'm gonna respect it.
What changed your mind?
I went to see Harvey
this morning.
Harvey gave you advice?
No.
And yes.
I just realized that if I go
his way, I am gonna lose you.
But if I keep going mine,
I'm gonna push you away.
So make your decision,
and I'll give you your space.
Thank you.
You go to Stanford...
We'll beat the odds.
Son of a bitch.
I'm sorry you had to sit
through that personal attack.
Oh, you think
that's what I'm pissed about?
You tried to cut a deal
that would screw Edward
and me in process.
I tried to include you.
You said no.
Oh, you think
that makes it any better?
Scottie, all this is
is Tanner trying to get us
to fight among ourselves.
Well, he's doing
a damn good job of it.
You think he didn't say
some things in there
that got to me too?
Well, I'm not bringing them up,
because right now,
we need to stick together.
Sticking together
means telling the truth,
so tell me, whose idea was it
to cut that deal,
yours or Jessica's?
It was hers,
and I didn't want
to go behind your back
just like you didn't want
to go behind Darby's,
but I did because in the end,
I knew I didn't have a choice.
And neither do you,
you just haven't seen that yet.
- Mike, I need your help.
- Okay, what is it Louis?
I need to you convince
Brian Galloway to come here.
Who?
The top associate candidate
of this year's class.
Stick with me.
Oh, yeah, Brian Galloway.
Harvard,
editor of the Law Review.
Welcome to the conversation.
Please tell me you knew him.
- No, I didn't.
- Damn it!
Louis,
he wasn't my year.
You've already got Katrina.
What's so important
about getting this guy
to come here?
Mike, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's not about him.
It's about Sheila Sazs.
Oh, yeah?
What about it?
I mean her.
Mike, come on,
don't be coy with me.
Everyone in New York knows
about our torrid affair.
Yeah, of course.
Torrid.
She had it all set up
for him to come here,
and out of the clear,
blue sky,
she's no longer going to be
exclusive with us.
- There's nothing you did?
- No.
She asked me to take the day
off, I said no.
Next thing I knew she was saying
that our relationship
wasn't special and that
she was free to see other firms.
Okay, Louis, I'm sorry,
but is it possible
that this has nothing to do
with work
and what
she's actually saying
is that she wants
to be exclusive with you?
Oh, Mike, you're so silly.
You know nothing about women.
If she wanted to be
exclusive with me,
she would just come right out
and say it.
Holy shit, it was staring
at me right in the face.
- Not necessarily.
- I've just been using her
for her candidates, I've just
been wham, bam, candidate ma'am.
- Okay.
- I mean, any woman
who's been repeatedly Litt up
would demand
exclusive dominion
over my body.
- Duh.
- Now, get out of my way.
I have a letter to compose.
I'm...
Not in your way.
- Hello, Scottie.
- Tanner.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I just came to bring you
a coffee in the morning.
After meeting you,
I'd say there's an 80% chance
there's a roofie in there.
No roofie.
Just a skinny vanilla latte
with extra whip
and a shot of caramel.
You looked up
my favorite drink?
It's all
part of the package.
You're here
to split me off from Harvey?
Well, he did
the same to you.
And you wouldn't even know
about it if it weren't for me.
You're a regular
Mother Teresa.
Look, I just came to tell you
that we can take it easy on you
if you'll just maybe say
that Harvey
knew about Stephen Huntley
two months ago.
That would be a lie.
Maybe it would just be
conjecture presented as fact.
Look, I'm gonna say
because you already know it.
I betrayed Harvey once.
It's never going to happen
again.
Okay, well,
then I'll just have to hear
your side of the story
at your deposition.
Ms. Scott,
to your knowledge,
did Harvey Specter
want this merger?
- No, he didn't.
- And did you try
to force it on him
because you'd lost to him
numerous times and you wanted
to get him back?
You're the only one
who's trying to get Harvey back
for losing, Tanner.
And I'm about to be
successful.
Isn't it true
that while you were engaged,
you came to New York
and slept with Harvey Specter
in an attempt to get him
to tell you he loved you
and he said no?
That is utter conjecture.
That's why we have
these depositions,
so I can ask questions
about things I'm conjecturing.
You're not asking questions.
You're throwing mud.
Am I?
The facts are,
you had a relationship with him
in law school,
you worked a case
against him,
and shortly thereafter,
ended your relationship.
It doesn't take a rocket
scientist to connect the dots.
- Tanner--
- Did you really think
that you could domesticate him?
A house in Westchester,
Harvey flipping burgers
on the weekends?
What kind of fantasy land
were you living in?
Tanner, that's enough.
She's not answering
this line of questioning.
Then I'll answer it
for her.
You loved him,
he spurned you,
and you set this whole thing up
to get him back.
That's insane.
Which part?
That you loved him?
That he spurned you?
Nothing?
Wow, I guess they're both true.
We're just not
supposed to believe
that you set this merger up
out of anger
because you knew what was
coming down the pike.
I had no idea
what was coming down the pike.
Oh, so you're telling me
that Edward Darby knew
but his number two
didn't know?
I was not the only one
that Edward Darby relied on.
He relied on Stephen Huntley
for what happened in the E.I.R.,
and they both
kept it from me.
Then why am I holding
this affidavit
with Stephen Huntley's name
on it
stating
you knew everything?
Because he's
a lying son of a bitch,
and you're a piece of shit,
and this is the end
of this deposition.
What you doing?
You know what I'm doing.
If you want to keep
your mind off Rachel,
try reading
Scottie's deposition.
I did.
That must have been
brutal for her.
Must have been brutal
for Harvey.
From what I've seen,
not much is.
Mike, he's not as hard
as you think.
Why are you talking to me
about this?
Because if I asked Harvey
what I'm about to ask you--
He'd say no.
I want to talk to Stephen.
- Donna, not a good idea.
- Mike, please.
I can't just let him hurt
somebody else
and do nothing about it.
So this is just
about protecting Scottie?
I'm not just
protecting Scottie.
I'm protecting Harvey,
because he may not know
how he feels, but I do.
I was told my attorney
was here to see me.
I'm sorry, should have said
"an attorney's here to see you."
You lied, so we lied.
See you got my affidavit.
Well written, wouldn't you say?
So is Lord of the Rings,
but you know what they both are?
Fiction.
What did Tanner offer you
to sign that?
He didn't offer me
anything.
Bullshit.
Tanner's a liar and a snake
and he doesn't do anything
without a reason.
So you say,
but I wouldn't know him
from a hole in the ground.
He came to me
with an opportunity,
and I took it.
How is making up
a load of shit about Dana Scott
an opportunity?
I didn't make up anything.
What I wrote was that
she was the conduit
between Edward and I.
She was my boss.
That is factually correct.
That's a misleading statement
designed to confuse a jury
in your murder trial
so that you can claim
Edward's testimony is a lie.
It is a lie.
We never had the conversation
he said we had.
Mike.
Can you give us a minute?
You told me I was wrong
about you.
How can you do this?
Donna,
my life is on the line.
So you'll drag
as many people down
as you have to
to save yourself?
Her freedom
isn't at stake.
No,
but her reputation is.
She'll survive.
You're lying about her.
Yeah, I am.
Stephen, I'm gonna
ask you this one more time.
If anything you ever said to me
was true, please don't do this.
I'm sorry, Donna.
I have to.
- You get what we need?
- No, she didn't.
Actually, I did.
What are you talking about?
You might not know this,
but every conversation
in this particular facility
is recorded,
with an exception made
for attorney-client privilege.
And as you pointed out,
we're not your attorneys.
Jessica.
Were you expecting
someone else?
- I--um--.
- - Nice place. Can I come in?
Yeah, of course.
Do you want some Cheerios?
- What would Cap'n Crunch say?
- Yeah, you're right.
We wouldn't want
to cross him.
I've never seen you wear this
at the office.
Something I should know?
Yeah, that's not-
I know,
and I know whose it is,
and that's exactly why
I'm here.
You told Robert Zane's daughter
my business.
Look, she's not gonna
tell anyone.
I know.
Because you're going to get her
to sign this.
This puts her in jeopardy.
You put her in jeopardy.
And if I won't do it?
Then you won't be working
for me anymore.
- I got your letter.
- And?
You drafted
a legal document.
That outlines
my exclusivity proposal.
This is
the least romantic thing ever.
You couldn't have the courtesy
to do it in person?
I sent it FedEx, Sheila.
It got there overnight.
P.M. delivery.
A.M. delivery is a scam,
Sheila.
It gets there
at the same time anyway.
Okay, you know what's a scam?
This letter,
which I am now ripping up.
No!
Sheila, please!
I labored over every word
of that.
The time for words is over.
The time for deeds is now.
Well, then give me a deed,
I'll do it.
Give me a mountain,
I'll climb it.
Gimme a Katy Perry song,
I'll sing it.
Your only deed is for you
to get off the phone
and figure out where I'll be
tomorrow night
so you can tell me
what you need to tell me.
Okay, can I just have
some sort of--
Hello?
Good to see you,
Tanner.
Hello, Harvey.
What do you got
in your hand there?
It's an arrest warrant
for your father.
Turns out he did a little
insider trading a few years ago,
and I pulled some strings.
- Bullshit.
- You're right, I'm lying,
just like Stephen Huntley did
on his affidavit,
and we've got proof.
Well, look who decided
to show up.
I was waiting for you
to get some points on the board.
Now we can start
having some fun.
Nice try, Tanner,
but that affidavit was bullshit,
now you got nothing to back up
your bullshit on Scottie.
You think I need backup?
It wasn't about her.
It was about you.
I'm going to drag her ass
through the mud
left, right, and center,
and when I'm done with her,
there's not a firm that'll
touch her with a 10-foot pole.
What the hell happened to you?
Why are you doing this, Tanner?
I'm doing it for my client.
You actually had me thinking
if we ever met again--
That I'd fight fair?
I do in the ring,
but this isn't the ring,
and you know very well that you
can stop me anytime you want.
If I settle.
There are lot of zeroes
on that offer.
You just need to decide whether
you care more about money
or your girlfriend.
Donna told me that Stephen's
affidavit is dead.
It is, but it doesn't matter,
because Tanner's
gonna keep coming after you
unless we sign this.
You'll never sign this.
Scottie,
you may not believe this,
but if the decision were mine,
I would.
Jessica--
she wouldn't even consider it.
I should have known.
This is about you getting me
to split you off from Edward
so you can convince Ava
to stop coming after you.
- This isn't about that.
- Then what is it about?
I can't stand to see them
come after you.
- Bullshit!
- It's not bullshit.
You think I can't take it!
Look, you're not listening
to me, okay?
I can't take it!
Scottie, Tanner can only
come after you
if Ava lets him
come after you,
and Ava's only letting him
come after you to get to me.
Take off the shackles off
and let me convince her
this fight isn't with me,
it's with Edward.
Okay, Harvey.
Okay, you win.
Shackles are off.
- Hi.
- Hey.
There's something that I need
to tell you, and...
I really don't want to.
Okay.
You're scaring me.
Jessica came by my place
this morning.
- She knows about us.
- She does.
Okay.
She says that you're
Robert Zane's daughter,
and if you want
to stay at the firm...
You need to sign
an affidavit.
Saying what?
That you know I'm a fraud.
Well, what if
I don't sign it?
Then she'll fire me.
I don't believe that.
You've got leverage.
No, that just stops her
from exposing me, not firing me.
- Bullshit.
- No, it's not bullshit.
If she fires me, what am I
gonna to do, run to the D.A.?
Have them throw me in jail
just to get her back?
I'm not going to do that,
and she knows it.
Can't stand that I put you
in this position.
And the only way I can see
out of this is...
for you to go to Stanford.
Miss Hessington, when we first met
did you admit
you bribed a foreign government
to get your pipeline?
I pled guilty.
I didn't ask you
what you pled.
I asked if you did it.
That's privileged.
Your client forfeited
privilege when she sued me.
Keep that in mind.
My client's not suing you.
She's suing
Pearson Darby Specter.
There is no
We split.
Edward Darby
wouldn't allow that.
Edward Darby doesn't have
the power to stop it.
But I do, and I'm not going to
let you make them suffer
for what Darby did.
Hell of a performance, Harvey.
Back-up singers
and everything.
It's still not
going to stop us.
And he isn't
making them suffer.
I am
for what he did to me.
Did what to you?
Get you a slap on the wrist
for your original
bribery charges,
get you off murder,
or stop you
from bribing witnesses?
Which brings me
to my next question.
Did you fire me
for refusing to bribe witnesses
on your behalf?
- You're under oath.
- Don't answer that.
I wouldn't.
It's a federal crime.
She doesn't have to.
Like I said,
we're not bound by privilege
and I've got three witnesses,
including your friend
Stephen Huntley
who testified to it
in open court.
You want to throw stones, Ava?
We've got some rocks of our own.
What are you doing,
Harvey?
I'm talking to your client
off the record.
No, no, no.
On the record, or not at all.
No, let him speak.
I want to hear
what he's got to say.
Ava, you can come at us
and we can come at you.
I don't want that.
You wanted to know if I'm sorry.
I am.
I'm sorry
I didn't listen to you,
I didn't believe you,
I am sorry that my history
with Cameron
put a target on your back,
but I am not sorry that I did
everything in my power
to help you
every chance I got.
If you don't believe that,
then keep coming.
But if you do, I'm asking,
put your anger where it belongs.
Tanner, I hope you still have
that quarter I gave you,
'cause I think it's time
to call your mom.
Harvey.
Fantastic.
I hear we won.
We hit a single.
Just kidding.
We knocked the son of a bitch
out of the park.
- Congratulations.
- Congratulations to you.
I hear you're representing
Stephen Huntley now.
Yeah.
Might as well be.
What's that
supposed to mean?
It means we sat and had drinks
when we thought Ava was guilty.
Now Stephen is.
What's the difference?
Guess your morning off
didn't do the trick.
What are we doing here,
Harvey?
We spend every minute
of our lives in this office
fighting with each other
over meaningless shit
for clients
that we don't even know,
and then when some
real connection comes along,
just some little piece
of happiness--
Mike.
I'm sorry.
Did she tell you
what she did?
Rachel?
I guess not.
Jessica's basically forcing her
to go to Stanford
instead of Columbia.
She found out
about you two.
I don't want her to go.
And there's nothing
I can do about it.
Come in.
I want to talk to you about...
This.
I see you haven't
signed it.
No, I haven't.
Then you must want something,
because you wouldn't be here
just to tell me
you weren't going to sign it.
Mike said you were worried
that Robert Zane's daughter
knew his secret, which got me
thinking about my father
and something
he's always said.
- Which is?
- Don't sign anything
unless you can get something
in return.
- It's called consideration.
- I know what it's called.
What do you want?
You want me to guarantee
that I won't do something
that I would never do.
I want you to guarantee
that you will do something
that you thought you would
never do but should do.
I can't wait to hear this.
Waive the Harvard rule
for me.
- You're not even a lawyer.
- But I will be,
and when I am,
I want to work here.
The Harvard rule
is the longest-standing rule
we have.
I have been killing it here
for the better part of a decade.
I'm better than most of
the associates in that bullpen
and I haven't even
gone to law school yet,
so imagine what it'll be like
once I have.
You are
your father's daughter.
Yes, I am.
But I don't want to work
for him.
I want to work for you.
To kicking
Travis Tanner's ass.
You got that right.
Mmm.
A pretty great meal.
Couldn't have done it
without you.
I know, I taught you
how to make it.
Right after we crushed
the bar.
I also remember
what happened later that night.
It was
a pretty great night.
Harvey.
Why am I here?
Well, I haven't cooked
anyone dinner for a while,
and I thought you deserved it.
I did,
but you've made it clear
that you don't want more,
and I don't want to go back
to the way it was, so...
I want to work with you.
What?
You've been associated
with the name Darby too long.
I can help you.
I don't need your help.
I'll be fine.
No, you won't,
and all that stuff about Tanner
coming after you and me
not being able to take it,
it was true.
I care about you.
Come to Pearson Specter.
I know that you care about me.
You have made that
very clear,
but I am not interested
in working with someone
day in and day out
where all they can manage to say
is, "I care about you."
- Is that all I've ever said?
- Actually, yes,
over and over again,
"I care about you."
Just what every girl
wants to hear.
- Scottie, that's--
- No, no, no.
If all you want to do
is work with me,
I can find a job
somewhere else.
It's the best I--
Sorry, I should just go.
I don't--
Scottie,
that's not all I want.
Then say it.
I want you in my life.
- Hi.
Thought you didn't like
coming down here.
- Can I come in?
- Yeah, of course.
I finished my list.
And?
Stanford.
It's the better fit.
Rachel, look--
I don't need a list
to tell me
that I don't want to be
without you.
You're staying?
Just try and stop me.
You were messing with me.
- You got me.
- I got...
You!
You got me!
How did you find me?
You're like me,
a gladiator of your profession,
and...
This is your arena.
This place has every
Harvard law student file ever.
It's like home for me.
And...It's where
you wanted me to say...
Sheila Amanda Sazs,
I want to be exclusive with you.
And I want to be exclusive
with you.
Yes.
A thousand times yes.
We're gonna make love.
And eat this picnic.
In no particular order.
Wait.
First, I'm gonna call my mother.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
To tell her the good news?
To tell her
you stopped being a pussy.
Do not touch
any of the files in here.
- Will you smack me if I do?
- Louis,
this is not a joke.
You're not even
supposed to be in here.
For the love of God,
forgive me, Sheila.
You gotta be kidding me.
Harvey Specter.
What a douche.
Mike Ross.
R-o, r-o, r-o.
"R-o."
"Richardson...
Jerry Ross"...
Mike Ross.
What the hell?
He's not here.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man