At the southern tip of South America,
the Andes mountains rise
almost vertically.
Their very height affects
life throughout the continent.
The barren slopes look inhospitable.
But like all parts of South America,
they're actually rich with wildlife.
A family of puma.
They live further south
than any other kind of cat on Earth.
These cubs are only six months old -
entirely dependent on their mother
for food.
She knows how to exploit
this rugged landscape to her advantage.
And she has to do so,
if she is to catch the continent's
most challenging prey.
Guanaco - a relative of the camel.
Two metres tall and over three times
the weight of a puma.
The mother's only hope is to go for
the throat and try to suffocate her prey.
Her cubs try to help...
...but they themselves
don't yet have the skills or the weight
to bring down such large prey.
And the mother is now badly injured.
Her wounds are severe
and will take weeks to heal properly.
But without food,
her cubs won't survive for long.
The weather in the Andes
is harsh and unpredictable.
Snow makes the camouflage
on which she relies much less effective.
But she must have food.
The guanaco have left
her normal hunting ground...
...and are now in the territory
of a much larger male puma.
He's just made a kill,
but he isn't about to share it with her.
To hunt here,
she'll need to leave her cubs behind
in the safety of their home territory.
Almost invisible in the shadows,
she's nearly within pouncing distance.
Another failure.
She's got her speed back.
Now she must hold on.
But she is in the male's territory,
so her prize isn't safe...
...and her hungry cubs
are over kilometre away.
In her weakened state,
she will need all her reserves of energy
to drag it back onto her territory.
Only her determination
to feed her young keeps her going.
Nearly there.
This one meal will barely last the whole
family for more than a few days.
Then their mother - somehow - will have to
summon the strength to hunt again.
Life for a hunter in this land
is as hard as it gets.
The Andes themselves were built by forces
deep in the Earth's crust.
In this part of the Pacific,
the ocean floor has been moving eastwards
for millions of years.
Where the sediments meet
the edge of the continent,
they're pushed together
and forced upwards.
This pressure creates fractures
up which molten rock rises
and is then spewed out as ash
and lava from great volcanoes.
Nearly 200 of them stretch in a line
along the length of the continent.
Some erupt with the force
of an atomic bomb every ten seconds.
As the collision continues,
the sea floor is dragged downwards,
creating a deep trench just offshore.
Rich, cold waters rise up from it.
And this upwelling creates
an abundance of life.
Here, on the coast of Peru,
there are so many seabirds fishing
in the offshore waters
that the cliffs are covered
in droppings over a metre thick.
Humboldt penguins regard the soft guano
as a good material in which to dig
their nest holes.
But it's a messy business.
It's the breeding season,
and more hopeful nesters arrive,
spotless from swimming in the sea.
Time for the residents to get cleaned up
and catch some fish
for themselves and their chicks.
To get to the sea, they cross
the remains of an old nesting ground.
Only 100 metres to go.
But the beach is already crowded
with sea lions.
They too have come ashore
to raise their young.
And they don't like being disturbed.
To get through such a minefield
needs a bold and courageous leader.
A brave start.
A dead end.
Now he's in trouble.
This is going to need
a bit of crowd surfing.
But now all the sea lions are roused.
Getting through them will be tricky.
A cleansing bathe in the ocean...
...well worth the effort.
The animals living along the Pacific coast
are cut off from the rest of South America
by the Andes.
They form a gigantic barrier,
stretching over 6,000km
from Patagonia in the south
to Venezuela in the north.
This is the world's
longest mountain range.
Some peaks are almost 7km high.
They are so tall they catch clouds...
...and so create an environment unlike
any other on the continent.
The cloud forest.
Every high valley here
has its own unique plants and animals.
One of them is the aptly named
Pinocchio lizard.
It was first recorded here 50 years ago
and then lost.
It's only recently been rediscovered.
Up here lives a creature
so rare that it's seldom seen,
even by those scientists
who have come here to study it.
The Andean bear.
Only a few thousand remain.
They eat mostly leaves and fruit,
often clambering up
to the very top of the canopy to do so.
He's looking for a type
of miniature avocado...
...30 metres up.
The only fruit remaining here
is out on the thinnest branches -
too thin to support the weight of a bear.
A more experienced bear
has turned up and wants a go.
Time for young ones to watch
and learn how to do it.
The trick is to bite the branch
just enough...
...to make it swing down
and bring the fruit within reach.
Whoops!
Now there's a race to be
first on the ground to claim it.
The moisture needed
to create a cloud forest
only occurs above a certain altitude...
...so each peak may now have
its own species.
In Venezuela,
there are similar small worlds,
created not by rain, but by rock.
A great layer of sandstone
once covered this entire area,
but rivers cut through it.
As the valleys widened,
the tablelands became first huge plateaus,
then isolated flat-topped mountains...
...and, eventually, towers and spires.
On the tops of the bigger ones, animals
and plants have now become so different
that they can be counted as new species.
There is no higher waterfall
in the world...
...than this one.
Angel Falls - almost a kilometre
from top to bottom.
The vertical cliffs surrounding
many of these mountains
have kept them largely free
from human exploitation.
No such barriers have protected
the lowlands...
...but a few patches of forest
still remain.
One in Colombia is the home
of one of the world's rarest monkeys.
Cotton-topped tamarins.
They're critically endangered.
Only a few hundred families remain.
They live largely on fruit
and are particularly fond of tree sap.
This is packed with sugars,
so it also attracts insects.
But tamarins like them too -
a little bit of protein
to add to their diet.
There used to be over 50,000 species
of insect to choose from...
...but as the forest
has shrunk around them,
it's becoming more difficult
to find the right ones.
South America is changing.
Over 95% of Colombia's lowland forest
has now been cleared.
Farming has taken the biggest share.
This patch of forest is now isolated.
The few tamarin families here
are now cut off
from the rest of their species...
...and beyond their boundary
lies an alien world.
Today, more than 2,000 species of animal
in South America are under threat.
All across the continent,
forest is being steadily cut down
and replaced by farms.
Images from space
reveal the scale of the destruction.
Throughout South America as a whole,
an area of forest the size of a football
pitch is being lost every five seconds.
Of all the forests at risk,
perhaps the most precious
lies in the very heart of the continent.
The Amazon rainforest -
the largest on Earth.
Over two million species of plants
and animals now live here -
more than is found on any other
of the Earth's seven continents.
Food is so abundant that some male birds,
instead of helping with nest duties,
try to mate with as many females
as possible.
This is a male manakin
showing off to a female.
He does so by dancing...
...and he has a team
of subordinate males to help him.
By supporting him now, they may
themselves eventually become leaders
and get a chance to mate.
The team is assembled
and the performance begins.
She takes a closer look.
The top male signals the end
with a final flourish.
What's the verdict?
Not good enough.
Unbelievable!
So it's back to practising.
Each animal species in this crowded
environment has to have its own way
of creating a niche for itself.
This is a poison dart frog.
Males raise their young
in a very special way.
A father will place each one of his
tadpoles in its own tiny pool of water.
This is one.
Nice and safe.
He might have up to five other tadpoles.
But he needs to remember
where he put each one of them.
This one isn't doing so well.
His tiny puddle has all but dried out.
The tadpole will die unless its father
can find a better place for it.
If dads are good for one thing,
it's piggyback rides.
Fathers are no bigger
than a human thumbnail,
but this enables them
to get to places that others can't.
This could be perfect.
The only problem
is that there's no food here.
Fathers need help.
Somewhere in this forest...
...is...
...mum.
A female could do something
a male cannot.
But first, dad must lead his partner
to their hungry tadpole...
...and mother deals with the problem.
She lays a single unfertilised egg.
And her tadpole gets a much-needed meal.
For the next six weeks,
parents continue their rounds -
an extraordinary test of teamwork
and memory.
Warmed by the tropical sun, the Amazon's
trees release so much moisture
from the surface of their leaves
that they create their own clouds.
And these, over the course of a year,
release up to six metres of rain.
The water flows through the saturated
forest along a thousand streams.
They eventually unite to form
the largest river of them all.
The Amazon carries more water
than the world's next seven biggest rivers
combined.
Some sections of its banks
are particularly sought-after.
Scarlet macaws travel over 100 kilometres
to visit them.
Macaw couples bond for life
and may stick together for over 40 years.
Pairs return to favourite trees,
ones they've known for decades.
Parents provide their chicks
with fruits and seeds,
but they're far from the ocean
and their diet lacks salt.
Without it, the chicks' brains
and bones will not develop properly.
So someone has to go and fetch it.
Many other creatures are looking
for the same thing...
...a clay lick.
The earth here may be 40 times
richer in valuable minerals
than anywhere else
in the surrounding forest.
Over a dozen species of parrot
jostle for space.
There's a strict order...
...in who feeds first.
Everyone is in a rush
to fill up and get airborne.
Parents have to carry over 5kg of clay
to the nest
before their chicks are ready to leave.
Once fledged, these young will follow
their parents for up to a year,
learning where to find the salts.
Many of the great riches of South America
lie far beyond the Amazon basin.
Over 1,000 miles
to the south of the Amazon,
there's one creek
unlike any other on the continent.
Here at Bonito, freshwater springs
bubble up from deep underground.
Filtered through limestone,
they create crystal-clear pools...
...and in them live some remarkable fish.
Piraputanga.
The water is so clear that they're able to
see what is going on above its surface.
Brown capuchins are up there,
looking for a meal.
The piraputanga watch them
attentively.
Wherever the monkeys go
along the banks, the fish follow.
The monkeys are on
their daily search for ripe fruit,
and the fish cannot by themselves know
where that might be.
But here it is.
And fortunately, the monkeys aren't the
neatest of feeders.
Every scrap is fought over.
One monkey has the job
of keeping an eye out for danger.
Anacondas are the largest of all snakes.
They grow to over 200kg.
And they usually
stalk their prey from the water...
...but it's not fish that they're after.
If the monkeys stray too close
to the water, they will be in danger.
The scout gives a warning call.
That might have to be the end
of the monkey's meal for today.
But now the piraputanga
know where the fruit is.
And there's still plenty left on the tree.
In the monkeys' absence,
they go for it themselves.
Success or failure
is just a matter of millimetres.
With a split-second adjustment,
the fish bends in midair
and collects the prize.
The piraputanga's extraordinary
feeding technique
relies on these waters remaining clear.
But today, the future of South America's
rivers has become uncertain.
As the human population has grown,
people have become more and more reliant
on its rivers for one of the essentials
of modern life.
Power.
Two-thirds of South America's energy
now comes from hydroelectricity.
No other region on Earth
is so dependent upon it.
But the way these dams are managed can
cause problems farther downriver.
These are the Iguazu Falls.
If the dams upriver suddenly release
their excess, Iguazu can double in size.
And that can cause major problems
for animals that live here.
These are great dusky swifts.
They fly alarmingly close
to the thundering torrent...
...and then vanish.
Miraculously, they're able to fly right
through the curtain of water.
And they do so because they've built
their nests behind the thundering curtain.
Their enemies - falcons,
like this caracara - can't follow them.
So the swift chicks are safe.
But now humans have created
new problems for the swifts.
Just as some of the chicks
are starting to fly,
the spill over the dams
is released in full force.
As the torrent grows,
parents give up on the last perches.
Now the chicks are alone.
But they don't yet have
their parents' waterproof feathers.
Every year, the sudden surges of water
sweep some to their death.
The chicks have never seen the world
beyond the falling waters.
Unless they can find a way through,
they will not survive.
Amazingly, driven by blind instinct,
chicks do manage
to power their way through.
These remarkable birds have colonised
a niche in which few can survive.
Yet their future,
and that of all wildlife in South America,
will depend on us striking a balance
between the needs of humans and animals,
on the richest and most diverse continent
on Earth.
Next time...
...a continent marooned
during the time of the dinosaurs,
where the castaways...
...are like nothing else on Earth.
Australia.