Here's something
that should hurt your brain.
We can empty
half of all the beds
in all the hospitals
in the world
by just giving people
clean water.
So have you ever heard
of Dean Kamen?
No.
No?
Uh, I don't think so.
I have not heard of
Dean Kamen.
I've heard of
the Cayman Islands,
but not Dean Kamen.
Okay.
Do you know what a
Segway is? Of course.
Yes, I know what those are.
Little trolleys?
The little things you ride with
two wheels? Yeah. Mmm-hmm.
So Dean Kamen's the guy
that invented the Segway.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Oh, wait. Is that the dude that,
like, drove a Segway off the cliff?
He's... He's dead, isn't he?
Didn't he
fall off one and die?
A lot of people think the
inventor of the Segway is dead.
But they don't really know
who invented the Segway.
This rumor
has been out that
the Segway guy has died.
One of the people that
hears this story is my mother.
So she, of course, calls my
cell phone and gets no answer.
There are so many messages.
I call my mother and say,
"Mother, what's wrong?"
"Now that I'm talking to you,
nothing!"
Oh, did that really work?
So what is that thing
actually for?
All you're really
trying to do is
see something
and hear something
that you knew to be
contemporaneous.
I was just trying to make
some noise to confuse...
Oh, but that should have information
about where in the system it is.
It also has the take
and it has the numbers...
Okay, come back, come back!
I must admit,
I do like technology.
I like machines and I like
the efficiency they deliver.
I'm guilty.
From a very early age,
I both wanted to know
more and more about the rules by
which this universe of ours operates.
And, through the
world of engineering,
I wanted to start
applying those rules
to create inventions that would
give people a better quality of life,
if those inventions work.
Most kids, when they grow up,
develop what's called good judgment.
That's what we
as adults call it.
When we actually lose our
sense of fun, our imagination,
and a whole lot of things
that I didn't want to give up.
When I was a kid, I thought,
"I'm gonna have a house,
where I can get up in the morning
"and go downstairs
"and open up
a giant glass wall
"and take a helicopter
out of my house
"and take off
right from my house
"and go anyplace
I want to go."
When I was a kid, I thought it would
be cool to have secret passages.
"I'm gonna put
secret passages in."
Some people want a classic
piece of artwork in their foyer.
A Monet. A Rembrandt.
In my foyer, I have
this old steam engine
built well over 150 years ago.
It actually ran a tugboat
called the HMS Oscar.
I would be terrified
to have to get on a horse.
Some great
big animal with teeth.
I don't wanna go near
a pile of muscle that big.
But I've never been afraid
of any machine.
That engine,
it's a work of art,
created by a different
kind of artist.
It also represents
great achievements
that took hundreds of years
to develop and understand.
When I'm awake, I'm working.
So I'm wearing
my work clothes.
Dean just doesn't
know the difference
between work and play.
So he always wears his jeans.
None of the kids like him.
I have all the letters, and
this one I got from Dean. 1964.
"Dear Mommy and Daddy.
I want to come home."
Exclamation.
"If I can't come home,
"please send the following
as soon as possible.
"One accountant.
"One marketing expert.
"Three secretaries.
"I'll try to write again soon, but
I have to go to volleyball now.
"Your willful
and outcast son, me."
That was written then.
He wanted three secretaries.
I remember very well
being a little kid.
I'd think and I'd look at the
world and I'd imagine things.
Everything I saw gave me
questions about everything.
Why, when you bounce a ball,
each time it hits the ground,
it bounces lower
on the next shot.
How does it do that?
You put a hot cup
on the table,
it cools off.
You put a cold cup on
the table, it warms up.
How?
Why?
Most of what the world does
is quite amazing.
And you could be
very confident
that it'll always do the same
thing over and over again.
But how does all that happen?
There are a few people
that actually
took little pieces of that
and made sense out of it.
I asked my father for these
great scientists and thinkers.
They're beautiful art.
And they're done by my father.
You start with Archimedes.
Over 2,000 years later, we still
refer to Archimedes' principle.
Staggeringly,
after Archimedes, we had a few
things, which included the Dark Ages.
We come out of them with
a guy like Leonardo da Vinci.
He was an artist
and an engineer,
a scientist.
I mean,
this guy was unbelievable.
And then you only have to wait
a few hundred years
to Galileo Galilei.
Really,
the first modern scientist.
He gave us
the scientific method.
He dies in 1642,
and we don't have to wait very
long, because in the same year,
Isaac Newton is born.
And Isaac Newton developed
Newtonian mechanics.
How masses move
and interact with each other.
Then, 1860s, comes
James Clerk Maxwell
and gives us what are now
known as Maxwell's equations.
Four statements that link
all of electricity, magnetism,
light,
into a comprehensive,
well-understood system.
And by 1905,
along comes Big Al.
He sort of put us
where we are today.
And I'm waiting for the next
big thing to happen.
Between this guy in 200 BC,
through this guy,
who was alive when I was born,
you've got 2,200 years.
And other than these six guys,
not much happened.
It's pretty humbling.
But it's, uh...
It's pretty exciting
to wonder about
what will be the contribution
of the next guy that deserves
a place on this wall?
Or woman.
Are you ready?
My middle brother has
most of the fame in the family
and he's known for Segway.
But the reality is he helped me
solve a problem we both used to say,
"You don't wake up in the morning
and say, 'I got to invent something.'
"You wake up in the morning
and you say,
"'There's a problem
to be solved.'"
I had just put a machine shop
in my parents' basement.
And I started building
electronics and selling it.
And then my brother would
come home from med school.
He was already working on his basic
research, treating babies with leukemia.
That was his specialty.
But to deliver his new drugs
and new therapies,
you couldn't use all the
standard medical equipment,
because even at
their lowest rates,
they were 10 times
too high a rate for a baby.
I said, "Bart, why don't you
leave the drug
"in the syringe that it
came in in the first place?"
"And then we'll build you
a little device
"with a precision loader
that delivers it
"directly out of the syringe
into the baby."
So he said,
"That would be great."
But by giving him those
little drug delivery systems
that were seen by
all the rest of the faculty
when he was still a student
in med school,
all these other physicians
and researchers
saw these little things,
and said, "Wait a minute.
"Since it's small
and battery operated,
"I can slip it in the pocket
of some adult
"and they can leave the
hospital getting their drugs
"with a portable system."
Which didn't exist
in those days.
And then I start
to ask these docs, like,
"What do you plan to deliver?"
"How about insulin?"
We moved out of the basement,
we started making
lots of different pharmaceutical
delivery systems.
Ended up building
a nice company around that.
I like to work
on interesting problems,
technical problems,
that if they are solved, also,
can be used by a whole lot of
people to make their lives better.
Which is why we spent
pretty much our whole career
at DEKA
building medical equipment.
The wiring has to go right
through the middle of it...
Right, so there's no rotation
of those components?
I'm an inventor.
What do inventors do?
Inventors look at problems,
the same problems everybody
else looks at, but see them differently.
We were working on a way to
make home dialysis a possibility.
Probably 20 years ago, we
said, "We can take dialysis.
"Let people do it at home.
Alone.
"Life support
in your own bedroom."
And most of the people
at Baxter said, "You're nuts."
In fact, throughout my life, I
only start on projects, typically,
if enough credible people
tell me, "You're nuts."
'Cause then you know,
"This must be a big problem."
Baxter had introduced the idea
of peritoneal dialysis.
The bad news is
while the therapy worked,
the machine,
that could, quote,
"Safely push this fluid
through a patient"
turned out to be this.
They loaded a bag up here
and you ran the tube
out of the bag,
not up to there, because
the fluid can't travel by itself...
They couldn't pump it, because if
something went wrong, you could...
Then you pulled the tube out and
then you opened up this little device...
Down to the floor... Made
a weight scale out of this
and they weigh the fluid
as it's coming out...
If the patient rolled over
and tugged on the tube,
took the bags
that were hanging here...
The patient had to run all that
stuff every day, or the nurse.
So we looked at this, and
said, "Baxter, it's a great therapy.
"You guys did
something unbelievable.
"But the implementation
of the solution
"is just too kludgy to fix.
"We got a better idea."
We said, "The problem isn't
"your machine is noisy, your
machine is heavy, or your machine is...
"The problem is this patient
doesn't have a functioning kidney."
We decided we could build a simple
machine that would allow patients
to dialyze themselves at home
without having to live in a hospital
or a dialysis center
every other day
for the rest of their lives.
It was a completely different
approach to a problem.
That machine needed
about five gallons
of pure, medical grade
water to operate.
If we could find a way to make
the purest water in the world
out of the tap water
in your home,
and turn it into
medical grade water,
we could eliminate the next
problem they were having.
Shipping all this water
all over the country.
We stared working on a machine to
turn tap water into water for injection.
It turned out that unless you
know everything about the water,
in the northeast, it has iron,
in other places,
it has other problems.
We decided that
a simple filter,
or a membrane,
or osmosis,
or activated charcoal
is unlikely to meet the need.
We decided we better go back to the
gold standard that the medical community
has used to make medical
grade water for 100 years.
That is, distill it.
The problem is the energy
required to distill water
requires that you take water in its
liquid phase at room temperature
and not only get it hot enough
to boil, to get frothy,
we need to get it all
to turn into steam.
Nature does it,
because you got the sun.
The biggest nuclear plant
we've ever seen
sitting out there that could boil
all this water out of the ocean.
That's an enormous
amount of energy.
We don't have a lot of energy.
The magic of a vapor
compression distiller,
particularly the little one
that we've made,
is that the water comes in,
it gets boiled,
it gets condensed,
and it comes
out of the machine
just a tad warmer
than it went in,
'cause we took all the energy
back out of it.
And by recycling
all of that energy,
we reduced the requirements
of this machine
from 25,000 watts, which is
about 20 houses worth of power,
to less power than
a hand-held hair dryer.
So now you take our machine
and you plug it into any
normal outlet in a typical home
and it uses
a little bit of power.
But it just keeps recycling that
energy over and over and over again,
so that it's no big deal.
I am
a very slow learner.
I'm very flattered that
you think I'm a real genius.
But if I'm a genius, all I can
tell you is I am the slowest,
dumbest genius
you'll ever meet.
You just gotta read it
and read it again,
and read it again.
Think about it,
and think about it again,
and then, all of a sudden,
it all starts to make sense.
While in third grade,
when Mrs. Pfeffer said,
"Evelyn, I can't understand,
he is so bright.
"But he's not producing
as he should."
I was having, as a little kid,
a lot of trouble
learning to read.
If I would see letters
out of context,
or words that could
be "pots" and "stop"
and "saw" and "was,"
I couldn't tell them apart.
My older brother could read
enormously fast.
And I always figured
it was practice
or it was something
that I was doing wrong.
We were very concerned.
I don't know
that we broadcast it.
Yeah, I mean, I don't know,
but we weren't ashamed.
We took him for testing
to the local psychologist.
He was a non-reader.
I wish I could
find a way to not be dyslexic.
But if somebody said,
"But here's the cost."
If it took away something
else that I'm good at,
at this point in my life, I'd probably
say, "No, I'll stay with what I got."
Compared to other problems,
this one's not so bad.
And maybe it was a catalyst to help
me do other things particularly well.
Once we realized we could take everything
out of water, no matter what it is,
organics, toxins, metals,
we had a process to turn
anything into pure water.
Why is it only for the
special subset of people
that have a dialysis machine
in their own bedroom?
The scalability
of this solution
is what is
attractive about it.
The fact that it could be used
all over the world
in all environments
with all kinds of bad water.
That was sort of an epiphany.
We recognized that a huge
potential opportunity existed
for solving the world's
water problems
with a vapor
compression distiller.
That same machine
could be carried into villages
and allow a few hundred
million people,
or a few billion people,
to have the purest water
in the world.
I hadn't realized
how big the problem was.
Analysis suggests
the world will face
a 40% shortfall
of clean water by 2030.
We live on a planet
70% covered by water,
and we're fighting over
a half of a percent.
As things change,
water conflict will escalate.
Competition for water
between Israel,
Jordan and Syria
has turned the
once-mighty Jordan River
into a trickle.
There's no way it's not
gonna effect everybody.
In Central America,
the lack of drinking water,
together with pollution,
are having a huge impact
on children's health.
Child mortality figures
are horrific in Afghanistan.
One child out of five
dies under the age of five
through drinking
polluted water.
Almost 50 children are
reporting in every day
with symptoms of
diarrhea and vomiting.
Here, four children
are forced to share one bed.
A million people
might die in Bangladesh alone
this year from contaminated water.
In the
underdeveloped world,
the average amount of time
per day spent by women
looking for water that's safe
for their kids is four hours.
And if it didn't turn out
to be the right stuff,
they spend the next day or two
burying their babies.
That shouldn't
be their choices.
They shouldn't
have to go that far.
They shouldn't have to
make the choice between
drinking the kind of stuff
you wouldn't give to your dog,
or not having anything at all.
Everybody else that's working
on the global water problem
is thinking of massive,
interconnected infrastructure.
They don't understand that the 21st-century
problem needs a 21st-century solution.
There's a lot to be said for,
"Let's minimize risk.
"Let's know what we're doing."
But sometimes,
when the need is really big,
and the currently available
solutions are woefully inadequate,
it is appropriate
to put a stake in the ground
and say, "We're not doing it
the way we did it before.
"We gotta find
a totally new approach.
"It's time to change."
Why do you take on
these impossible tasks?
It's always, like,
the hardest thing.
What is... What compels you?
Well, first of all,
believe it or not,
I don't get up in the morning
and look in the mirror and say,
"Go after some
impossible problem.
"And make sure
to frustrate yourself
"beyond reasonable.
Again. Today.
"You've been doing it
on water for 15 years,
"just keep doing that."
I do not go look,
every morning,
for the most difficult problem on
which I can continue to frustrate myself
and all of my people and fail.
That's not the goal.
It's a consequence,
but not a goal.
Ginger piques
nationwide interest.
Will it just solve
world hunger?
I went to my office and there
were boom trucks with cameras.
"What's going on?"
And people were saying,
"Well, this is the headquarters
"of the place with
the great secret project
"that's gonna
change the world."
I didn't know about the leak,
but it certainly wasn't,
as many people suspected,
a marketing scheme.
People were speculating,
it could beam you places,
it was a transporter,
like in Star Trek.
And I was worried from that day
forward that no matter what we did,
it would have the potential of
having people say, "Really? That's all?
"You turned lead into gold,
I was hoping for platinum."
After months of hype,
the wraps are coming off that
top-secret invention codenamed "IT."
I wanna know what "IT" is.
What is "IT"?
What does "IT" do?
And when will "IT" be
somewhere where I can buy one?
We're about to unveil
the invention
that's been the subject
of hundreds of media reports
in the topic of a
global guessing game.
Some say it will
change the world,
some say that it's gonna be
as broad as the Internet.
I'm tempted to say,
"That's it?"
But that can't be it.
Hey, you know what
would be really cool?
If it had four wheels and a compartment
where people could sit inside.
Ginger is the evolution
of walking.
First, we crawled
on all fours.
No, first we climbed
out of the ocean.
Then, we were
four-legged beasts.
And then we learned
to walk erect.
And now,
We ginger.
People that live in cities, people that
only wanna move around a small community
shouldn't be using
a 4,000-pound machine
to move their
150-pound ass around town.
What are these?
Oh, good.
I like to work on projects
where there's a discontinuity.
Where you can't use
linear thinking
to get from A to B to C
to where we are.
You have to take
a big intellectual leap.
Greetings, foot people.
How are things
back in the 20th century?
Gentlemen, forward!
The traditional Segway,
as far as I know,
made a huge splash
when it came out in 2002.
But is it true that it's
only sold about 50,000?
What went wrong there?
Well, I think the problem for
the Segway was really the price.
At about $5,000,
it's a pretty expensive toy.
In retrospect,
there's probably lots of ways
to go back and play the
coulda-woulda-shoulda-mighta.
Could it have been cheaper?
Could we have addressed
the market differently?
But we didn't do
either of those.
And what difference would
that have made, we'll never know.
Very smooth!
I don't think my perspective of the
Segway has changed very much.
It really is that connection,
that segway between
walking and cars.
I don't know what people
will be doing in 10 or 20 years
when there's nine or ten
billion people on this planet,
most of them living in cities.
But I know one way
they won't be doing it.
They won't be sitting in
3,000-pound machines called cars,
creeping along, sucking up
each other's exhaust.
That's insane.
Are there three items
you can't live without?
You mean that exist today,
or that I hope will exist soon?
Either one.
Well, you know,
the one that, sadly,
I don't think will
come about in my lifetime,
the one I've always wanted
is a time machine.
The only thing
that ever really scares me
is the fact that life is short
and you can't do everything.
I work as much as I can, as hard
as I can, but you can't do everything.
The only thing we have
that we can't make any more of
is time.
There's an eternity behind me,
and I will never
get to experience that.
I won't see the big bang,
I won't know how it happened.
I won't even be able to see
things of a mere 100 or 200
or 300 years ago.
I will not be able to see
Lincoln deliver
the Gettysburg Address.
There's a long timeline,
then I was born.
And then in a
relatively short time,
a dot along that line,
I'm gone.
And there'll be
a very long future out there.
I won't be
part of that, either.
So in that very short segment
of this nearly infinite line,
where I have the capacity to see the
world and understand and do things,
I don't intend
to waste any of it.
Why is everybody saying that
there's a looming water shortage?
Okay? Why?
Well, how about 50%
of all human disease
on this planet today
is a result of
water-borne pathogens.
So people drink the water,
the disease is in it,
and then they get sick?
50%.
How about... Stop drinking
water. That's my point.
Most organizations,
when they want to clean water,
first say, "What's
wrong with the water?"
And if it's ocean water, they say,
"Let's use osmosis membranes."
If it's water that's got
heavy metals in it,
they put charcoal filters
in front of it.
If it's water that's got
bioburden in it,
they say, "Let's use
antibiotics or chlorine
"or something to kill
the bioburden."
But you had to know which
of those processes to use
for any particular problem
with the water,
and you had to have access
to that particular solution.
"No, no, no. We'll just
use chlorine tablets."
Well, that's great.
As long as you can run down
to the local 7-Eleven
to buy the tablets,
pretest the water.
Oh, wait a minute, you can't.
They don't even have roads.
You can't imagine
that in these little villages,
they have, oh,
an epidemiologist,
a microbiologist,
an organic chemist,
somebody to...
So I decided, you gotta take a
different approach to the problem.
We've seen
in the last generation,
we went from Ma Bell,
big, centralized systems
to cellphones.
We went from big, mainframe
computers to personal computing.
Why can't we go
in the same way
in the developing world
to point of use generation
of pure, clean water
out of anything,
instantly where you need it?
You have to build a box,
maybe the size of this,
that is a simple to operate
water utility.
This is an early
version of my black box.
We made it black, we
want it rugged to sit outside.
If you touch it, it feels like
the bed liner of a Chevy truck.
People ask me
what it's made out of.
It's actually made out of
the bed liner of a Chevy truck.
Because I wanted it rugged and I
figured those guys know how to do that.
You've got
an incredible invention here.
Um, tell me what this does.
That box is a vapor
compression distiller
with no filters, no membranes,
no chemicals.
You can stick one hose that
comes out of it, which I'll show you,
into any source of water...
So this thing right here?
This is the dirty water?
Over here? That's dirty water.
You stick a hose
into anything that looks wet,
Anywhere in the
world... A puddle?
- A puddle, the ocean.
- The ocean.
A chemical waste site.
A latrine.
50 gallon drum of urine.
A 50 gallon drum of urine.
Okay.
And it comes through this
machine and it comes out here
as perfect, distilled water.
We said,
"What if we make a system
"that might have a
sophisticated technology inside,
"but the use of it is simpler
than all the others?"
So no substance put in there,
except the water,
will actually end up
in the water over there?
That's correct. I'm gonna
put that to the test right now.
Let me help you.
All right.
I guarantee you,
that water's gonna be
sweet, spicy
and chili flavored.
Thank you, sir.
Dean's now
the official clapper.
- You are, you are...
- I'm gonna put a credit.
I need a credit for that.
Truth is transient.
And there's no place where
the truth is more transient
than in technology.
What was true when you
were a kid about technology
is probably not true anymore.
The idea that somebody
in a little village
in Ghana, or in Bangladesh,
that has no electricity today,
or has no tap water today,
the idea that
tomorrow morning
somebody there is
gonna wake up, "Oh, look,
"transmission line,
switch gear,
"high voltage, low voltage,
transformers."
The idea that that's suddenly
gonna appear out of nowhere
is ridiculous.
If you want
a good example
of where technology helped
transform the developing world,
think of the difference
between
big, centralized phone systems
and cell phones.
There are 400 million
cell phones in Africa.
There are a billion
cell phones in India.
Global organizations,
they work on top-down
government-to-government big programs,
and we're working on bottom-up
point of use generation
of water.
I was told a very long time
ago, when I started my business,
that I'd never get anywhere
without partners and without a tie.
So I figured I'd kill
two birds with one stone.
I had a tie made out of denim
and I gave it to my partner.
So I've had this guy in
my office now for 30 years.
We've never had an argument.
Uh, he's always supportive.
He's my partner,
my silent partner,
and, uh, he's good
to have in the office.
...saw, my friend,
Dean Kamen,
whom I have known
for more than 20 years.
I saw the Segway before
most people knew what it was.
And a few years ago, we were out
in Colorado together, and he said,
"I've got this
water purification deal
"and it can
revolutionize the world.
"And here's how it works."
He never made me
ride the Segway.
He never made me get up
in that
wheelchair that climbs up
the stairs.
I never had to take any risks
to brag on Dean Kamen.
He pours this awful fetid
water into this machine
and it drips down,
and he says,
"Now drink it."
And so...
I did.
And I'm still here,
it works.
So this is a machine
we built in 2006.
We'll lift the insulating case
off and show you what's inside.
The very first units we built,
which required a few years,
times a few dozen engineers,
cost literally
millions of dollars apiece.
This is made out of,
as you know, expensium.
Where's the unobtainium?
Most of what's in here is
made out of unobtainium.
We do have all the
unreliabilium in here.
Um... And, uh,
the icantmaketwoathem
is in here.
My father had one mood.
He was happy.
He loved what he did.
And he wanted to sit
and do art.
- You got me in there?
- Oh, you're in.
One of the tales
Dean would tell,
somebody asked him
about his father's work
and he says, "You know, I
don't think my father ever slept."
He said,
"I'd wake up in the morning
"and my dad was
at the drawing board.
"And I'd go to sleep at night, and my
dad was sitting at the drawing board."
I work about eight
to 10 hours a day.
Still?
Yeah.
My father was not
one of those.
Leave It to Beaver fathers.
After dinner,
all the other kids
and the fathers would go out
and play ball on the streets.
My father would finish dinner
and go upstairs to where
he had his second studio
and he would be working.
And I would sit there
watching him.
And I basically said to him,
"Dad, you know,
I feel badly for you,
"'cause all the other fathers
come home from work
"and they get to play
with their kids.
"But you have to go back
to work."
He put down his brush
and he said, "Dean,
don't ever feel sorry for me.
"I love what I do.
I'm an artist.
"I get to do something I love
all the time.
"You need to find something
that you love to do.
"And then you'll be
the lucky guy."
I'm the luckiest guy
in the world.
I get up every day knowing
that there's important things
that I really
wanna accomplish.
I tell every kid I meet, "Figure
out something you really love to do,
"get so good at it
"that you can make a living
doing it.
"If you don't do that,
"you're cheating yourself out
of a happy, meaningful life."
Now, jump.
- What do you think?
- Good.
May I have
your attention, please.
After we had
refurbished them,
I took the first floor
of one of my old mills
and built it into
a hands-on science center
that I donated
to the community.
One morning, I walked
into the little science center
and I noticed that almost
every kid in the place
was wearing a sweatshirt
or a jersey
that was about the Patriots,
or the Bruins.
And I happened to stop and say to
one of them wearing one of these jerseys,
"Can you tell me the name
of a famous living engineer?"
No, I can't.
You know, we gotta fix that.
And I just went around to every
kid and say, "Could you tell me
"the name of some role model,
scientist, engineer, inventor?"
And not a single one could.
One of the adults finally
said to me,
"Einstein,
but I think he's dead."
There's nothing wrong with
having great superheroes
from the world of sports, and
entertainment, and the arts,
but you'd think
there'd be room for
a few people that contribute
to society by curing disease,
or creating cell phone
technology, or...
You just look at what we take
for granted
and nobody has any idea
how it got here.
But somehow we think
it's remarkable
that this guy
can get the ball in the hoop
at a slightly higher percentage
than somebody else.
It's just amazing.
Anyway, I walked out of there
and decided I'm gonna build
an organization,
the purpose of which is
to change the culture
of the United States.
People, get ready,
the robots are coming.
FIRST is an organization
whose sole goal
is to convince a generation
of kids
that science and technology
and engineering
actually is fun
and accessible, and rewarding,
and important.
They already feel that way
about sports.
So we said,
"Let's package science,
technology, engineering and math
"into a
sporting competition."
The kids working with
world-class scientists and engineers
build a robot
that's gonna compete with, literally
at this point, thousands of other robots.
FIRST was set up
on the premise
that we don't have an
education problem in this country,
we have a culture problem.
The only difference between
this sport and all the others
is every kid
on our teams can turn pro.
There's a job out there
for every one of these kids.
Thank you.
Lots of people ask me
why I put so much
of my own energy into FIRST.
Oh, you're the sophomore?
We got you for three years. Okay.
Go to a FIRST event,
walk through the pits,
talk to the kids.
I am very confident that
in those stands is some kid
that's gonna win a Nobel Prize
for curing a major disease,
or creating a new technology.
FIRST is another one of my
almost overnight successes.
It's only been 21 years.
And it's gonna be an overnight
success, I'm sure, this coming season.
I'm still waiting
to where I can say.
FIRST is where it
should be, which is
in every school
in the country.
I've been accused of being
too aggressive
about the need for FIRST.
So I've decided to be
the new gentler Dean.
I no longer say, "We need FIRST
in every school in the country."
We only need FIRST in the schools
where you care about the kids.
He'd be a good father.
He'd be a tremendous father.
But, uh...
As a matter of fact,
several years ago, I said,
"I promise, I'll take
care of the baby
"until the baby
is housebroken."
Of the many decisions
I've made in my life,
one that I am totally
confident was the right one
was not to have children.
Am I willing to devote
virtually my whole life
to my children?
Could I do that
without being resentful?
I doubt it.
The funny thing is, every child
that comes into the building
always runs to Uncle Dean.
He picks them up,
plays with them.
Every one of them.
Every decision you make
is a set of compromises.
The only thing we have a
finite amount of is our time.
I'm not a Superman,
and I couldn't
be as good a parent
as my parents were to me
and still do all the other things
that I feel compelled to do.
So I will live with the fact
that I had great parents
and I tried to do things
for the world and other kids
that in some ways are a testament
to what my parents did for me.
But I don't need to
go down that road.
Inventions really are, I
think, a lot like children.
You make them, and generally,
you're surprised
by what you did,
but after 17 or 20 years,
they both sort of go off to
the world, and never look back.
As currently envisioned,
the SlingShot
will produce 1,000 liters
of pure water every day
from any kind of impure water.
A thousand liters
of water a day
is enough for a hundred people
to all have plenty of water to drink,
to cook, and for hygiene.
And the goal is that machine
will continue to do that
without much maintenance or
overhaul for at least three years,
by which time it will have
produced a million liters
of clean water per machine.
We worked on the machine with
the mental model of sooner or later
it'll reach the time when
we have to try it somewhere
outside of our own lab.
And, uh, you know,
I would've liked a little
more time, but as they say,
"The safest place for a ship
is in the harbor.
"It just doesn't
do you any good there."
We needed to send
this thing out
and we needed to
get real feedback.
So I decide
we gotta test these machines.
So I took some
of my engineers.
They're not exactly international
travelers, but what the hell?
And we supported the trial just
to see whether the technology
would be accepted into those
environments and perform as we expected.
At the time
we sent machines to Honduras,
I was sort of, but maybe not
completely, ready to let them go.
I knew that that machine was
delicate, fragile,
very, very handmade.
This is crazy.
But Hector says,
"No problema."
Lord help us.
But I also knew,
sooner or later,
you've gotta run the risk
of letting people
really use something.
And we had reached that point.
Okay, here it is.
June 3rd, at about
1:30 in the afternoon,
we're starting to fill
the product bag.
Water's going in.
We just put it
in this little town
and said any kid
on the way to school
can come and get
a 20 liter jug of water.
The first week,
it was all boys,
'cause as we all know, there's
no reason for girls to go to school.
But after about a week,
we noticed
something really surprising.
Suddenly, all the families decided
the girls ought to go to school, too.
That was a pretty nice,
unplanned
side effect or benefit
of this program.
We proved our machine
does what we said it would do
with the locally
available water,
and that the community
saw the value of it.
The bad news is we noticed
that most people
would transfer it into a bowl or a
pot, or something that was not clean,
and they'd have
their hands in it.
And we realized they didn't understand
that just because we made it clean,
it's not gonna magically
stay that way.
Clearly, we needed
to give them better ways
to move it and to store it, and
we needed to give them education
about what to do
and not to do with the water.
And DEKA
is a small R&D company
in Manchester, New Hampshire.
We have not only
no global reach,
we have no marketing,
no sales, no distribution.
The experience in Honduras
made it really clear
that just delivering
the machine
is not gonna
solve the problem.
People accept new ideas
very slowly.
In the 1840s
and '50s and '60s,
the telegraph had come along.
Click, click, click,
and a telegram
could go anywhere.
Alexander Bell realizes,
instead of clicking a switch,
it could use
the same infrastructure
that Western Union
put in place.
But instead of sending a telegraph
key signal, you could send voice.
Watson? Come here, I want you.
Alexander Bell was, of
course, all excited about this.
He goes to the biggest company
out there, as the story goes.
The board of directors
of Western Union
basically said,
"You've done a beautiful job
"of making this novelty that
you've just demonstrated to us,
"but of what use would this be
in a serious business?"
It didn't take very long before he
became essentially Bell Telephone,
AT&T.
And Western Union
scrambled for years
to try to go back
and buy those patents,
to catch up, because they had
all that infrastructure.
But they never did.
You gotta be an optimist,
if you try to do this stuff.
If you asked me 15 years ago
how long did I think it would take?
I would've said,
"I don't know, a year or two."
And I would've believed
that I can make this
and then I'll show it
to people,
and then the light bulb
will go on in their head
and they'll see the opportunity
and success will be imminent.
I think the reason
that the SlingShot problem
turned out to be so long
is because it isn't just
a technology problem.
How are you gonna get these
machines to the people that need them?
And we started to worry.
How are we gonna
make that happen?
Why isn't this a success?
I made it work,
it technically does the job,
it takes less than a kilowatt.
Why doesn't it work?
Well, I decided, "It's
the distribution, stupid."
I'm pretty stupid.
We realized
that without a partner
that has an efficient,
effective means
of delivering these machines
and the associated information and
knowledge and education about them,
we'd never be able
to turn this thing
from the science fair project
that it was
into an innovation that could
spread around the world.
What do you want
to do with this?
Well,
since 1.1 billion people,
20% of the world's population,
goes to bed every night sick or thirsty,
because they don't have access
to water, clean water,
we thought we'd put
these in production,
figure out how to get them
placed around the world
and we'd wipe out
50% of human disease.
I made a machine that I thought
would help people with healthcare.
That's my day job.
So I went to my medical
company clients. They can help.
They pretty much said,
"We can't help you.
"We'd love to support it.
We'll help you with money.
"But, Dean, we can't get this
stuff to these places, either."
We'll see what we can do.
I went to governments.
Maybe that's what they're for.
When capitalism doesn't work,
aid organizations, NGOs.
Well, they like to deal
with big-scale stuff.
They also might help
with funding, they told me,
but these big organizations
don't have
people that go out
to these little villages.
They don't have an efficient
distribution channel.
I went to the United Nations,
said, "I've got this box.
"Let's figure out
how to help get it out there."
Their basic answer was, "Good
for you, we're rooting for you.
"But we don't do that.
We don't distribute products.
"We don't build sustainable
micro-economic systems.
"We don't lend people money,
we don't make entrepreneurs.
"That's not what we do."
I was somewhat disappointed.
I believe all of these global
organizations want us to succeed.
But it's a different way of thinking
that we're delivering to them.
Otherwise, they're going to a
place that they haven't been before.
And getting people to do that
is very hard.
Innovation is a very
difficult, frustrating process.
I was probably...
I don't remember, but young.
Probably eight or nine,
when I had just gotten
a new bicycle.
I was just riding it
around and around the block.
Then this kid jumped out,
grabbed the bike,
pushed me off it,
and told me
he didn't want to see
this Jew riding
around the block.
And I was lying there,
and I knew
that if I didn't ride around
the block again,
I would just feel like
I'd been defeated.
And to this day I remember
looking up at this guy
and saying,
"I'm not gonna fight
with you now.
"That would be stupid.
"I'm quite sure
you could easily beat me up.
"But I'm gonna get
on my bicycle
"and I'm gonna ride around
this block again,
"and if you stop me, you
better be prepared to kill me."
And I just looked him
right in the eye,
and he just walked away.
And I got back on the bicycle
and I rode around the block
again, and again, and again
until it started getting dark.
And he never, ever
bothered me again.
One of my all-time
favorite quotes,
not by an inventor, per se,
but a guy dealing
with some really big problems,
Douglas MacArthur,
who said,
"In war, as in every
other human endeavor,
"failure can be summed up
in two words.
"'Too late.'"
I don't wanna be too late
delivering water.
Every year that we wait, another
couple of million people die,
most of them kids.
On the one hand,
I am the entrepreneur in heat,
who always thinks
everything takes too long.
Every project I've ever done,
it takes too long.
On the other hand,
that's another
few million people dying,
because we started
production late.
We gotta get going.
This is a really,
really big day.
I've been given
the opportunity
to talk to the entire
board of directors
of the Coca-Cola Company
about using our
vapor compression distiller
to solve the major
global health problem,
bad water.
We're flying to Atlanta,
we're currently
at 40,000 feet.
We're flying
at about 433 knots,
a little over 500 miles
an hour.
12-3, 653.
Lots of people have
asked me, "Why Coke?"
It's called FIRST.
And a goal!
Final 4, Round 2 has begun!
It grew so big, it had so many
teams from around the country
that it outgrew any venue
in the state.
We needed
a major sports arena,
and we realized we could put it
in the home of the 1996 Olympics.
The 70,000 seat Georgia Dome
in Atlanta.
And we're setting up
down there at this big arena
and you look up
and what's the biggest,
most visible building
on the skyline?
And it suddenly hits me.
Is there some company
in the world
that gets its product
everywhere?
Every little village?
Yeah.
The Coca-Cola Company
has bottling operations
in 206 countries,
which is more
than the number of countries
that are admitted
into the United Nations.
It turned out,
fortunately for us,
that they had
some of their own problems.
They said to us, "We haven't
really updated our fountain system
"in decades."
Do I have a passion to get up in
the morning and work on that project?
Hmm, not so much.
But I said to them,
"I'll help you with your
machines, you help me with mine."
And, literally,
we had a handshake
with their chairman
who said to me, "We'll try."
A couple of years
and a lot of effort later,
we delivered
and they introduced
their freestyle machine.
We went back
to Muhtar Kent and said,
"Now let's figure out
"how we can work together on
the other box, my water machine."
...2-6 clear to land.
The wind's 210...
If Coca-Cola decided
that it is
in their best interest,
it's in the
world's best interest
that we quickly deploy, literally,
hundreds of thousands of these machines,
they could do it.
What are you gonna say
to people about Coke's
earlier troubles with water?
Well, I think we've now come
to live in a world of sound bites,
where everybody wants a simple
one-sentence, or in some case,
one-word answer.
And in our culture,
we have people that think
businesses is the source
of all evil
and other people that
think the opposite.
All those simplistic answers have
the advantage that they're simple.
They all have the disadvantage
that they're wrong.
No Pepsi, no Cola!
We want drinking water!
For every liter of soft
drink the company makes,
it has to extract three liters
of water.
And angry farmers
claim that Coke
is literally sucking the water
from beneath their feet.
Coca-Cola has been asked to
pay $47 million in compensation
for alleged
environmental damage
caused at a bottling plant
in Southern India.
The plant,
one of its largest there,
was forced to close in 2005 after massive
nationwide protests against the company.
- No Pepsi, no Cola.
- We want drinking water.
Unbridled power by anybody,
a government agency,
a corporation, is always
potentially dangerous.
But in the end,
most companies work hard
to earn the respect and trust
of their customers
because it's in their
enlightened best interest.
We all
have to conserve water
and therefore, Coca-Cola
has been the first business,
in a way, that has declared a
goal of water neutrality by 2020.
Nobody treats water
with dignity in the world.
Everybody thinks it's free,
it's available,
and then we have said
that by 2020,
we are going to globally
become water neutral.
That means, give back to
the world every liter of water
that we use in our beverages and to
make our beverages. That you take.
I think
it's a waste of energy,
and it's a disservice
to ourselves
to look for
who we're gonna blame.
And I think,
if we can orchestrate
what government does well,
what NGOs do well,
what giant corporations
do well,
what little inventors do well,
the result of that is we
make the world a better place.
By sitting around
trying to figure out
which one of those entities
is a bad guy,
we do nothing.
Wait a minute,
isn't it Sunday now?
So I get double overtime.
So that's triple overtime.
Where's Jimmy Hoffa
when I need him?
My mother calls,
as all mothers do,
"I'm still worried, Dean, you're
working too hard, you're running too far.
"You need to just slow down."
"Okay, Mother.
I agree with you."
"So should I
stop doing FIRST?" "No."
"Okay, I'll stop working on
that medical product." "No."
"Okay, I'll just stop working
on the water machine
"we hope to supply
to families around the world,
"so two million babies
will have clean water." "No."
"Okay, Mother, which of the things I
am working on do you recommend I stop?
"Which ones?"
And there's never
a good answer.
So I keep going.
Some people like to play golf.
Let them go play golf.
We agreed with
the Coca-Cola Company
that we would go out
and build 15 machines
in this pilot production run
to be used in trials.
We were gonna be in five
different schools in Ghana
and then from there,
depending on how those trials go,
we're moving to other places
around Africa and Central America.
Huh? Okay, it depends.
There were so many
horror stories we had heard,
of attempts to do something
like bring clean water to places,
that had ended in failure,
not for technical reasons,
but for social, economic,
financial, political reasons.
I was afraid that, once again,
it's gonna be
a science fair project
and not an innovation
that spreads through
that community
in that part of the world.
Going, going, going, going...
Gone.
When the first
images came back
and we saw
a crowd of excited kids
smiling and laughing, and watching
these kids just guzzle this water down,
everybody realized that our
ideas are one step closer to reality.
So, as all of you know,
probably, only too well,
I am a big believer that the
last thing you ever want to do
is relax,
go take a nap
on that bear skin rug,
before you're sure
you shot the bear.
This bear ain't dead yet.
But even I think sometimes
it's nice to take a little bit of time
to celebrate.
Couple of weeks ago,
we finally got in writing
with signatures on it, the deal.
We are partners now
with the Coca-Cola Company.
We've gotta deliver no less
than 50 working machines
of the next generation,
half the weight
and half the size,
deliverable by
the end of this year.
You know, if it works,
and we supply water,
we will have potentially supplied
more healthcare through this project,
than the sum total of all the
projects we've done in 30 years.
So, Jim,
don't screw it up.
Cheers!
To all of you!
Stewart, Stewart...
Have some pizza, will you?
These people are way too smart
not to be scared.
Now, eat the pizza.
And drink the beer.
And then get back to work.
A long time ago,
in a faraway place,
I, literally,
designed the circuit boards.
I etched them in the ferric
chloride dish in my mother's oven.
These days, I have
400 extraordinary people,
and each has some specialty
that is in a different
zip code of capability
in their specialty
than I ever was.
Well, let's do that again.
You hit me in the nose,
you're dead.
Dennis, I got good news
and bad news. What's that?
These things are working...
To make one more of the
models of the machine you've seen,
I say to the 20 people
in there,
"You make the compressor wheel
out of that block of aluminum.
"You make this part
out of steel."
You add up the cost of all those
people and all those resources,
and it turns out, it costs
hundreds of thousands of dollars
to put another model
out there.
In five out of five
locations in Ghana,
we met every
expectation we had
for performance
and acceptance,
and we sadly confirmed,
yup, the basic machine is
too heavy to bring to scale,
it's too expensive
to bring to scale,
and it was too hard to set up
and deal with the sometimes
erratic access to electricity.
And as a result
of that experiment,
we said, "Let's figure out how to make
them more cost-effective to manufacture,
"smaller and lighter,
and let's do the next round."
So I know we're going with the
plastic housing, instead of the aluminum,
but that aluminum rotor,
and all that machining
was obviously...
Costly.
Right.
How are we doing that? So we're
gonna go to an injection-molded rotor,
just like we did
with the housings.
Right, so there's your rotor.
So...
Plastic rotor.
Yep.
Our trials would be
one, two, three machines.
What we're calling
the "Alpha Build,"
will be between 50
and 100 identical machines.
In a real factory,
in a period of a month,
you could stamp out
10,000 machines,
not one.
The labor cost associated with that
10,000 machines is almost nothing.
To make one more machine then,
is the cost of these finished parts,
which we will get down to a
few thousand dollars per machine.
This device will be less
than half the size,
less than half the weight
of the machines
that we used
for the Ghana trials.
And the goal is to have them all
finished for the next level of testing
in Central America
and in Africa.
And if that project
goes as we hope,
the next round of development should
be relatively high-volume production
to start the serious project of
giving water to a few billion people.
I think somebody
that's a really big person
is somebody that doesn't mind
helping everybody else around them.
A really big person helps
everybody else be big,
and doesn't use their bigness
to keep everybody else small.
My brother was a big person.
Libby, my niece, is here.
She's been with FIRST
her whole life.
She lost a dad.
I lost a brother.
My mom
lost her son.
The whole FIRST community
lost a great resource.
He was a mentor,
he was a volunteer,
he was a judge.
He was somebody everybody
could aspire to be like.
What I admired about Bart
was he had a little bit of my
father in him that I don't have.
That he was so easy-going.
And he was always conscious of making
everybody around him feel comfortable,
which was an incredible asset,
since the people around him,
most of the time, were little kids,
that would otherwise be
scared to death because
they have cancer.
Patrick.
Just a month ago. Yeah.
Thank you.
You stay very, very healthy.
It never even
came into my head
that I'd get old, and not
be able to call my brother.
I believe, right now, I can
pick up the phone and call him.
I can't...
I can't really believe that
that's not the case.
Life is so short.
And Bart's passing
just gives me
even more urgency.
My whole life,
every time I thought of something
good and important to do,
I wanted to do it now.
It's not a coincidence
I build clocks.
'Cause the world's in a race.
Between all sorts
of catastrophes,
and technical expertise.
We can't let catastrophe win.
So time is critical.
Coca-Cola selected
ideal locations
for the next level of testing.
Mexico,
South Africa,
Paraguay.
What we're learning is, if there are
206 different countries on this planet,
we have to ask ourselves at least
206 different ways to be successful,
because in each environment,
there are different challenges.
The ideal would be a machine
that has no weight, no size,
no cost, never breaks down,
is available wherever you
need it, all the time, free.
That will never happen.
There is, I think, a very
pervasive but naive assumption
that aid means
you give things away.
If you give things away,
with this mythical idea
that it should have no cost,
it will end up demonstrating
that it had no value.
It will be those people that are
drinking the output of this device
that are protecting it,
maintaining it,
in some cases,
creating a business around it
and becoming entrepreneurs.
The Wright brothers flew
at Kitty Hawk in 1903.
The day after they did that,
you didn't see airlines.
You didn't get
frequent flyer miles.
In fact, I believe, it was at
least a decade after they did that,
before anybody had any
commercial use of any airplane.
Where we were with the first
machines that you saw in Ghana,
we were like the Wright
brothers, with their first flyer.
Where are we now
with our Alpha machines?
We're one of those early airplanes
with the big propellers, spitting smoke.
Where would we like to be
with our next machine?
You know, the dream liner.
Where do we want
to be after that?
A spaceship.
I think the reason that water is
such a big problem these days
is because all the people in the
western world don't see it as a problem.
In fact,
they don't even see it at all.
Even here, in the richest
country in the world,
our pure clean water isn't as
pure and as clean as we thought.
Sadly, most of us will probably
come to see a world where
you can't trust
tap water anymore.
At least 41 million of us
are drinking water that contains
traces of prescription drugs.
Anti-seizure medications,
prescription pain killers.
Even the anti-depressant
ingredient in Prozac.
There are, literally, for instance,
tens of millions of women
that are taking birth control.
And every day, they literally
pass through their body, hormones
that municipal water systems
can't filter out.
And tiny, tiny, tiny
amounts of hormones
have a big effect
on your health.
The average age of puberty for
young girls in the United States
has been dropping
pretty radically.
The problem of global access to
water is getting worse everywhere,
including, in the next
decade or two, North America.
There will be many places
around this country,
where water becomes
a serious issue.
Everybody asks me, "Well, why
do we call the box SlingShot?"
As a little kid, I was always
the smallest kid in my grade,
and I heard the story
of David and Goliath,
and to me, the moral of that
story was, "Technology is cool."
And people say to me, "How?
How did you get that moral out of it?"
I say, "Well, there was
this really little guy, David.
"He had this really
big problem, Goliath.
"But he had this little
thing called the slingshot.
"And that little piece of technology
took out that really big problem."
Dean, where are you? Stand up.
Now, let me tell you.
About seven years ago,
I did drink
some of the ugliest, most
contaminated water you ever saw.
Dean came and put it
in his little machine,
I drank it down, and
I'm still here. It works.
I mean, it works.
I drink it all the time.
It works and it is just an
amazing piece of equipment.
You start putting
all these pieces together
and the chain will finally go from a
crazy idea to, "Of course. It was obvious."
Let's put water machines
all over the world.
There's no easier way to wipe
out 50% of all human disease.
Let's just do it.
- Simple.
- Overnight success?
I think in less than 20 years, we're
gonna be an overnight success.
We want to be helping get
water to everybody on this planet.
It's the right thing to do.
It's simply
the right thing to do.
We can do it.
Therefore, we should do it.
So why is it prevention
to give people clean water?
Call me crazy.
We have
a Department of Defense
and we build the ultimate
weapons of mass destruction.
But how about if we build
weapons of mass construction?
And what if we go around the
world and give everybody clean water,
and it says "US" on it,
your friend?
Maybe we'll have
a Department of Peace.
And maybe
we will prevent the wars.
And if we can get these water
machines into high volume production,
I think we put them
around the world
and there's a way better shot
that a large part of two billion people
will be our friends.
I don't have time for things
that just don't matter.
So, number one, is I'd like to work
on big problems and solve them.
Number two,
is at least I'll be able to say to the
world, "I worked on a really big problem.
"I didn't solve it, but I
tried. What did you do?"
And at least, I hope in the
end, I didn't waste my time.
What I really, really want
is a time machine.
If I could step
into some device
and transport myself back
to have a conversation, 2,300
years ago with Archimedes...
"Hey, Archi. What's up with
that buoyancy thing?" You know...
I don't know what I'd say.
Or if I could go forward
even just 100 years,
will they have answers to questions
that we simply don't understand now?
And will they be answers that
are, "Oh, why didn't we see that?"
Do you think
you could build one?
As I said, whenever you
talk about technology,
using a word like "never"
always comes back to haunt you.
We will cure every kind of
cancer you can think of.
We will make computers that outperform
anything you could possibly imagine.
I don't say "never"
to just about anything,
but I'll say
it's gonna be a long time
before there's a time machine,
especially one that has
the beautiful convenience
of what H.G. Wells
had in mind.
Get in it, dial in a time,
get out.
Get back in,
dial in a different time.
Now, that's an invention.
If anybody,
or any group of people
come up with
a device to do that,
they deserve the whole wall.
Are you ready?
Are we all watching?
This is pressure.
Dean, higher.
Oh, I failed!
Oh, all right, all right.
Ready?
You know,
I don't want to say anything,
but I think I reached
the pinnacle of this.
For you to be thanking
me, it makes my brain hurt.
I mean, it's the veterans that gave
me the opportunity to do all these things.
And I thank all of you...
We could empty half of all the
beds in all the hospitals in the world
by just giving people
clean water.