''Spirit Stallion of the Cimarron''
The story I want to tell you,
can not be found in a book.
They say the history of the West was
written from the saddle of a horse.
But it's never been told
from the heart of one.
Not until now.
I was born here.
In this place that would come
to be called the ''Old West''
But to my kind, the land was ageless.
It had no beginning and no end.
No boundary between earth and sky.
Like the wind in the Buffalo grass.
We belong here.
We will always belong here.
They say the mustang is the
spirit of the West.
Whether that West
was won or lost in the end
You have to decide for yourself.
But the story
I want to tell you is true.
I was there.
And I remember.
I remember the sun, and the sky
and the wind calling my name.
In the time when the wild
horses ran free.
## Here I am
## This is me
## I come to this world so wild and free
## Here I am
## So young and strong
## Right here in the place where I belong
## It's a new world
## It's a new start
## It's life with a beating of
## a young heart
## It's a new day
## In a new land
## And it's waiting for me
## Here I am
## It's a new world
## It's a new start
## It's life with a beating of
## a young heart
## Yeah, it's a new day
## In a new land
## And it's waiting for me
## Here I am
And so I grew from colt to stallion
As wild and reckless
As thunder over the land.
Racing with the eagle.
Soaring with the wind.
Flying?
There were times I believed I could.
Like my father before me
I became leader of the Cimarron herd.
And with that honour
Came responsibility.
## I hear the wind
## Across the plane
## A sound so strong
## That calls my name
## It's wild like the river
## It's warm like the sun
## Yeah, it's here
## This is where I belong
## Under the star skies
## Where eagles have flown
## This place is paradise
## It's the place I call home
## The moon on the mountain
## The whisper through the trees
## The winds on the water
## Let nothing come between this and me
## It's everything I want
## It's everything this here
## And when we are all together
## There's nothing
## To fear
## And wherever I wander
## The one thing I've learned
## Yes
## It's to here
## I will always
## Always
## Return
Something new came upon
the land one night.
Something that changed my life
forever...
And so my journey began.
A wiser horse might have turned
and ran.
But I wanted to know what
strange creature was here.
Look.
Man, look at that stallion,
it is beautiful.
Follow the horse! Let's go!
Look out!
Don't you get away!
I was scared.
I didn't know what was going
to happen to me.
At least my mother
and the herd were safe.
Come on!
## I got find another fight
## I got run another night
## Get it out, check it out
## I'm on my way and I don't feel right
## I got come back
## I can't be beat, and that's a fact
## It's Ok, I'll find a way
## Ain't gonna take me, down the way
## Yeah
## Don't judge a thing 'till you know
## what is inside it
## Don't push me, I'll fight it
## Never gonna give it up, no
## If you can't catch a wave
## Then you'll never gonna ride it
## You can't come uninvited
## Never gonna give it up, no
## You can't take me
## I'm free
## Why did it all go wrong
## I wanna know what's going on
## What's this holding me?
## I'm not where I'm supposed to be
## I got fight another fight
## I got fight with all my might
## I'm getting out, just check it out
## You're in my way,
## You better watch out
Open the gate!
Come on!
## Don't judge a thing 'till you know
## what's inside it
## Don't push me, I'll fight it
## Never gonna give it up, no
## If you can't catch a wave
## Then you'll never gonna ride it
## You can't come uninvited
## Never gonna give it up, no
## You can't take me
## I'm free
## Yeah, I'm free
What seems to be the
problem, gentlemen?
We got this crazy one here, Sir.
- Pure Mustang, Colonel.
Really?
The army has dealt with
wild horses before.
This one will be no different.
I remember the first time
I saw a rattler curled up in my path
-Induct this animal, Sargent.
-Yes Sir!
This one didn't look like a rattler.
But I was still thinking...
snake.
Grab him, grab him.
Okay Murphy, he's all yours.
He's a wild one.
We'll see how wild he is,
when I am done with him.
You want a fight, do you?
Right.
Make sure that's good tight.
Murphy, look out! Watch out!
Murphy, are you okay?
Corporal, round up some volunteers to
take this animal to the stables.
Not the stables. -Sir?
-The corral.
It's time to break that horse.
# Well you think that you can take me on
# You must be crazy
Make sure it's good tied.
## Ain't a single thing you've done
## Is gonna phase me
## If you wanna have a go
# I just wanna let you know
## Get off my back and into my game
## Get out of my way
## Cause I'm wild and untamed
## Get out of my face
## Or gimme your best shot
## I think it's time
## You better face the fact
## Get off my back
Ok, my turn!
## You know is all just a game
## that I'm playing
## You think that you can find a
## way in, is what I'm saying
## If you wanna have a go
## I just wanna let you know
## Get off my back and
## into my game
## Get out of my face
## Cause I'm wild and untamed
## Get out of my way
## Or gimme your best shot
Another rider!
## You know the train is coming off its track
## Get off my back
## Yeah, get off my back
## Get off
## Get off, get off, get off
## Get off my back
Sargent. -Yes Sir.
Tie this horse to the post.
No food or water. Three days.
Yes Sir.
My heart galloped through
the sky that night
Back to my herd.
Where I belonged.
And I wonder if they'd miss me
As much as I miss them.
We got a hostile!
Bring him there this way.
Well, what do we have here?
We caught him
by the supply wagon, Sir.
Ah, a Dakota.
Not as tall as the Cheyenne,
and fine featured as the Crow.
Take him away gentlemen,
show him our best.
Corporal, take him to the stock case.
Not the stock case. The post.
No food or water.
What are you looking at boy?
He was called Little Creak.
And he seemed different from the rest.
There were just no end to the
strange ways of the two legged.
With the Colonel permission, Sir.
Incoming patrol report hostiles
headed North.
The railroad has expressed concern, Sir.
They requested additional patrols.
How long has it been, Sargent?
Sir?
-The mustang.
How long has it been tied?
Three days, Sir.
Good.
Fetch my crop and spurs.
Take it easy!
Back up! Back up!
You see gentlemen,
any horse can be broken.
Move along mustang.
There are those in Washington who believe
the West will never be settled.
The northern pacific railroad
will never breach Nebraska.
A hostile Dakota will never
submit to providence.
And it is that manner of small thinking.
That would say this horse
could never be broken.
Discipline, time, and patience.
Are the three great levelers.
Sometimes a horse's gotta do,
what a horse's gotta do
And this was one of those times.
Get off me!
Soldier! Secure that horse!
I wasn't sure
what happened back there.
And I wasn't about to stop and ask.
All I knew was I was headed home.
I couldn't believe it.
One moment I was free,
and the next... more ropes.
I couldn't understand it.
She treated the scrawny two-legged
Like one of our kind.
Prancing around him
Like a love struck ear ring.
It was down right unnatural.
Great mustang, today I will ride you.
This ought to be good...
Mares.
Okay, Rain, lets see if you can teach
This mustang some manners.
Okay, I admit it
She was charming
In a stubborn, irritating kind of way.
So, I let her show me her world.
Bye-Bye horsey.
For the first time in my life,
I felt my heart torn two ways.
Give it back!
Mustang!
I had to hand to that boy.
He just wouldn't give up.
I'm never gonna ride you, am I?
And no one never should.
You can go.
It's okay, go.
Go on, get out of here.
Go home.
I knew this was hard for her,
and she was scared.
But more than anything,
I wanted to share my homeland with her
I laid beside her that night.
Hoping, praying that somehow
she would be okay.
There are a couple
of horses over there!
Leave her there.
She's not gonna make it.
Oh, Rain!
Easy, girl.
Easy.
It will be okay.
You saved my life.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Come on, it's gonna be okay.
## Sound the bugle now
## Play it just for me
## As the seasons change
## Remember how I used to be
## Now I can't go on
## I can't even start
## I got nothing left
## Just an empty heart
## I'm a soldier
## Wounded soul I must give up the fight
## There's nothing more for me
## Lead me away
## Or leave me lying here
## Sound the bugle now
## Tell them I don't care
## There's not a road I know
## That leads to anywhere
## Without a light
## I fear that I'll stumble in the dark
## Lay out down
## Decide
## Not to go on
## That from high
## Somewhere in the distance
## There's a voice that calls
## Remember who you are
## If you loose yourself
## Your courage soon will follow
## So, be strong tonight
## Remember who you are
## Yeah
## You're a soldier now
## Fighting in a battle
## To be free once more
## Yeah, that's worth fighting for
It'll be alright.
I didn't know
why we were brought here.
What I did know
was we had to find a way to escape,
and get back home.
Well, that is it, we're rolling
the steam over the mountain.
We got six days to connect to Utah.
Move out and gone.
Ready to go!
We're almost on the top!
That was the moment I understood
They were headed to my homeland
And I had to stop them.
Get back!
Oh, we got to stop!
Hold it!
Get the mules up here!
I don't know where he came from
Or how he got there.
But I sure was happy to see him.
I don't believe it.
Go! Go! Run!
We got 'em now!
Where did they go?
There they are!
Up there!
Oh no.
Oh yes.
## Don't judge a thing 'till you know
## what is inside it
## Don't push me, I'll fight it
## Never gonna give it up, no
## If you can't catch a wave
## Then you'll never gonna ride it
## You can't come uninvited
## Never gonna give it up, no!
## You can't take me
## I'm free
You will always be in my heart.
Take care of her,
Spirit...
Who cannot be broken.
I will miss you, my friend.
I've been waiting
so long to run free.
But that goodbye was harder
than I ever imagined.
I will never forget that boy.
And how we won back
our freedom together.
## I hear the wind
## Call my name
## The sound that leads me
## Home again
## It sparks up the fire
## A flame that still runs
## To you
## I will always return
## I know the road is long
## But where you are is home
## Wherever you stay
## I'll find the way
## I run like the river
## I'll follow the sun
## I'll fly like an eagle
## To where I belong
## I can't stand the distance
## I can't dream alone
## I can't wait to see you
## Yes, I'm on my way home
## Now I know it's true
## That every road leads to you
## And in the hour of darkness
## Your light gets me through
## You run like the river
## You shine like the sun
## Yeah
## You fly like an eagle
## Yeah, you are the one
## I've seen every sunset
## And with all that I've learned
## It's to you I will always
## Always
## Return
-The end- Fixed and lyrics by PROMAC.