Hey there, all you sleepy
Angelenos. A good, good morning to you.
It's your buddy, Romeo Midnight.
I know.
I'm the voice you normally
listen to in the middle of the night.
But today is special, Los Angeles.
It's my favorite day of the year.
Today is Valentine's Day.
And that's why I'll be here all day and
all night, playing the songs you love...
...and the songs you love
to love to.
Hi.
Okay.
When I was a kid, most of the advice
that my dad gave me was crap.
There's one thing that he said
that was pure genius.
He said, "If you ever are with a girl...
...that's too good for you...
...marry her."
So...
Wow.
- Really?
- Happy Valentine's Day.
Happy Valentine's Day.
She said yes!
Julia, call me as soon as you get this.
I got big news. Big news.
- She said yes.
- You're kidding.
- What?
- I mean, you're kidding!
- You thought she'd say no.
- Man, come on. You know me...
...always preparing for the worst.
Immigrant mentality.
- Forget it. She said yes. This is good news.
- Yeah, and get this:
I don't even have to play it cool today.
I can be a sappy cheeseball all day...
...mooning about love to total strangers,
and no one'll think I'm a moron.
Because it's Valentine's Day, huh?
And everyone is romantic
on Valentine's Day.
Get your head out of your ass
and use your damn turn signal...
...you freaking moron.
Good morning, Los Angeles.
I'm Sherry Donaldson
with the KVLA news team.
- And now let's check the weather.
- Good morning.
Sun shines on late morning,
and look at these numbers.
Highs in the upper valleys in the 60s,
and a bit cloudy by the coast...
...until mid-morning,
when the marine layer burns off.
Susan, what the hell is this?
Oh, the boss thinks
it's gonna up the ratings.
And we're clear.
Not talking about Pippi Longstocking,
I'm talking about this.
I'm a sports journalist,
I don't do lifestyle.
You're my number two sports journalist,
Kelvin, which means...
...that on slow sports days,
you do the pieces I want you to do.
The station wants more fluff.
I'll do some follow-up stories,
do some investigative reporting...
...bring it back to you?
There's only one story today, Kelvin.
It's all yours.
It's not complicated.
It's your basic man on the street.
"Tell me, John Q, Jane Q,
what does Valentine's Day mean to you?"
It gives me acid reflux.
That's what it means to me.
We spend a lot of money. Nobody cares.
It's not a real holiday.
We don't take the day off.
Come on, Susan.
And we're coming back
in five, four, three...
Listen, I'm a player...
...but I shut down my player-ness...
...from New Year's to Saint Paddy's Day
just so I can avoid this day.
I need happy, I need romantic,
I need love...
...and I need it from you.
You need Jesus.
Go. Go away now.
Sunflowers! Beautiful!
Good morning!
- Hello, good morning.
- Hello, hello.
I need my lucky bamboo.
Actually, I need both flats, and...
- Do you hav...? I actually need the whole lot.
- All of them?
- Want my Gerbera daisies too?
- No, no, no. No... Yes.
Alphonso's gonna
pick everything up later.
- Mr. Reed, why are you always happy?
- Why not be always happy?
- Reed?
- Simon.
- Reed.
- What's up, man?
- How are you?
- All right.
- What's going on?
- Hey, I'm gonna be on TV.
- Interviewer over there.
- Really?
Nice! Listen, I need to talk to you.
Morley said yes.
She said yes?
What is with everybody?
She said yes. I'm getting married.
It's great news, huh?
Listen, I need to get her something,
like, really nice, though, like...
Not roses, something out of the ordinary,
you know?
Ah... Huh.
- Wow, what is it?
- No, no, no.
Do not open until perfect moment.
Ready for the interview.
Kelvin Moore here, KVLA Channel 13...
...right here at the downtown
flower mart with Mr. Simon Pham...
...that's P-H-A-M, not with an F.
Mr. Pham, how many red roses do you sell
on Valentine's Day?
The Captain and Tennille
were married on Valentine's Day.
What's that you said?
The Captain and Tennille were married
on Valentine's Day.
A hundred and ten million red roses
are sold in America every Valentine's Day.
- Sixty percent are produced in California.
- Does he work for you? I mean...
I'm a florist.
I own Siena Bouquet, 2173 Rosewood.
- And what's your name, sir?
- Reed Bennett.
- Hi. How are you? Sports guy. Sports.
- Reed Bennett. Yeah, sports.
- Okay, from Santa Montica...
- Siena Bouquet.
- Santa... What is it? Siena Bouquet.
In the Val... Off of Ventura.
Well, you do have a flaw after all.
- Oh, yeah? What's that?
- Your job.
I thought women liked doctors.
We do like lab coats, but the flying
around everywhere is not so good.
I'm only going to San Francisco
for one night.
Couldn't somebody else do it,
just tonight?
No, I'm the best.
If it's any consolation,
when I'm fixing his heart...
...you can hold mine.
Oh. Thank you.
Hey, what are you doing? No.
I can't miss my plane. No.
I can't believe you're leaving me
on Valentine's Day.
- You said you had something to do.
- I do have something.
I do have something to do.
I just don't know that I wanna do it.
- You know my friend Kara?
- Which one's Kara?
Neurotic, hot mess.
She throws this annual
"I Hate Valentine's Day" dinner.
- It's a bit of a downer, actually.
- What's there to hate?
Nothing, if you're a handsome,
divorced doctor.
But for the rest of us single women,
it's kind of a giant cosmic bitch slap.
It's the universe saying,
"Look, remember when you were 14...
...and you had cystic acne and braces...
...and you played the saxophone
in the band...
...and no one would invite you
to the winter formal?
Well, nothing's changed."
I would crawl over cut glass
to take you to the winter formal.
And then I would prescribe Retin-A
for your skin.
That's why you're my valentine.
So we have a professional here.
I'm sure you've heard a lot of stories
on Valentine's Day.
Do you still believe in love?
Hell, yes. Love is the only shocking act
left on the planet.
Well, if he said it, folks,
it must be true, because he is a florist.
What is it?
Oh, you're up.
- Did you get my good side?
- I don't know. Roll over.
Last night...
Was...?
- Amazing.
- Okay, thank you.
- Wow. Well, I used to be a gymnast.
- Oh, well, that explains a lot.
Yeah, I didn't hurt you, right?
- You're so cute.
- I thought you wanted to be a poet...
...not a photographer.
- A girl can change her mind, Jason.
That's how last night happened.
- Anyway, I could not write that photo.
- Okay, yeah. Um...
Is my nose kind of...?
It looks kind of big for my face.
I think that's L.A. Talking.
I think you have a great nose.
Oh, my God. Is that the time?
What? What? No, it's 3 minutes fast.
I don't like being late.
- I have to go. I just...
- Just like that?
Yeah, I'm sorry. I just...
Skirt? Skirt, skirt, skirt.
What? Oh, right.
I think I half-remember that.
- Three minutes? Why not 5 minutes ahead?
- I don't wanna seem eager.
But, yeah, you know what? Stay.
Hang out for a little bit.
Maybe we can grab breakfast.
- Oh, I knew it. I knew it.
- What is that, techno?
- What?
- The ring.
Oh, no, I think it's, like,
a little more retro. It's kind of '70s.
Thank you so much for last night.
I had a blast.
And there is fresh coffee for you
in the kitchen.
- I think I'm out of coffee.
- You were.
I borrowed some from your neighbor.
She was surprised...
...you had female company,
thought that you were gay.
Don't worry, I set her straight.
Bye.
Hi.
Oh, I was thinking about you
all night long.
Oh, I'm sorry I didn't answer
on the first ring.
It's not my fault.
I was thinking about
what you were gonna do to me...
...and I just couldn't wait.
I didn't have a free hand.
Oh, baby.
You know just how Katia likes it. Mm.
Well, it's Valentine's Day, sugar.
How about something special?
My roommate just got home.
Do you wanna have a threesome?
If he says yes,
it'll take me a minute to change.
Ooh. I think that's a very good idea.
Edgar, we said we were not gonna
give each other presents this year.
I know, I lied.
- So did I.
- Wow.
Today's the day I make most of my dough.
I deliver love-grams to businesses.
I even delivered a breakup-gram today.
Folks, from the chubby messenger
of love himself...
...that Valentine's Day is about love.
It's about romance.
It's about commercialism that...
- Found the glue, Grandma.
- Well, good.
This is really a hard day for him...
...because they used to make
handcrafted cards together.
Well, maybe we should've offered
to do that with him.
I did.
But he said it was only fun
when it was with his mother.
So, Edison...
...what are we doing for breakfast today?
- I can't eat, Grandpa.
Who said that? So you can't eat?
What's the matter?
What's the matter, you sick?
Yeah. Lovesick.
Julia, it's Reed.
I've been trying to reach you.
Call me back, please.
Oh, boy. Oh.
- Hi.
So my boyfriend texted me this morning.
And he was like,
"Look outside your door."
Oh.
And... But, you know,
I look outside my door...
...and my boyfriend's
nowhere to be found.
Right.
- But there's this giant white bear.
- Yeah, the bear.
- On the ground. The floor.
- I get it.
- Yeah. Isn't that the sweetest thing ever?
- Ever and ever.
Do you live here? In this building?
Because I see you in the lobby all the time.
- Because I live here.
- No, I just visit. Just visiting.
All right, well,
I'm gonna go to school now.
Gonna take my bear with me.
- I hope you get a lot of valentines today.
- Thanks.
Hello, everyone.
This is your captain speaking.
On behalf of myself and the flight deck...
...we wanted to wish everyone
a happy Valentine's Day.
Hope you had an opportunity
to get a little rest.
But according to my digital readout here,
we've still got another six hours...
...before we reach our final destination
of Los Angeles...
...where the weather is expected to be warm
and sunny after three days of rain.
- Oh, hello.
- Hey.
- Hey, is Reed here, or is he on a run?
- Yeah, he's in there.
- Okay. Hey, guys.
- Hi, Julia.
- How was last night, brutal?
- Yeah.
- Have you been up all night?
- Hey.
- Wow, everybody's here today.
- Oh, whose child is this? Hello?
- Oh, there's your mother.
- Please hold.
- Hey, Nikki.
- Good morning.
Oh, these are yellow. Where's Reed?
Your pal's in the café.
The pastries were late.
Oh, yeah. I think he might be having
a rough morning.
Hello, Siena Bouquet.
- Hey. Reed.
- Just need...
We need the morning glories.
Oh, there they are. Perfect. Great.
- Hey, I got your message. You okay?
- Yeah.
- What happened?
- Well, you just sounded like...
- You sounded like maybe she said...
- "Yes."
- She said yes.
- No.
Why doesn't anybody have confidence?
- She said yes?
- Yes.
Oh, my goodness. Okay. I didn't...
I didn't get it, but congratulations!
- Call me Mr. Engaged.
- You're getting married.
Hi, I ordered some tulips.
Yes. You can't put the baby on the counter,
it's dangerous.
- But I can't get my money out.
- She should be off the counter. Thanks.
- Here, let me hold her.
- Thank you.
- You should know we're Jewish.
- God loves us all.
- Thank you.
- Hello, Siena Bouquet.
He's the first decent guy
I've dated in a long time.
It's going that well, huh?
I am so sick of dating.
I'm so jealous of you guys.
When do I get to meet
the phantom physician?
- I think soon.
- You guys got plans tonight?
No. He has to go to San Francisco,
so we're gonna talk on the phone.
You know what you should do?
You should fly up and surprise him.
- You think so?
- Yeah. Why not?
- No.
- Come on.
I don't know where he's staying...
You make a call, you find out.
What's the big deal?
- God, you really think I should go?
- Why not?
Come on, it's Valentine's Day.
You don't think. You just do.
Go.
- Get out of here.
- Congratulations.
- Hello there.
- Hi.
Hey, honey.
I'm just pulling into the airport.
I'll call you when I land, okay?
Okay, I get it. Okay, have a safe flight.
I'll talk to you later. Bye.
Thanks. Bye-bye.
Hello. Good morning. I'm home.
- Hi, Daddy.
- Hey, peanut.
Hi, sweetie.
- Did you fix all the broken hearts?
- I did.
- Happy Valentine's Day.
Happy Valentine's Day to you.
- Surgery went late. I stayed at the condo.
- I figured.
Doesn't Daddy juggle well?
- Yeah.
- Mm-hm.
What are you doing?
Sorry, l... Excuse me,
I was trying to close the window.
I'm sorry.
No. For leaning on my shoulder? Come on,
it's the least I could do. A 14-hour flight.
Oh, God, that's better.
- You on active duty?
- Yes, sir.
- Two bars. Is that lieutenant?
- Two bars is the captain.
You have a loved one in L.A.?
Well, I'm sure he'll be happy to see you.
How long...? How long has it been
since you've been home?
Eleven months.
And how long do you get to stay?
Just till tomorrow.
Wow. Fourteen-hour flight both ways
just for one night.
Wow, that's romantic.
You're a romantic.
I mean, that's quite a gesture.
That's commitment.
You on Facebook?
- I need some chrysanthemums.
- What? You should speak English.
- I had to learn when I came.
- Chrysanthemums and calla lilies.
- I don't know what it...
- Michael, calm down.
What language do you speak in?
I used to speak Bulgarian,
but I'm an American citizen now.
Does anybody here speak English
with a Bulgarian accent?
- Over here. I do.
- There he is.
Bulgarize away. Here we go.
There she is!
The future Mrs. Reed Bennett!
Oh, chrysanthemums.
- Hi, babe.
- Hi, baby.
Hello, fiancée.
It sounds weird. Have you said it yet?
Nikki, take over for a minute.
Come this way.
Wait, these are for you.
I knew they were for somebody.
- Sarah, have you met my fiancée?
- Hi, Morley.
- Hi.
- I just like saying it. I feel so grown-up.
Next, please!
- Look what you forgot.
- See, that is...
Is one empty hand.
Oh, yeah.
Don't be mad.
Mad? Why would I be mad?
I'm concerned.
Well, just...
Do you have any idea what it would be
like at work today if I wore that thing?
- I mean, people will be asking me...
- "Where'd you get the big ring?"
You know, "How many bridesmaids?"
And, "How did he do it?"
- "Gonna have kids? How many?"
- Three.
- What?
- Two dogs, and maybe some chickens.
- We can talk about it. We don't have to.
- Sweetheart, I just think right now...
...it would be better if maybe
we could just keep it a secret.
- Where are you from?
- I am from Ruse.
All right, you guys can start
a Bulgarian village together. All right.
Oh, my God, look, there's the bride. Hi.
Listen, I called my BFF, Tony.
He is already on the dress.
He does all the gowns in Vegas.
Cher, Celine, Carrot Top.
This is going to be so much fun!
Oh, my God, it's...
- Breathe, breathe.
- I have to breathe.
Okay.
- See what I mean?
- Yep, I get it.
So...
...Iove is the problem?
- Did you ever have it?
- Oh, yeah.
How old were you when you got it?
Let's see. I'd just started working
at an architectural firm...
...and there was this beautiful young girl,
and she was studying to be an actress.
Was your heart kind of going:
Yeah. Yeah, just that way. It went,
bumpada, bumpada, bumpada, boom.
You betcha. Just like that.
One day I got up the courage
to introduce myself.
I walk out, walked right up to her
and opened my mouth and...
...nothing comes out.
- Nothing?
Nothing. Not a peep. But she's just waiting
for me to say something, I'm like a statue.
So finally she says,
"All right, I'll meet you here at 6:30."
She knew what you were going to say.
Yep. Yeah. She's been reading my mind
like that for 51 years.
The pretty girl was Grandma, right?
The pretty girl is Grandma, right?
- When are we gonna get there, Grandpa?
- Coming up to Moorpark.
Making a left turn right here.
What's Moorpark spelled backwards?
- I don't know.
- "Kraproom."
- Grandpa.
- And don't say that in school.
Hello, Siena Bouquet.
- I'll come with you on runs.
- You got it.
But we gotta hustle. They're flying in now.
I'm always hustling, baby.
No, no, no. Like, "hustle" hustle.
Like, no, don't dilly-dally, okay?
Let me tell you, I don't dilly-dally.
- I only upsy-daisy.
- All right.
When a man loves a woman
Crazy businessman.
This guy, like, he wants to give
family discounts to his 30 cousins.
What is this?
What have you got going...?
Excuse me. Can I help you?
I'd like to send a dozen of those
to the best girl at my school.
- And this musical card.
- A dozen of those with thi...?
This... It's...
Okay.
- All right, where am I sending these to?
- Falcon Crest Elementary.
You can MapQuest it.
I actually know where it's at.
I got a friend that goes there.
Cool. During recess
would be the best time.
When you get there, just hand me
the flowers, and I'll do the rest.
- Okay?
- I'll be there. Thank you, sir.
What's up with the cutest kid in the world
coming in here?
And he shorted me. He just gave me, like,
15 bucks for a $55 arrangement.
- Could I please have my receipt?
- What, did you get audited last year?
I did.
They always get the good guys,
I'm telling you. Here.
Thanks.
So, like, last night, amazing.
This morning,
she couldn't get away fast enough.
Any chance there was a little, shall we say,
disappointment on her part?
No. What? No. None.
At all.
- Well... No, no, no. It was fine.
- Fine's not good enough, dude.
It was better than fine.
It was a solid A.
Minus. B plus, A minus. A minus.
I hate Valentine's Day.
Why can't these guys deliver their
flowers to their girlfriends themselves?
- Wait, what?
- They just dump them in the mailroom.
- I mean, if they don't wanna take the time to...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- It's Valentine's Day today?
- Hello?
Happy Valentine's Day.
Wha...? No, it's a Monday.
Valentine's Day always falls on a Thursday.
That's Thanksgiving, Hoosier-head.
- Really?
- You're 25. You thought that for 25 years?
Dude, he's from Indiana.
They only celebrate Love Your Cousin Day.
No, you're thinking of Kentucky. Of course
Liz was acting weird this morning.
You do have something planned
for tonight, right?
How could I have something planned for
tonight? I didn't even know until right now.
I can do my lunch break,
and I can do after 5?
Okay, great.
No, no, no.
I don't mind people with fetishes.
No, no, no, very creative people.
I gotta put you on hold, sorry.
Good morning.
- You're a strong, confident person.
- Good morning. Who are you?
I am Liz. I am one of the receptionists.
I'm subbing for Monica.
Oh, yeah, Monica,
because she wanted today off.
Shit, she has a life.
She had a funeral, which is a life,
I guess.
Well, Liz, I'm Paula.
I know they call me Bipolar Paula. Don't.
But you should know I'm in crisis.
- Okay.
- I don't wanna talk about it.
- It has nothing to do with being alone...
...on Valentine's Day.
- Of course not.
And everything to do with the client
in crisis.
- That sounds challenging.
- "Challenging"?
Gotta figure out if he still has
an athletic career.
If he doesn't, big fat problemo.
Well, I'm here
to help you solve that problem.
Who's on hold?
My mother.
I'm sorry.
Hangs up on her own mother.
That's cold.
We might just get along.
Hello, I'm Hannah Storm.
And with football season officially over...
...the only lingering question is:
What will Sean Jackson do?
A devastating loss
in the championship game last week...
...leaves his future in question.
His contract is up, and at age 35...
...he's one of the oldest quarterbacks
in the league.
Does his team want him back?
Of course I want Sean Jackson back.
But it's not my decision.
If not,
will he test the waters of free agency?
Or will he make this easier on
everyone...
...and just retire?
Come on, Hannah. Lighten up.
Hi, neighbor!
- Hey, Sean.
- Hey, girls.
Hey, when are you gonna come over
for a swim?
Oh, sorry, sweetie.
I got lots going on today.
- I'm running out of patience.
- And I'm running out of willpower.
But right now, I gotta make a call.
No. Uh-oh.
Help, Heather!
I'm coming, I'm coming! Yeah, hello?
Kara, it's Sean.
Hi, hi. What's going on?
What's going on?
- Media blitz on my career has begun.
- Yes, I know. Are you okay?
Of course I'm okay.
It comes with the territory.
What I'd love is for
my highly paid publicist to take care of it.
I'm on it. I've got my people standing by
and a press release ready to go.
- What else?
- I got a meeting with my agent today.
I want you to meet me there
in about an hour. You'll be there?
Hello? Hello? Did I lose you?
Malibu. You pay a fortune to be here to get
crappy cell phone reception.
No, no. I'm here. I'm here.
I'll be at the meeting.
Outstanding.
Drumline, keep your eyes on Scotty.
Registration for the AP exam
is due next week, so don't flake.
Hey, Grace.
I was thinking of putting together
just a little test-prep group for the class...
...and I was hoping I could pick your brain
about what to focus on...
...since you've taken the test,
and I've... I haven't.
- Yeah, yeah. You know, no problem.
- Oh, great. How about today after school?
You know, I can't today.
I nanny after school.
How about today at lunch?
Uh. See, normally that would
work for me...
...but today at lunch, I'm gonna have
sex with my boyfriend for the first time.
- First time having sex for both of us.
- That is quite a special time for you.
It's Valentine's Day,
we're in love, we're both 18...
...and I just want it to be special and...
The point is, my parents work,
so they'll be gone during lunch.
Lunch is the only time it can work out.
You know, I'm free tomorrow lunchtime.
- Lunchtime tomorrow, I'll definitely be free.
- Oh, you'll be done having sex by then?
- Yeah, I'll see you tomorrow. It'll be good.
- All right.
Bye.
Come sign
the latte petition. Right here, kids.
- Yeah. Right here.
- Okay.
- You're gonna eat first?
- No.
No? Maybe some Gatorade.
That's... Yeah, I don't wanna
get dehydrated.
- You're not gonna eat lunch?
- No. No lunch.
- Well, did you have a big breakfast?
- No.
Do pushups. I'm telling you,
I do them before I run.
- What? Pushups make you run faster?
- No. Makes you look better.
I'll get you a sandwich
when you come back.
- Yeah, thanks. That's a good idea.
- Save the lattes.
They're putting lattes
in the vending machines? Finally.
- Hey.
- So I'm gonna go to English...
...and then I'm gonna go set up.
- I'll see you there.
All right.
Thank you, Felicia.
Mr. Schwabbe, I'm so glad you're
taking care of this.
- You got it.
- And I like caramel lattes...
...just, like, FYI.
- Duly noted.
Have fun at lunch!
What do you think?
We're gonna wait.
I think we should just, like,
enjoy this time.
- Yeah. Okay. Good.
- Did you like your gift?
- I didn't open it yet.
- You need to open it.
It's... It's my track shirt.
Yeah, but I ironed on your lucky number
on the back.
Thirteen.
But that's your lucky number.
You don't even like it.
- No. No, I love it. I can't wait to wear it.
- Okay.
- Try it on now, then.
- Now?
- Yeah.
- Well...
...you know, a little uncomfortable
taking my shirt off in public.
- But, hey, I'll wear it later, okay?
- Okay.
Are you gonna carry it around all day?
Shut up.
- Let's see if this fits in my locker.
- Right.
This is his fifth paternity test.
What are we talking about?
So I spoke with the GM. They passed.
Passed?
We got to the playoffs. I was all-league.
They decided to go another way.
They're chasing that kid from Alabama.
I'm working on a press release
saying it was a mutual parting.
- Well, so now what?
- Well, we... We look for another team.
I don't know. Maybe I'm done.
- You're not done.
- Absolutely not.
And I'm not speaking as someone
who makes a lot of money off of you.
I'm speaking as your fan.
Right now, you can still make
a ton of money doing what you love.
Well, the problem is, Paula,
it's not the only thing I want out of life.
A relationship. Kids.
Well, you can still have that
and play football.
Look, I'm not complaining.
I've been lucky. But...
So, what is he telling me?
What are we gonna do?
I think we should take a beat
and let Sean think about what he wants.
- Right?
- Right.
We have no time for thinking.
Put it on their tab.
- Come on!
- Ha-ha-ha!
- That's seven in a row.
- It's amazing.
You are like... This woman's a shark.
- You are good at this game.
- Not really.
Just witnessed a tactical game of reading
your opponent and adjusting accordingly.
Wait, are you saying
that you're reading me?
Thank you.
- Happy Valentine's Day.
- Oh, thank you.
Yes, I can read you.
It's part of my training.
Everyone gives subtle hints.
- Hints? Like what?
- Giveaways.
You boarded the plane wearing a suit
but no wedding ring.
Serious, but not committed.
You let a stranger
sleep on your shoulder.
Kindness, but also feels good
to be needed.
The heart-shaped candy.
Another giveaway.
Either you have a problem with sugar,
which, based on the syrup...
...you put on your pancakes,
I wouldn't think so.
Or you have a problem with candy
in the shape of a heart.
Which means you might have a problem
with romance...
...and things pertaining to this day
in particular.
Not bad, soldier.
Okay, Edison. Thank you very much.
Now you all have seen how to properly
place your valentines...
...into our fabulous envelopes,
go ahead. Great.
And while you are doing that quietly,
a little history about Valentine's Day.
Valentine's Day was a massacre in
Chicago where they shot everybody...
...and put a curse on the Chicago Cubs.
Thank you, Franklin, but this
is a different Valentine's Day. Lose the hat.
Okay, in ancient Rome...
...Emperor Claudius II, who was also
known as Claudius the Cruel.
Claudius the Cruel banned all marriages...
...because he wanted his soldiers
to concentrate on war.
But there was a priest who was known
as Valentine...
...who secretly married everyone anyway
because he believed in love.
Claudius found out about the marriages,
and he threw Valentine in jail...
Girls. I'm watching you.
Thank you.
Anyway, on February the 14th,
Valentine wrote a note to his beloved...
...and he signed it:
"Farewell, from your Valentine."
Let's see. Are there any questions?
Franklin, I can't wait to hear this.
Go ahead.
Miss Fitzpatrick,
are you in love with anyone?
I saw you on TV today.
- Was it on?
- Yeah, that's why I'm here.
Yes. We're famous!
- Yay, we're famous.
- Yes.
So you're the owner, I take it.
Yeah, tech... Yes.
My grandfather actually started it in Italy.
Yeah, my dad brought it over,
but now I got the shop.
That's great. It's a family business.
Look, I hate to play this card,
but I'm a doctor.
I have surgery in an hour and a half.
Is there any way you could help me?
- Say no more.
- Thank you.
Could I get an order form, please,
for the great doctor here?
I need two arrangements.
Something special, long-stemmed roses for
each one of my...
...ladies.
I need your discretion.
We have an understanding, right?
I understand. There's a florist code.
Great. Here's the credit card.
And here are the addresses.
These are the addresses for the ladies.
- Harrison Copeland?
- Yes, you need... You want some ID?
Nope. Should be good. Uh...
Okay, this Julia Fitzpatrick,
that would be your...
...girlfriend.
- Yes.
- And this Pamela Copeland...
...it's the same last name as you.
Would that be your wife?
Yes.
I thought we had some sort of code,
understanding.
The code is the code. I just wanna
make sure that your understanding...
...is the same understanding
as my understanding. Understand?
- Yeah, can you run the card, please?
- Yep.
Thank you. I have to get my wallet.
I'll be right back.
- Wish me luck.
- All us virgins are pulling for you. Whoo!
If you need any help, text me.
Pushkin.
Good girl. Go play.
Pushkin, no. Downstairs, Pushkin.
One...
Oh, Grace
When I saw your face
Hey, you. Come on.
Mommy's home for a minute.
Wha...? Come on, sweetie.
Made my heart race
Like a high-speed chase
- Grace
- Grace?
Oh, my...! Alex!
- Holy... Mrs. Smart. Oh, my gosh!
- What are you doing here?
I'm rehearsing!
- Naked?
- Naked! Yes!
It's... It's experiment...
I'm doing an... Ow! Experimental show.
It's very, very avant-garde type of thing.
And the... Oh, shit! I mean, excuse me!
- It's okay. I've heard the word before.
- Not shit!
God, look at the time. I gotta go.
Thank you for everything, though.
Ow!
- I'm so sorry!
- It's okay.
- Are you okay?
- Please! Do not come closer.
This does not look right, Alex.
- Thanks for everything and...
- Oh, my God.
- No, Pushkin. Pushkin, no.
- Pushkin. Pushkin.
That's okay.
You know what, I'm gonna just...
All right. Breathe. Oh, my goodness.
All right.
See you very soon, Mrs. Smart! Bye-bye.
MRS. SMART:
Alex, honey, cover your hoo-hoo!
- Grace! Grace!
- What are you doing? What happened?
- Mom.
- What, your mom?
- Yeah, sure. My mom was at your house.
- Wha...?
- My mom. What did you say?
- That I was rehearsing.
Naked? Did she buy it?
I think so.
My fear made me very convincing.
I wrote you a song.
If you do that again, Vladimir...
...I will have no choice
but to get down off my horse...
...and punish you.
- Hello? Who wants a valentine?
I am wearing my thigh-high
black leather boots...
...carrying my riding crop.
Now pull down your pants
and bend over.
I think this floor has the most valentines.
What a sweet little pink ass you have.
And I will beat it with my crop...
...until you submit to me,
you filthy peasant.
I will beat it, and beat it,
and beat it, and beat it.
Thank you for calling Naughty Nymphos.
The charge will appear on
your credit card as Vague Entertainment.
Hi there!
Hi. Well, if it isn't the gymnast.
Well... Yes.
To paraphrase some poet:
"There's a hell of a nice universe
next door.
- Let's go."
- E.E. Cummings.
Yeah, E.E. Good stuff. Yeah. Good stuff.
- I think you said he was your favorite.
- Yes.
I did say he was my favorite.
He had me at the font.
I feel, like, so stupid for forgetting
that it's Valentine's Day today.
- Oh, no. It's really not a big deal.
- You know what, it is to me.
So can I take you out tonight?
Yes. That would be wonderful. Yes.
- How fast does that cart go?
- Well, let's find out.
Liz...
...there's a man on line 2 asking me to
cover him up in Vaseline and bubble wrap.
I'll take care of that. Damn prank callers.
And he doesn't have a Russian accent,
so I don't think you'll need your horse.
- You heard that?
- It's my phone line.
Oh, Paula. I'm so sorry. I am so sorry.
Am I fired?
It's cool.
You got a way with dirty words, I like that.
Just make sure
you answer my calls first.
Absolutely.
Oh, you do not have to worry about...
...that.
Probably not gonna make
Employee of the Month.
You're listening to
"Mike and Mike in the Morning" on ESPN...
...America's number one
sports talk show.
And, Greeny, the news of the hour:
Sean Jackson, now a free agent.
- What's he supposed to do?
- He can check out Craigslist...
...see who's hiring.
Oh, man. Hey, man, you see this?
You did this.
Man, you're gonna pay for this.
Easy, big fella. I know it was my fault.
If you just call my business manager,
he's got all my information.
And I'll have my business manager call
your business manager, okay?
Sean Jackson. Oh, man, my neck.
Oh, and my back.
And my chest. I'm just kidding.
- Whoa, dude, will you sign my hat?
- Sure.
Thirty-five completions,
three touchdowns on the ground.
They think you should hang it up.
That's gratitude for you.
Well, thanks, buddy.
But that door's pretty messed up.
You got another truck?
Yeah, but I'm already behind.
Valentine's Day is kind of a big day
flower-wise.
I don't know why people get flowers
delivered. You can give them yourself.
Some folks like to get flowers
at the workshop.
To some people, love doesn't exist unless
you acknowledge it in front of other people.
You're a superstar, Sean. Drive better.
Whoop!
Yeah, Kara, it's me.
Listen, I know what I wanna do.
I think.
Oh, no, man, not today.
So, what do I do?
Do I tell her and break her heart,
or keep it to myself and stay out of it?
- It's none of my business.
- You want my opinion?
Yes. No.
Well, it depend... What's your opinion?
Ask yourself,
if the situation was reversed...
...what would you want her to do?
- Why you gotta be so sensitive?
- It's because you're so fragile.
Okay, so a neutral chlorine atom
has 17 protons and 17 electrons.
And, if these two atoms become...
- Hi.
- This order came into the shop for you.
- I thought I'd deliver it myself.
- Hey, guys, this is my friend, Reed.
- Say hi.
- Hi, Reed.
Take a look at chapter 10, section two.
Just, quietly, to yourselves.
They're from Harrison.
Did he come into the shop? Wow.
Did you meet him?
I kind of need to talk to you.
Do you have a second?
Yeah, sure.
Edison, you're in charge.
- Recess. Let's party.
- Sit down, and be quiet. Got that?
I'm just glad you got to see them.
They're so cute.
- Yeah. They're great.
- Hey, guess what.
I got a flight. I'm leaving at 5:30.
I'll be there by dinner.
You know what, actually,
I don't think it's a good idea.
- Why? It was your idea.
- Well, sometimes I have bad ideas.
It was a genius idea.
- Mr. Bouquet, what about my flowers?
- Is everything okay?
- I gave you $13.
- Oh, right. I remember.
Yeah, they're probably on the truck.
Don't worry, man, they'll be here soon.
Edison, I've known Mr. Bouquet
for a long, long time.
If he tells you your flowers are gonna
be here, then they will be here.
Just give me 30 seconds.
Hold down the fort. I'll be right back.
Don't get on the plane.
Why not?
You're sweet.
Is this because Harrison
came into the shop?
And it made you realize that things
could change between us.
No, it's not about me.
Because up to now, all these years,
I've just been there for you.
And with Morley, if she works late...
...if you wanna see a bad movie
she doesn't wanna see...
...or if you wanna have junk food
that she's not gonna have...
...I'm clearly your go-to girl.
- And you're the best.
And now, there's this guy in the mix.
And he's not just a guy...
...he's a man.
- You're afraid he's gonna steal me?
- No. When he came in...
Because, listen, since l...
- I'm your buddy. Don't worry.
- I know.
I'm not going anywhere.
But thanks for coming. I'll call you later.
Hey, what's happening in here?
Get back in your seat!
What in the... Stop that.
Get back. That is enough.
Have you lost your minds?
To your seat. That's it, that's it.
I can't talk right now!
I'll have to call you later!
Break it up. Let's go. Come on.
Stop it. Stop looking at me like that.
I tried to tell her.
Not hard enough, Reed.
- You don't know.
- Oh, I don't know?
No, you've never seen her sad.
She looks like an abandoned puppy dog
when she cries.
I'm not gonna do that to her.
Especially not today.
I'm not gonna ruin Valentine's Day for her.
I know what day it is. We got a van full
of flowers. At least hurry up. We're behind.
You can't rush love.
I'm gonna drop this off in the bedroom
before Morley gets home. I'll be right back.
He's not gonna hurry.
I'm gonna fish.
- Hey, how was your day?
- Go, go.
- What...?
- Go!
No, wait.
- I want to get out of here.
- Okay, breathe. Like I taught you.
All right, now tell me what's wrong.
She doesn't know I love her.
She didn't get her flowers.
She doesn't know.
I need to make things right.
Will you please help me, Grace? Please?
Of course. But first, soccer.
Hang on. Okay, I can hear you now.
Okay. It's gonna be me all alone
at my own party.
Nobody R.S.V.P.'s. It's L.A. Everyone wants
you to think they have a life.
- I hate you being so in love.
- Oh, I know. Thank you.
Speaking of which, I am going to
San Francisco. Sorry I won't be there.
Whack the heart for me, honey.
I gotta go. Bye.
Carmine, relax. It's me.
- Hey.
- Reed.
What are you doing here? Are you okay?
Is it...?
I'm sorry.
I love you.
But I'm just not ready
for this kind of commitment.
And I didn't know that this morning.
No, it's okay.
I shouldn't have rushed it. We can wait.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I shouldn't have been surprised
when you asked.
I should be thinking
about our future together.
But I'm still focused on my future.
Look, you can still have your career,
baby.
We're getting married.
We're not becoming monks or something.
And then there's the whole thing
with my parents' horrible...
Your parents? Wait a second. Just because
your parents had a bad divorce...
...does not mean that you're going to have
a bad divorce.
They're not hereditary.
It's not like it's contagious, all right?
You're not getting it.
You know, the first phone call I made
after you proposed was to my office.
To confirm my 10:00 meeting.
It's really beautiful.
For someone else.
Don't worry. It's...
Me and Carmine will be fine. Won't we?
Won't we, Carmine?
Right, baby?
Carmine, come. Come here.
Okay, all right. Yeah. Okay...
Did you even consider marrying me?
Of course I did.
But when you ask a girl to marry you,
do you want her to just consider it?
Or do you want her to just know?
It's Romeo Midnight, back again.
And if those topsy-turvy feelings
have got you twisted inside-out...
...think of the poet Rumi,
who 800 years ago said:
"All we really want
is love's confusing joy."
Amen, brother.
She was there, huh?
Is that it?
So this, you believe.
You don't buy it
when she says yes to me...
...but when she dumps me...
...that you can wrap your head around.
I had a feeling.
- Excuse me?
- That it wasn't right, Reed.
- Man, you know, an inkling.
- An inkling?
You had an inkling,
and you kept it to yourself?
You don't keep inklings to yourself.
You share them. You're like:
"Hey, guy. I got an inkling...
...you're headed for a fall here."
That's what friends do.
That's common knowledge.
It's in the damn handbook.
I'm sorry, Reed. You're right.
I gotta stop Julia, don't I?
If it's the damn handbook,
I think you better.
Now, let's go.
Next.
I'm going to visit my boyfriend.
I'm surprising him.
- Oh, yeah. Guys love surprises.
- Is that sarcasm?
I surprised my husband once.
Now he's my ex-husband.
- Oh, that sucks...
- Yes. Never touch security, ma'am.
- Yes, ma'am. Copy that.
- Okay.
- Next.
- Have a nice day.
You too, ma'am.
I never had a inkling before.
I didn't know what to do with it.
We gotta get to the airport.
- Oh, shit. The flowers.
- Well, I'll deliver them. You go.
I don't have a car. All I have is this van.
My cousin Flaco lives nearby. He's got
a car you can borrow. It's a Chevy.
Yeah?
A hybrid.
Right over there.
Guy leaves. I said, "We can't take the dog."
He says, "You know, he'll be right back..."
Hi. I need your first ticket...
...out of terminal G to San Francisco.
- This counter for oversized items.
Right. L... But you sell tickets.
- But you sell tickets, right?
That counter is for oversized people
this counter is for oversized items, okay?
Okay, here's my luggage.
Now it's a matched set.
Buddy, I'm 52 and I'm wearing
a bright blue shirt to work.
- Please don't make me madder than I am.
- I'm sorry.
- There's this girl.
- Don't tell me...
...that'll take the fun out of guessing.
Gonna be tough.
There's a very pretty girl,
and she's about to get on a big airplane.
And if you don't stop her,
she'll never know how you really feel.
- Not exactly.
- What am I missing?
If she gets on the plane,
she's gonna find out the hard way...
...that the guy
that she thinks she's in love with...
...is a spineless, lying creep.
- That's no good.
No, it is no good,
and I can't let that happen.
Because this girl, she is great.
She's like...
Like sunshine.
Everything is better when she's there.
I can't stand the idea of some jerk
hurting her. I just can't. I can't.
Can you please be quiet...
...so this nice young man
can sell me a ticket. Please?
Take it easy.
Here, this'll get you
to any gate in the place.
- She's like sunshine, huh?
- Yeah.
Well, in that case, it's on me.
Go on, get out of here.
Thank you.
Right this way. Come on. Let me see.
All right.
Hey, sir. Sir.
- Just a moment, sir.
- Attention please.
Flight 464 to San Francisco...
...is now boarding at gate 13
in terminal G.
The... The man left his shoes.
Mister, the man forgot his shoes.
We've got a Code Foxtrot.
- Excuse me. Excuse me!
- We've got a Code Foxtrot.
Oh, on Mount Tam?
Do you think? Because I heard
there's a little restaurant...
He's a friend of mine. It's okay.
What are you doing?
- Just...
- Where are your shoes? Are you okay?
He's married.
- What?
- Harrison. He's married.
He was married, and now he's divorced.
No. He's still married. Her name is Pamela.
They live in Brentwood.
I know because I delivered flowers to her.
I tried to tell you at the school.
Did he say it was his current wife?
"I'm sending flowers to my current wife"?
He didn't have to. I could tell.
Like you could tell
that my old boyfriend Eddie was gay.
- Eddie was gay.
- Eddie is married with two beautiful kids.
- Eddie has a cat named Babs.
- You've tried to talk me...
...out of every boyfriend since we've met.
- I'm telling you the truth. I promise.
I'm going.
No, hang on, hang on.
Come here, come here.
Why, hello there. I'm with security.
Do you think that Morley
and I belong together?
- What does that have to do with anything?
- Just tell me. Do you?
I don't know.
If you love her and if she loves you...
- Answer the question.
- Fine.
No.
- Personally, I don't see it.
- That's what I'm doing here.
Because apparently everyone
and their mother felt that way...
...but nobody had the guts to tell me.
And now, I'm left with some stupid ring
and an empty closet...
...and an ache in my gut the size of Texas
because nobody told me.
- She left you.
- Today.
I'm sorry.
This will serve as your final boarding call
for flight 464 to San Francisco.
- I don't want this to happen to you.
- I'm sorry about Morley...
...but I'm going to see my boyfriend.
You know it's the truth.
Sir, your shoes are still at security.
We're not allowed to touch them.
Sir, what kind of man takes his shoes off
and leave them off in public?
Now, you know,
it's some nasty stuff on these floors, sir.
Whoa.
Sorry.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm sure
you've noticed we're experiencing turbulence.
Nothing to be concerned about
but the captain has turned on...
...the seat belt sign for safety.
Please return to your seats
until we pass through this...
...which should be in just a few minutes.
- Yeah.
- I'll just put it there.
Watch your hands.
You look very pretty.
Thank you.
- Are you nervous?
- Yes.
No reason to be. The minute you walk
through that door nothing else...
...is gonna matter.
Thank you.
Franklin rules!
Hey, Edison, wanna warm up together?
Yeah, Edison.
Warm up with your girlfriend.
Grow up, Franklin.
Are you gonna watch
Discovery Channel tonight?
- It's about giraffes.
- No, I can't.
I have to work at my mother's restaurant.
- The one with the pointy towers?
- Yeah.
I went there for your birthday party.
It's a busy night for us. We have a wedding,
and a party for people...
...who hate Valentine's Day.
- Why hate Valentine's Day?
- I don't know.
We have it every year,
and it's all of Miss Fitzpatrick's friends.
Really?
Not in Franklin's house!
Come on, the game's starting!
- Edison, what the heck is wrong with you?
- I'm in love.
So am I, but I can move my feet.
Did you see it?
I went like this with my head.
I kicked the ball with my head!
Didn't you see it?
Oh, I did see it, honey.
Mommy's so proud of you.
Let's go find Daddy.
I'm Kelvin Moore. Happy Valentine's Day.
Welcome to the famous Hollywood Stars...
Don't you know who I am, huh?
- You think I wouldn't find you here?
- What are you doing?
- I'm trying to work.
- Look at this, everyone!
This is not in... This isn't for pictures.
Miss. Oh, mother, what's going on?
Why so...?
"Cisco Martinez is a cheating rat."
She's loco.
I don't know what she's talking about.
- No, rata. You rata!
- Cisco! Cisco!
- What are you doing? This is...
- Oh, she kneed him in the gonads.
My goodness, I feel for you.
The Dodger Dog.
- I'm okay.
- Sleeping with them?
Anyway, my name is Kelvin Moore.
Happy Valentine's Day.
KVLA, channel 13.
We done?
Got a text. Sean Jackson
is calling a press conference.
This could be my exclusive, okay?
Listen, keep filming.
All right, do some B-roll
or something like that, all right?
No worries, boss.
It's my day.
Hey, listen, I need to be able
to talk to Kara for two seconds.
I already gave you everything on the
press conference, so we are good.
I'm trying to do something special.
Look at the profile. I'm from KVLA.
- The number two sports guy.
- On my way to number one.
I wanted to ask her one question
about Sean Jackson.
I need to be able to ask Sean Jackson
one question on camera.
She's on a conference call,
she's very busy.
- I don't know if I can...
- My bladder.
I gotta use the bathroom. Got a bathroom?
Oh, I dropped my notes.
- No. You can't just barge into an... Kara.
- Kara.
- Damn.
- Oh, Kara. Are you okay?
- Oh, do I look okay?
- Should we call a doctor?
No, it's this day.
Christmas, New Year's, Fourth of July,
she's fine.
- Valentine's Day, not so good.
- What are you doing tonight, Kelvin?
I'm actually here about the Sean Jackson
interview, but we could talk.
Relax, I'm not asking you out.
I'm just curious.
How are you spending
this happiest of all days?
- Let me just...
- You don't wanna call somebody?
I just wanna know if, in fact...
...I am the only person
on the whole freaking planet...
...who is completely
and 100-percent alone on Valentine's Day.
I asked you a question.
Yeah. I'm working.
9, 10, and 11:00.
Usually, I do two, but people want it off,
so I'm happy to cover for them on this day.
You don't like to go out
on Valentine's Day?
- I hate it.
- Me too.
It's my fault I'm alone.
I'm neurotic to the nth degree.
I don't have time to work on myself...
...because I'm too busy
fixing everyone else.
- Right.
- My closest relationship...
...is with my BlackBerry.
- Right.
- Thank God it vibrates.
- Oh, no.
- But do you know...
...who has always been there for me?
- Who's that?
- Candy.
- There's somebody.
I cannot get enough.
And I know it's bad...
- Kara.
...but I need it.
I need it, and there is not a shortage
on Valentine's Day.
And that is my future.
I'll be a Ionely old lady
with rotting teeth.
- No, no, no. No, you're not.
- And a chocolate mustache.
Okay, maybe you should try some tofu
or something.
Okay. It'll balance out your emotions.
I don't want a mustache.
You'll look hot with a mustache.
Or without it. It doesn't matter.
- You can let go of me now.
- Yeah, I should.
- Well, I guess we're done here.
- All right.
You can check with Heather.
- She'll validate your parking.
- You have a blessed day.
On your mark.
Get set.
I'm Greg Gilkins at
my old high school, Henderson High...
...and today's subject: Young love.
I'm joined by Felicia, whose boyfriend,
Willy, will be joining us shortly.
- Felicia, if he's the star athlete, you are...?
- Not the cheerleader.
- I'm on the dance team.
- Maybe you could show us a little bit.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Don't hurt yourself.
- Yes.
- I haven't seen moves like that...
...since the '94 Northridge quake.
You guys are...
How do you feel about each other
this Valentine's Day?
- Oh, my gosh. I totally love him.
- I'm crazy about her.
Willy, what is it about her
that makes you so happy?
Well, she's beautiful,
she makes me laugh...
...and she does my geometry.
- Bonus.
- Yep.
- And, Felicia...
...what is it about Willy that's so cool?
What, besides the fact that he's totally hot?
He's an amazing athlete.
Go show them, babe.
Go show them, go show them.
He's so good.
How about this? I cook her dinner and then
serve it to her in front of a fireplace.
- That says romance.
- That says cheap-o.
Okay, not a problem.
I got her tickets to the movie
at the Hollywood Cemetery.
Oh, yeah. Chicks love the cemetery...
...on Valentine's Day.
- Don't you think you should get a gift?
Gift? I'm supposed to get her a Prius?
We've been dating for like two weeks.
Is there a two-week gift?
If you want there to be a third week
there is.
- So how did you guys meet?
- It's really funny, actually.
Like, I was not into him at first.
He used to shoot spit wads at me
in Spanish class...
...which is, like, so junior high.
But then one night I was brushing out
my hair when I got home...
...and I found this spit wad,
but it was really a note.
And it said, "What's up?"
And I was like, "That is so cute."
And then I liked him.
Oh, my God. Baby, are you okay?
Walk it off, baby. Just walk it off.
You're still hot, baby. You're still hot.
- He rolled out of that like a ninja.
- He's usually good at those.
He's quite the athlete,
you're quite the dancer, huh?
- Five, six, seven, eight!
- No, I think... I think we're okay.
Oh, we haven't seen that one.
- Way to go. She tell you the spit-wad story?
- She did.
- Yeah, she's mushy like that.
- You like it.
- I know.
- Oh, I miss high school.
There you have it, young love.
Full of promise, full of hope...
...ignorant of reality. From Henderson High
on Valentine's Day, I'm Greg Gilkins.
Okay.
Sorry, Mr. E., but they can't get your
flowers delivered today...
...but they'll figure it out tomorrow.
- No, it has to be today. It has to.
Oh, just let him go.
Let him go, let him go, let him go.
I'll tell you, today's a lot of pressure for
anyone, let alone a little kid. Come on.
Tell me about it. I haven't been having
the best day myself.
Is everything okay with Alex?
- Not really.
- Uh-oh. What happened?
Alex and I were supposed to...
...have sex today.
For the first time. For both of us.
I wanted it to be magical,
and I'm realizing that...
...it's hard to plan something
to be magical, you know?
- Yes, that it is.
- Love can't be planned.
It's not love she is talking about, Edgar.
It is sex.
He's going to Stanford.
I'm going to Yale.
And it's just hit me recently that...
...it's gonna be really hard
to stay together.
So I guess I thought that if we had
this amazing thing connecting us...
...it'd make it easier, somehow,
but I don't know...
...hearing myself say it out loud,
it all sounds really stupid.
And it's not like I'm gonna sleep with
one person for the rest of my life, right?
I mean, that's just crazy. Who does that?
- Oh, crazy people like us. We did.
- No.
- That's amazing.
- Well, granted, it was a different time...
...and people weren't as promiscuous
as they are now.
And there were times we spent
long periods apart, but we managed.
I'm not saying it was easy
or suggesting it for you.
Just saying it's possible.
And actually, we're gonna renew our vows
this spring, right?
- Would you excuse us a minute?
- Yeah. I'm gonna take this.
Hey. No, I'm just at Edgar and Estelle's.
What are you doing?
Alex, I gotta tell you something.
I don't know if today's the day.
I want it to be special,
you want it to be special...
...and, you know, we tried
to make it special, but, you know...
Do you wanna go back there and see
my mom after what happened earlier?
I don't think so.
All right, well, okay.
Um...
You know what, Alex, sorry.
I need to call you back.
I have to go. I'll call you later. Bye.
Edison!
Remember when you went away
to Florida to build the apartments?
You remember that.
And you were gone a very long time.
Yes.
You were gone so long.
I was so Ionely.
And...
Well, Joey came over. It was my birthday,
and he brought flowers, and...
- I sent you flowers, hon.
- Yes, you did.
And champagne.
Joey? Wait a minute.
- Joey Keenan?
- Yes.
- My business partner.
- That's right.
And we sat and we talked
and we had dinner, and we...
And then...
It wasn't anything at first. And...
- You had an affair.
- Yes. But it didn't last long, Edgar.
Didn't last long,
and we regretted it very much.
I'm so sorry.
- You're the only man I've ever loved.
- Then why tell me now?
It's been bothering me.
Our vows and everything.
And I wanted to tell you the truth.
The truth?
Well, unfortunately, Estelle...
...the truth makes everything else
seem like a lie.
I'm sorry.
Why do you hate heart-shaped candy?
I think it's because it reminds me that this
is Valentine's Day, and I'm recently single.
- We weren't on the same page.
- Sorry.
- It's okay. It's over.
- Nothing to be done?
No, no. I've seen the enemy
and the enemy is me.
You could go for the stewardess.
She seems to like you.
I think she likes everybody,
that's her job.
She looks over here every 5 seconds.
- No.
- Ready?
- Five, four, three...
- You wanna bet on it?
- I'll bet you a bag of pretzels.
- Okay.
Five, four, three, two...
- Oh, there it is.
- Okay. All right, that was a coincidence.
- Five, four, three...
- Stop it. Stop it.
- Looked on three. She's gonna come here.
- Excuse me.
- Can I get you anything?
- A bag of pretzels, please.
Two, actually.
Thank you for the flowers, Mr. Troken.
Ready for your sponge bath?
Yes, please.
Hi, excuse me. Hi.
Could I ask you a question?
I'm looking for Dr. Copeland.
Is he here tonight?
- Not tonight, no.
- Sorry, Dr. Harrison Copeland.
Not tonight.
- Could you tell me where I could find him?
- Are you a patient? Is something wrong?
Look, can I ask you a question,
just woman to woman?
Okay.
Is Dr. Copeland married?
Not divorced or not separated...
...just full-on married
to a woman named Pamela?
They just celebrated
their 15th anniversary.
Cardiology Center.
Los Angeles Hospital, may I help you?
Bistro Garden, early seating.
Kara, I'm still here. I'm in L.A.
I have a lot to tell you. Give me a call.
May I have your attention, please?
I'm Sean's publicist...
...and recently there has been a lot of
speculation about his future.
And rather than keep you all in suspense,
he will make a brief statement at this time.
- Hey, boss. Sorry, elevator took a year.
- Cleaning up?
- I'm trying to be you.
- All right.
First off, I'd like to thank everyone
for coming.
I know it's Valentine's Day and you might
have other plans, so I'll be quick.
The cliché...
...when someone's retiring
who doesn't wanna retire...
...is to say that it's because they wanna
spend more time with their family.
I don't have a family,
and with everything football has given me...
...the biggest thing it's taken away is that.
Because of who I am...
...because of my job...
...I haven't been able to live the life
I want to.
With that in mind, I'll just say the thing
I came here to say.
I'm gay.
I knew it!
- Any questions?
- Are you kidding me?
And be cool, because I'm not above
kicking anybody's ass.
Sean, you for real?
Uh, first question.
Sean, come on, help me out.
Kelvin Moore, KVLA.
Sean, I'm confused here.
Are you saying that you're retiring?
Oh, right, that.
No, Kelvin. No, I'm not retiring.
I'm gay, and I'm gonna play.
Pick up the phone, Estelle. Edgar.
- Rosato martini with soda, table six.
- You got it.
I'm not really a waitress, I'm an actress.
I just did a day on Days of Our Lives.
- Happy Valentine's Day.
- Happy Valentine's to you.
- You look beautiful.
- Thank you.
- Olivia's gonna need braces.
Well, that makes sense.
- I had them, you had them.
- I know.
Bistro Gardens restaurant.
Good evening.
- Hi.
- Harrison?
- Are you okay?
- Excuse me. Excuse...
- You all right, sir?
- You okay?
Great. Well, my name is Julia,
and I'm gonna be your server tonight.
Why don't I get started
with a few specials?
Yes, please.
Tonight the chef is featuring a dish
that he likes to call the lying, stinking pig.
- You're kidding. How is that cooked?
- He starts by cutting off the pig's testicles...
...and he chops them up really finely,
teeny, tiny pieces.
And then he takes those testicles,
and he pulverizes them...
...and adds in a little arugula,
some sage...
...feta cheese, and shoves the mixture...
...back up the pig's...
Well, for lack of a better word, ass.
- Really?
- Yeah. Then he cuts out the heart...
...the cold, useless, tiny, little heart...
...then fillets it on either side
and it's a nice amuse-bouche.
- I'll have the salmon.
- Good choice.
For you, sir?
I'm not... I don't... I don't know.
Oh, just so you know,
the heart of the pig...
...little something like this.
Did we get a toy?
Maybe I'll give you a little time
to juggle the choices, sir.
Nicely done.
Miss Fitzpatrick, my son Franklin
really loves your class.
- Oh, he's got a great imagination.
- Yeah.
So I guess we'll charge these to...
- Oh, charge these to my friend over there.
- I figured.
I put in some lobster tails
and a cheesecake.
Thank you, Amos.
And then maybe these?
Put that ticket right...
Put it where you're looking. Yep.
Yep. Great. Thank you.
Now let me take that thing.
Thank you very much. Appreciate it.
Oh, crap. Just go.
Golden Kadahi, best Indian restaurant
in Los Angeles. How may I help you?
Hi. This is Rehka speaking.
- Hey, Liz.
- Oh, hi.
- Hey.
I made it. Cannot even believe it.
- Oh, sorry.
- Sorry.
- Hi.
Wow, Liz, you look beautiful.
Thank you. Paula's indefinite trip
out of the office coincided very nicely...
...with my "haul ass home
and throw on something festive" plan, so...
You look wonderful.
Hi.
- So...
- I was think...
- What? Did you want...?
- Sorry. Go ahead. No, you first.
- Please. You should.
- You...
Oh, okay.
You don't wanna be an agent, do you?
No, but I may need an agent...
...so I figure might as well
learn the business while I'm agentless.
Good evening, sir, ma'am.
Welcome to The Blvd.
Would you like the four-course
Sweetheart's Menu...
...or the eight-course Eternal Love?
- Whoa, slow down.
Is there, like, a one-course
"Only Been Dating For Two Weeks...
...But It Looks Promising" option?
Because...
I'm kidding.
I realize that, sir.
I'll come back when you're serious.
He's your biggest fan.
Hello? That's my water.
You know, I didn't touch mine,
so why don't you go ahead and have it?
Happy Valentine's Day.
Well, same to you.
- Charlie!
- What?
She said happy Valentine's Day.
- Look...
- I can't talk now?
I'm sorry this place is such a zoo.
It's fine. I mean, they're fighting,
they're mating, and I'm in the zoo with you.
God.
Jason, um, I really like you...
...and I was... I just...
I'm just wondering how you feel...
...about the idea of...
Oh, God. I've gotta...
I'm gonna take this outside.
- Sure, sure, sure. Yeah, yeah. Go. Yeah.
- I'm sorry. Thank you.
Go ahead.
- Be right back.
- Sure.
All right, Stanley, listen to me.
We're gonna make this hard,
and we're gonna make this fast.
Yes, we can get you
two adjoining rooms.
Yes. But with the door open,
you still have to pay for both.
Okay. Bye-bye now. Hi.
Hi. Welcome to the Beverly Wilshire.
- How many checking in?
- Two.
- Two?
- I mean one.
Well, technically, it's two.
One person and Carmine, my dog.
A person and a dog.
Okay, that would be our pleasure.
Oh, okay.
Oh, and by the way,
happy Valentine's Day.
You too.
And Julia's not even in love
with that guy.
How do you know that?
She was too calm about the whole thing.
I mean, always under control.
Listen:
"The way of love is
not a subtle argument.
The door there is devastation."
The master.
So according to Rumi,
love has to be devastating?
Listen. You don't step into love, my friend,
you fall in. Head over heels.
You ever seen somebody fall
head over heels in love for real, Reed?
It's ugly, bro. Toxic, septic.
Come on, boss. Still got a few hours left.
Make something happen
with somebody someplace.
- Cookie?
- I'm good.
Day's not over yet, man. Give me some.
Hey, tell me something.
How'd you and your wife get it so right?
That's easy. I married my best friend.
Thought I was your best friend.
Yeah, you're my man. That's my lady.
- Night.
- Good night.
- Go give your wife those cookies, huh?
- Best for the best.
Yeah. Best for the best.
- Kate. Hey, have a great trip.
- Thanks. Nice meeting you.
Yeah.
- This is my taxi!
- No, no, I been waiting.
- I been waiting 45 minutes.
- Be a little patient, folks.
- Hey, Redmond.
- Welcome back, Mr. Wilson.
- Did you have to wait long?
- Not long at all.
- Check any bags?
- No.
They're right through there.
May I help you, captain?
Thank you.
You okay?
No, I'm fine. It's just the SuperShuttle, it's
gonna take nine stops to get to my house.
Thought I'd pay for a cab, and I go
there, and the line's two miles long.
- Now I'm headed to the rental car place.
- Which is gonna take an hour.
- I'm gonna help.
- Really?
Yeah, I have a car.
I live in the Valley.
I want you to have it.
You traveled so far for a few hours.
You should spend every possible second
with this guy.
And it's already paid for.
Redmond will take you
wherever you need to go.
You just give him the address.
Thank you. Thank you.
He's a lucky man.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Rani, sweetheart, why are you moping?
Is this about a boy
because it's Valentine's Day?
Did you get many valentines?
Oh, sweetheart, don't be sad.
When the time is right, your father and I...
...we are going to find you
a nice Indian boy.
Hey, cheer up, Rani.
I'll be your valentine.
Alex, please, for now,
be our delivery boy.
I have an Indian wedding,
and I have a private party going on.
Perfect.
Beverly Wilshire, this is Michelle.
Yeah, I'm gonna have to put you on hold.
All right, thanks. Bye-bye.
Excuse me.
You didn't happen to see a really pretty girl,
blue dress, come through here?
- Are you a guest of the hotel, or...?
- No, we were at the early seating.
Okay. Yeah, she was on the phone,
and she just went out that way.
- Oh, okay. Thanks.
- Yeah, no problem.
Put the blindfold on right now, Stanley.
Oh, you know what's gonna happen
when you do.
Sugar and your little kitty cat...
...oh, we're gonna lick you
all up and down.
Scratchy little tongues
going up and down your...
Oh! Rrrrr. Mm.
Oh, Stanley, I'm gonna have to have
a mint julep to cool down after that one.
Talk to you next time. Thank you.
Oh, God.
That is a really unusual way
to talk to your boss.
- It's not what you think.
- Really? Oh, awesome.
Because what I think it is is you leaving me
to talk dirty to your boyfriend, Stanley. So...
- No, no, no.
- What a relief to know...
...you're not someone who licks people
with their scratchy kitty-cat tongue.
I moonlight
as an adult-phone entertainer.
- Like phone sex?
- Yes.
This is the busiest day of the year
for phone sex.
Surprise.
Why didn't you tell me?
Okay.
I'm broke. I have a hundred-K student loan
I have no idea how I'm going to pay off.
I have no health insurance.
So if you know of a job
that will pay a poetry major...
...more than $40 an hour,
with her clothes on, I'm all ears.
Okay.
- I'm out.
- Are you gonna call me?
Well, you know,
I'd like to say yes, but...
...I don't know if I can afford it.
I'm sorry, that was... I'm sorry.
Come on, you know I didn't mean that.
I'm just... This is, like...
This is way too much for me, okay?
I'm from Muncie, Indiana.
Like, the wildest thing I ever did was...
...leave Muncie, Indiana.
- Look, this is me, it's not you.
- Yeah.
I just...
I'm sorry, Liz.
Welcome to the Hollywood Forever
Cemetery. Enjoy your romantic evening.
Please, everyone form a single-file line.
She said she would meet me right before
showtime. Here it is...
...but she's not here yet, and...
I got her these flowers
because I'm so sorry.
I mean, it was a small fire.
It's a small dog. Everything's fine, and...
We're sold out.
Oh, I'm sorry, sir, but we are completely
sold out. Only pre-sold tickets.
No, you don't understand.
I need a ticket tonight.
But I mean, I packed a basket.
It's got her favorite.
- Ham hocks and squid and...
- Actually...
...you know what, sir?
I have an extra ticket.
- Oh, that's your ticket?
- That's my ticket.
It's your lucky night. Have a great time.
All right, everyone, we are sold out.
- So who do I thank?
- Jason, from Indiana.
Edgar, from New York.
Yeah, my wife and I used to come here
every Valentine's Day, but...
Well, except tonight.
Well, you know,
I had the extra ticket, so...
On Valentine's Day.
Well, there's gotta be a story there.
Well, yeah, not a good one.
Pretty much the worst
Valentine's Day story of all time.
You wanna bet?
Thank you, officers.
- Thank you, Nikki. They're beautiful.
- Thank you.
Siena Bouquet.
Yeah, we're still open
for about another hour.
Mister?
You owe me flowers.
Where we taking them?
Okay,
I'm gonna go now. Have a nice life.
You came.
What happened?
He's married.
Now that's open-heart surgery.
- Peppermint Pattie?
- Yep.
Don't step on the people,
step on the grass.
Step on the grass.
This telephone girl, you like her, huh?
Thought maybe she had the trifecta.
Trifecta? What's that?
Oh, you know,
it's like the big three S's.
Smart, sensitive, sexy.
That's my trifecta.
- Her?
- Mm-hm.
You mean, like, literally, that...?
- Literally. Her.
- She was hot.
Still is.
Hey, hey.
- You guys came!
- You're here!
I thought you were going out
with your new boyfriend.
I thought you had a date
with your old boyfriend.
Same guy.
- No.
- Not surprised.
Booked back-to-back at the same
restaurant. Thought we wouldn't notice.
- What?
- Please lead me to the alcohol.
- Right here. Sit down.
- We are gonna take good care of you.
What happened to the piñata?
- Oh, it got what it deserved.
- Oh, more sad and Ionely people.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, Elise.
I'm driving around, looking in all
the places he's probably gonna be, but...
Anyways, like I said, just call me back.
But no big deal, I've got it under control,
so I'll find him.
I've found him! Found him.
Oh, my God, he's in a van. Shit!
What are you doing in a van?
Edison!
Burn, baby, burn!
Justin Levy.
Broke up with me
on the morning of my birthday...
...still showed up to my party.
Burn, baby, burn!
Ivonne Quinteros.
Dumped me for the piano player
at the Beverly Wilshire.
- Two hours ago.
- Oh, Charlie.
- Burn, baby, burn!
- Fire marshal know about this burning pot?
- Oh, hey, Kelvin.
- Hey.
Back to the wine.
- What are you doing here?
- I had a little time...
...before my 10:00 broadcast, somebody
said there was a gathering of my people.
- How did you find us?
- Heather.
Right, right. Well, welcome.
- Hi. I'm Julia.
- I'm Kelvin.
- Hi. So you guys know each other?
- Yes.
What misadventure of the heart
brings you here?
Oh, actually, I'm Kara's date.
- Fascinating.
- Yeah.
Whoo.
- Edison!
- All right, buddy.
- Don't move!
- I'm really, really sorry.
Okay, but you can't do that to me.
Do you understand?
I know, I know.
But this was really important.
- She had to get her flowers.
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah, I'm his babysitter.
- I'm his florist.
Look, I'm glad you're okay.
Do you want me to come in there
with you?
No. I think this is one of those things
I have to do myself.
I've been driving Holden for a long time.
He's never given his car up for anybody.
You must be pretty special.
Over?
Why do you keep talking like it's over?
I love you.
Edgar!
- Hey, get out of the way!
- I'll always love you.
- Edgar!
- Excuse me.
Down in front!
Edgar, where are you?
I know you're out there.
Shh!
- Who the hell is Edgar?
- He is my husband, and shut your mouth.
- Edgar, answer me.
- Answer her, Edgar.
- Lady, I can't see through you.
- Edgar, where are you?
- Estelle!
- Edgar, answer me.
- That must be Edgar.
I'm here! I'm coming.
Sorry.
- I see.
- Hey, run lower!
Listen to me. I know I let you down.
Maybe you don't think
I deserve forgiveness...
...but you're gonna give it to me anyway,
because when you love someone...
...you love all of them. That's the job.
- I know that now.
I'm so sorry.
And now, please, you gotta love
everything about them.
Not just the good things,
but the bad things too.
The things that you find lovable,
and the things that you don't find lovable.
Shh. I understand.
I'll never leave you.
At first I was afraid, I was petrified
Kept thinking I could never live
Without you by my side
Then I spent so many nights
Thinking how you did me wrong
And I grew strong
And I learned how to get along
And so you're back from outer space
Julia, I found this little friend of Rani's,
and I think he's looking for you.
I'm not little.
Edison, are you okay?
Does somebody know that you're here?
Yeah, my babysitter's outside.
Okay.
- Oh, now go
- Go
- Walk out the door
- Out that door
Just turn around now
This is for you.
- For me?
- You're my valentine.
Thank you.
Oh, this is beautiful.
Wha...?
Are you sure that I am really the person
that you wanna give this to?
Yeah. I mean, I think so.
Why?
Well, when you pick a valentine you have to
be sure that you choose the right person.
Or else you could be overlooking someone
who's even more special to you.
Rani? But I don't love her. I love you.
Is it our age difference
that keeps you from going:
Boom, boom, boom.
Yeah, a little bit.
Is it my height? Because I'm gonna grow.
Well, then, no, it's not your height.
It's just it wouldn't be right,
because I know Rani likes you.
Really?
Well, I like her a lot too.
She's the only other fifth-grader
who has Frank Zappa on her iPod.
- See?
- And she loves giraffes.
See, giraffes, it's something you guys
have in common.
See, it's things like that
that can turn a friend...
...from someone that you like
into someone that you love.
Has that ever happened to you,
Miss Fitzpatrick?
Hello?
Hey, hey
Back to the chocolate!
I am the chocolate.
Oh, you are.
Thank you so much for coming.
You are the most special valentine
I have ever had.
- But it was great. And bye.
- Bye.
- Don't know how to do that.
- I'll teach you.
- There you go. Right on... There it is. Close.
- Okay.
I know, you gotta go to work.
Bolly, bolly!
Here. Happy Valentine's Day.
I don't usually go for girls my own age,
but you're pretty cool.
Wow, thanks.
I don't really have anything else to say.
Now I'm wondering
If your love's still strong
Here I am
Signed, sealed, delivered, I'm yours
I saw Edison.
I tipped the valet
to keep an eye on him.
I have the delivery van
set up over there.
We could take a trip to Mulholland.
Come check it out.
- Alex, can I be honest with you?
- I love it when you're honest.
I don't know if I'm ready for this.
- Lie to me.
- No, look, I'm serious.
Signed, sealed, delivered
I'm gonna go now.
Bye.
I guess that I thought that if we did this,
we'd have this special bond...
...and now I'm realizing that something
like this you can't just plan, you know?
It has to happen.
I mean, we have a chance
to make it happen.
But did you hear what you said,
"make it happen"?
We shouldn't have to make it happen.
Look, sit.
This is so sweet, and...
Look, Alex, I love you. I just...
I really think we should wait.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. I love you too.
And...
...we can still make out.
Bye.
Paula Thomas. Whoever this is better have
a good reason for calling me this late.
You want me to do what?
Boy, do you know who you're talking to?
Oh-ho-ho-ho.
Vladimir.
Well, let me tell you something, Vladimir.
You don't know what rough is
until you've dealt with a true African queen.
Let me get my stick.
Kneel to Nzinga!
Attention, I'm going home now.
But I wanted to say goodnight
to the world's greatest boss...
...and tell him that we all love him.
Good night, Nikki.
You saw.
Yeah.
I'd like to take to comment
on the story that we broke earlier.
Quarterback sensation Sean Jackson...
...has popped the lock on the closet
and come out.
What does this mean? Will there be more
house music played in the locker room?
These questions aside, Mr. Jackson's
name is likely to be remembered...
...alongside Jackie Robinson,
Muhammad Ali, and Billie Jean King...
...who endured their share
of trash-talking as well.
But let's allow future generations to decide
where to place Sean Jackson in history.
It's not about defiance...
...it's about what a man will do for love.
I stand behind you, Sean. Metaphorically.
- Oh, jeez.
- Thank you.
Good night.
And that's it for tonight's news.
Happy Valentine's Day to all of you.
Sherry Donaldson for KVLA, channel 13.
- Good. Hey, man.
- Excellent.
- Hey, way to go, bro.
- Cue music, cue logo.
You sneaky little cupid.
You got romantic after all, didn't you?
I may get a few letters on that,
but I got your back.
- Thank you.
- Happy Valentine's Day, Kelvin.
Same to you.
Well, those stairs never looked so good.
Interesting perspective on Sean Jackson.
Just a second.
Who is it?
You forgot your camera.
Can I come in?
Sure.
Jason, I feel bad about
how you found out about my job.
It was awkward, and I'm sorry.
But that is the only thing
that I apologize for.
No. I should be the one apologizing.
If you want to be
a adult phone entertainer...
...that's cool.
I don't know, Jason.
When you found out something about me
you didn't like, you judged me and bailed.
I don't think that's a promising
foundation for a relationship.
You know what? You're right.
I just spent all night in a cemetery.
And I actually learned something.
In a relationship...
...you have to accept the other person...
...for all of what they are,
not just the parts that are easy to like.
And you're stupid if you turn your back
on something as important...
...as...
...Iove.
So I bought this for you. At the store.
And this one goes...
Sugar can't answer the phone right now.
She's got to make love
to her boyfriend on Valentine's Day.
And, for the record, this is what I like.
Simple.
Yeah.
Let's just keep it really simple.
- I also like make-up sex.
- Whoa, what a coincidence.
- You too?
- Me too.
Yay!
Hi.
- Sorry.
- Yeah.
What are you doing with the flowers?
They're all the ones that nobody wants.
So you're giving them a second life?
Yeah, most shops throw them away.
I like the idea that tomorrow, somebody's
gonna see them floating by and...
Yeah.
- Wonder where they come from.
And the mystery of it all.
I used to actually put them together...
...and practice new designs with them...
...and drop them off at a random doorstep
with a note saying:
"Somebody out there loves you."
Then I got to thinking...
...what if they found out
that someone was me?
Would they want me to be the one that
loves them?
I would...
...want that.
Am I about to kiss my best friend?
I hope so.
- Not great.
- That was awkward. Awkward.
- Just not great.
- Yep.
- But this is my old... Where I get down.
- This is your spot.
You really helped me out. Susan is...
- Giving me a chance to be number one.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you, again.
- Thank you.
- I'm gonna have to teach you.
- That is...
- No... I'll teach you this.
- It's not natural.
- Keep the fist... It's a little...
- Thank you. Okay.
- No, no, no. Open your...
- Open.
- You know what? I got a better idea.
- Not happening.
Okay.
That was nice.
Well, you didn't exactly, like,
knock it out of the park.
Well, we've never practiced,
you have to admit.
- Maybe we should practice, then.
- Okay.
Mommy!
You're so big.
- Did you imagine it better or worse?
- I did.
- You imagined it better?
- I gave you more credit.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Well, I hate that I'm not living up to my...
- Well, I don't know.
It's Romeo Midnight, one last time.
Only 30 seconds left now
before it's just another day.
So count it down with me, lovers.
And raise your glass to those three
little words that we all want to hear:
"Let's get naked."
I never had a inkling before, man.
I didn't know what to do.
I need to get to the airport.
Stupid...!
Vladimir! Let me get my whip.
You know I always
wanna answer yours first...
Oh! Just... Let's do...
I never had a inkling before.
I didn't know what to do with it.
Shoot, we gotta get to the...
It's stupid. Stupid seat belt!
Oh, there's a...
Hold it, there's a finger in there.
You on Facebook?
I can't hear out of this ear.
Are you guys on Facebook?
I never had a inkling before.
I didn't know what to do with it.
All right. I gotta get to the airport.
She's probably at the gate by now.
How did you do that?
- Hey, I'm Taylor.
- And I'm Taylor. Too.
Yeah. It's confusing. Yeah, we know that.
Marker.
If you look out the window,
ma'am...
...we're passing
the famous Rodeo Drive.
- Have you ever shopped here?
- I did once, actually.
But, big mistake. Big. Huge.