It's a no.
I thought you liked the idea.
That was before I realized that
it was nothing but sassy remarks.
I thought you wanted our
baby to have a relationship
with its biological father.
If you're going
to get this worked up,
it makes me think
I don't really know you.
What if I could
make it more like you?
I might be able to give it the
ability to learn from your heart.
You really think we could do that?
We can try.
Rachel Zane deserves
to be in the Bar.
You're not only
gonna stop blocking her,
you're going to run interference
for her if someone else does.
And in return,
you'll do what I want.
No. But I'll do what you
want for something else.
We need to come up with a lawsuit
against Velocity Data Solutions.
No.
What do you mean, no?
Fabricating a lawsuit to
manipulate a stock is illegal.
It's not illegal
if we find a legitimate suit.
So, let's finish the job and get
you back to being a lawyer.
"Tenants are required to be
notified of all construction
"by certified letter."
Is this a certified letter
or not?
Objection. Your Honor, this
is the fraudulent attorney.
Open your mouth in my courtroom
again and you will be removed.
Mr. Grady, do you have an
objection or not? I don't.
Then the court
has no choice
but to dismiss
this case with prejudice.
The guy
holding up your interview
was trying to get us to do something
because he thought he could.
- Are you going to?
- Yes.
He is.
Are you saying
what I think you're saying?
I'm in.
Okay, Rachel's gone.
I don't want any bullshit.
You're telling me
that no matter what we do,
Rachel's getting
into the Bar.
What I'm telling you is
if she doesn't get in,
that asshole isn't going to
be the one that stopped her.
Okay, I'm in.
What do we have to do?
I told you
what we need to do.
We need to make a dent
in Velocity Data's stock.
Harvey, that's no joke.
You realize how much we're
going to have to sue them for
to make their earnings
take a hit?
You're damn right I do.
They're a huge company, which means
it's got to be something huge.
I don't even know
if that matters.
No matter what
we sue them for,
they're just going to
want to settle.
I know that. Which means we need to
insist on an admission of guilt.
I get it.
You want me to run this whole
thing through the clinic.
It's the only way to
make it look legitimate.
Harvey...
I don't know if I can
convince Nathan to do that.
Well, you better.
Because if anyone figures out that
we're doing this for personal gain,
your chance of getting
into the Bar is gone.
Wait, you were captain
of the glee club?
The official title is
"lieutenant colonel,"
but that's cool you didn't know that.
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, my God.
You still had
braces at 17?
Actually, I had them
again at 28.
Wow.
Between this,
your nasal passages,
the skin tag epidemic
and the foot surgeries,
you've really had
a lot of medical procedures.
Tara, I know what
you must be thinking.
And I swear, I will not pass any
of my maladies onto our child.
Louis, I wasn't
thinking that.
But, you do understand that
biologically this isn't your child.
Of course I do.
Okay.
But I was thinking we would have
at least one child of our own.
At least?
At least.
You were right, Louis. Getting
to know each other is fun.
Good, you're here.
I need your help.
Is this about the worker
comp case from Flushing?
No. This is about
Velocity Data Solutions.
What about them?
They're a dirty company.
They've been getting away
with shit for years.
I could never go after them when
I worked at Pearson Specter
because we were always on the
other side of these things.
But I can
go after them now.
Mike, if this is going to
require me going to court, I...
It's not.
Look, Oliver,
I know what happened
the other day.
But you don't have to be a trial
lawyer to be a great lawyer.
What are you saying?
I'm saying that you have skills
that other lawyers don't have,
and I'm going to put those
skills to use right now.
What do you need?
You see those boxes?
That's every case that Velocity
has settled in the last 20 years
where the names of the
plaintiffs have been sealed.
We need to figure out who those people
are, what they got paid not to say,
and then we need to get every
damn one of them to come forward.
Mike, what did
these guys do to you?
They didn't do
anything to me, Oliver.
I just don't like it
when people think
they can get away with anything
just because nobody is watching.
That was fast.
What was fast?
Well, I assume you're here to tell
me you filed suit against Velocity.
What I'm here to tell you, Craig, is
Mike Ross is going to handle Velocity.
Then we have a problem.
'Cause I didn't cut a deal with
Mike Ross, I cut a deal with you.
And there's a reason you're an
in-house counsel and I'm not.
What are you
talking about?
Once we drop whatever bomb
we're going to drop,
they're going to want to settle
without an admission of guilt.
And everyone knows
settling is what I do.
So, Mike Ross is going to
take this to court?
He's not even
a goddamn lawyer.
Welcome to
the conversation, Craig.
That's what
I'm here to talk about.
You're going to make
Mike's hearing official.
I can't do that. It's too soon.
Bullshit.
You think I don't know
you only said yes
about Mike to get me
to help you?
Of course
that's why I said yes.
And the hardest thing about
getting him into the Bar
is getting him a hearing when he
hasn't even gone to law school.
Which is why
you're going to sponsor him
based on his years of work
at Pearson Specter.
You're talking about
reading the law.
You're damn right I am. There's
precedent and you know it.
Listen to me.
I can influence the vote,
but I cannot sponsor someone
I'm going to be voting on.
Then find someone
who will.
Because if you don't get him a hearing
in the next week, this thing is off.
And one more thing, Craig,
you and I won't be
talking again.
Because in case you haven't
figured it out yet,
this is a hell of a lot more serious
than cheating on your wife.
See the money,
wanna stay for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
P® Krishna_Teja P®
Harvey, what are you doing in here?
What do you mean?
It's an executive kitchen,
I'm an executive.
Yeah,
but you're a bagel guy.
This place is like
croissant central.
Then maybe
I came in here
hoping to spend some
quality time with you.
Are you saying you want to
hear about my night with Tara?
Of course I do.
Right after we make friendship
bracelets and braid each other's hair.
For your information,
it was a magical evening.
But actually, I'm here
to talk about business.
What business?
Couture Apparel.
Jessica and I always gave
their CEO an annual analysis
of their legal needs
for the upcoming year.
And now that she's gone,
you want us to do it.
Exactly. Sounds like
a dog-and-pony show.
It is more than that, Harvey.
It is a show of force.
For one day, Carly
Donahue needs to feel
like the most important
client in the portfolio.
And having one partner go by
himself doesn't send that message.
Louis, relax.
I'm happy to do it.
You are?
Of course I am.
I told you.
We're partners.
You know, Harvey, I always
dreamed it could be like this.
Partners, confidantes,
friends...
I had the exact same dream, Louis.
Really?
No, not really.
Does that mean you're never
going to go mudding with me?
Yes, Louis,
that's what it means.
I'll give Donna
the details on that meeting.
Hey. I hope
you got a hammer,
'cause I just brought you
some nails.
You found something.
Yeah, I did.
I already found
six cases we can use,
and that's just
the tip of the iceberg.
So, let's grab our coats and go kick
Velocity's ass up and down the street.
Easy, Tyson, you have to tell me
what kind of suits these are first.
They're mining suits, which means health
problems or corporate negligence.
Either way, the damages
could be through the roof.
Oliver, this is great.
I know.
And if you asked me to make an
argument about it in court,
I'd probably shit the bed.
But, Mike, I'm telling you,
there's something here.
And I'm telling you,
maybe one day
you'll overcome your court
stuff, maybe you won't.
Either way, this proves that
you're a hell of a lawyer.
Thanks, Mike.
I've got to admit, it feels pretty
good to know I can do what I just did.
Then why don't
you start drafting a suit?
'Cause after I get
these people on board,
that's exactly what
we're going to have to do.
Donna, you're never going to
believe what Louis just asked me.
Give me three guesses.
He wants to be you,
he wants to look like you, he wants
to wear your skin as a body suit.
Okay. Did you just talk
without saying anything?
What's the big deal?
You do it all the time.
Good one, Donna.
You're on fire today.
Okay, what the hell
is going on here?
Oh, you mean
The Donna?
It's just a little product that
Benjamin and I have been working on.
It doesn't have my emotional
intelligence yet,
but I thought I'd have a little
fun with it in the meantime.
Do you have your emotional
intelligence yet?
When it can top that,
you might have something.
Loser. Okay.
Which one of you said that?
She did.
Sorry, buddy.
Grill's shut down.
We don't open again
till 5:00.
That's okay. I'm not here
for a cheeseburger.
I'm here to talk about
Hazelton Mining Company.
What about it?
You filed
a complaint alleging
life-threatening health
problems resulting from work.
That complaint
mysteriously went away
and I want to help you get the
compensation that you deserve.
I don't need any help
from an ambulance chaser.
I'm not an ambulance chaser,
Mr. Stamos.
My name is Mike Ross.
I work at a clinic and our
commissions are capped at $50,000.
So, we are not in this
for the money.
Then what are you
in it for?
Let's just say
Velocity is bad news.
Well, I'd like to help.
But, even if I wanted to sue
those bastards, I can't.
I know.
You took a payout and you signed
a non-disclosure agreement.
That's got nothing
to do with it.
They made us all
sign those things.
If any one of us breaks it,
it negates them all.
Then negate them all.
That's easy for you
to say.
I'm dying
of something
with a name so long,
I can't even tell you
what it is.
And you're talking about your fee being
capped at more money than they paid me.
Listen to me. If that's really all they
paid you and you really are dying,
we can shatter those NDAs
in about five seconds.
You don't understand.
I was their supervisor,
Mr. Ross.
I was responsible for all
those guys that got sick.
And I'm the one that got us the
money that went with those NDAs.
And let me guess.
Ever since you signed them, you
haven't had a good night's sleep.
Tell me I'm wrong,
I'll leave right now.
What do I have to do?
Rachel, what are you
doing here?
Can I come in?
Of course.
Can I get you something?
No, I'm good.
Thank you.
If this is about checking out
the place for your wedding,
it might be better
during the day.
No, I didn't come
to talk about that.
I came here
to talk about this.
Rachel, this is terrific.
You passed the character and fitness
committee without even having to go in.
I know. Then why do you
look so concerned?
Because I know what you and Mike
are doing to make this happen.
Rachel, this letter has nothing
to do with what we're doing.
You deserve this and all this guy
is doing is the right thing.
Okay, let's say
that's true.
What about what you two are doing to
make the same thing happen for Mike?
Listen. No, Harvey, I
need you to listen.
He just spent the past
couple months in prison,
and it was
supposed to be years.
And I can't let
that happen again.
It's not going to
happen again.
I know it isn't,
which is why I'm here.
I need your word that if
things start to go south,
that you will pull the plug
on this whole thing.
Rachel. Harvey, I
want your word.
You got it.
Things go south,
it's done.
Hey, Mike,
you got a second?
Yeah. What's up?
I was hoping
you could tell me.
Apparently, Oliver was in
the conference room all day
working on some case
against Velocity Data.
Uh, yeah, I gave him
an assignment.
What do you mean you
gave him an assignment?
He had
the workers' comp case.
I took care of that.
Mike, your job isn't
to generate cases.
It's to consult on the cases
we've already taken.
I know that.
But it's also to help
our associates
become better lawyers.
Oliver got his ass kicked
in court the other day.
I'm just helping
to build him back up.
And there are plenty of other cases
you could have used to do that.
Instead, you went and you
signed a class action,
which is something
we do not do.
Well, why isn't it
something we do?
These men have life-threatening
health problems.
They need someone to
give a shit about them.
It isn't something we do because we
don't have the time or the manpower
to take on a giant
like Velocity.
Nathan, I don't know
what you want me to say.
I went out there, I signed these
guys, and they trusted me.
I can't back out now.
This the kind of shit you pulled
when you were at Pearson Specter?
On occasion.
Then I want you to say the next time
you think to pull something like this,
you have the common courtesy
to tell me before you do it.
I suggest a warm bubble
bath and a pint of Chunky Monkey.
Because if you're not
good to yourself,
how can you expect anyone else
to be good to you?
And for your information,
the initial program
was vanilla bean
and an Enya CD,
but it learned from you.
Pretty awesome, right? No,
Benjamin, it's not pretty awesome.
You can’t just
give it platitudes.
What are you
talking about?
The key to having empathy is making
people feel supported in their feelings.
Not just trying to solve
their problems.
That is the dumbest thing
I've ever heard.
No, it isn't.
And not only that,
you have to
tailor its response
to the feelings
the person is having.
How am I supposed
to do that?
You have to
have it listen.
Okay, I get it. You're saying it has
to understand the feelings of its user
and express that understanding
in a sympathetic manner.
Exactly. Now, you think
you can do that?
Of course I can.
All I need to do is continually
expose it to what it's not providing
and eventually the feedback loop will
show it how to be more like you.
In other words, awesome.
Yes, that's the entire point
of this exercise.
And for the record,
no one awesome
listens to Enya.
Maybe not her later work.
You're the whole team?
Seems fair.
There's only one of you.
I'm not an attorney,
Mr. Ross. I'm CEO.
Then you must be serious.
Why don't you give me a number?
You want a number? Zero.
Because I'm not going to be
shaken down by the likes of you.
This isn't a shakedown,
Mr. Palmer.
Those men are dying from conditions
that your company knew about.
Those men signed
non-disclosure agreements.
And if they break them,
we can come after them
for every penny they've got.
And I've got a way to bust every
damn one of those agreements.
No way. Those things
are airtight.
Airtight doesn't apply
when signed under duress,
which is exactly what
dying of lung cancer
and not being able
to afford a doctor is.
Well, good luck making
that argument 1,000 times,
because I'm going to fight each and
every one of them to my dying breath.
You can't do that.
They're a class.
I can and I will.
And you move forward
with this,
I'm going to bury that shit-hole
legal clinic of yours
in so much paperwork, you're
going to choke to death.
So, you just called me down
here to tell me no to my face?
I called you down here to show you
that if you pursue this action,
those men are going to
be left with nothing.
And so are you.
That's a hell of a strategy.
But I guess
you didn't get the memo
that my co-counsel on this
is Pearson Specter Litt.
Bullshit. Their name's not on
any one of these documents.
Because they wanted
to keep a low profile.
But go ahead, pick up the phone.
I'll call them myself.
Then I guess I'll see you and
your big law firm in court.
But, like I said,
I'm not going to be shaken
down by the likes of you.
Harvey, I just got a phone call
from the lawyers at Velocity.
They wanted me to confirm that we're
co-counsel with Mike on this.
What did you tell them? What
do you think I told them?
I told them yes.
Because if they're asking,
he obviously bluffed
and I'm not going to
hang him out to dry.
Where are you going?
I'm going to find out what
he did and why he did it.
What the hell did you do? Relax,
Harvey, I was just coming to tell you.
No, I specifically said that I can't
be seen to be involved in this thing.
And you also said we only
had one shot at this.
I was the one in
the room with this guy.
He had me and he knew it.
So what?
So, you always said that
if I'm in a knife fight
and I'm losing,
to pick up the gun.
And Pearson Specter Litt
is a goddamn gun.
Look, I know this isn't
exactly what we wanted,
but I can still be the one to
insist on admission of guilt.
So, what's really
going on here?
I promised Rachel that if this thing
got too risky, I'd pull the plug.
And it just got
a hell of a lot riskier.
Well, it also got real.
Those miners need us.
I'm not going to
abandon them.
So, what do you
want to do?
What do you think I want to do?
I want to kick this guy's ass.
Then here's the situation.
I got 150 miners on board
and I can bust the NDAs.
But I can't make
the action a class
'cause they already
signed those rights away.
I get it. He doesn't think we can get
all those separate cases to court.
Well, he's got
another thing coming.
I've got 10 brand new associates upstairs
begging to work on a case like this.
You're going to oversee every single
one them if it takes all night.
Then I have to meet you
at your office in an hour.
There's something I need to
take care of first.
Louis, whatever it is,
it's going to have to wait.
No, this will just take a second,
it's about the Carly Donahue meeting.
I was thinking...
Louis, I'm sorry.
But I'm not going to
be able to make it.
What? Why the hell not?
Mike needs my help
on a case.
Harvey, you may not
want to accept this,
but Mike doesn't
work here anymore.
And firm business
takes priority over...
Listen. Louis,
this is firm business.
And if what I think
is going to happen happens,
Mike's going to end up
back here when it's done.
What?
You remember that thing
that we took care of for Rachel
that you said might be worth doing?
Well, it turns out
it was worth doing.
Only, I'm doing it
for Mike.
Holy shit. Seidel agreed
to go to bat for him?
Yes, and once it's done
and Mike's in the Bar,
he can come back here
and work again.
Harvey, that is great.
And nobody wants that
more than I do.
But it's just one meeting.
Louis, I know that.
But, in about three hours,
I'm going to be underwater
for the next three days.
Harvey. Louis, I know I told
you I'd be there for you.
But I need you
to be there for me.
Okay, Harvey.
I'll do it.
Good, you're still here.
Box up the Velocity files
and meet me downstairs.
Where are we going?
Pearson Specter agreed
to partner on the case.
Shit, that's big.
You want in?
Hell yeah.
Give me 10 minutes.
Hey.
Yeah.
You want to tell me
what this is?
That is an agreement
to co-counsel,
and I was just going to
come tell you about it.
How many times are you going to
make a move without telling me?
Nathan, I'm sorry,
but I had to move fast.
The guy at Velocity
was putting the screws to me.
Is something shady going
on here, Mike? What?
First, you bring in this
huge case out of the blue.
Then, all of a sudden,
you bring in your old firm?
You're the one who said we
didn't have the resources
to handle
this sort of thing.
So, I just brought in
someone who would.
Yeah, I bet they're getting
a sweet deal out of it, too.
It's not like that. They're
taking half their usual fee.
That's all they're getting.
And what about you, Mike?
What are you getting? What
are you talking about?
You're going to tell me
you're not using this
as a stepping stone to get
back to your old firm?
What? No. Nathan, I don't
want to go back there.
Bullshit.
I don't believe you.
Something is going on here
and I know it.
You know what, Nathan?
For your information,
Harvey Specter did offer me a
consulting job, just like you did.
Except his had one more zero at the end
of it, and I still turned him down.
I chose to be here.
But I don't want to be
second-guessed at every turn.
So, either you're
going to trust that
my heart is in the right
place or you're not.
Well, for your information,
Mike,
right now, I really
don't have a choice.
Hey.
Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay.
How the hell am I supposed to keep Carly
Donahue's business all by myself?
Because, Louis,
you're co-managing partner
and you're
one hell of a lawyer.
You just don't
get it, do you?
This woman wants to know that
she is special to this firm.
If I walk in there by myself, she's
going to laugh me out of the room.
Then why didn't you
tell that to Harvey?
Because, I know how
important Mike is to him
and I didn't want to
let him down.
Then don't.
That is not...
Louis, if this woman needs
to know she's special to us,
there's more than
one way to do it
and Harvey's not the
only one you can bring.
Donna, that's great,
but the meeting is tomorrow
and I don't even know
these new associates yet.
Yes, you do.
You know Katrina,
who's not just a new associate,
she's a junior partner.
And you know Rachel, who's
as good as a fourth-year.
You go in there with a
show of force like that?
Trust me.
This woman is going
to be blown away.
Okay, Donna.
Show of force it is.
Holy shit,
Otis Redding's first album?
You sure Harvey won't mind
if I take it out?
Are you kidding me?
No, he says if that
collection's not for everyone,
then what's the point
of even having it here?
Sounds like a great guy.
The best. Gandhi. Harvey.
You serious?
Hand to God.
The man's practically
a saint.
- What's going on?
- Oliver, Harvey Specter.
Harvey Specter, Oliver.
Nice to meet you, Oliver.
Would you like me
to pour you a drink?
- Would you?
- No, I wouldn't.
Now, put that down,
get out of my office
and if I ever catch you touching
one of my things again,
I'll shove it up your ass.
Is he serious?
Not about the ass part,
but I'd put it back.
Mike, you set me up.
Mmm-hmm.
Welcome to
Pearson Specter Litt.
You enjoy that?
Yeah, it felt okay.
Good. Now, why don't
you go make sure
everyone knows
exactly what they're doing?
It's 9:00 p.m.,
the clock's ticking,
and we got to
get this thing done.
And what are you
going to do?
I'm going to figure out what we're going
to say to that Velocity son of a bitch
when he walks in here tomorrow
begging for a settlement.
Do you have any idea
what this is about?
Gretchen said that Louis had
some special assignment for us.
All I know is, I got a rambling
voicemail about Neapolitan ice cream.
Neapolitan ice cream?
Yes. Chocolate and vanilla melded
beautifully with strawberry.
Just like we're about to
do for Carly Donahue.
Louis, did you just
call me chocolate?
Why would I do that? You're my white swan.
Katrina's my black swan.
The math ain't that hard.
What's with the boxes, Louis?
This is everything the firm has
ever done for Couture Apparel.
You're taking us to
your annual meeting?
I'm not just taking you.
We're running it together.
Okay, Louis... I know
what you're thinking.
How the hell are a junior partner
and a third-year law student
supposed to fill
Jessica's size thirteens?
Well, the answer is
you can't. No one can.
Then why are we here?
Because we used to
dazzle Carly with rank.
This year, we're going to
dazzle her with substance.
By knowing her business
better than anyone else.
I'll take care
of the business.
What you two are going to do is personally
tailor the presentation to her.
And as of now, we have less
than 24 hours to do that.
We won't let you down, Louis.
I know you won't.
You think Jessica really
wears size thirteens?
That's exactly
what I was thinking.
Oliver, how's it going?
It's going okay. I'm finished
drafting six complaints.
What is it?
It's nothing. It's just,
in the time I did six,
most of them did nine or 10.
I guess that means you're
in the home stretch, huh?
I guess I am.
Look, Oliver, I know
what you're thinking.
But I was telling
Nathan the truth.
I'm not looking to come back here with
these guys instead of working with you.
I know you don't want to
come back here, Mike.
I guess I just wanted to say
these associates are badass,
and I appreciate you choosing to
work with someone like me over them.
You mind if I ask
how you're so sure
I don't want to
come back here?
Because these associates
are amazing lawyers.
But not a single
one of them mentioned
an actual human being involved
in this case the whole night.
They're just trying to win.
And there's nothing wrong with
that, but that's not you.
Yeah, Oliver, there is
something wrong with that.
And that's why
you're going to be
a better lawyer
than any one of these guys.
I'm going to go tell Harvey
that we're in the home stretch.
How's it going, genius?
What?
I said,
how's it going?
I'll tell you
how it's going.
It's not going to work.
What?
But I thought that you said...
I don't care what you thought.
This isn't Westworld.
I can't make her human.
Benjamin, I'm not asking you
to make her human,
I'm just asking you to give
her a little compassion.
Well, I don't know
how to do that.
And it's supposed to learn
from itself, but it isn't.
Hey.
What's going on?
The story
I always told myself
was the only reason I didn't work in
Silicon Valley was that I didn't want to.
But the truth is
I don't have what it takes.
And then you come in here,
calling me a genius, and...
Benjamin,
it's okay.
You're only human.
If it doesn't work,
it doesn't work.
Really?
Really.
Besides, if I can't
show you compassion,
how can I ever expect
The Donna to show compassion?
Thanks, Donna.
I'm sorry
if I got your hopes up.
You figure out what we're
going to say tomorrow?
You get those
complaints ready?
I asked you first.
Yeah, but I'm not
the one who had
the least experienced lawyer I've ever
met put this thing over the goal line.
Oh, come on. I thought I was the least
experienced lawyer you've ever met.
No, you were the least
experienced dickhead I ever met.
Right.  Because
that kid may be green,
but he's the only one of you two
that actually went to law school.
Don't I know it.
Mike, what's on your mind?
Nothing. It's just,
this whole thing we're doing
is making me lie to a lot of
people including Oliver, and...
I'm not thrilled about it.
What are you
talking about?
Nathan thinks there's an ulterior
motive to this case and he's right.
Oliver saw it.
I had to lie to both of
them to cover it up.
Maybe that's true.
But you need to
keep your eye on the ball.
You deserve
to be a lawyer.
You're doing good for those miners
and that's all that matters.
I don't know, Harvey.
What do you care so much about
what this kid thinks, anyway?
Because he's the reason
I decided to change my mind
about doing
this whole thing.
What do you mean?
He's a great kid.
And he's going to
be a great lawyer.
But I had to watch him tank a case
without being able to help him
and a woman ended up
on the street.
I thought if we do this, then
I'll never have to sit back
and do nothing while someone I
care about is losing ever again.
Then stop worrying
about what we're doing.
Because tomorrow
isn't about losing.
It's about winning.
This is ridiculous.
We've been up all night,
and we've got nothing.
Yes, we do.
What is this?
This is the key to keeping
Carly Donahue's business.
How is a three-year-old interview with
Gourmand magazine going to help us?
Because it shows
she's a foodie.
And like Louis said,
we need to show her that we don't
only understand her company,
we understand her.
I get it.
What if we structured the
presentation like a nine-course meal
and paired a discrete piece of
legal analysis with each course?
Like a paired
wine tasting.
Coupled with
a paired wine tasting.
Hold on.
Are you a foodie, too?
What I am is a lover of fine wine,
delightful cuisine and the ballet.
In any order you pick.
Well, I don't think we
can have dancers at the meeting.
No, we can't.
Which means unless
you know how to cook,
we need to find ourselves a world-class
chef and we need to find it fast.
What about this?
Mike and I just met
with a world-class,
French trained chef
to cater our wedding.
I mean, if he's available, then...
Book him.
Well, don't you want to
hear more about his...
Rachel, if I can't trust your taste
in pairings, I can't trust anyone's.
What are you talking about? I
never thanked you for this.
But you knew your father and
I would be a great fit.
And if you hadn't set me up
with him after I was fired,
I don't know
what I would have done.
I'll book the chef.
I assume from the fact
that you called,
you got
our Christmas present.
I didn't call you.
I called Harvey Specter.
Well, he called me.
I wanted to come have
a little chat with you
before you got it
into your head
that you could go
behind my back
and cut a deal without
an admission of guilt.
What?
Look, I don't give a shit
how much you offered.
You're not going to buy
your way out of this thing
without telling the world
what you did.
I don't think you understand what
the word "settlement" means.
I understand
what it means to you.
I just don't give a shit.
One hundred million. With an
admission of guilt. Sure.
Where do I sign?
Listen to me.
A hundred million dollars is the biggest
payout this company's ever made.
No, it's not.
Because I'm not taking it.
What is wrong with you?
I'm willing to cut
your clients a check
that will change their lives and
you're too stupid to see it.
Here's what I see.
Every day this case drags on, your
stock is going to take a hit.
And every quarter
when the board meets,
that's going to be
their first question
and your biggest
goddamn headache.
So, the real question is,
"Are you ready to take responsibility
for what you did or not?"
I see you wore your power suit
for your return to the majors.
You're going to play
in Yankee Stadium,
you've got to wear
the pinstripes.
How did it go?
Good. He did exactly
what we thought he would.
Tried to lowball me, called me
an idiot and then kicked me out.
How high did he go?
A hundred million.
What?
Nothing.
It's just, I would have
gotten him up to two.
And how exactly would
you have done that
when you told me
not to counter?
I'm more intimidating.
I walk into a room, people cave.
It's a gift.
I think it's a gift
when you leave the room.
My gift to you
was saving your ass
when you screwed the pooch by
involving me in this case.
Seriously, Harvey, I...
I appreciate
you rolling with this thing.
Especially when I had
to improvise.
Don't worry about it.
The truth is, I like getting the
chance to work with you again.
Besides, don't tell Rachel,
I like the added risk.
Oh, I know.
How do you know?
Because you told me. "Life is
like this and I like this."
What am I, Luke Perry?
Sometimes.
Look, I've got to go.
Because this asshole's going to
be back in my office in an hour
trying to cut a deal with
me behind your back.
Oh, my God.
This is amazing.
You really think so?
I know so. It's the perfect legal analysis
combined with the perfect presentation.
So, you don't think the fact
that Jessica isn't here...
Jessica "Schmessica." Carly's
going to be blown away.
I should promote you
both right now.
Will you?
No.
Worth a try.
Okay, we have some time.
So, I'll meet you both
back here in an hour.
Where are you going?
Going to go
have a prunie.
Want to clean out the pipes
for the nine-course meal.
Mike Ross.
Yes?
I'm Craig Seidel.
What? What are you
doing here?
I want to know
what the hell you're doing.
What do you mean,
"What am I doing?"
I mean you filed 150 suits,
not just one.
And James Palmer's going
to fight each one of them.
Which means this thing is
going to drag on forever.
And we're going to drop
the hammer on him
as soon as he gets
to Harvey's.
Now, I don't want to
see you again
until I meet you for the
first time at that hearing.
Don't you walk away
from me.
I hired Harvey
to do a job,
he farmed it out to you
against my will
and you're going to
goddamn listen to me.
No, you didn't hire Harvey.
You tried to mess
with my fiancée's life
and you're lucky we didn't
have you disbarred.
So, instead of coming to my
place of work and harassing me,
why don't you go back
to your hole
and we'll tell you
when it's done?
Okay, but your
window's closing.
This thing doesn't
get wrapped up soon,
your shot at being
a lawyer is over.
If you're going to
bankroll a suit,
at least have the balls
to negotiate it yourself.
I take it you didn't
like the offer.
Admission of guilt isn't an offer.
It's suicide.
It's Mike Ross' case.
It's his call.
Bullshit. Mike Ross
is some clinic worker.
You're Harvey Specter.
And from what
I hear about you,
you don't give
a shit about guilt.
You're right, I don't.
So, why don't you tell me how much it's
going to take to make this go away?
Five hundred million. Half a
billion dollars. Are you insane?
You poisoned your employees, Mr.
Palmer.
You're lucky
you're not in prison.
Two hundred million.
No.
Three hundred.
Okay.
Make it 350
and call it a day.
Five hundred.
Not a penny less.
In that case,
make it zero.
Because you just confirmed what
I suspected since this morning.
You picked the exact number to
make my stock take a nosedive.
And we both know
who benefits from that.
Craig Seidel. I don't know
what you're talking about.
Then I guess you also
don't know that Mike Ross
just got an appointment
with the ethics board.
And it's a crime
to trade this for that.
Which means
your lawsuit is over.
Then I'll do
something else.
You think I won't go after you for
stealing technology from Seidel's company?
You have no proof
I did anything.
No, but he does.
And I don't give a shit
about his marriage,
and I'm going to
make him come forward.
His marriage? Is that what
he told you this is about?
I've got news for you,
Mr. Specter.
The reason he hasn't come forward has
nothing to do with his marriage.
So, why don't you
go find out what's what?
And I've got a feeling
when you do,
you'll drop this case
by morning.
Hey-
You ran out of the
presentation so quickly,
I didn't get to ask
what you thought.
I had to get to class.
But I thought
it went great.
What about Louis?
He was over the moon.
I'm sure he's glad
to have you back.
I'm glad to be back.
Well, I should, uh... What was
it like, working with my dad?
You said it was a great pairing
and I was just wondering...
What you were missing.
Yes.
You were missing a brilliant,
tireless, sweet, funny, charming man.
Who may also be the best
litigator I have ever seen.
Maybe you didn't
understand my question.
I was asking what it was like
to work with Zane, not Kaldor.
Rachel, I'm serious.
I learned a lot about your
father while I was there
and I'm telling you,
it was all good.
What about his temper?
Well, maybe
it wasn't all good.
Well, good night.
One more thing
I learned about him.
He doesn't just love you,
he respects you.
How would you know that...
When he offered you
that job, he was beaming.
He told everyone in the office
that his brilliant baby girl
was going to work for us and she was
going to blow us all to smithereens.
He said that?
Rachel, I didn't tell you that
to make you feel bad.
He was okay that
you didn't take his offer.
It doesn't make me feel bad.
It makes me feel great.
Is he in?
No, he had to run out.
All right,
do me a favor.
Just tell him I need to talk
to him when he gets back.
You mind if I ask
what it's about?
I just got off the phone
with Carly Donahue.
Louis, what happened? Rachel
said that it went great.
I thought it did, too. But
then she called me and said
that the next time she asks for
a meeting with me and Harvey,
she better get
a goddamn meeting
with me and Harvey
instead of two nobodies.
What did you tell her?
I told her how dare she talk
about my superstars like that.
She's lucky to have them.
Louis, that's great.
Good for you.
She fired us, Donna.
Oh, Louis, I'm so sorry.
Look, this isn't your fault.
You couldn't have known.
It's okay.
I just need to go home.
Shit.
It's okay, Donna. It's
not your fault either. Yes, it is.
I'm Donna.
I should have known.
Maybe. But you always say, "Part of
being human is messing up sometimes."
And you may be Donna,
but you're still human.
Holy shit.
You are ready.
Oliver. Hey, what are you
doing in here?
I want to know
if I was wrong about you.
What are you
talking about?
I want to know if you're using this
case to get back to Pearson Specter.
Oliver, we talked
about this.
I thought you understood
that's not who I am.
I thought so, too.
But then I got to thinking.
You fooled so many people
for so long,
what if
you're fooling me now?
Because you said
Pearson Specter
would never take on a case like
this when you were there before.
Yeah, because they
never wanted to be
on the wrong side
of a corporate lawsuit.
Then why are they on the
wrong side of one now?
Oliver. Please. Don't
lie to me, Mike.
Just tell me
what's going on.
It's a long story, but...
We brought the suit so that
I could get into the Bar.
So, you were lying to Nathan,
only not about what he thought.
Listen to me.
I'm not going to listen.
And you need to tell him what's going on.
I can't do that.
And I wasn't lying to him when I said
I'm not going back to my old firm.
I wasn't lying to him when I said
these people's lives matter to me.
And I wasn't lying
to either one of you
when I said I care about what kind
of lawyer you're going to be.
Well, if you care what kind
of lawyer I'm going to be,
set the right example.
Because you owe it to Nathan
to tell him the truth.
Hi.
Hey.
What's this?
It's every yearbook
I've ever had.
It was so nice doing it
with yours the other night,
I thought maybe tonight
we could do it with mine.
Louis, what's wrong?
Nothing's wrong.
I had a bad day and I wanted
to talk to you about it.
But you went to
all this trouble
and I don't want to
bring you down.
Louis, my yearbooks
are always going to be here.
And hearing about something as
important to you as your work
isn't going to
bring me down.
It's going to
bring us closer.
Are you sure? Because I have
a lot of bad days at work.
Which is all
the more reason for you
to have someone to make
you feel better at home.
Okay, but it's kind of
a long story.
Well, then you sit
right here,
I'll go make you a drink, and then
you can tell me all about it.
You know what
I'm in the mood for?
I can't tell
which one yet,
but I'm pretty sure it's either a
Peach Schnapps or a ice cold prunie.
You really are getting
to know me, aren't you?
I sure am.
Jesus Christ.
What are you doing here?
You guys told me to
stay away from you.
Yeah, that was before I had a chat
with your buddy, James Palmer.
Look, I don't even know James Palmer.
So, whatever he said...
He didn't have to say anything.
All he had to do was point.
So what? This is an off-shore
account in my name.
An off-shore account
with $300,000 in it,
deposited exactly a day after Velocity
supposedly stole your technology.
I was told by my accountant
to shelter certain earnings.
Bullshit. You don't even
have those kind of earnings.
And you didn't have to keep this
quiet because you're married.
You kept it quiet
because you're in on it.
I was in on it.
I saw a chance to jump ship
and get paid in the process.
But instead,
they pulled the job
and put just enough money in
that account to implicate me.
You piece of shit.
Please. My employees are gonna
lose their jobs because of me.
We need to keep this suit going
and get that technology back.
No, buddy.
You don't give a shit
about your employees
and I don't give
a shit about you.
This deal is done.
You can't do this.
Yes, I can. And I didn't have
leverage before, but I do now.
So, you're not just getting
Mike an interview,
you're going to block anyone
who tries to vote no.
And if you don't, your boss is gonna get an
anonymous tip that you sold trade secrets.
And I'm going to make sure
to send this along with it.
You're my attorney. You work for me.
You can't do that.
I don't work for you.
Remember, Craig?
That's how I set it up.
See you at the Bar.
^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
P® Krishna_Teja P®