You made a fool out of Dad
for the last time.
Harvey.
Bobby.
You get the hell out
of my father's house!
I am walking out of here
with that thing in my hands
or I'm putting your firm
in the ground.
Take the painting.
You told me
that painting
was the one happy memory
you had of your mother.
Every application I filled out
today asked if I was a convicted felon.
None of these places are going to
hire me after I check that box.
A legal clinic isn't the
only way to give back.
Are you offering me
a teaching job?
I am.
You think this is funny?
Cracks me up that our teacher
was in prison last week.
All you care about is proving to me
that you should be managing partner
when everyone in the world
knows that you shouldn't.
So, if you think I'm gonna
let you be managing partner,
you're out of
your goddamn mind!
One of the students told his
parents that you were in prison.
I tried to explain the
situation to them, but...
I'm sorry, Michael.
They're all leaving, Donna.
First Jessica,
now Mike.
They're family.
You always talk like
we're your only family.
You need to go make things
right with your mother.
Mike, what are you
doing here?
I thought school
started at 7:00.
It does.
I just don't work there anymore.
What?
What happened?
One of the students told their
parents that I was a criminal.
Oh... They went to the
Archdiocese and...
You know,
Father Walker had no choice.
Why didn't you
tell me this last night?
Because I didn't want
to step on your moment.
You were so happy
about Louis' offer.
So, what are you
going to do?
I'm going to take the day to
enjoy my life as a free man.
And then, tomorrow,
I'll start
all over again.
Hey.
Ray's downstairs
waiting for you.
I didn't call him.
I did.
He's got your black suit
and an overnight bag,
and he's taking you
to the train station.
Donna.
You need to go to your
father's funeral, Harvey.
I can't. There's too
much going on here.
Listen to me. You just
suffered a huge loss
and you're acting
like it's business as usual.
I'm acting like
I've got a job to do.
Harvey, if you don't
grieve him...
I will grieve my father
in my own way.
No, you won't.
You'll bottle it up and
you'll try to move on. But...
She's gonna
be there, Donna.
I know she is.
But this funeral
isn't about her.
And it's not about you.
It's about your dad,
the man you loved more than
anyone in the entire world.
And if you don't say
goodbye to him,
you're gonna regret that
for the rest of your life.
Donna, what are you
doing here?
The question is, what are
you still doing here?
I made you an 8:00
reservation to Boston
which means you should be
halfway there by now.
I missed my flight.
Harvey, you never
miss your flight.
And the last time
you said you did,
you were
lying to me then, too.
Donna.
Please tell me you
didn't change your mind
about seeing her.
I didn’t.
Then what's the problem?
I haven't seen the woman
in seven years.
And the last time I did...
I know what happened
the last time you did.
Listen to me.
Every day.
You go out in the world
and you find a way to win.
It's who you are.
It's what you do.
Donna, this isn't
about winning.
Yes, it is.
But it's not just one person
in this case, it's two.
And right now,
you're both losing.
What if I can't do it?
Then don't get on
that plane.
But that bag sitting over there tells
me that you're ready to forgive her.
And if you are, then
that's all you need to do.
See the money,
wanna stay for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
P® Krishna_Teja P®
Nathan.
You remember me.
I remember everyone.
What are you doing here?
I'm here because I may not
have been there
when you dropped off
your resume, but...
I still run that clinic.
I'm here
to offer you a job.
I don't understand.
Hector Suarez.
I'm assuming you remember
him, too, right'?
What about him?
Well, after you left,
I picked up your file.
Don't tell me.
You kept him
in the country.
No, Mike. You did.
And I thought,
maybe this guy
will become a lawyer someday.
And then I read about you
in the paper last year
and found out
you never did.
So, you knew that I faked
being a lawyer twice,
and you're still here
to offer me a job?
I wouldn't be,
except for this.
You told the truth.
As far as I'm concerned that means
you're worth taking a chance on.
Wow, you really are
a do-gooder.
I'm not here
to do good for you.
I'm here to do good
for my clinic.
Because I'm hiring
a partner-level attorney
from one of the top firms
in the city
for the price of the kid
who gets me my coffee.
You have a kid
who gets you coffee?
No, we can't afford that.
But if we could,
I'd pay him what I'm going to pay you.
So, are you in or not?
When do I start?
I don't think I've ever
seen you in a suit before.
Harvey, you made it.
Uh, wouldn't miss it
for the world.
Come here.
Uh... Huh.
Harvey, listen.
Um...
You don't have to
say it. I know.
She's here.
It's not just that.
She asked if she could say
a few words about Dad.
And what,
you're going to let her?
Harvey. She is not
saying a single word
as long as I'm here.
Yes, she is.
And if you make a scene
in front of my kids
on the day that we put
our dad into the ground,
I swear to God, I will
beat the shit out of you.
Because she's my mother,
and I'm going to let her
say her piece.
Hey.
Harvey.
It's good to see you.
I wish I could say
the same thing, Lily.
But I'd be lying
if I did.
Well, I'm sorry
you feel that way.
And whether
you believe it or not,
I loved your father,
and I am sad to see him go.
Yeah, well,
I don't believe it.
And I didn't come here
to see you,
I came here
to honor my father.
So, get up there and say
what you're going to say
and let's get this
over with.
Harvey.
What are you
doing here?
I wanted to talk to you.
I can't believe it.
This is wonderful.
I thought maybe you wanted
to get dinner tonight.
There is nothing
I would rather do
than get dinner with you,
but I can't tonight.
I wish you would
have called.
I would have, but, uh...
You didn't have
my phone number.
No, I didn't.
How about tomorrow night?
I wasn't really planning
on being here two nights.
My firm is in
a vulnerable spot right now.
Harvey,
it's the kids' art show.
It's once a year.
I can't cancel it.
You know what?
This is silly.
You flew
all the way up here.
No.
We can do it
tomorrow night.
Don't tell me.
You took the job.
Actually,
until this morning,
I didn't think there was a chance
in hell I was getting this job.
Sounds to me like you had a
friend at the front desk
who put your resume
at the top of the pile.
Sounds to me like
I owe that person a beer.
Just so we're clear,
I'm that guy.
I get the picture.
Welcome to the clinic, Mike.
Thanks, Oliver.
I see you met Oliver here.
I did. We got along
right away.
Good, good.
Well, you're off
to a good start.
I guess the only thing left is for
you to show me where my desk is.
Right. It's, uh, right inside
that office right there.
I didn't think
I was getting an office.
Look, just because
I'm paying you dick
doesn't mean I'm not gonna
give you the tools
for the job.
What exactly is my job?
Because as far as I can tell, I'm
the only one here with an office.
Everybody, listen up.
You have a new supervisor,
starting today.
His name is Mike Ross.
Mike is from
Pearson Specter Litt,
and he knows more about law
than all of you combined.
So, if Mike tells you
to do something,
you do it.
I don't mean to question
the new world order,
but what is his title?
Great question,
Marissa. Um...
Senior Individual
in charge of you.
Any more queries?
I didn't think so.
All right, back to work.
Let's go.
You really weren't kidding when you
said you were doing this for you.
No, I wasn't.
I've been trying to get
somebody in this position
for this money for
the last 10 years.
And now that I have, I'm going
to take full advantage of it.
Then why don't you go back
to wherever your office is
and stay there for
the rest of the year?
'Cause I'll be busy
kicking ass out here.
That's what
I like to hear.
Hey.
Who do you have to know around
here to get a good table?
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Do my eyes deceive me, or do you
look just like my big brother?
Only older, fatter
and douchier.
I appreciate you noticing.
I put in a lot of effort.
Seriously, Harvey,
why are you here?
I thought it was time to,
uh, make my peace with Morn.
Harvey, that's great.
But, uh, a lot has been said
over the years.
You can’t just show up
on Mom's door.
Actually, I already did.
What? When?
I went over
to the college.
She's having an art opening
tonight for her students.
So, we're going to have
dinner here tomorrow night.
Well, then,
I will get you a table.
And what
you're going to do is
cancel whatever fancy
bullshit hotel you booked
and you're going to
stay the night with us.
Marcus, come on.
I'm at the Ambassador Suite
at the Ritz.
Don't think of saying no,
because I'm going to tell Katie
and the kids that you're here.
Do you guys offer
room service?
If by room service you mean
string cheese and Triscuits.
Oh, yeah.
We've got room service.
All right.
Well, then, count me in.
Marissa, right?
Mike.
I know.
The new boss.
What?
Uh, it's nothing. It's just,
where I come from, the, uh...
The bosses
don't bike to work.
I guess this is no Pearson Specter Litt.
No, it's not.
Which is actually why I came here.
I'm glad.
Because there are a lot of people
here who could really use your help.
But I'm not one of them.
Aren't you still
a law student?
A law student who's won every case
I've had since I've been here.
Right. So, I guess that
means you have everything
under control on
the Price case then.
You just got here. How did you...
I'm a fast reader.
Marissa, I'm not trying to throw my
weight around here on the first day.
But according to her file, Ms.
Price missed her court date.
Which means I need to know
what your plan is.
My plan is to have
Ms. Price explain
that she is a single mother living
in an apartment with a broken window
and no heat for months, and
they're trying to kick her out.
And if all you're going to do is
tell the judge that it's not fair,
you're going to lose.
You need legal foundation.
I have legal foundation.
Berger v. Chozick.
Tenants are permitted
to seek injunctive relief
if vital repair requests
have gone unanswered.
Then I hope
you have backup.
'Cause the attorneys
representing the other side
have kicked out 300 tenants
in the past six years,
which means they are not messing around.
I'm not either.
Which is why I have Ms. Price
coming in at 3:00 tomorrow.
So, is there anything else
I can help you with?
Or maybe you can
spend some time
on some of the other people's
cases around here.
Louis, I need your help.
Of course.
What is it?
Teddy Doyle just called.
He has an emergency.
So, you mean Harvey needs my help.
Louis.
Donna, give me one good
reason why I should help him.
You're not helping Harvey,
Louis, you're helping the firm.
Teddy is a client
of all of us.
No. Harvey made it clear
that there is no us.
Louis, Harvey's going through
something right now.
His outburst
wasn't about you.
You can believe
whatever you want.
But Harvey lashed out at me.
And now, he's not even man enough to
come to me to ask me for help himself?
Why should I even lift
a finger to help him?
Because he went to go make
things right with his mother.
And he did it because of how he
felt after he lashed out at you.
Otherwise, he'd be taking
care of Teddy himself.
So, do you want to
help him or not?
What do you need me to do?
Mike?
What's going on?
Rachel, I thought you weren't
getting home till 8:00.
It's 8:30. I guess I
lost track of time.
I have just been buried
in this paperwork.
Yeah, I can see that.
Are we being audited?
Igor a job.
And I would have
called you right away
but I've been swamped from the
minute I walked into the clinic.
You got a job
at a legal clinic?
Mike, that's amazing.
Yeah, it is.
Um... And yes, they
know about me.
In fact, it's the
reason I got hired.
Let me guess.
They were smart enough
to appreciate
they can get someone
with your experience
for 10 cents
on the dollar.
You got it.
$35,000 a year,
to be exact.
Mmm.
Which means that we should probably
start packing up the place now,
because we definitely cannot
afford to live here anymore.
I would live
in a shoebox with you
if it meant
you were happy.
Oh. I think you meant that
you would live in a shoebox
as long as the Thai
place still delivered.
And the sushi place.
Of course.
You want one?
You kidding me?
After reading Pinkalicious
for the seventh time?
I need a six-pack.
It was nice
putting them to bed.
Oh, yeah.
Let's hear you say that after
doing it 365 days a year.
I thought Katie put them
to bed most nights.
Yeah.
I was saying it for her.
Thanks for making me
stay over, Marcus.
Well, maybe after
tomorrow night,
you could do it more often.
Maybe.
Thank you all
for coming.
I'm Lily.
I was married to Gordon
for almost 30 years.
We didn't make it
the whole 30,
and for a long time, I considered
myself a failure because of that.
But Gordon didn't.
A few years
after our divorce,
I wanted to apologize
for things not working out.
He just smiled and said,
"Lily, what the hell
are you talking about?
"We achieved
something together
"that neither one of us
could have done on our own."
Our sons.
Harvey and Marcus.
When Gordon was on the road,
he would call home.
Six times a day
to check on them.
"Did they eat enough dinner?
"Had they done homework?
"How many points
did Marcus score?
"Did Harvey get his tux
for the prom?"
Gordon was proud of a lot
of things in his life,
but none of it compared
to how proud he was of them.
They were his everything.
And no matter where he is...
I know he is watching
over them right now.
What are you doing here?
I'm doing my job.
This is my case, not yours.
No, Marissa, it's our case.
We're on the same side.
And if you'd just listen to me,
you might learn something.
Like what? Like the ways experienced
attorneys can trick you.
I'm not gonna get tricked.
So, if you don't mind, I'd
like to meet with my client.
I've already met with her.
You met her without me?
When did you do this?
A half hour ago.
You said 3:00, so I
called her in at 2:30,
because I knew you wouldn't
give me the chance to meet her.
Just like I know the other
side is gonna approach her
when you're not there.
They can't do that.
Why?
Because it's unfair?
Because it's illegal.
Only if she pursues them,
which she'll never do.
Because they're gonna find out
whatever her weak spots are
and then they're gonna offer her exactly
the amount she needs to get by,
and then
she's gonna take it.
If she does that,
she'll end up homeless.
Which is why we need to be
prepared for it to happen.
Now, do you want to work on
this thing together or not?
I'm sorry I didn't tell you that she was
going to speak before you got here.
I just didn't have it in me
to have it out with you.
It's okay, Marcus.
She got to you,
didn't she?
I'm sad about Dad.
And, uh, yeah,
she pulled on that string.
But one speech doesn't
make up for everything.
Maybe it doesn't.
But you have to
start somewhere.
Yeah. Well...
I'm going to
head back home.
Oh, come on, Harvey.
Come to the house
for the wake.
I got a few things I got
to take care of at work.
Oh, come on, Harvey.
You're not leaving
because of work.
It's time to let things go.
I complained about the heat
not working a million times.
The landlord always says he's going
to fix it, and then nothing happens.
We couldn't afford to move,
so I was just making do.
But then, my little
guy, he got asthma.
The doctor said that we need to
keep all of the windows shut,
keep out the pollution.
But the window
in the living room,
it's been broken
for seven months.
My son is
only three years old.
The sound of him
wheezing at night,
not knowing if he's gonna
wake up in the morning.
So, I thought, since that
slumlord only cares about money,
I'm not gonna pay rent until he fixes
the window and turns on the heat.
I'm so sorry, Sofia.
That sounds terrible.
It is.
And no one should
have to live like that.
But by violating your lease,
he has grounds to evict you.
Which is why you have to give him
a check for the money you owe him
while this case
moves forward.
I... I can't do that.
You don't have
the money anymore.
I had to buy blankets,
space heaters.
There were a couple of nights
that A.J.'s breathing was so bad,
we had to go to
a motel down the street.
Don't worry, Sofia.
Not only are we gonna get your
window fixed, but I promise you,
you'll get to
keep your home, too.
Thank you.
Are you crazy?
What are you talking about?
You just told her
you were gonna
fix her problem.
Because I'm going to fix her problem.
That's not the point.
Even if you think you can
make everything better,
you don't guarantee
that to a client.
You know what?
Maybe you don't care about
these people, but I do.
Oh, my God.
And I'm willing to fight
to make sure
they stay in their home
and I'm not afraid to tell her that.
This is not about caring.
There's a real world
out there.
And like I told you,
there's an experienced lawyer
on the other side looking
to exploit our mistakes.
If you over-promise
and under-deliver,
you're just making them that much
more vulnerable to a shitty offer.
Is that what they taught you
in corporate low-balling 101?
Excuse me? You don't give a
shit about these people.
And Nathan and everyone else here
might be buying your bullshit,
but I know
why you're really here.
I get it.
You checked up on me.
I didn't need
to check up on you.
I've heard your story
1,000 times.
You couldn't hack it
at your corporate law firm.
So, you're slumming it here
until you can figure out a way
to jump back into your cushy,
stick it
to the working man job.
I see that I'm right.
So, keep your wisdom
to yourself.
Because I'm actually here
to help people,
Not just remind them what a
cruel world it is out there.
Harvey Specter's office.
Donna, it's me.
Harvey, hey.
Are you almost here? Because your
6:00 is in the conference room.
I'm not back
in New York yet.
You were right, Donna.
About what?
If I'd missed his funeral, I never
would be able to forgive myself.
Good luck making up
with your mom.
How did you know?
Because you've never
missed a flight
in your entire life.
And the only reason
you'd stay longer
is if things are going better
than you thought they would.
Thanks, Donna.
I don't need
your thanks, Harvey.
I'm just really happy
you're there.
I know
what you're thinking.
How could she not know?
I checked the box.
You did.
But I was the one who brought
the application to Nathan
and he told me
not to tell anyone.
Why not?
Because he didn't
want them to judge you.
I would have thought
everyone knew, anyway.
Why would you
think that?
Because it was
all over The Journal.
People here don't
read The Journal.
We read
The Huffington Post.
So, what Marissa thinks is what
they all think. I don't know.
But for what it's worth,
I wouldn't have said anything
whether Nathan told me to or not.
It's not my story
to tell.
Thank you, Oliver.
Yeah.
You made
your strawberry pie.
It was his favorite.
Maybe you forgot
it was mine, too.
I didn't forget.
It was a nice speech.
Thank you, Harvey.
Harvey.
When my parents died,
I felt like I was completely
alone in the world.
I don't want you
to feel that way.
I want you to know
that whether you want me
in your life or not,
you still have a mother
that loves you
and will always
be there for you.
I know that.
Harvey, I'm...
I'm sorry for your loss.
Are you kidding me?
You brought him here?
Harvey...
I said you have the nerve
to bring him here?
He's my partner. Is that what you
call every guy you slept with
while you were with Dad?
Don't speak to me
like that.
Bobby and I
are still together.
- You think I give a shit?
- You should,
because it shows
what kind of man I am.
You're a piece of shit.
You have no right being here the day
we put my father in the ground.
Harvey, please.
We were just about...
Yeah, I don't care
what we were about to do.
You spit in Dad's face
by bringing him here.
It's okay, Lily.
I'll go.
I don't care
whether you stay or not.
No, well, I do.
And he is staying.
Because you may not
want to hear this,
but your father accepted
him a long time ago.
You know what? You want
to take his place, Bobby?
Why don't you go
right ahead?
Maybe one day, you'll even walk
in on her with another guy
and you'll know exactly
what my father felt.
The only difference will be
at least then,
I won't be asked to keep
the goddamn secret.
So, what's good here?
Actually,
everything's good here.
You eat here a lot?
Of course I do.
This...
This feels strange,
doesn't it?
Yeah, a little bit.
So...
Where do we start?
I guess we start with me telling
you that I'm ready to forgive you.
Why now?
Someone very special to me
convinced me that I needed to.
Whoever it is,
I'm glad she did.
That's good.
I want you to know
that I forgive you, too.
Forgive me for what?
For the last time
I saw you.
And for you being
gone all those years.
I had my reasons to be gone.
Yes. You did
when you were younger.
But you're not
a child anymore,
and you haven't been
for a long time.
I can't believe you. You're
turning this around on me?
I'm not turning it
around, Harvey.
You have no idea what
it's like to have a child
who acts like
you don't even exist.
And you don't know what
it's like to have a mother
who asks you to lie to
his own father for her.
Harvey, I never
should have done that.
And I have been
trying to tell you
I am sorry about it
for 20 years.
But until yesterday,
you made it clear to me that you had no
interest in whether I lived or died.
Because I didn't.
Well, can't you understand
how that could
devastate a person?
I can understand
how this was just a mistake.
Because you are
the same selfish,
self-centered, disloyal
woman you always were.
And you are the same
self-absorbed,
childish man
you always were.
Well, whose fault is that?
Oh, there you go.
Leave.
That's what you do best.
What did you just say to me?
I said take a look
in the mirror, Harvey.
Because I may have neglected
my family in the past,
but you've been doing it
for as long as I can remember.
So, what am I supposed to
tell the kids in the morning?
You tell them I've got
business back in New York.
You want me to lie for you.
God damn it, Marcus,
she had the nerve to say
that I owed her an apology.
If that's her, you tell her
I've got nothing more to say.
You know what, Harvey?
You can tell her yourself.
Because I'm done being
in the middle of you two.
- Bobby.
- Where is he?
Hey, now's not the time to...
Why, you son of a bitch.
You think you can just
walk into our lives, and...
And rip open old wounds?
Your lives?
You better get the hell out of my face
before I do something that you'll regret.
You already did something I regret by
talking to your mother the way you did.
That woman gave up the right
to be called my mother
when she got together with
you behind my father's back.
Well, maybe you don't consider
her to be your mother.
But she's my wife.
And if anyone else spoke
to her the way you did,
they'd be on the floor
right now.
- You want to take a swing at me?
- Harvey.
Harvey. No, no, no. Let him
get it out of his system.
Because I know I want
to get it out of mine.
I didn't come here
to fight, Harvey.
I came here to tell you I've never
seen your mother more excited
than when she was heading out
to have dinner with you.
She was finally gonna get
to reconnect with her son.
And then you pulled the rug
out from underneath her.
You took that
excitement away.
So, when you leave this time, just
stay gone. Because the truth is,
this family works better
without you.
Rachel, I need you
to help me with something
and I need it quickly.
What is it?
Teddy Doyle
needs to access the proceeds
from the sale of his company that
were put in trust to avoid taxes,
and he needs to do it without
triggering those taxes.
Louis,
are you kidding?
This isn't Dubai.
He's not gonna be
able to do that.
I know that. But I need him
to be able to, anyway.
Give me the file.
I'll figure something out.
Thanks.
I'm proud of you,
Louis.
For what? Teddy Doyle
is Harvey's client.
And I heard
about your thing.
So, this must mean
that you forgave him.
I did.
Bring that to me as soon
as you have something.
Hey, Mike, I've got a question
about the Haberman case.
He lost his job. They're taking his car.
I'm trying...
You need
a reaffirmation agreement.
Can I help you in a minute?
Yeah.
Great.
Hey, everyone, can you
listen up for a sec?
Marissa.
This won't take long.
When Nathan introduced me,
he told you that I used to
work at Pearson Specter Litt.
What he didn't tell you is why
I don't work there anymore.
And the reason isn't that I couldn't
hack it as a corporate lawyer.
It's because
I wasn't a lawyer at all.
Here. Read that.
That is my story.
That's what I did.
Every word
of these articles is true.
I never should have been
at Pearson Specter.
But not being a lawyer isn't the
only reason I didn't belong there.
You see, the whole reason that I wanted
to be a lawyer in the first place
was so that I could help the kind of
people that come into this clinic
every single day.
Now, I thought
you all knew this,
but it's clear to me now
that you don't.
Now, Nathan wanted
to protect me.
But...
I'd rather have you
respect me.
If any of you have
any questions at all,
please come talk to me
about it. But if not,
let's get back to work.
Mike.
You didn't
have to do that.
Yeah, I did.
Hey.
You're still here.
My flight isn't for
another two hours.
I wasn't gonna let that
asshole drive me away.
Listen, Harvey,
about what Bobby
said last night?
You don't need to make
excuses for him, Marcus.
Oh, I'm not
making excuses.
I am telling you he had every right
to say what he said to you.
I don't believe this.
You're on his side now?
The only side I'm on
is my family's.
The family that you've
never been a part of.
Marcus, come on.
Do you know what it's like
to tell a 5-year-old
why Grandma and Uncle Harvey can't
be in the same room together?
Because that's the position
you put me in.
Year after year.
There's a whole life going on here
that you're not even a part of.
You think I don't know
what I've missed?
I'm not just talking
about birthdays, Harvey.
I got sick again,
a couple of years ago.
What?
Why didn't you tell me?
Why would I?
So that we could have this
at the same time?
Marcus.
No, listen to me.
You know who helped out when
Katie was taking me to chemo?
Mom made dinner
every night.
Bobby took my kids
to school every day.
Which means, while they
might be monsters to you.
To my kids,
they're Grandma
and Grandpa.
And you might not have liked
that shit coming from Bobby,
but it's the truth, Harvey.
Whether you want
to hear it or not.
Do you
have a minute?
Of course.
I'm sorry that
I misjudged you.
It's okay.
Like I said, we're on the same team.
We are.
And I also should not have
promised Sofia that we would win.
But I told you that
I wouldn't stop looking
for a way to keep her
in her home,
and I think I found one.
Marissa, it doesn't matter what
kind of legal basis you've got.
If she can't pay her rent
in the meantime, then...
That's what
I'm talking about.
Troy v. Suffolk.
As long we can prove that she tried
to tell the landlord about the heat.
Yeah, but we can't prove it.
She doesn't have it
in writing.
We can if we use
the phone records.
Phone records
aren't proof of a complaint.
No, but the only people
who call their landlord
three times a week
for two months
are people who have a
problem that needs fixing.
Then we enter
the motel receipts
and the receipts
for the space heaters
as substitution
for rent paid.
And not only
can he not evict her,
she doesn't have
to pay back rent.
We just need to convince the court
to accept these phone records.
The problem is, we can't
convince the court of anything.
I'm not a lawyer yet.
And I was hoping you
could do it, but then...
It's okay.
I've got just the person.
Harvey.
Can I come in?
Depends on why you're here.
I'm here to apologize for
the way I acted last night.
Is this 'cause Bobby
came to see you? No.
It's because
Marcus got sick
and you took care of him and
he couldn't even tell me that.
Harvey...
I'm so angry.
I don't wanna be
angry anymore,
but I don't know
how to stop.
Then let me say how sorry I am for all
the pain that I have caused you.
You don't need to tell me
how sorry you are.
Yes, I do.
Harvey, we both may have played
a part in the last 20 years.
But I was an adult
and I put you
in that position.
And not a day goes by that I don't
understand why you hate me.
I was your mother.
I was
supposed to protect you,
not scar you.
Harvey...
I am so sorry.
I don't hate you, Morn.
I hate what you did,
and I probably always will.
But I don't hate you.
I'll take that.
What is it?
It's nothing. It's...
It's just I had your painting on
my wall for the longest time.
And I just realized...
How much I missed it.
I love you, Harvey.
I love you, too, Morn.
Your Honor, my client is a single
mother with two small children.
And my dog is
a Labrador Retriever.
But the only thing
that's relevant here
is that his client hasn't paid
her rent in three months.
And the reason she hasn't paid
it is because she's had no heat
and a broken window
all winter,
despite repeated requests
for repairs.
There is absolutely
no documentation
- of any such requests.
- That's not true.
My client called her landlord 20
times over the course of two months,
as you can see from
her phone records.
That's not
proof of anything.
It's proof your client spoke to mine for
an average of two minutes per call,
and it wasn't to talk
about the weather.
Your Honor,
Mr. Grady gave me
a copy of this nonsense
20 minutes ago
and he specifically agreed
it wasn't relevant.
That... That is a lie. Really?
Because I have a phone
record of a two-minute call
that I made to you
10 minutes ago.
You may have called me,
but we didn't talk
about that.
That's right.
Just because I called you doesn't mean
I can prove what we talked about.
Your Honor,
she called 20 times.
Yeah, probably to
say why her rent was late,
because she never paid it.
But we won't know that because
we don't have it in writing,
which is what
the court requires.
Your Honor, I need...
I'd like to request time
to confer with my supervisor.
His supervisor?
He's a lawyer.
You have to help him.
I can't.
I just need a minute to..-
To gather my thoughts.
What is this,
pre-school circle time?
Your Honor, the woman
didn't pay her rent.
The deadline is now.
We are requesting
permission to evict
if we don't have a check
by 10:00 a.m. tomorrow.
Your Honor, please.
She's gonna lose her home.
Time's up, Counselor.
Permission granted.
Harvey, what are you
doing here?
When did you get back?
Ten minutes ago.
How did it go?
It went well.
I'm glad.
As a matter of fact,
I need your help
with something.
Anything.
But there's something
you have to do first.
Mr. Ross.
Ms. Price, I wanted to talk to you.
Do you have a minute?
Not really.
They're coming tomorrow.
I've been packing and...
They're not coming.
$3,600?
Should be enough to cover your
rent for the last three months.
I don't understand.
The clinic has a fund
to help
with this kind of thing.
And we do it
all the time.
But...
This is from you.
It's just quicker to do it
from my account.
Red tape and all that.
I don't know what to say.
Say you'll take that to your
landlord first thing in the morning.
And if they do anything but
give you a written receipt,
you call me right away.
I will. Thank you.
You're back.
I am.
And I heard you took care
of my client.
Thanks, Louis.
You're welcome.
But we're partners,
and they're all our clients.
They are.
Louis,
I didn't mean it when I said you
weren't ready to be managing partner.
Yes, you did.
Maybe I did.
But the truth is,
I'm not ready either.
What do you say we both act
as interim managing partners?
I'd be honored.
It seems to me
the first order of business
is what are we gonna do
about the name of the firm?
I don't know
about you, but...
I think we should keep it
exactly the same.
Me, too.
I mean, you never know when she's
gonna want to come back, right?
No, Louis, you never know.
What are you two
still doing here?
We've still got
12 hours.
We're not going to stop trying
to keep Sofia in her apartment.
Good for you.
But you don't have
to do it tonight.
Turns out she got
a little grace period.
How did she get that?
It's amazing what you can do when
you care about your clients.
Then I guess
first thing tomorrow,
we should plan
our next move.
I guess we should.
^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
P® Krishna_Teja P®