(HARVEY READING)
Your execution
date has been set.
When?
Thirty days.
You said you were
gonna find Maria.
JUDGE: You have one week
to find a witness.
After that, his execution
date is set in stone.
We found the guy who's
been feeding Sutter
his information.
Phillip Allen, I know.
He came by to cut a deal
two hours ago, so I gave
him one.
No, you goddamn didn't.
Relax.
As far as the SEC
is concerned, Mike led
directly to the witness
that's going to put
that piece of shit away
for the rest
of his life.
You have a small window
to come clean with the SEC
and save yourself.
I would never turn
on my own father.
I didn't take this deal
for that son of a bitch,
I took it
for my wife.
And if you ever
contact her again
without my blessing,
I swear to God, I will beat
the shit out of you.
Jim Rogers found
your missing witness.
She died three years ago.
You're informing
on your roommate.
I know it,
you don't get me
out of here soon,
your bunkmate's
going to know it, too.
SEAN: They pulled Mike's deal.
Goddamn it. I drove
that guy to you.
If I tell them that,
they're going to
know what we did.
Sean, please. There's
got to be another way
to make this happen.
SEAN: I'm sorry,
Harvey, there isn't.
Jessica, can I talk
to you for a second?
Harvey, can it wait?
I just got some bad news
about our death row case.
No, it can't. Cahill
just pulled Mike's deal.
What?
I thought he was
a man of his word.
He's saying it wasn't him,
it was his superiors.
But what difference
does it make?
It makes all
the difference
in the world.
Because if it's him,
you can go over his head.
I go over his head,
everybody knows
we're in on this
thing together.
So, what you're
telling me is that
not only are
they pulling
Mike's deal,
but you're going
to lose this case
for nothing?
Yeah, I guess that's
what I'm telling you.
Then you're
not going to like
what I have to say.
But if Mike's not getting out,
you might as well win.
What?
Harvey, we're in
the middle of building
ourselves back up.
You lose this case,
we take it in the knee.
Jessica, the guy
is guilty.
And you're his
goddamn lawyer
and you took
this case.
And I never
would have taken it
if it wasn't
to get Mike out.
JESSICA: Well,
you did take it.
And if it's just
going to kick us
back down the mountain,
then I don't care
what it takes.
You win that
goddamn case.
JUDGE DORSEY: We're gathered
to hear The United States
vs. William Sutter
on charges of insider trading.
Is the prosecution
prepared to deliver
its opening statement?
We are, Your Honor.
Ladies and gentlemen
of the jury.
William Sutter
has been earning
outrageous returns
for decades.
Now, I'm sure
the defense is going
to try to convince you
Mr. Sutter trades
with his gut
or his instinct or some
mysterious explanation
that is impossible
to verify.
But that isn't how
he makes his money.
And we can prove it.
We have a witness
that can document
giving inside
information
to William Sutter
time and time again
over the last ten years.
And when we present
that witness to you,
you will be leaping
out of your chair
to convict that man
beyond a reasonable doubt.
JUDGE DORSEY:
Mr. Specter.
What the hell witness
is he talking about?
Didn't it have to
be in discovery?
It sure as hell did.
What are you gonna
do about it?
I'm going to stop it
dead in its tracks.
Mr. Specter,
is the defense ready
to deliver its
opening statement?
No, Your Honor,
but we are ready
to request
an immediate three-day delay
of these proceedings.
On what grounds?
The prosecution
knows what grounds,
because he just violated
the rules of discovery.
Your Honor, I have
absolutely no idea
what he's talking about.
Yes, you do,
because you
just introduced
a witness into
your opening statement
and this is the first
I'm hearing about it.
It's the first
time you're
hearing about it
because the witness just
came forward yesterday.
I'm sorry,
did the Internet
go down?
Did you go over
the limit on your
friends and family plan?
Because we're required
to be notified
and I don't even know
what this person's name is.
His name is Phillip Allen and
he's prepared to put that man
behind bars where he belongs.
Mr. Cahill,
that's enough.
Your Honor, we need
three days to depose
this witness.
This is ridiculous,
they've lost, they know it,
and they're just
trying to stall.
Then you should
have thought of that
before you decided
to drop this bomb
in my courtroom.
Mr. Specter,
you have three days.
I wasn't expecting
you so soon.
We have some news
we wanted to
give you in person.
RACHEL:
We found Maria Gomez.
Leonard, she died
three years ago.
What does that mean?
It means that
we have five more days
to find something
we can use to get
your case re-opened.
Sounds like a polite
way of telling me that,
in 30 days, I'm gone.
And what if there
was a way to get us
more than five days?
Then let's take it.
JESSICA: You have the right
to have a family member
present at your execution.
If you have
a relative
that's sick
who needs time to
get better to travel,
we can petition the court
for a delay and they
have to grant it.
The woman
who raised me,
my Aunt Harriet.
She has MS, but...
That's not going
to do us any good,
because she doesn't want
anything to do with me.
She never came
to visit you?
She thinks I'm guilty.
And says I brought
shame on the family.
Even if you did,
you need her now,
she has to see that.
I reached out to her,
Rachel, 1,000 times
my first years here.
I wrote her that
there was nothing
I needed more than
to know that
I had her support.
She didn't give it
to me then and she...
She's not going to
give it to me now.
Well, maybe
if she could see
that two women
like us believe in you,
then she'll be able
to believe in you too.
If you could
make that happen,
that would mean
the world to me.
Then we'll
make that happen.
That was nice work
in there,
you think it was
good enough to
get us a mistrial?
Mistrial?
You're lucky they
didn't find you
guilty after that.
What the hell are
you talking about?
Enough bullshit, William.
This isn't
the SEC
asking anymore,
this is me.
Who the hell
is Phillip Allen
and what the hell
is he going
to tell them?
He's an investment banker
who used to work for me.
And he's not going
to tell them shit
about me
because he doesn't
know shit about me.
Then why were you
so surprised when
they said they had him?
Because he can
tell them about
my daughter.
I get it, he gives
inside information to her.
So, if this
goes down,
she goes down
instead of you.
No one's going down,
because they can't
prove she told me
what he told her.
Which means
if you do your job,
we both get off.
William,
you're taking
a huge risk.
What the hell do you
think I hired
a gunslinger
like you for?
So, stop telling me
I can't win
and go ahead
and start winning.
See the money, wanna stay
for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody want to know
how it feel
Everybody want to see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind...
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
P® Krishna_Teja P®
You keep eating
eggs every morning,
you're gonna
have a heart attack.
Didn't you hear?
They're good
for you now.
What happens
five years from now
when they become
bad for you again?
You worried something's
going to happen to me?
I'm worried I'm going
to have to deal
with another roommate.
Took me long enough
to get used to you.
Kevin.
I'm sorry.
Water under the bridge.
All right? You had my
best interest in mind.
You want some bacon?
Now, that's always going
to be good for you.
Amen to that,
brother.
Look who it is,
Frick and Frack.
We're in the middle of
a conversation, Gallo.
Oh, I bet you are.
Mike here is a really
good listener,
isn't he, Kevin?
What do you want?
Nothing.
It's just nice
to see you guys
are such
good friends.
Nice to know you can
trust each other.
I only wish I could
trust that Mike here
was really working on
getting me out on parole.
We are working on it.
Well, you're running
out of time.
Would you listen
to me, Gallo?
No!
There's
no more listening.
You've got until
6:00 tonight to get
Harvey down here.
After that, I'm gonna
to schedule a little
hearing of my own.
Can I help you?
I hope so.
My name
is Rachel Zane
and I'm a lawyer working
on your nephew's case.
My nephew's case was
over a long time ago,
and thank God for that.
Ma'am...
I'm here because
we believe
Leonard was wrongly
convicted of those murders.
Well, that's what
they all say,
isn't it?
But just because
he suckered you
doesn't mean he's
going to sucker me.
He didn't
sucker anyone.
I looked at the evidence
and I got to know the man.
So, you've got proof
he didn't do it?
We're working on it.
But if we can't
find a way to push
back the execution,
then, in 30 days,
it won't matter anymore.
What do you
want from me?
I want you to ask
the court for a delay
so you can be with him
at his execution.
I'm not gonna
watch him die.
Ms. Deon, please,
you raised him.
I raised Leonard from
when he was 14 to 17.
I took him in,
I loved him.
He was no good then
and he's no good now.
Look, if that's the case,
you don't have to
be at the execution.
But if you could sign
this request that says
you're too infirm
to travel this month,
it will at least
give him the chance
to prove you wrong.
I'll sign your letter.
But I'm not
watching him die.
Thank you.
There you are.
I've been on pins
and needles all morning.
How was dinner?
It was a complete
and total shit
show, Donna.
Louis, what happened?
What happened was,
I found out the woman
of my dreams is spoken for.
She's married?
She might as well be.
She has this long term
boyfriend who lives
in California
and they have
this arrangement where
they see other people.
And even though it was
the most wonderful night
of my life,
I'm moving on.
I don't understand.
The most wonderful
night of your life?
Why did you even
stay through dinner?
Because she gave me some line
about being the only person
she'd ever done this with.
But now that
I think about it,
what the hell difference
does that make?
Huh.
I think it makes
all the difference
in the world.
What are you
talking about?
Louis, if you're really
the only man she's ever
done this with,
then that means you've
got something that this
other man doesn't have.
How could you know that?
They've been
together three years.
I can't compete
with that.
Because when you're happy,
you don't go looking
somewhere else.
Donna.
Louis.
I told you I broke up
with Mitchell, but
I didn't tell you why.
He wanted to see
other people.
He wanted to
move in with me.
And when he asked me,
I started picturing
a life with him.
And that's when
I knew he wasn't
the right one for me.
How can I know
I'm the one for her?
You can't.
But you'll never know
if you don't fight for her.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Harvey Specter's office.
WOMAN: You have a call from
Danbury Federal Prison.
Do you accept...
Yes.
MIKE: Donna, it's me.
I need to talk to him.
I don't have him, Mike.
He's in court.
I don't care where he is.
I need to know what's going on
with Gallo's parole hearing.
DONNA: Nothing's going on.
What the hell do you mean
nothing's going on?
Harvey was hoping
that you were going
to be out of there
before he had to
go through with it.
Goddamn it, Donna.
Gallo knows
about me and Cahill.
If he doesn't
see some progress
by the end of the day,
he's going to tell Kevin.
Mike, Harvey didn't want
you to know this yet, but...
There is no you
and Cahill.
What?
Cahill pulled your deal.
What the hell are
you talking about?
His superiors said
you didn't hold up
your end of the bargain.
That is bullshit,
I've been busting
my ass
to hold up my
end of the bargain.
I know that and
Harvey knows that,
and he's trying to
get your deal back.
Well, you tell him
that while
he's getting around
to making Cahill honor
his goddamn word,
maybe he can
take just a minute
to honor his word
and get Gallo
his goddamn
parole hearing.
I got it.
She signed it?
She did, an affidavit
from her doctor, too.
All right, I'll go to court
and make this happen.
You start going back
through every piece
of evidence we have,
because this
gives us some
breathing room
to find something, but
we still have to deliver.
Jessica.
Look, Rachel, I know
you want to go to
court with me,
but we don't
have the time.
No, that's not it.
Well, then,
what is it?
She signed
the request,
but she wouldn't
actually agree to
be there with him if...
Rachel, it's not
our job to reunite him
with his family
if it comes to it.
It is our job to make sure
it doesn't come to it.
I meant she doesn't
want to come
because she thinks
that he did it.
And if we can't convince
his own aunt that
he's innocent,
how are we going
to convince
12 strangers?
Right now, I'd rather
focus on the fact that
we're getting the man
another 30 days
to save his life.
Mike, sit down,
I need to talk to you.
You needed to talk
to me yesterday
when Cahill decided
to pull my deal.
He's saying it was
the people above him.
And I didn't want
to tell you about it
until I figured out
how to get it back.
Yeah well,
the amount of things
you're not telling me
are really starting
to pile up.
I know you found out
about Gallo, I'm sorry.
But I give you my word,
it's being taken care of.
Oh, like my deal was
being taken care of?
Listen to me, I'm going to
neutralize Phillip Allen
so you still have
a chance to
walk out of here.
But that's not going
to happen if you don't
get Jill Miller
to testify
against her father.
Goddamn it, Harvey.
I've been down that road.
Jill's not going
to go for it
and neither is Kevin.
Well, then, you better
figure out a way to make him.
Because once
I blow Phillip Allen
out of the water,
the next person up
on Cahill's hit list
is Kevin's wife.
(LINE RINGING)
TARA: Hello.
Hey Tara, it's me,
Louis Litt.
I know who you are,
Louis, you don't have
to use your last name.
Well, I don't like
to be presumptuous.
I mean, you can
have another man...
I mean, you can have
another Louis in your life.
Speaking of
other men, Louis,
I'm glad
you called back.
I had an amazing
time the other night,
but I wasn't sure
you were okay
with what I told you
about me having a...
Oh, please,
Tara, it's 2016.
If a man can't be okay
with his woman
seeing other men,
then what was
Susan B. Anthony
even fighting for?
(CHUCKLES)
Well, in that case,
Louis Litt,
how would you like
to go out tonight?
Tonight?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Then tell me where to
be and I'll meet you
there at 7:00 p.m. sharp.
Okay.
JEFF: Jessica Pearson
in court.
I haven't seen
that in a while.
I like to get
back in the ring
from time to time.
So, what giant companies
are you merging today?
Behemoth Steel and
Global Everything?
That was Tuesday.
Today, I am here
to save a man's life.
We took over
an Innocence
Project case.
Innocence Project?
So, what are you trying
to do, rehabilitate
your firm's image?
What I'm trying to do
is help a man get justice.
And if doing that
helps my firm
look good, even better.
Fair enough.
How have
you been, Jeff?
I've been good.
Listen, I know we talked
about me looking you up
when this whole mess
was over.
But I want you
to know...
It's okay, Jessica.
I understand.
No.
What I mean is,
it's not over.
I'm still in it.
You really are
fighting to rehabilitate
your image, aren't you?
I am.
It's good to
see you, Jessica.
It's good to see you,
too, Jeff.
What are you
doing here, Sean?
I'm here to
protect my
star witness.
He's got his own
attorney for that.
I don't care,
and we're here for you
to get your discovery,
not lecture me
on procedure.
I'm here to demonstrate
how Mr. Allen's
cross-examination
is gonna go.
Now, sit the hell down.
Mr. Allen, what exactly
are you getting in return
for your testimony
against my client?
He's getting immunity
for the crimes he committed.
Are you going to answer
for him when he's on
the stand, too?
What were those crimes?
I gave William Sutter
inside information
over the course
of a decade.
And how exactly
did you do that?
When my bank
was hired to review
a transaction
and I determined it
was going through,
I'd call Jill Miller
and I'd give her
the relevant names
of the parties.
Jill Miller?
I'm confused.
You told the SEC that you
were feeding William Sutter
inside information.
We had an understanding.
Understood by who?
William Sutter.
Did you ever have
a specific conversation
with Mr. Sutter?
I mean, when was
the last time you were
even in the same room?
Jill said that
he understood.
Bullshit, you can't testify
William understood anything.
It's called hearsay.
It's called the truth.
I don't give a shit
what you call it.
If you don't have proof,
the jury can never hear it.
Do you have proof?
Oh, I don't believe this.
You don't have a paper trail?
I have
the phone records.
I mean to Sutter.
She's his
goddamn daughter.
Yeah, and every
murderer has
a father, too.
Doesn't mean
they're in
on the crime.
Save your metaphors
for the trial, Harvey.
We don't need them here.
I don't need to
save anything for trial
because you made a deal
with this man for nothing,
you handed me my best witness,
and this deposition is over.
You son of a bitch.
How dare you?
How dare I what, Sean?
Defend my own client?
Bullshit.
You weren't trying
to defend your client.
You were trying
to ruin my case 'cause
you're pissed off about Mike.
I sure as hell am.
We had a deal,
and you broke it.
So, now,
I'm breaking it, too.
Well, you know what,
Harvey? I don't care
what you're breaking.
Because Phillip Allen
gets me the daughter
and that gets me
right back to Sutter.
Good, because that's exactly
what I'd expect you to do.
Oh, I get it. You aren't
trying to win this thing.
You just wanted to
discredit Phillip Allen
so I had no choice
but to reinstate
Mike's deal.
You're damn right
that's what I wanted.
So, instead of
getting mad at me
for doing what
you should've done
in the first place,
why don't you start
turning up the heat
so Mike can get
this goddamn woman
to turn on her father?
MIKE: Kevin.
Oh, good,
you're here,
you can help.
I know you made me
promise not to bring
this up again, but...
Mike, I told you.
Listen to me.
I just talked
to Harvey,
a man named Phillip Allen
has come forward and...
Wait, you talked
to Harvey?
Listen, this guy cut
a deal with Cahill.
All right? That means
he knows all about her.
Look, what do you
want from me?
I want you to
convince her
that this is it.
She has a one-time chance
of getting immunity if she
turns on her father now.
How the hell do you
even know this Cahill guy
will do that?
Because I know how
bad he wants Sutter,
and offering Jill
a deal is the best way
to make that happen.
Or he promises her a deal,
then takes it away.
And no one's
kissing my kids goodnight
for the next two years.
Harvey wouldn't
let that happen.
He's William's lawyer.
He's... He's not
selling out his
own client.
You're his client, too.
Only to protect the guy
who's paying his bills.
He doesn't give
a shit about me.
Maybe not, but he does
give a shit about me.
What are you...
What are you saying?
I'm saying that
offering Jill a deal
doesn't just get
her out of prison.
It gets me out, too.
You've been
informing on me, Mike?
Yes.
Get the hell out of my sight,
you traitor piece of shit.
Kevin listen to me,
I'm only telling you this
so that
you'll see what...
See what?
How full of shit
you are?
Telling me you grew up
without a mom and dad
just to gain my trust?
That is not
why I did that,
and I just told
you the truth so that
you trust that
I care about you.
Bullshit, because
here you are,
willing to leave two
little kids all alone
just to get your
goddamn freedom.
Kevin, I'm sorry,
but that...
No, you're not,
but you're about to be.
Come on. Fight!
Fight back, you traitor.
Kevin, we don't
have time to...
Fight me back.
Listen to me.
Come on! Fight!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(BOTH YELLING)
This isn't done,
Mike!
Get him
out of here now!
No, no, no.
Get him to solitary now.
Not solitary!
It's my fault!
You don't have to do this!
Shut up, Ross!
Another word
and you're going
to solitary, too.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
Harvey Specter.
WOMAN: You have a call from
Danbury Federal Prison.
Do you accept
the charges?
Yes.
Harvey.
HARVEY: Mike, good.
I did my part
and I took care
of Phillip Allen.
Tell me you did yours
and got Kevin
to talk to his wife.
I tried. Instead,
I got him put
in solitary.
What? How the hell
did that happen?
I told him I was
informing on him
and then he started
beating the shit out of me.
Are you kidding me?
Why would you do that?
Because lying
wasn't getting it done
and I'm living
on borrowed time,
so I thought I might
as well tell him, anyway.
Then you better
figure out a way
to get him out of there,
because we need to get
Jill to turn on Sutter
before Cahill gets her to.
That's why I'm calling you,
I already have a way.
I just need to know you
did that other thing
you were supposed to do.
I need to know you got
Gallo his parole hearing.
Let's get to it.
What happened?
Good news.
The court granted
our motion.
They pushed your
execution back a month.
I don't believe it.
You convinced my aunt
I didn't kill those people?
No, Leonard, I didn't.
I don't understand.
You, you said that
she had to agree
to be there for me.
She agreed
to sign the papers.
But she's not
gonna come.
Goddamn it.
Leonard, don't take
your eye off the ball.
This was about
buying us time.
Take my eye
off the ball?
Do you even give
a shit about me?
Of course we do.
I... I know you do.
But I want to know
if she cares whether
I live or die.
I just got
your execution
pushed back.
That's not
what I asked you.
You didn't even go
see her, did you?
I have a firm to run.
And only one of us
needed to get
her signature.
But two of you
could have helped
convince her
that I'm innocent.
Don't you get it?
The woman who raised me
wants nothing to do with me.
JESSICA: Leonard,
I know you're
disappointed.
But it's not my job
to repair your
relationship
with your aunt.
It's my job to
get you out of here.
I ain't never
getting out of here.
Don't you
understand that?
So, you go play your
game with the courts.
But whether it's
30 days or 60 days,
it doesn't matter
because I'm going
to die in here, lady.
And the one thing
I asked you to do,
you didn't.
You didn't even
care enough to try.
Just get out.
You better be here
to tell me I have
a hearing.
That's exactly what
I'm here to tell you,
but you're not
gonna have anything unless
you do something for me.
Bullshit, that wasn't
part of the deal.
I don't give a shit.
I'm tired of you
threatening me.
So, if you even want a chance
of getting out of here early,
you're gonna do
something for me.
And by the way,
it's too late
to tell Kevin
that I've been informing
on him, I already did.
What do you want?
I need you to get
him out of solitary.
You're kidding me, right?
I can't do that.
That's bullshit,
you switched
into my cell
the first night,
and ever since
you've been bragging
about everything that
you can do in here.
So, how about you
stop telling me
that you can't do it,
and just tell me
whether or not you will.
All right, Mikey.
I'll get your ticket
to freedom out
of solitary for you.
But if you get out
of here and I don't,
you should know
I can get to you
just as easily out
there as I can in here.
And when I say
get to you,
you've got to remember
what I did to make Harvey
put me away
in the first place.
Do you want to talk about
what happened at the prison?
No, Rachel, I don't.
Because whether Leonard
believes me or not,
I really do
have a firm to run.
I know you do.
Then you know I have
ten other things to do
before I get out
of here tonight.
Then I will
leave it alone.
But for what it's worth,
you were there for me
when the victim's
father lashed out at me.
And so,
if you want to talk
about it with someone,
I just want you
to know that I'm...
I'm here for you, too.
I appreciate
that, Rachel.
But right now,
I'd rather you
spend your time
finding something to
get Leonard Bailey out.
I will.
(LINE RINGING)
JEFF: Hello?
Hi, Jeff, it's me.
How would you like to have
dinner with me tonight?
I would love to, Jessica.
Just name the place.
What?
Nothing.
I just haven't been
in this place since
I was here with you.
I remembered how
much you liked it.
So, how come you
decided to call me?
You said you
were still in it.
You told me once
that you think
maybe things happen
for a reason.
You mean running
into me today?
I mean after
I ran into you,
I was pretty much
accused of being
cold, heartless,
and uncaring.
And I can take it
when it's lawyers
saying that about me.
But this was from
the man whose life
I'm trying to save.
And you wanted
to be with someone
who knows
a different
side of you.
I thought I wanted
to be with someone
who knows that's not
a side of me at all.
Jessica,
I told you
I loved you once.
And when I said that,
I meant that
one of the things
that I love about you
is your ability to
push emotion aside
and knock the shit
out of people.
(CHUCKLES) So, you think
I'm cold but you
love that about me?
I'm saying that's
one of the things
that I love about you.
The other thing is that,
in your heart,
you're not cold at all.
What do you
say after dinner,
you take me home?
I say I think that
we should take it
slow this time.
Listen, I know
you hate me
right now.
But right this second,
we are on the same side.
I know.
You do?
Yeah.
Because they just
let me out of solitary
and I went to call Jill.
I was going to
tell her everything,
but before I got
a chance to do that,
she told me
she was indicted.
Kevin, I'm so sorry.
I don't need
sorries, Mike.
I need to find
a way to keep
my wife out of prison.
Then let me help you.
You can help me.
But it can't be
by trying to get her
to turn on him.
Because I'm telling you,
there is no way in hell
she's gonna do that.
You really think
she's willing to go
to prison for him, too?
Look, the night
I found out about her
and her father,
I asked her
how she could
have gotten involved
in something like this.
Turns out she found
out his whole place
was a Ponzi scheme.
She flipped out on him
and he gave her
some bullshit
sob story
about how the returns
were running dry.
He told her that if she
got inside information
for him, one time,
it would keep them
from losing everything.
And the next thing she knew,
it was too late to stop.
Yeah, he tricked her.
And when I tried
to tell her that
and get her to quit
with me, you know
what she said?
She said she'd
never do that.
Because no matter
what he did
with the business,
she knew he was willing
to run into a burning
building for her.
So, she was willing
to do the same for him.
Kevin, I need you
to let me use
your cell phone.
I need you to trust me.
DONNA: (OVER PHONE)
Harvey Specter's office.
Donna, it's me.
I need your help
and I don't have
much time.
What do you need?
I think I have
a plan to get
Jill to talk.
Mike, shouldn't you be
telling Harvey about this?
I'm calling him next.
But whatever we do,
we are not going to be
able to get her to talk
unless you first
get her to listen.
Hey, Tara.
I know I called
four minutes ago
and I know you
said 7:00 p.m. sharp.
But now, I'm thinking
you said 7:00 p.m. short.
And I don't exactly
know why that
would be. Uh...
But it's 7:12 and I'm
just wondering
what... Hello?
Goddamn it.
Louis, I just saw
you called two times.
I'm so sorry I'm late.
Tara, please,
there's no need
to apologize.
I had them hold
the reservation
for 15 minutes, and it's
only been 13 minutes.
So, I'm sure
it'll be fine.
Thank you, Louis.
The Litt party
is ready.
Awesome-ness,
I'll have a table for you
as soon as one is ready.
As soon as one's ready?
I asked you to hold
our reservation
for 15 minutes and it's
only been 13 minutes,
you hipster douchebag.
Excuse me, sir.
Is everything okay?
No, everything
is not okay.
This asshole
gave away my table.
Hey, man, it's all good.
I'll get you another table.
Hey, man, it's all bad.
I don't want another table.
I want the one I reserved.
So, why don't
you tell those people
that you gave them
something that
belongs to
someone else?
Because I am not
going to share
the most exquisite table
on the planet
with another man.
Louis.
This isn't
going to work.
Louis, Louis, please.
Talk to me.
Look, I know I said
I'd be okay with this,
but I'm not okay.
Because the whole time
I couldn't reach you,
I kept thinking
that you were on
the phone with him
and laughing
with him
and loving him.
And as long as you
have another man,
I'm always going to
think that you're with him
or thinking about him...
Louis, that's not...
Let me finish.
You are the most
riveting woman
I've ever met.
You've cast
a spell on me.
And I would never
tell you how
to live your life.
But I will not
share you with
another man.
And I don't
understand why
any man would.
I want you,
and I want
all of you.
But if I can't
have that...
Louis?
Take me home.
Here, let me
help you with that.
Oh. Would you?
Of course, us redheads
have to stick together.
Thank you.
You're welcome, Jill.
Who are you?
I'm the woman
who tricked you into
going to Danbury.
I have nothing
to say to you.
Please, I came here
in person
because I don't
want to trick you again.
Then say whatever
it is you're here to say.
I'm here to tell you
about my father.
He committed
a crime years ago
and before he did,
he tried to get me
to put my toe in
the water with him.
I said no, but
I almost said yes.
Because I loved him
and I knew he was
a good man.
What do you
want from me?
The same thing that
I wanted the last time.
I want you to visit
your husband
in prison tomorrow,
and I want you
to keep an open mind.
TARA: Louis, I knew
you were passionate,
but I had no idea
how passionate.
That was magic.
Yeah, I take pride
in my work.
Well, you should.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, in that case, there's
another show starting
in about 15 minutes.
Okay. You know
what that means,
don't you?
You're going
to be exhausted,
which means you're going
to have to spend the night.
Well, then, what do
you say we make
the whole day of it, too?
What exactly do
you have in mind?
There's a dress rehearsal
of the Barber of Seville
at the MET tomorrow.
And I could get
us in as patrons.
Louis.
I would love to.
William,
we need to talk.
I'm here, just
like you asked.
They indicted
your daughter.
I know, she told me.
And I told you,
you were playing
a dangerous game
using her to shield you.
Jill's a big girl,
she can take
care of herself.
Take care of herself
or take care of you?
Are you accusing me
of something?
I'm not accusing you,
I'm telling you.
You need to wake
the hell up.
What did you
just say to me?
Do you know what
Cahill's going to do
once Jill is arraigned?
He's going to sit
her down for
as long as it takes
until she cuts a deal
to give you up.
She would never do that.
You have no idea
what she'll do
when they get her
into that room.
And I'm telling you,
if my loser of
a son-in-law didn't cave,
then Jill sure
as hell won't.
Listen to me, goddamn it.
This isn't going to be
what it was like with Kevin.
What do you want
from me, Harvey?
I want you to
give me authorization
to cut you both a deal.
You turn yourself in,
you get maybe three years
and you keep her out.
Why the hell
would I do that?
Because
if she turns on you,
you're going
to be getting
a hell of a lot more.
I'm not cutting a deal.
And you think
if you're willing
to do this to
your own daughter,
she won't be willing
to do it to you?
Jill's a young woman,
I'm an old man.
She does a few years,
it hardly makes a dent.
When she gets out,
she can still play tennis
and go to Pilates
and do all the things
I always gave her
the money to do.
You knew it might
come to this,
didn't you?
WILLIAM: I love my daughter,
Harvey, but she'd be
nothing without me.
And she knows
if she does this for me,
she'll be taken care of
for the rest of her life.
HARVEY: So, that's it.
No deal?
WILLIAM: No deal.
I'm sorry, Jill.
I want to cut a deal.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Can you do that for me?
No, I can't.
Why not?
MIKE: Because he represents
your father.
But I don't.
So, I can.
Tara, I didn't think
today could
get any better.
But whatever you did
to that water pressure,
it is a thing of beauty.
I haven't felt this
fresh and clean since...
Louis, I have
to talk to you.
What is it?
Joshua called, he's coming
to town tomorrow for two days.
But after last night,
I thought it was over
between the two of you.
Louis, we've been
together for years.
I can't just
not see him.
So, you're going
to break up with him?
I don't know.
Welcome
to Danbury, Sean.
You know, you're taking
a big risk that someone's
going to recognize me
and figure out that
you're up to something.
I'd be taking
an even bigger risk
if I didn't hand this
to you personally.
You're not going
to weasel out
of my deal again.
What is this?
That is an iron-clad
agreement
between your office
and Jill Miller.
You're representing
Jill Miller now?
Yes, I am.
Does she know that
you're not a lawyer?
She does.
And she's okay with it
because I'm also
the guy who's keeping
her out of prison.
Let me save you
the trouble of
reading that.
It says that she's
going to testify
against her father,
pleads no contest
and receives
full immunity.
But it also says
that you acknowledge
that I brought her to you.
Hmm.
Well, then, I better
bring it to my office
and sign it.
Oh, and for what
it's worth,
I didn't try to weasel
out of your deal.
I did everything I could
to keep it in place.
Well, now
it's back in place.
Because I just gave you
everything that you need.
No, Mike, you didn't
give me everything yet.
Because what I still need
is William Sutter behind bars.
(KNOCKING)
What the hell
did you do?
Nice to see you,
William.
Can I get you
a drink?
You think
I wouldn't find out
that you recorded me
and played it
for my daughter?
I didn't play it
for her,
I played it for
my other client,
Kevin Miller.
Jill just happened
to be there when I did.
And now,
she's turning on me.
Then I guess it
turns out
she didn't want
to wait five years
to play more tennis
like you thought.
Goddamn it.
You broke
attorney-client
privilege.
I didn't break
anything, William.
Because like
I just told you,
Kevin's my client, too.
And I had an
obligation to share
the facts with him.
So, instead
of attacking me,
you should be
thanking me.
Because I went to
Cahill and cut you
the best deal
you're ever
going to get.
Why would you
do this to me?
You did this
to yourself, William.
You had me represent
both you and Kevin,
which means I had
to choose between
two clients.
And you said it yourself.
You're an old man,
and they're a young couple,
and I chose them over you.
I didn't have you
represent us both.
It was your idea.
I guess it was,
wasn't it?
You son of a bitch.
You set me up.
And I'm going
to make sure
the world knows it.
You can tell the world
anything you want, William.
But you've got no proof
and you'll be telling
it from behind bars.
Either way,
I suggest you
sign this deal.
Because it's the best
you're ever going to get.
Jessica, what are
you doing here?
I had a great time
last night.
And I was going
to call you about
going out again
next week because I know
you want to take it slow.
But then, I found out
that you wanted
to take it slow
because you may
not be here
much longer.
How did you find out?
They called
for a reference.
And what did you
tell them?
I said they'd be lucky
to have you.
Thank you.
Why didn't you
tell me?
Because I wasn't sure
I was going to take it.
But now, you are.
Jessica, if I thought
there would be
a chance in the world
that you would come with me,
I would have asked you.
But we both know
that's not gonna happen.
Because you told me
it's not over yet.
But what you meant
is that it's never
gonna be over.
It's my firm, Jeff.
It's the thing I've spent
my whole life building.
And I'm not
judging you for it.
You are who you are,
and I love who you are.
But I've been thinking
about going back
to Chicago
for a long time now.
And as much as
seeing you again
makes me want
to stay here...
This is something
I have to do.
Like I said,
they're lucky
to have you.
It's done.
Sutter took the deal.
Jill's safe.
Thank God.
I'm, uh,
sorry that Jill had
to hear what she heard.
It was the only way, man.
Besides,
you didn't say it.
No, but I did know
what I was doing
when I agreed
to inform on you.
I'm sorry.
You didn't deserve
any of that.
Hey, look when
we first met,
I let Gallo in here.
And that was as
much a betrayal
as what you did to me.
MIKE: Yeah, but you
didn't know me.
I knew you.
What, are you trying
to make me hate you?
(SNICKERS)
No.
It's just that
I'm getting out
and you're not.
No, I'm not.
But you kept
my wife out of prison.
And as far as
I'm concerned,
that makes us square.
Thank you, Kevin.
Where are you going?
Me?
I'm going to give
you a few minutes
to enjoy the fact
that you're getting out.
And to call
Rachel and tell her.
Hey.
Donna, I'm
onto something.
I just need one second
to write it down.
What is it?
What are you
so happy about?
I think I just
figured out a way
to get Leonard Bailey's
case reopened.
Rachel, that's amazing.
Come on, get your things.
We can talk about
it on the way out,
because we're
going to celebrate.
No, it's good news but
I'm not ready to celebrate.
Yes, you are.
Because I'm not
talking about
your case.
Rachel, Harvey
and Mike did it.
Mike's getting out.
What?
You heard me.
They did it.
Sutter's going away,
which means Mike's
coming home.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
Come on.
Let's go have some fun
while you're still single.
(LAUGHS)
Oh, my...
It's Mike.
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
I know it's you.
It's over,
I'm coming home.
I just heard.
I love you so much.
RACHEL: I love you too.
^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
P® Krishna_Teja P®