(HARVEY READING)
(ON PHONE) Rachel,
it's Professor Dunbar.
I was wondering if you'd be
interested in helping me
with the Innocence Project.
You want me to help you get
an innocent man off death row?
What do you want,
Harvey?
Help me protect Mike Ross.
He's in there
with a guy I put away
and the guy is no joke.
What am I supposed to do?
You're supposed to move
the guy to another prison.
You want me one-on-one,
you got it.
I'm gonna use this
and they're gonna hold you.
No!
What's going on here?
Why did you come back
with the guard?
I didn't do it to
get you to forgive me.
I never should have let him
in here in the first place.
The time you served
while awaiting trial
was never factored
into your sentence.
You're eligible for parole
in six weeks.
You think I don't
know this is your
protector's idea
to get me off your back?
No, Frank.
Harvey's idea
was for me to
tell these guys
that you were an informant.
I figured out a way
to get Mike out early.
What's the catch?
He has to inform
on his roommate.
Mike gets him to turn,
he's free.
When do you need
an answer by?
Yesterday.
And the answer
needs to be yes.
JESSICA:
Harvey, wait a second.
Where are you going?
Where do you think I'm going?
I'm going to see Mike.
And I know
what you're going to say,
but Mike went to prison
so we wouldn't have to,
and now he's in danger
from a guy I put away.
So, you'll forgive me
if I don't stand around
and wait for you
to drop the hammer.
You think I like
the idea of him
rotting in that place?
But if you want
this thing to work,
you can't go running up there
in the middle of the night.
You heard Cahill,
he needs an answer yesterday.
What he needs is results.
And if Mike's lawyer
pulls him out of his cell
in the middle of the night,
then his roommate is going to
sense there's something wrong
before this thing
even gets started.
Fine. But I'm going up there
first thing in the morning,
and nothing you say
is going to stop me.
KEVIN: Can't sleep?
Not really.
Well, as long
as you're up,
you might want to think
about putting up
some pictures of your own.
That way you won't
have to keep staring at mine.
How old are they?
Maddy is seven
and Nate just turned five.
They look really sweet.
Yeah, they're...
They're great.
How often
do you get to see them?
I don't.
What do you mean
you don't?
Bad divorce or something?
Nah, nah. Nothing like that.
We've been married
for 10 years.
I just... I just
don't let them come here.
What? Why not?
They shouldn't see
their father as a criminal.
Kevin. Come on, man.
I know it's hard on them.
It tears me up every
single day that I'm here.
But they're kids.
They're resilient.
Yeah, I wouldn't be so sure.
Well, Mike,
you don't have kids.
So, you don't know.
No, I don't.
But I do know what it's like
to be a kid missing his dad.
Please don't tell me your
old man abandoned the family.
Both my parents died
in a car accident
when I was 11.
Hit by a drunk driver.
Jesus. That's...
I'm sorry, Mike.
Well, it was a long time ago.
Kevin, I understand
the instinct
to protect your children,
but what are you
protecting them from?
What do you mean?
I mean, we've been roommates
for a while now.
Don't you think it's time
you told me
what you're in here for?
(DOOR BUZZING)
GUARD: Hey, Ross.
Your lawyer's here.
Now?
I'm just the messenger.
You want out
of this box or not?
Mr. Bailey,
my name is Rachel Zane.
I am a law student
at Columbia,
and I'm here to talk to you
about your case.
Student?
Yes.
We work alongside
the Innocence Project
to determine if you have
the criteria for an appeal.
Do you know how long
I been sitting on death row?
Twelve years.
I read your file.
And for the last 10 of them
I've been writing letters
and begging any lawyer
to listen to my story.
And they finally get around
to getting back to me,
and they don't
even have the courtesy
of sending me a real lawyer?
Mr. Bailey, trust me,
I will fight for you.
You're a student.
You can't do shit for me.
Well, you know what?
You killed two people
in cold blood.
You know it and I know it,
and that's why
you're in there.
So, thank you
for making the decision
to not take your case
an easy one.
You don't know me.
All you know
is what you've read
in some damn file.
I didn't kill anyone.
I've been saying it
for 12 years
and I can prove it.
You're right.
I don't know you.
And you don't
know me either.
So, do you want
to take a chance
on each other or not?
I need help...
Ms. Zane.
So, let me help you.
Harvey, what are you
doing here?
There's something
I need to talk to you about.
Sit down.
What is it?
I just got a visit
from Sean Cahill.
About Gallo?
I thought you said
he can't get him transferred.
He can't. But it turns out
there's a way
he can get you out.
What do you mean "out"?
I mean out, as in
you walk out that front door
and you never look back.
What's the catch?
Mike.
Harvey, you're not here
telling me
that I can get out
with that look on your face
if there isn't
something else.
He needs you to inform
on your cellmate.
What?
If whatever you get
leads to a conviction
of his father-in-law,
he'll commute your sentence
and you get to walk.
What did the guy do?
Who cares what he did?
I care.
Because if it was so bad,
why didn't Kevin turn on him
in the first place?
Mike, what does it matter?
He can get you out.
This is my
only friend in here.
I'm not going to betray him.
Friend?
Listen to me, God damn it.
There's someone in here
trying to kill you
and I'm giving you a way out.
I'm taking care of Gallo.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
It means that I did
what you told me to do.
I threatened to tell people
that he was an informant.
But what I also did
was find out
a way to get him parole.
Parole? Are you crazy?
He's not going
to get parole.
Who's going
to say he deserves it?
You know what, Harvey?
Instead of coming in here
and telling me
to betray my cellmate
because Gallo
will never get parole,
maybe you should
be helping me
get it for him.
I'm never helping that
piece of shit do anything.
And this isn't about Gallo,
and you know it.
No, it's about you telling me
to turn on the one guy
in here that I trust based
on some plan that Cahill
has that we don't even
know will work.
No, Mike.
It's about giving you
a chance to get your life back
while it still
looks the same.
Now, are you going
to take it or not?
(SINGING) See the money, wanna
stay for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
P® Krishna_Teja P®
Son of a bitch,
it's the prune juice
all over again.
What the...
Hey, douche stick.
Are you responsible
for my mugs being here?
I didn't.
I don't.
(STUTTERS) We didn't have
anything else to use.
I don't give a shit.
Take those things and
put them back where you...
Well, if isn't Louis Shit.
What's happening, boss?
You bastard.
You took my mugs
and you didn't even have
the balls to do it yourself.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
But if something
of yours is in here,
it had nothing
to do with me.
Really? Why don't you ask
the stuttering ass clown?
We needed them for our
(WHISPERING) urine tests.
What did you say?
You peed on my catch phrase?
I don't know what's funnier.
You got a catch phrase
or that we peed on it.
I want those mugs sterilized
and I want them destroyed.
They're your mugs,
you do what you want.
But I'm not touching them
with a 10-foot pole.
You know how much
asparagus Luterman eats?
Later, Chief. (CHUCKLES)
How did it go this morning?
I was petrified.
Death row,
how could you not be?
It was not just that.
When I got there,
it hit me that if I do this,
I have a man's life
in my hands.
Rachel, you can handle it.
I know I can.
Then why do I get
the feeling that something
is bothering you?
Because when
I got back from there,
I was so angry about what
happened to that poor man
that I sat down,
I started working
on this case, and I...
I haven't moved since.
I don't understand.
Why is that bad?
Because it's the first time
since Mike left
that I haven't thought
about him every second.
Listen to me.
That's a good thing.
It doesn't feel like
a good thing.
Rachel, you can't live
your life on pins and needles.
It's not healthy for you.
It's not healthy for Mike.
It's not healthy for anyone.
And forgetting
about him is healthy?
Isn't that why
you took this case?
To give yourself
something to focus on?
Yes, but I just...
Then don't fight it.
If working to free
an innocent man helps you
to forget about Mike
for a while, he would be
the first person
to tell you to do it.
And trust me, if you really
lose yourself in this,
I have a feeling it's going
to seem like a lot less than
two years before he gets out.
LOUIS: Where's Harvey?
Harvey's not here.
Well, get his ass in here,
because he made some goddamn
side deal with those traders
and I want them out.
Louis, I am telling you,
now is not the time.
And I am telling you
that I cannot look
at their smug, stupid faces
for one more day.
Maybe you don't have
to look at them.
What are you talking about?
Louis, did I ever tell you
about my first apartment
in the city?
No.
I was sharing
a 400-square-foot studio
and it was a disaster
until we finally decided
that we had to separate
our spaces for privacy.
Well, this isn't
The Brady Bunch, Donna.
We can't put
a masking tape line down
the center of the office.
I'm not talking
about masking tape, Louis.
I am talking
about hiring an architect
to reconfigure the offices.
(CHUCKLES) You're right.
We can even do
a remodel, which is what
I've been wanting
to do for the last
five years.
And the best part is,
you don't have to deal
with those asshole
traders ever again.
Donna, you're a genius.
I know.
Get me the names of six
architects before lunch.
Louis, you have
your own secretary.
Thanks for nothing.
Why do I even?
Nice of you to show up.
I've been peeling
these potatoes by myself.
Sorry, I, uh, got caught up.
Speaking of which,
how did it go
with your lawyer?
You getting out of here?
What?
I'm just kidding.
What's going on?
Nothing.
It's not important.
Your lawyer shows up
without you knowing about it,
and it's not important?
Come on, do I look like
I was born yesterday?
I just said
it's not important.
And I'm sorry
I left you hanging,
but you wouldn't even have
this job without me.
And I wouldn't even need this
job if it weren't for you.
So, what's your problem?
I'm sorry, Kevin.
I'm...
I'm just not having
a good day.
Hey, it's okay.
Don't sweat it.
All right?
I mean, it's none
of my business anyway.
No, actually,
it is your business.
He came here to tell me
that he tried to get Gallo
transferred, but...
It's not going to happen.
Well, as long as
we stick together,
we can deal
with Gallo anyway, right?
Yeah, that's...
That's what I told Harvey.
Well, next time
you talk to him,
tell him
I said thanks for trying.
How did it go?
He said he had
to think about it.
What? Why?
Because he's an idiot,
that's why.
So, what are you
going to do?
I'm going to figure out how
to buy us some time.
Well, you better do it fast,
because Cahill's
in your office,
and he wants an answer.
Sean.
What did he say?
He said he wants
to see the details in writing.
I'm not in the mood, Harvey.
And I'm not messing around.
Please tell me
you're kidding me.
Oh, come on,
this is bullshit.
You know my word is good.
HARVEY:
Yeah, and I told him that.
And he doesn't want
to risk putting a target
on his back and then find out
commuting his sentence
really means
cutting it in half.
He's not risking anything.
No one's going to find out.
I'm sure that's exactly
what Frank Gallo thought.
So, either put it in writing
or we don't have a deal.
He didn't go for it, did he?
What are you talking about?
Mike being at risk
has nothing to do
with putting
anything in writing.
And you told me
he wouldn't go for it.
So, Harvey,
tell me the truth.
All right, he said no.
But, Sean,
I'm telling you
he'll come around.
He just needs
a couple of days.
Do you know
how many strings I pulled
to put this thing in motion?
What I know is you wouldn't
have pulled anything
if this case
wasn't huge for you.
So, instead of yelling at me
for saying that it's going
to take a couple days,
why don't you just give me
a couple of days?
Okay, Harvey,
the deal's still
on the table.
But if I find a way
to move forward
without his help,
there is no deal,
and he does
the whole two years.
Jessica.
Harvey.
What's going on with Mike?
I gave him Cahill's offer.
And he's thinking about it?
I'm working on it.
Well, in the meantime,
while you were out,
I got a call
from Nathan Byrnes.
He thinks someone's trying
to take over his company.
Why the hell
would he think that?
Because word on the street
is someone's selling off
a block of his stock.
That doesn't make sense.
We bought Sutter's
shares from him.
Those goddamn traders.
No way.
They wouldn't do that
without telling me.
They bought it in good faith.
Well, they're dumping it
in bad faith.
I'll take care of it.
No.
You have your hands
full with Mike.
I can handle this.
Jessica, it was my idea
to involve them.
I should be the one
to take care of it.
I don't care
whose idea it was, Harvey.
You take care of Mike.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
AUTOMATED VOICE:
You have a call from
Danbury Federal Prison.
Do you accept the charges?
Yes, of course.
Mike, is everything okay?
Yeah. Yeah, everything's fine.
I was just thinking
about you.
I was thinking
about you, too.
You were?
Yes.
In fact, I was just
in the middle of a heated
discussion with you about
the best way to handle
a death row appeal.
I don't understand.
I took on
an Innocence Project case
just to have something
to take my mind off
of our troubles.
But I...
I didn't want
to take my mind off of you.
So, I figured I would
just imagine we were working
on it together.
I don't know what to say.
Say you're in.
I mean, that depends
on what strategy
we landed on.
Mike, seriously.
Is there something wrong?
MIKE: No.
I just wanted to make sure
you were doing okay.
And that...
That we were still good.
Now that I have
something to take my mind
off our situation
and connect me
to you at the same time...
Yeah.
We're better than good.
Then can you do me a favor
and transfer me to Donna?
Of course.
Can I ask why?
I only get one phone call
and I'm pretty sure
she had something
to do with the idea
of you imagining us
working together.
So, I just want to thank her.
Okay.
I love you.
MIKE: I love you, too.
(RINGING)
Hello?
RACHEL: Donna,
I have Mike on the phone.
Put him through.
Hello?
MIKE: Donna.
If Harvey's there,
do me a favor.
Keep your voice down,
and don't tell him it's me.
Mike, what's going on?
I'm not taking
the deal, Donna.
Are you crazy?
It's not that simple.
What's not simple about it?
Harvey said that if you...
I don't care what Harvey said.
Because what he didn't say
is that if I do what he wants
and someone finds out,
then I may never get back
to Rachel at all.
Harvey would never
let them find out.
Donna, look, I called you
so that I didn't have to have
this argument with him.
Now, I don't have much time.
Are you going
to do this for me or not?
I'll tell him.
Then I also need you
to tell him
something else for me.
If he comes here
to try to change my mind,
I'm not going to see him.
(MIKE HANGS UP)
You mind telling me
who the hell said
you can dump Nathan Byrnes'
stock without talking to us?
I don't know what you're
talking about.
Who's Nathan Byrnes?
CEO of Exodyne.
Oh, that Nathan Byrnes.
In that case,
I said I could sell
that stock because I own it.
Just like I own this one
and this one and this one.
Hey, look at that.
My Neubacher Capital
position's going
through the roof.
That's not the deal you made
with Harvey, and you know it.
Welcome to the big bad
world of Wall Street.
Now, do you want something
or can I get back to work?
Oh, I want something.
You're going to unwind
that sale and buy
those shares back.
At a premium?
Not going to happen.
I'm your landlord.
And the fact you had
to lease
to me means you don't have
much of an operation.
You listen to me,
you little piss-ant.
You don't know
who you're messing with.
Then why don't I find out?
Over dinner.
You've got to be
kidding me.
You want me to have dinner
with you in exchange
for backing off that trade?
I think of it as you get
to have dinner with me
and I choose to back off
that trade
because I am a stand-up guy.
Well, let me let you in
on a little something,
there, Stu.
I don't share dinner staring
down the barrel of a shotgun.
So, why don't you
unwind that trade
and then ask me out?
And then we'll see if you're
as charming as you like
to think you are.
You know what?
I am charming.
But I'm not an idiot
and I'm not unwinding
my trade without getting
something in return.
Harvey, I need to talk
to you about something
and you're
not going to like it.
About what?
That was Mike
on the phone before.
Why didn't you get me?
He's not taking
the deal, Harvey.
The hell he isn't.
Where are you going?
To that prison.
Harvey, the reason
he called me and not you
is because he knew you
wouldn't take no for answer.
And I'm not going to.
Which is why he said
if you show up there,
he's not going
to leave his cell.
Then get me Rachel.
No, no. Harvey,
you cannot tell her.
Like hell I can't.
She's the only one
who can convince him.
If you tell her that
Mike's not taking a deal
that can get him out,
it will tear her apart.
And if I don't tell her,
he's going to be in there
for two more years.
Is that what she wants?
That's between them.
That's why I want to
tell her.
She'll make it between them.
Harvey.
God damn it.
He plays Checkers
with this guy
and thinks
he owes him his life.
No, that's not fair
and you know it.
Because Mike's loyalty
is the reason
you're not in prison.
That's what's
killing me, Donna.
Don't you understand?
He's in there instead of me
with a guy I put away.
And I can't just sit here
doing nothing
when he has a chance
to get out.
Which is why you have
to think of something else.
Because if you tell Rachel
about this,
the life that's waiting
for Mike when he gets out,
it isn't going to be there.
Harvey.
I'm surprised
to see you here so soon.
I didn't think you'd
turn him this fast.
I need more time.
I don't think you understand.
I'm being pressured to move
to another investigation.
You've got 24 hours
to change his mind
or this thing is done.
Then I need you
to do something for me.
I am doing something for you.
I'm getting Mike
out of prison.
Well, you need
to do something else for me
or that's never
going to happen.
What are you talking about?
I need you to get
into a room with him
because he won't listen
to what I have to say.
What exactly
do you want me to tell him
that you haven't already?
Sean, Mike's a bleeding heart.
You need to make
the case directly to him.
He needs to see
the victims of whatever
the hell this guy did.
That's a swell idea, Harvey.
But if I go into that prison
and someone sees me,
not only are we dead
in the water,
but Mike's life
isn't worth shit.
You think I don't know that?
What the hell do you think
I'm doing here?
What are you talking about?
I have a plan,
but you're
not going to like it.
Why not?
Because I need you
to pull another string
and I need you to do it
before Frank Gallo tries
something else with Mike.
All right, fake lawyer.
Let's see what you got.
You're going to let me look
into it for you?
Look into it, shit.
You're going to get me
out of here like you promised.
I never promised.
I said there was an excellent
chance you could get...
Six weeks, brother.
I'll be counting the days.
I'll file the motion
first thing in the morning.
There you go.
That's what
I'm talking about.
And if I find out you're
screwing me on any level,
you better hole up in some
dark corner of this prison
and pray to God
I don't find your ass.
What was that all about?
Looks like he took me up
on my offer after all.
God damn it, Gretchen,
where the hell is she?
Where the hell is who?
That architect
you were supposed to call.
She's not supposed to be here
for another half hour.
And if I want
someone's business,
I show up a half hour
early at the latest.
And what exactly
are you looking
to have me do
about your little conundrum?
I want you to give her
a call and tell her
if she doesn't have
the goddamn common courtesy
to show up early,
then she might as well
not show up at all.
Mr. Litt.
Ah...
Yes.
I'm Tara Messer.
I'm here to discuss
your remodel needs.
My needs?
GRETCHEN: Well, I'm sorry,
Ms. Was Going To Be
Our Architect,
we no longer need
your services.
Gretchen, calm down.
You are overreacting
like a crazy woman.
You're hired.
I am?
Oh, yeah.
You're right for the job.
I can feel it.
Oh, you can feel something,
all right.
Then why don't we start
with what you're
looking for in the space?
Oh, the space.
Right, the space.
Exactly. What I'm looking for
are clear, yet unobtrusive
boundaries between
our offices and the tenants'.
But it needs to be elegant
and organic or we might
as well not do it at all.
I understand.
Like the perfect aria
leading seamlessly
to its inevitable cadenza.
You're an opera lover.
Second only to the ballet.
Then I suggest
we start with a marriage.
I mean, a tour.
Excuse me.
Professor Dunbar.
Do you have a moment?
This is the faculty lounge,
Ms. Zane.
You're not supposed
to be in here.
I understand that.
And I'm sorry.
It's just,
this is important
and you weren't
in your office.
What can I do for you?
I met with Leonard Bailey
yesterday.
He's the inmate on death...
I know who he is.
Is there a problem?
Yes, there is.
He's rotting on death row
for a crime
that he didn't commit.
So, you met with him
for 10 minutes
and you're ready
to release him.
No, what I'm saying is...
You're a second-year
law student, Rachel.
I asked you to be a part
of this because you're
one of my brightest students,
but I also asked you
in particular
because I didn't think
you'd be so naive.
Excuse me?
Your job wasn't to talk
to Mr. Bailey once and,
after being moved
by his tale of woe,
tell me to jump him
to the top of the pile.
It was to assess his case
and present evidence.
And that's exactly
what I'm doing here.
I just left two boxes
of textbook
prosecutorial misconduct
with your secretary.
You found
all of that since yesterday.
Yes. Because while
I may only
be a second-year law student,
I have been a practicing
paralegal for the past
eight years.
Looks like I have
some reading to do.
I'm sorry
for interrupting your day.
Good afternoon, Ms. Zane.
Good afternoon, Professor.
And then we use
the glass motif
you already have
to partition their space
from yours starting
at that wall over there.
And no one ever knows
they're two separate entities.
And if we use
the frosted glass,
you'll never even have
to lay eyes on them.
Well, there's just
one more thing.
You want to know
if I can design another
bullpen area
for your side.
After all, it's the heart
and soul of the space.
You get that?
It's my job to get that.
I don't understand.
To me, architecture isn't
just about design.
It's... It's about
connecting with my clients
on an intimate level.
Well, you're very good at it.
You know, it's too bad
you already sublet
to someone else.
We're looking
to expand ourselves.
This space
would have been perfect.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
In fact, it's so perfect,
I would have made you
an offer on the spot.
Anyway, I'll have some plans
drawn up as soon as I can.
We need to get rid
of those traders.
Excuse me?
I don't care
what kind of deal you
and Harvey cut with them.
We need to get rid of them
and we need to do it now.
Well, Louis,
I'm not going to do that.
Because whoever
we replace them with,
this conversation
is just going
to happen again.
Because we both know
that you're out of your mind.
It's not going
to happen again.
Because
in this particular case,
I am not out of my mind.
Why do you
want me to do this?
Because I'm in love
with an architect.
Let me get this straight.
You want me to further
antagonize people
that I'm already
fighting with
because you don't have
the balls to ask
a woman out on a date.
That's one way
of looking at it.
No, there's another way.
The answer is no.
Okay, fine.
I'll just stick
to the original plan
of having her completely
redesign our space.
And I'll just make sure
it takes long enough
for her to fall madly
in love with me.
And it shouldn't take
more than two or three years.
Louis, I want you
to look at me
when I say this.
If you hire this woman
to do anything relating
to this firm's space,
I will personally
throw you off the roof
of this building.
Is that clear?
So, you'll think about it?
Get out.
Yo.
(IN AUSTRIAN ACCENT) Ahnold.
Come on.
Let's see what you got.
I didn't know you played.
Played?
Shit. I set
the P.S. 92 single game
scoring record.
P.S. 92 is
an elementary school,
my friend.
Yeah, sixth grade.
I dominated.
KEVIN: I thought you had
to file that motion
for Gallo's parole.
MIKE: I did.
Already?
It was an 18-page
sentencing amendment.
I could do that in my sleep.
I should get you
to do some work for me.
Why? You need some?
No, but if I did,
I'd probably get myself
a lawyer who didn't sleep
in a prison.
(CLEARS THROAT)
You all right?
I don't...
I don't know.
What do you mean,
you don't know?
(COUGHS)
What is it, your stomach?
Oh, my God.
Something's not right.
Take a deep breath.
Put your head down.
Oh, God. I can't.
That's not going
to do anything.
I think...
Oh, my God, I think
somebody did something to me.
Hey, can I get
some help over here?
Guard! Mike, talk to me.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
It's Gallo.
Gallo must have put
something in my...
Somebody do something!
Guard!
Call Harvey.
Mike.
Mike!
Where is he?
If I knew who
you were talking about,
maybe I could...
Mike Ross.
I need to see him right now.
And who are you?
Harvey Specter.
I'm his attorney.
Mr. Ross
is in the infirmary,
but you can't
see him in there.
Then get me the warden.
I don't appreciate
being pushed around,
Mr. Specter.
I don't care.
I want everyone
to know what
happened here today.
They saw what happened.
Yeah, there's a difference
between seeing and knowing.
Are you Kevin Miller?
Who are you?
Harvey Specter.
I'm Mike Ross' lawyer.
Look, I already told
the warden I didn't see
anyone touch his food.
Did you see Frank Gallo
with him?
Did you or didn't you?
Are you trying
to get me killed, man?
Did he touch
his food or not?
Yeah, he did,
last night at dinner.
But Mike offered
to get Gallo parole
and Gallo took him up on it,
so why would he poison him?
Because he didn't really
take Mike up on that offer,
he just did it
to get close to him.
Or he did it to give Mike
a taste of what happens
if he doesn't come through.
Either way,
you stay the hell away
from that son of a bitch.
All right, that's enough.
Let's go.
GALLO: Hey, Counselor.
I heard your boy had
a little tummy ache
out in the yard.
You piece of shit.
You goddamn poisoned him.
Guards, get him out of here.
I didn't do shit.
Why don't you come over here
and say that to my face?
You think I won't?
God damn it.
I said get him back
to his cell!
Hey. This wasn't
part of the deal.
We talked about
you seeing his roommate,
not rushing Frank Gallo.
Yeah, well, my guy's lying
unconscious in the infirmary.
So, sue me.
How did you know Gallo
would take the bait?
Because he's an animal.
And animals always
take the bait.
Well, I'll give you credit
for knowing how
it would go down.
I don't need credit.
I need to know
where Mike Ross is.
Where I was instructed
to put him.
Let me tell you something,
Mr. Specter.
I don't know you.
So, in case you're thinking
of trying anything,
that kid has
a monitor on his leg.
And if it goes dark
for even one second,
I'm going to make sure
that you end up
in a cell here with him.
It's not going to go dark
and he'll be back here
when I said he would.
Then, after that,
I'm going to make sure
he gets out of here. For good.
HARVEY:
How are you feeling?
What's going on?
Where am I?
You're in the back of my car.
You were drugged.
By Gallo.
By me.
What?
Cahill got the warden
and the prison doctor
to put something
in your food.
They're the only ones
who know what's going on.
What the hell
are you talking about?
We needed to change your mind
about taking this deal.
And we couldn't do it
as long as you're in there.
Jesus Christ.
So, you drugged me?
We needed a cover for why
you're not in your cell,
and this was
the only way to do it.
Are you insane?
You broke me out of prison?
I didn't break you
out of anywhere.
Cahill sanctioned it.
And if anyone's insane,
it's you.
Because you're the one
turning down a chance
to get out of that place.
But we don't have time
to talk about that right now.
Cahill's waiting for us.
You got me out
to see Cahill?
I said he's waiting.
I didn't say that's
where I'm taking you.
Well, then, where the hell
are you taking me?
You think me spending
a couple of hours with Rachel
is going
to change my mind?
If it doesn't,
there's something
wrong with you.
So, are you going
to yell at me
or are you going to take
the only chance
you're going to get
to be alone
with the woman you love
for the next two years?
Please tell me
that you did not tell her
about Cahill's offer.
HARVEY: Oh, I wanted to.
But you have Donna to thank
for the fact that I didn't.
What am I supposed
to tell Rachel about
why I'm here?
If it were me,
I'd tell her the truth.
Now, since you
don't want to do that...
You're lucky
I came up with something else.
Wait till it hits 30
and then sell it.
Well, look who it is.
You change your mind
about my offer?
I'm not there just yet.
But I did come to apologize.
I didn't mean
to be so combative before.
You're a proud woman.
I understand. Bygones.
You know, your operation here
is kind of impressive.
You mind if I, uh,
look at one?
You can take
a look at anything
of mine you want.
(CHUCKLES)
Huh. Now, what does
that line right there mean?
What the hell? That's my
Neubacher Capital position.
Well, it seems
to be falling
very quickly.
Is that a good thing?
You did this.
I'm not sure what you mean.
All I did this afternoon
was call my friend
at Jacobson Kearney
and have them issue
a press release about their
client's merger negotiations.
I mean, how was I supposed
to know that it would make
your Neubacher position
fall through the floor?
You used the information
I gave you yesterday
about my holdings,
that's how.
That's inside information
and I can prove it.
No, it could have been
if your attorney hadn't
filed your position
with the SEC
10 days earlier
than he had to.
I'm not going to forget this.
Good. Because my operation's
been around a hell
of a lot longer than yours.
And we can be friends
or we can be enemies.
But you mess with me again
and I'll not only
kick you out
of these offices,
I'll put you in the ground.
Rachel.
Oh, my God.
How?
Harvey.
Oh. I don't understand.
I know you know
about Frank Gallo.
But what you don't know
is that they put me
in solitary confinement
for 36 hours.
Oh, my God.
It's okay. I was safe.
Then Harvey made them watch
the video, which showed
that I was only
defending myself.
Turns out they were more
than happy to trade six hours
and an ankle bracelet
to avoid a lawsuit.
We only have six hours?
Yeah. And I don't want
to waste any of it.
Mr. Litt. What are you...
Oh, please, call me Louis.
What can
I do for you, Louis?
Tara, I'm afraid
I have some bad news.
We're not going
to be moving forward
with the renovations
after all.
I'm sorry to hear that.
No, it has nothing
to do with you.
And of course I will
pay you out of my own pocket
for any of the work
you've already done.
That won't be necessary.
Please, Tara, I insist.
In that case,
I might as well
at least show you
what I had in mind.
As you can see,
these are just
rough drawings.
Not to me.
Here's the frosted glass wall
curving in an elegant "S"
that separates the space.
It's beautiful.
That's not even
the best part.
Because I know how important
the new bullpen is to you,
I modeled it after
the Kimmel Center
in Philadelphia,
and I enclosed
the entire space.
In mahogany.
(EXHALES)
It would
have been exquisite.
But some things
weren't meant to be.
Yeah.
How would you feel
about renovating
my summer house
in the Hamptons?
I appreciate
the thought, Louis,
but I don't do
residential work.
It's not residential.
I use it as a home office.
But it would be so small.
Oh, no,
I want the entire house
to be a satellite
division of the firm.
Are you sure?
I've never been as sure
of anything in my entire life.
Then I look forward
to working with you, Louis.
Sean, what can I do for you?
Where the hell are they?
What?
I've been sitting
in my office
for two hours
waiting for them.
Where the hell are they?
I don't know.
Maybe they're
caught in traffic.
Listen to me.
I can contact the prison
and find out exactly
where they are.
But I do that,
it starts a tornado
of shit with your boss
in the eye of the storm.
So, you're going
to tell me right now
what the hell they're up to.
He's waiting for Mike
outside of his apartment.
Waiting for him to do what?
He's with Rachel.
You've got to be kidding me.
I didn't pull in every favor
I have
so Mike Ross
could have some
conjugal visit.
No, you pulled in every favor
you had so that Harvey
could convince Mike
to do what you wanted.
And this is going
to make that happen.
By getting him laid?
By reminding him
of what he's missing out on
if he doesn't
take your deal.
That wasn't the plan.
Where are you going?
I'm going to go down there
and do what we said
we were going to do.
I'm going to show Mike
the innocent people
that lost everything
because of that bastard.
Sean, please.
If you do that,
Rachel will find out
about everything
and that can't happen.
Why not?
Because Mike chose prison
over her once.
And if he does it again,
she'll never forgive him.
Mike's problem, not mine.
No, that's Harvey's problem.
He promised Mike
he wouldn't tell her,
and Harvey's
a man of his word.
If he were a man of his word,
he would be here right now.
So, what are you going to do?
I'm going to do what should
have been done
in the first place.
I'm going to tell
Mike's fiancée
that he has
a chance to get out
but he doesn't want
to take it.
You want to tell me
what that was all about?
Harvey and Cahill got Mike
out of prison to convince him
to take the deal.
And Harvey brought Mike
to Rachel instead of to Sean.
He broke Mike
out of prison.
Is he crazy?
It sounded crazy
to me at first, too.
But Harvey's living
with the guilt
of putting Mike
in there and Cahill
was willing to do it.
So, can you blame him?
No, I can't.
But I want to know how
this whole thing shakes out.
And I want to know tonight.
(GASPS)
Shh.
What time is it?
We still have time.
Oh, my God.
Oh, I fell asleep.
You did.
Why didn't you wake me?
Because you looked
so peaceful.
Rachel, come on.
I don't want us
to waste any...
We're not wasting anything.
Mike, I don't know
how well you sleep in there.
So, to be able
to give you this...
Thank you.
Can I cook you something?
I'll make you
anything you want.
No, I just
want us to lie here
and stare at each other
and not say anything.
Oh, God.
You're so beautiful.
I thought
you wanted us to be quiet.
Well, I couldn't help it.
You know, you always tell me
how beautiful I am.
You never give me a chance
to tell you how handsome
I think you are.
I thought you loved me
for my mind.
I do.
But that doesn't mean
that I don't also think
you're handsome.
Mike, what's going on?
There's something
I need to tell you.
Does it have something
to do with why
you're really here?
Because I didn't believe
what you told me earlier.
Why didn't
you say something?
Because you're here.
So, I didn't care.
What's that?
I'm unwinding
my position
with Nathan Byrnes' company.
Well, I appreciate that.
But I don't need
to take home
the paper trail.
It's not a paper trail.
It's an engagement letter.
Turns out my attorney
was filing my positions
before he had to,
so I let him go.
You want me
to take you as a client.
If you'll have me.
On one condition.
I hear
you've been having fun
with Louis Litt.
But it stops now.
Done.
I should have known a guy
who would hire a fraud
like that would pull
a stunt like this.
This stunt
is going to get you
exactly what you want.
No, Harvey.
I'm going to get what I want
by telling
that kid's fiancée
the truth and letting her
do the work for me.
Listen to me, Sean.
She doesn't know
because he doesn't
want her to know.
I don't give
a shit what he wants.
Then trust me.
This is the only way
to get what you want.
Trust you?
You lied to my face.
I made a judgment call.
Then look me in the eye
and tell me you didn't make
that call
before you asked me
to get him out.
I knew it.
The whole time,
you were always going
to bring him here.
Because this
is the way to get it done.
Then why didn't you tell me
that in the first place?
Because it would have
ended up
with you wanting
to use Rachel.
It ended there anyway. Now,
get the hell out of my way.
Don't make me
stop you, Sean.
Are you threatening
a federal prosecutor, Harvey?
You're goddamn right I am.
Well, you better think
about this move more than you
thought about the last one.
Because it's not going
to end well for you.
As far as I'm concerned,
it's the same move.
I made a promise
and I'm not going
to break it.
MIKE: Harvey.
Whatever you're
fighting about, you can stop.
I told Rachel everything.
I'm taking the deal.
Then let's get in the car
and get moving.
^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
P® Krishna_Teja P®