This isn't Westworld.
I can't make her human.
I'm just asking you to give
her a little compassion.
Well, I don't know
how to do that.
I just got off the phone with Carly
Donahue. She fired us, Donna.
This isn't your fault.
You couldn't have known.
It's okay.
I just need to go home.
You filed a complaint alleging
life-threatening health problems
and I want to help you get the
compensation that you deserve.
Even if I wanted to sue
those bastards, I can't.
We can shatter those NDAs.
What do I have to do?
I want to know if you're using this
case to get back to Pearson Specter.
You said Pearson Specter
would never take on a case like
this when you were there before.
We brought the suit so that
I could get into the Bar.
One hundred million. With an
admission of guilt. Sure.
Where do I sign?
I'm willing to cut
your clients a check
that will change their lives and
you're too stupid to see it.
Are you ready to take
responsibility or not?
You think I won't go after you for
stealing from Seidel's company?
I don't give a shit
about his marriage.
The reason he hasn't come forward has
nothing to do with his marriage.
You didn't have to keep this
quiet because you're married.
You kept it quiet
because you're in on it.
My employees are gonna lose
their jobs because of me.
We need to keep
this suit going.
You're not just getting
Mike an interview,
you're going to block anyone
who tries to vote no.
See you at the Bar.
Mr. Stamos.
What are you
doing here?
I wanted to, um, get you the
authorization to our medical records.
Thanks.
But, uh, you didn't come
all the way down here
just to hand me
some paperwork.
You're right.
I came to find out what's
going on with our case.
We should hear
something soon.
How can you know that?
Because Harvey's negotiating
with James Palmer as we speak.
What do you mean?
Why is Harvey Specter
negotiating this?
I told you
when we took him on,
he's the best negotiator
in the city.
I don't care who he is.
You're the one that came to me.
You're the one I trusted.
I know that.
But we've got a good cop/bad cop
strategy to get the offer up.
An offer? You didn't tell
me there's an offer.
That's because things have been...
How much?
The number on the table
is a hundred,
but we're hoping
to get a lot more.
Jesus Christ.
A hundred million?
Take it.
I know it seems like a lot of money.
It is a lot of money.
Not when you have to split it
between 150 men who have cancer.
Do all the math
you want, Mr. Ross,
but a hundred million is a hell
of a lot better than zero,
which is what we've been
walking around with.
Mr. Stamos,
you have to trust me.
We know what we're doing, and I
am not going to let you down.
Fine.
You do your
good cop/bad cop thing.
But if that number doesn't go
up in the next two days,
I'm telling my guys to take the
offer that's on the table.
Benjamin.
The Donna is ready. What
do you mean she's ready?
I mean, five minutes ago,
she expressed empathy to me.
But it wasn't working before. I
was convinced it never would.
I don't know what you did, but you
said it could learn from itself,
and that's exactly
what happened.
Oh, my God, maybe
I really am a genius.
Yeah, maybe you are.
Well, then, it's a good thing
I didn't throw this away.
What's this? I've compiled
a list of everybody
who's invested in products like
this in the last five years.
That's great, but we're
not going to need this.
Why not?
Because the thing that makes
The Donna special is me.
Which means we need to look
into investors who know me.
Yes. Correct.
And nobody knows you
better than Harvey.
Do you think he'll make
calls on our behalf?
He would, but I'm not going
to ask him to do that.
Because I want his clients to see
this as coming from me and not him.
Then what's the next step?
The next step for you is get
ready to present that thing,
because I'm going
to get us some meetings.
Boom-shaka-laka.
Do you have any idea
what time it is? I do.
But it couldn't wait.
Where's Rachel?
She's at her parents' house.
Why?
Because I have some news, and
she's going to want to hear it.
What is it?
We got it. You're in.
You're going to be a lawyer.
What? How?
Seidel was in on it.
He got paid.
And I got proof.
Which means we don't have to worry about
tanking Velocity's stock anymore.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe it.
I'm going to be a lawyer.
I know.
There's just one thing.
Palmer figured out that we're
doing this with Seidel.
And unless
we drop the lawsuit,
he's going to come
after us for collusion.
Wait. What?
No, this is bullshit.
I'm not giving up on those miners.
You have to.
No, I don't.
Mike... Look, the only
thing we did wrong
was make a deal
to get me into the Bar.
If I pull out of that hearing,
Palmer can't touch us.
Are you...
Think about
what you're saying.
I don't need
to think about it.
I'm not throwing
those guys under the bus.
Mike, we've come too far.
I don't care.
Tell Seidel
the deal's off.
What if there was another way?
Harvey,
if you're talking about somebody
else handling this case...
No, I'm not.
Listen to me.
There's no way Seidel
came up with the idea
to sell that shit
to Velocity himself.
The woman he had an affair
with has to work for them,
which means we can leverage
her to sink Palmer.
Are you kidding me?
No. I'm...
Harvey, listen to yourself.
You're talking about out-and-out
extortion and blackmail.
I'm not going to do
any of that shit
just to get
into the goddamn Bar.
You were the one that told me that
after watching that kid lose,
you never wanted it
to happen again.
And now,
that same kid is telling us
that what we're doing
is wrong.
And he's right.
Mike...
No, Harvey, it's enough.
You promised Rachel that you'd pull
the plug if things got too risky.
Well, it just got
too goddamn risky.
See the money,
wanna stay for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
P® Krishna_Teja P®
Hey.
What's going on?
You got out of bed
before it was light out
and you never came back.
I want to talk to you
for a minute.
About what?
I know you went to Harvey and you
made him promise to pull the plug
on my getting into the Bar
if things got too risky.
He wasn't
supposed to tell you that.
You really think
he wouldn't?
Mike, I only made him promise
because I care about you.
It's okay.
I know why you did it.
And I understand it.
And last night, I ended up
pulling the plug myself.
So, it's over?
It's over.
I'm not going
to be a lawyer.
Mike...
The thing is,
I was fine with it
until Harvey started dangling
it in front of my face.
I think the problem was, I actually
started believing it could happen.
Do you want me
to stay with you today?
No.
I'll be okay.
Besides,
you've got
a lot of work to do
and I've got
a big case to win.
Harvey, there you are.
Louis needs to see you
right away.
Donna, whatever it is, I
don't have time right now.
Well, you need
to make time.
Because he came looking for you
last night and he's upset.
Well, I'm sorry,
Donna.
But I'm too busy to hear about
another crisis with his girlfriend
or drama in his canasta club, or
how his mouth guard doesn't fit.
Couture Apparel fired us. What?
Carly got upset that Louis brought Rachel
and Katrina to the meeting instead of you.
And when he stood up to her
about it, she fired him.
Shit.
Harvey, he feels terrible about it.
He thinks he let you down.
Well, he didn't.
I let him down.
And it turns out
it was all for nothing.
What do you mean, nothing?
What happened?
Palmer figured out
what's going on with Seidel
and Mike would rather pull
his deal than drop the case.
But then he'll never
get into the Bar.
Why do you think I said I don't have
time for anything else right now?
So, you're telling me that
asshole's holding all the cards
and Mike's never
going to be a lawyer?
No.
No one's ever
holding all the cards.
And I don't give a shit
what Mike said.
I'm not folding
when I know we can win.
Louis, before you say anything,
Donna told me what happened.
Harvey, I am so sorry.
I know you are.
But I didn't come here
to scold you.
I came here
because I need your help
or Mike's deal's
gonna fall apart.
What?
How's that possible?
Let's just say,
someone's got leverage on us
and I need to get
leverage on them.
What kind of leverage?
There's a woman who works at Velocity.
She had an affair with Seidel.
I need to know
who she is.
Thousands of people
work at Velocity.
Yeah, I know that.
But to do what she did,
she'd have to be
a top corporate officer.
Well, that narrows it down, but
it's still going to require
huge amounts of research
and hundreds of phone calls.
No, Louis. It will only
require one phone call.
Because what I need
is access to their database.
No.
Harvey, there's got
to be someone else.
Vanessa doesn't do this kind
of thing and you know it.
I swore that I would never do business
with that son of a bitch again.
I know that, Louis,
but if we don't do this...
All right, get out.
Close the door
behind you.
Oliver.
What's up?
What's up is,
we've got work to do.
Mike, I don't mean
to be an asshole,
but I'm not doing anything until you
tell Nathan exactly what's going on.
There's nothing to tell.
Are you kidding me?
You said you were doing this case
as a way to get into the Bar.
And I just
withdrew my application.
There's no deal anymore.
So, whatever it was
I was going to tell Nathan,
I don't have
to tell him anymore.
Just like that, you're
giving up your chance?
Look, I heard what you said last
night about setting an example.
So, instead of telling Nathan
that I was up to something shady,
I'm telling you
that I'm not.
What do you need me
to do?
I need you
to get down to PSL
and grab half a dozen of those
associates and bring them back here.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to do whatever I can to
make sure this thing isn't over yet.
Screw those assholes.
They're nothing but a
bunch of dickless losers.
Yeah, I'll break them into little
pieces for you. You have my word on it.
All right,
I've got to go.
I love you, too, Mommy.
Stu.
Donna.
Got to say, I didn't figure you for
a guy who calls his mother "Mommy."
What can I say? If a man doesn't
have the confidence to do that,
then he's not
really a man.
But I'm guessing you didn't
come all the way down here
just to evaluate my relationship
with the greatest woman on Earth.
No, I didn't. I came
here to show you this.
What's that?
It's a game-changer.
And I'm letting you in
on the ground floor.
That's a bold statement.
Turn it on. Keep it for
as long as you want.
And then, when you're blown away,
come back to me with an offer.
Because my partner and I,
we're going wide with this
and we're going
to need an investor.
Why are you coming to me
with this?
Because I wanted to give someone the
chance to take it off the market.
And it needed to be someone with the
confidence to call his mother "Mommy."
It's typical you would
have us meet you here.
Gambling's for suckers,
you know.
It's only gambling
when the results are unknown.
There's nothing wrong with
tilting the game in your favor.
I like this guy, Louis.
Why haven't I met him before?
You know why. So, why
don't we just get to it?
We need you to hack into Velocity
Data's personnel records.
Now, can you do it or not?
You want to say that
a little bit louder,
so the Fed over there
can hear it?
Relax, Jerry. What Louis
is trying to say is,
there's a woman
who works there
who has information we need
to make a deal.
Make a deal?
I don't know.
That... That's starting
to sound like blackmail,
which is a little bit
out of my league.
Bullshit.
It's in your league.
And it's starting to sound like you're
renegotiating, like you always do.
You know what, Louis?
I've just about had enough of
your bullshit over the years.
I renegotiate
because you low-ball me.
I... I told...
Jerry, you're not dealing
with Louis on this one.
You're dealing with me.
So, why don't you tell me what you
need and let's get this thing done?
If I'm going
to access anything,
I need to know
more than you just told me.
Because I don't get
what you want,
there's no going back
a second time.
All right. There's a woman
who works at Velocity
who slept with the in-house
counsel at my client's company
and convinced him to sell
confidential information.
Let me guess.
She promised him the moon,
then hung him out to dry.
Yeah. Why?
You don't need to access Velocity's
records. She doesn't work there.
How do you know?
Because I know who she is.
And the price just tripled.
Tripled?
You hypocritical
piece of shit.
You don't even have
to access anything.
Well, you know
what they say.
You don't pay the plumber
for banging on the pipes...
You pay him
for knowing where to bang.
Yahtzee.
And I'm telling you,
where I'm banging,
a whole lot of shit's
going to fall out.
So, you're either going
to pay up or you're not.
Am I interrupting?
To tell you the truth,
I've just been
staring at this screen
for the past 15 minutes.
That's what I do all day.
I call it working.
But I'm going to guess
that's not why you're staring.
I was thinking about Mike.
He told you
he gave up the deal?
He did,
and he said that he's okay
not being a lawyer.
But the look on his face
didn't say that at all.
Then you might be interested
in what I have to say.
Because it involves getting
Mike into the Bar after all.
Harvey, why are you telling
me this instead of Mike?
Because you asked me to pull
the plug on this whole thing
if it got too risky,
and what I'm talking about is going
to make it a hell of a lot riskier.
And what did Mike say?
He doesn't want to do it.
Why not?
You know why not.
It's not 100% legal.
And you can say no
if you want to.
But the look you saw
on his face?
That's not going away
any time soon.
Okay.
I'm in.
But this time, if something
goes wrong, you take the fall.
Okay, I will.
Now, are you going to go back
to staring at that thing
or you want to help me
get Mike into the Bar
and have some fun
at the same time?
What do you need me to do?
I need you to go home,
put on something
a hell of a lot nicer,
and meet me at this
address in an hour.
Hi.
Hey, sweetie.
I'll be done in a few minutes.
How was your day?
Fine.
Louis, we talked about this.
You can share
your day with me.
I'm here to cheer you up.
It's not that.
It's just that, sometimes,
I have to do some less than great
things with less than great people
and I'd rather just wash the
memories from my brain.
What do you mean,
less than great things?
Nothing. It's not
that big of a deal.
Are you talking about
hurting an innocent person?
No, of course not.
Then, how bad can it be?
Well, it's not
that bad at all, Tara.
As a matter of fact,
I'm doing it all to help
someone I care deeply about.
And sometimes to do good, you've
got to get a little dirty.
Well, then, maybe you can take me
home and get a little dirty with me.
Sweetie, I want to,
but I'm just not in the mood.
Are you sure this isn't something
you want to share with me?
Yes, I'm sure.
Okay.
But I want you to know
you can tell me anything.
Tara, I'm sorry, but I'm going
to have to meet you at home.
What is it?
Nothing. I just have
to go see Harvey, okay?
Okay.
Louis, I've got about two minutes.
I'm going to meet Rachel.
Well, take two minutes
to look at this.
What is it? It's a letter
from Allen Fields.
Shit.
He's putting us in review
based on our recent affiliations.
You know what that means.
Yeah, I sure as hell do.
Well, then, you should know that I
just got 10 more from 10 other clients
and they all say
the same thing.
That son of a bitch.
Louis, I am not
going to be bullied.
No, I don't care
what you're going to be.
Now, we lost Couture Apparel because
you were too busy with Mike.
This is the same exact thing
in different clothes.
Louis. Harvey, I just had
to lie to the woman I love
because I didn't want to admit
the whole truth about Mike.
Now, I'm willing to go with
the Hail Mary of using Jerry.
But what I am not willing
to do is risk our survival.
Louis.
Harvey, that is enough.
You know what needs to be done.
Do it or I will.
Mr. Palmer.
I take it you didn't
get the memo.
This case is over.
That's because
it's not.
What the hell is this?
That's a copy of my letter
to the New York Bar
removing myself
from consideration.
No interview, no application,
no quid pro quo.
Which means this case
is far from over.
You have got to be
kidding me.
You're going to give up
your chance to be a lawyer
for some miners you didn't even
know existed before last week?
Well, I know
they exist now.
And I know they're
dying because of you.
So, we're going
to settle this thing
and we're going
to settle it right now.
Well, I'll tell you
what I'll do.
I'll write you a check
for $10 million right here.
Ten million.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Oh, you told them you'd get
them a hundred, didn't you?
Yeah, you did.
I can see it in your face.
Well, I suggest you tell them
you accidentally added a zero.
Because you're not
getting a nickel more.
Let me remind you, Mr. Palmer,
we filed 150 suits against you.
And we are going
to fight them all.
And that shook me before.
But who's going to supply the
manpower to fight those suits now?
You know who.
I guess you really didn't
get the memo, did you?
Because Pearson Specter Litt
just withdrew from this case.
I'll find someone else.
I highly doubt it.
Hey, listen to me.
Your company
hurt these people.
Now, you were willing to settle
for $100 million before.
This is your chance
to do the right thing
and clear your conscience
at the same time.
Sounds to me like
a chance to clear yours.
This is a take it or leave
it offer, Mr. Ross.
And whether
you take it or not,
I don't ever expect
to see you here again.
Ms. Cromwell?
Yes?
My name's Michelle Ross and I was
hoping to employ your services.
My services?
Yes.
I'm a junior partner
at Rand Kaldor,
and I'm looking
to make a change.
I'm sorry, I don't really do
much work with the legal sector.
Actually, I was hoping
to use my experience
and parlay it
into the business world.
Well, I can take your resume,
but to be honest,
I don't have a client who's looking for
a candidate like you at the moment.
I know you don't.
In fact, since
we're being honest,
I know exactly what kind of
candidate you're looking for.
What kind is that?
One that can be manipulated into
selling their employer's products.
Who are you?
It doesn't matter
who I am.
What matters is,
I know what you do.
You don't know
anything about me.
I know that, officially,
you're a headhunter.
But unofficially, you meet your exclusively
male clients at places like this.
I also know that at the end
of each of those meetings,
you say to them,
"I never do this,
"but would you like
to have dinner?"
And then, dinner leads to
dessert, dessert leads to sex,
and sex leads to them falling
for you, and that leads to...
All right,
I've heard enough.
And you don't have
proof of anything.
Actually, I do.
But you know what?
I don't need it.
Because one of two things
is going to happen.
Either I am going to hire someone to
tell every one of your male clients
when you meet them
that you're going to rob them,
and then your cushy job making $1
million per sucker is going away...
Or?
Or you're going
to tell me about every time
you've done this
for James Palmer.
And you're never going to hear
from either one of us again.
I can't do that.
My job requires
a reputation for discretion.
You're going to do
what we want,
or you're going to find out how much
your reputation protects you in prison.
Oh, I get it. You're not
worried about Palmer knowing.
You're worried
about word spreading.
Trust me,
he'll never tell a soul
and your business
will stay intact.
How can you be sure?
The same way I'm sure
that you don't have a choice.
The question is, are you
going to go against him
or are you going
to go against me?
Okay, I'm in.
Just like that?
Just like that.
This thing
is damn impressive.
But before
we move forward,
I need to make sure
you're good with one thing.
What's that?
I want 90% ownership.
90%?
Are you out of your mind?
No, I'm not.
And I'm not in the venture capital
business. I invest in the stock market.
Which means I'd be using
my own money on this.
Money that you'd
earn back in spades.
I hope it turns out
that way.
But this thing has a lot of risk
and I'd be taking all of it.
Then maybe you should
take none of it.
Donna.
As good as
this product is,
I'm telling you as one
business person to another,
you have no credibility
to do this.
Believe me, these are the best
terms you're going to get.
Well, you see, that's
where you're wrong, Stu.
Because like I
told you once before,
I'm Donna, this is awesome,
and I can do better.
Well, I hope
you prove me wrong.
But in the meantime, I won't
be used as a stalking horse.
Which means if you walk away now,
you can't come back to me later.
Oh, you don't have to
worry about that, Stu.
Because once I
walk out that door,
I promise you
I'm not coming back.
I can't believe you.
Listen, Mike, before
you say anything...
I know you didn't give a
shit about those miners,
but the least
you could have done
was stuck around long enough
to give me some leverage.
We had no choice.
Palmer pressured
10 of our top clients
to drop us
unless we pulled out.
So, it's either
them or me.
Unless you can replace
$30 million in billings,
you're damn right it is.
Harvey, without you backing
me, those miners are screwed
and there is nothing
that I can do about it.
There's something you can do about
it, you just don't want to do it.
You're talking
about that woman.
You want leverage on Palmer,
she's the one who's got it.
Harvey,
we've been over this.
I'm not going
to use that woman.
And what if I told you
we already did?
What?
Mike...
We not only found her,
we got enough to force that
bastard into a settlement.
The question is,
are you willing to use it?
What do you mean, "we"?
Mike. No, no. You
just said "we."
Who the hell is "we"?
Rachel.
Me and Rachel.
You dragged Rachel
into this.
I didn't drag her
into anything.
I went to her for permission
because I knew how you felt,
and she jumped at the chance
since you're too stupid to.
You had no right.
Mike, listen to me.
You had no right!
Night, Johnny.
Benjamin?
Donna.
Uh, I hope you don't think it's
weird that I came to your place.
Well, I find it a little weird
that you know where I live.
I work in IT,
I know where everyone lives.
But that's not what
I came here to talk about.
What did you
come here for?
I'm freaking out
about tomorrow.
I mean,
what if we're not ready?
Relax, Benjamin,
it's going to be fine.
How can you know that?
Because I already
did a practice run.
What are you
talking about?
There's a guy I know
who I thought might invest,
but he's not really
in this business.
So, I brought The Donna over to
him and I gave him our pitch.
And it went okay?
It went more than okay.
He made us an offer.
Then what in God's name do we need to
put ourselves through this torture for?
I turned him down.
Wait. Sorry, what?
Donna, this is our dream.
I know that, Benjamin.
But he wanted
to own 90% of it.
And I'm not willing to
give up 90% of our dream.
Now, go home
and get some sleep.
Because we've got our
first meeting tomorrow.
And you and I are going
to kick some serious ass.
When were you
going to tell me?
Mike... Were you ever
going to goddamn tell me?
Don't speak to me like that.
You went behind my back
When you knew
how I felt about this.
No, I went behind your back because
I knew how you felt about it.
Is that supposed
to make it okay?
No, look, I was the one that didn't
want to let things get too risky.
But when Harvey laid it out for
me, I decided that it wasn't.
Then why didn't you
come to me first?
Because you're the one
that says
forgiveness is easier
to ask for than permission.
That's a bullshit reason.
Then how about focusing on the
fact that I did it for you?
Rachel.
Mike,
this morning, when you told me it
was over, the look on your face...
I don't want you to have that
look for the rest of your life.
Rachel, I was upset.
It had just happened.
No, Mike. That's just it.
It hadn't.
You've been living
with this for so long.
That's why you gave Harvey
the go-ahead to begin with.
I did that because
I had to watch Oliver fail
and there was nothing
I could do about it.
And if it wasn't Oliver,
it was going to be someone
else or something else.
There's always going to be some
reminder that you weren't a lawyer.
And it would eat away at you because
it's what you're meant to be.
You shouldn't have done
what you did.
I know you're mad at me
for going behind your back.
But I'm not
going to apologize.
Because I don't want to
spend the rest of my life
with a man who gave
up on his dreams.
And I know that you don't
want to be that man either.
Louis?
What are you doing
in here?
Rachel, can I
talk to you a second?
Of course.
I heard Mike had a problem
involving that woman.
Yes, he did.
We actually got into a fight
about it last night.
What's he going to do?
I don't know.
But thank you for doing whatever
you did to find her, anyway.
Of course.
So.
What are you doing
in here?
Do you ever wish
you hadn't found out?
What?
Do you ever wish you'd never
known about Mike's secret?
Or, for that matter,
never even met him?
Louis,
what's going on?
Tara and I have been
sharing a lot lately.
But there are still
things I haven't told her.
And yesterday, she asked me what
I was having a bad day about.
And the truth is, it was
pretty much about Mike.
And I wanted to tell her
about it, but...
You don't know
how she'll react.
No, I don't.
I still haven't even told her I knew about
Mike's secret before he got caught.
Let alone the fact that I
used it to get name partner.
Louis...
Rachel.
When Sheila found out, she said
I wasn't her soul mate anymore.
But that was Sheila, Louis.
And the key phrase
is "she found out."
You didn't tell her.
So, you were okay
when Mike told you?
No, I wouldn't say
that I was okay with it.
But I love him,
so I forgave him.
And I can't guarantee
that Tara will forgive you.
But I can tell you that if she
finds out some other way,
then she won't.
Thank you, Rachel.
I appreciate your time.
Thank you for
sitting down with us.
It's our pleasure. I'm
Andrew and this is Russell.
I'm Donna.
And my name is Benjamin.
Mind if
I call you Ben?
Yes, actually,
I mind very much.
But you open up
that checkbook of yours,
and you can call Ben here
whatever the hell you want.
I appreciate that,
but before we get started,
you should know that we get pitched six
personal assistant devices a month.
And you should know
that our device
makes Siri and the Alexa
look like toaster ovens.
Well, that may be the case,
but I'm concerned that the
market is already saturated.
If you were so concerned,
you wouldn't be sitting here
in the first place.
Is that a fact?
Yes, it is.
Because you're the head
of the investment team,
and the head of the team
doesn't waste his time
unless he thinks there might
be something in it for him.
There might be other things in
it for me than just investing.
Yes, there could.
Like marking your territory.
Because anybody can see by the
way you two are sitting there
that he's gunning for your job
and you don't like that one bit.
That's not...
Who told you that?
No one told me that.
Just like no one told me
that you can't fire him
because that will
make you look weak.
Which is why
you took this meeting,
because you didn't want him
taking it without you.
Okay. How in the hell
are you doing all this?
I'm doing this
because I'm Donna.
And if it hasn't dawned on you
already, so is this device.
Now, do you want to puff up your
chest and play office politics
or do you want to hear
about an opportunity
that could vault you both
to the top of the ladder?
Why don't you tell us
about your product?
Can I get a black coffee?
Make it two
of whatever he's having.
You here to tell me
what a dick I am
for going behind
your back again?
No, I'm here to find out what
time your meeting with Palmer is.
I don't know.
What do you mean,
you don't know?
Well, I wasn't going to do it
without your permission.
Which means there is
no meeting with Palmer.
Well, I'm giving
you my permission.
Mike, I'm not
trying to be an asshole.
But we went to a lot of trouble
to get that shit on Palmer
and you looked like
you wanted to kill me.
So, how do I know you're not
gonna want to change your mind?
Because I want
to be a lawyer.
I don't care
how we do it.
Then take out your wallet,
pay for this coffee,
and let's bring
this thing home.
Well, that was the most amazing
27 minutes of my entire life.
Hmm. Which part?
When you sat there
with your mouth glued shut,
or when you shit the bed
describing the operating system?
Oh, my God, I knew I should have
stopped after the design specs.
Benjamin,
I'm teasing you.
Now I don't know
if I should believe you.
Then listen to me
carefully.
You killed it.
Thank you.
But in fact, we killed it.
You're damn right
we did.
Now, get going. I'm going to
see you back at the firm.
Where are you going?
I accidentally forgot my pen
in the conference room.
Oh, I have one
you can borrow.
Benjamin, when I say accidentally,
I mean intentionally,
because it gives me an
excuse to go back in there
and eavesdrop on what
they're saying about us.
Oh, that's a great idea.
Can I come with you?
No, I need
to do this alone.
Why?
Because when
they see me without you,
they're going to think
it's two against one
and they'll make me
an offer to cut you out.
Wait, you actually think
they would do that?
Of course they will.
These guys are vultures.
Well, then, shouldn't I go
with you so we can stop it?
Do you trust me?
Yes, I do.
Then trust when they make me the
offer, I'm going to act outraged,
tell them we'll never do
business with them,
and they'll give us
an extra 5% right there.
Okay.
So,
what did you think?
I thought
it was impressive.
Well, then, I think
you're easily impressed.
- You didn't like it.
- I liked it just fine.
But do you know
how much it would cost
to roll out a piece
of tech like that?
Between the engineering, design and
beta testing, it costs a ton of money.
You're the one who says you've got
to spend money to make money.
I also said when you fund a
project, you fund the person.
And the truth is,
I'm not funding that woman.
So, why did
we take this meeting?
I took it as a favor
to Harvey Specter.
Now, if she was starting up
a lemonade stand,
I might throw in a few bucks.
But there is no way in hell I'm getting into
business with a career legal secretary.
You don't
have to tell me twice.
- You want to grab some lunch?
- Yeah.
Maybe a drink.
I feel like I deserve it after having to
sit through that with a straight face.
Hey, Jimbo.
Nice club.
A little heavy
on the wood for my taste.
A little heavy on the
douchebag for mine.
How did you get in here?
I told them I was your cousin,
we had some bad news,
and you were going to
want to hear about it.
Bullshit.
Maybe not the cousin part.
But here's the news.
We've got your balls in a vice
and there's only one way out.
The hell you do.
And since you decided to
just wade back into this,
those six clients of yours
are gone.
Mmm.
I don't think so, Slim Jim.
See, the only reason you almost
got to us in the first place
was you found
my Achilles' heel.
But then,
we found yours.
I've got to say,
she sure is pretty.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Maybe this
will jog your memory.
Names, dates, phone numbers, e-mails,
bank statements, wire transfers.
Proof of over a dozen instances of
you committing corporate espionage.
Lucky for us,
she isn't just pretty.
She's a hell
of a bookkeeper.
What do you want?
For you to do what you should
have done in the first place.
You're going to settle with
those miners for $200 million.
You're going to forget you ever
heard of us or Ms. Cromwell.
And you're going to honor your
original agreement with Craig Seidel.
What do you care about
that weasel's future for?
That's between me and him.
Oh...
One other thing?
This really is
a take it or leave it offer.
It expires in 15 seconds.
And once it's signed,
I never want to hear about
your shitty little company
doing something
like this ever again.
There you are.
Where have you been
since that meeting?
I've been doing
some thinking.
And I've been wondering if my
partner sold me out all day.
Well, I hate to break it
to you, Benjamin,
but that's actually the
opposite of what happened.
What do you mean?
I mean...
They don't want
to make us an offer.
In fact, they don't want
anything to do with The Donna.
It's my fault,
isn't it?
Benjamin... You don't have
to protect my feelings.
A chain is only as strong as its weakest
link, and I know that's what I am.
No, you're not.
Turns out, I am.
Listen to me.
You have designed
an incredible product,
and I don't want
to hold you back.
Which is why,
as of right now,
I am dissolving
our partnership
so you can take it out
on your own.
Where the hell
do you think you're going?
We're partners.
I'd rather throw The Donna into the
ocean than move forward without you.
Benjamin, please,
don't be a martyr.
I'm not being a martyr.
I'm being a partner.
We're in this together
or not at all.
So, it's up to you.
Are we going to give up
on our dream?
Or live to fight
another day?
Live to fight, Benjamin.
Live to fight.
Again?
What the hell is it
this time?
The same thing
as it was last time.
I need you to get
that hearing back for me.
Are you kidding me? You know how
much trouble it was the first time?
I don't care how much trouble it was.
You're going to do it again.
Unless, of course, you don't
want the original terms
of your deal
with Palmer upheld.
What are you
talking about?
We had him guarantee
to pay you what he promised
and to hire you over there
at the end of the quarter.
Why would you do that?
Because I don't just want you
to set that hearing.
I want you to bulldoze anyone
who stands in my way.
Look, it's up to you.
You take the job and the
money and you get me in,
or you stay
on a sinking ship
and wait for them to figure out
that you're the one who sank it.
I'll make it happen.
Yeah.
I'm not surprised.
I would have thought you'd
be at happy hour by now.
These days, my happy
hour is the 60 minutes
from the time I get home
to the time I pass out.
You're a hard worker, Stu.
Turns out they don't just give
you money for your looks.
Hmm. But you didn't come
all the way back here
just to tell me
how hard I work.
I came to see
if you'd reconsider.
You couldn't beat it, could you?
No.
But that's not
why I'm here.
Then why are you here?
Because even though
I didn't like your terms,
you spoke to me as an equal and
you treated me with respect.
And that's the kind of person I
want to be in business with.
What would you say if I told you
the offer was back on the table?
I'd say my assumption is
the terms won't be as good as
they were the first time around.
The terms
aren't going to change.
Why not?
Because I don't want to go
into business with someone
who feels like I'm
giving them the shaft.
I want to go into business with someone
who's happy with my partnership.
Thank you, Stu.
You're welcome, Donna.
Oh, and just so you know,
when I put my money
where my mouth is,
I throw everything
I have into it.
I wouldn't expect anything less
from a big mouth like you.
Done?
Done.
I've got to say,
the world's going to be
a better place
with you as a lawyer.
Why? Because we just strong-armed
some jackass into doing what we want?
No, because you did what it took to
get those miners what they deserve.
Speaking of which. You want
to come with me after this?
Where you going?
To tell those miners
that the world's best lawyer
just got them
what they deserved.
Second best.
Ah, potato, potahto.
Seriously, Mike,
you go tell them.
Besides, after that,
you've got some preparing
to do for that hearing.
What are you
talking about?
I just told you,
Seidel's got it in the bag.
And if you think there isn't
going to be some kind of hitch,
I haven't taught you shit.
If you think whatever it is,
I can't handle it,
then you have not
been paying attention.
You mean like when you handled
yourself into going to prison?
No, I mean when I came out
smelling like a rose.
Hey, I was there
when you came out.
And rose wasn't the aroma you
were emanating.
You're right,
I was emanating awesome.
You really are like me,
aren't you?
Unfortunately.
Welcome back
to the Bar, Mike.
Thanks, Harvey.
Technically, I wasn't... Yeah. Actually,
you really weren't in the Bar, ever.
I'd ask how your day was,
but the last time I did that,
it didn't go very well.
Tara, can I be
honest with you?
Of course.
You can tell me anything.
It's part of getting to know each other.
I told you that.
I'm just not sure that this
is what you had in mind.
Louis, what is going on?
The other day, when I didn't want
to tell you what I was upset about,
I was trying to figure out a way
to get Mike Ross into the Bar.
You mean the fraud
who worked at your firm?
It's a long story. But we're
friends now, and we're past it.
What do you mean,
it's along story?
I mean, I knew Mike was a
fraud before he was arrested.
And I didn’t just know.
When I found out about him,
instead of going to the police
or going to the Bar,
I leveraged it to get
my name on the wall.
Tara, say something.
Say What?
You just told me you found out
you were working with a criminal
and you turned it
into a promotion.
I know that.
But you said that we should
get to know each other.
What do you want me
to say, Louis?
I didn't know what
your favorite movie was.
Or what side
of the bed you like.
But I thought at least I knew
what kind of man you were.
Tara, please.
This is the thing I'm most
ashamed about in my life.
And I'm telling you
to show you
that I'm never going to hide
anything from you.
Well, maybe you should hide
some things from me.
What?
You heard me.
I heard you.
How dare you say that to me after
what I had to find out about you'?
What is that
supposed to mean?
It means you're sitting there like you're
the high priestess of moral authority,
when the first time we slept
together, you were with another man!
How can you say that to me?
I was upfront about it
with you and with him.
You were upfront about it
with everybody
and then you wanted me to be
upfront with you about things.
And now, you're looking
at me like I'm a monster!
You know what?
That's it.
That's it?
Well, where are you going?
I'm sleeping at my place tonight.
Look, Tara, please.
If I knew that you were
gonna react this way,
I never would have
told you any of this.
But you did tell me,
Louis.
Good night.
Tara, wait.
I'll give you a call when I've had
a chance to figure things out.
^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
P® Krishna_Teja P®