Hello?
I am armed...
with a... with a big gun.
Oh, my...
- Oh, m...
- God.
At least do it with
a little authority.
Someone's going to think
I raised a pussy.
You scared the crap out of me.
How did you get here?
I live in a nursing home,
not a prison.
They have a shuttle service
and a very muscular driver
named Donald.
Grammy, I'm making
a lot of money right now.
I could have sent
a car for you.
Then, I wouldn't have gotten
to see a very muscular driver
named Donald.
Why didn't you call?
I could have been here.
Oh, my God.
Our dinner.
I have been working so hard,
I forgot what day it is.
That used to happen to dad.
That's what happens when
you care about your job.
And don't give a rat's ass
about your grandmother.
Well, yeah, that is why
I put you in the home.
Good morning, everyone.
Before we get down to business,
I would like to offer
a big welcome back
to Daniel Hardman.
We're thrilled to have you home.
- Now, moving on...
- I'm sorry, Jessica.
Before you do that,
I want to say one thing.
While I am delighted
to be back,
I want to be clear.
Nothing's changing.
Jessica is still the head
of this firm.
I'm here in
a number two capacity.
Just think of me like
a seasoned advisor.
Like Bill to Hillary
if she'd won.
Thank you, Daniel. Moving on.
Prescott hospitals' negotiation
with their nurses' union.
Nobody wants a strike.
I'm going to need someone
who's going to bring this home.
Therefore...
Not to jump in here too quick,
but I did bring Prescott
into the firm.
I'm your man.
What I was going to say is
I brought Harvey up to speed
on this last night.
He's got it covered.
Been prepping all morning.
Really? The whole morning?
I learn fast.
Maybe I could still help.
Mind if I take a look?
Later.
Jessica likes to keep
these meetings headlines only.
I'll swing by your office.
- Sounds like a plan.
- Next order of business.
Nurses' strike assigned
to me last night?
Goddamn Daniel.
Picked up right
where he left off.
Trying to cut my legs out.
Why are you grinning?
I'm just glad to have someone
in the room who pisses you off
more than I do.
You know why I picked you,
right?
Because you knew
I'd roll with your lie.
Because you need a chance to
get out of the doghouse.
I got your tea service for you.
You think that's going
to cut it?
- What do you want me to do?
- Put him in his place.
Ahh! It's a can opener. What?
Paying for your sins
of last night?
I wish you hadn't said that.
Why not?
'Cause I spent the night
with my grandmother.
- Is she hot?
- What is wrong with you?
- You started it.
- I most certainly did not.
Prescott Hospital.
I need a complete summary
of their nurses'
union negotiation.
From whom?
Rachel?
No. No, it's too soon. I...
I broke it off
before we even started. No.
Tell her about
the exciting night
you spent with
your grandmother.
Trust me.
She'll realize she dodged
a bullet.
Oh.
And I need four bullshit
pro bono cases right now.
I don't have
any pro bono files.
I'm a corporate lawyer.
That's what we do here.
I do it on my own time.
- Thanks, Rachel.
- Wait a minute.
Why are you asking me
for case files?
I'm not allowed to say.
Harvey asked Mike,
and he was too afraid?
Like a baby girl.
You okay? No.
But I am too busy
to do anything
other than throw myself
into this stack of work anyhow.
Well...
as long as you're making
healthy choices.
Yeah.
Make yourself at home.
You know, I can see myself
in this thing.
I would find that really
distracting, of course.
I'm swooning.
I thought the plan was to meet
in your office.
I thought I'd save us
some time.
This is a child custody
dispute.
Little Lenny. So sad.
You need props to
make your point?
You said you changed.
Why don't you prove it
by doing some good?
Harvey, I have changed.
But I don't have to prove
anything to you.
Not as long as
you sit in this office
and pretend to practice law.
But when you stick your nose
in my cases,
that's another story.
If you haven't noticed,
my name is on the door.
They're all my cases.
The name of this firm is
Pearson Hardman.
You said it yourself,
you're number two.
I answer to number one.
No matter who you answer to,
one way or another,
you will learn to treat me
with respect.
Fine.
I respect you,
but I don't work for you.
And I sure as hell
don't work with you.
Pick up the phone.
Little Lenny deserves the best.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right
♪ all that time imagine this ♪
♪ The greenback boogie
You know the head
of the nurses' union
isn't a lawyer but a nurse,
right?
What's your point?
What if you get schooled
by a hot nurse?
What are you, 12?
What, you can talk about
my grandmother,
but I can't make a nurse joke?
Yup.
Actually, I was 12
when I had my first
caregiver fantasy.
Let me guess. Nurse Ratched.
Say what you will.
You had a kind
of stocky hotness.
Listen, our goal
is to reach a fair agreement
between a hospital
and its nurses.
There are no winners.
Did you have a stroke?
There's always a winner.
Of course there's a winner.
Just needed to make sure
you were ready to stick it
to the nurses.
Don't say it.
Ah. Negotiator number five.
Meet the new boss.
Same as the old boss.
Jameson was our last
negotiator. Trust me.
I'm not Jameson.
That's what he said about
the one before him.
You're all the same to me.
I'm over here,
you're over here.
Well, let's see if we can't...
You're going to have
to buy me dinner first.
I can do better.
You're expecting me
to offer you this.
You're willing to settle
on this.
You're praying for this.
Well, your prayers have
been answered.
You know, I'll even buy you
breakfast in the morning.
Not so fast, blondie.
Prescott Hospitals is hurting
as much as anyone else.
You push any harder,
they're going to go out
of business, and nobody wins.
This is the best
you're going to do.
And it's a deal
you're ready to take.
We were ready.
But what about the new account
you funded yesterday?
Yeah, that's right.
I know about it.
This isn't my first rodeo.
Then you also know that
money's off the table.
Money's fungible.
Everything's on the table.
I'm sorry,
but that account was funded
by donors specifically
for the development
of new robotics for surgery.
I used to change bedpans
for a living, junior.
I know what bullshit
smells like.
This isn't bullshit.
Even if Prescott wanted
to give that money
to the nurses,
they couldn't, legally.
So they're willing
to raise money
for equipment but not nurses?
I get it.
Nurses are sexy,
but nurses aren't sexy.
Well, you need to find a way
to get us access to that money,
or we don't have a deal.
That's not going to happen.
Well, then we're done.
You leave this table,
it means only one thing.
I know exactly what it means.
We have
a fully funded strike fund,
and we're going to use it.
We reject your proposal.
Reminder: Ask Harold
to dye his hair.
Orange is the color of a clown.
No, strike that.
Harold is a clown.
Annual survey
of associates came out.
Pearson Hardman ranked second
to last in quality of life.
Who beat us?
Louis, I know you
take great pride
in making the associates' lives
miserable...
Well, I did until the survey
said I was second best at it.
You're missing the point.
Harvard wants to rescind
our on-campus
recruiting privileges.
What?
Wait.
Pearson Hardman is Harvard.
Harvard is Pearson Hardman.
One can't survive
without the other.
There's no need
for histrionics just yet.
Histrionics?
This is the gravest day
I've ever known.
Jessica, let me handle this.
Why do you think I'm here?
Screw you.
Mine likes to be scolded too.
I keep getting
these dating site pop-ups.
It's like my computer's
accusing me of being single.
Do you know
why it's doing that?
My mother's in there?
Did you search for
a dating site?
- No.
- When?
Last week.
You, me, happy hour,
Harvey's corporate card.
Are you crazy?
You want to leave the office
at 5:00?
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
Happy hour starts at 4:00.
It's a bad idea.
You're never going to get
an injunction to stop
the strike outright.
You read that in a book,
or is that what
your five minutes
practicing law have to say?
Not a book
but every labor decision
from the last ten years.
But I'm telling you,
it's a safer bet
arguing for the temporary
restraining order.
First of all,
a T.R.O. delays a strike,
an injunction stops it,
and I want to stop it.
Second of all...
never use that phrase
"safer bet" with me again.
- Safer bet.
- You know what?
You don't deserve the privilege
of seeing me win.
I've gathered you all here
to ask you
just one simple question.
Do any of you have the desire
to strip down and exchange
underwear with each other?
Any takers?
No?
Well, of course not
because you don't want
to air your dirty laundry
in public, right?
But evidently, you did.
And while I'm personally proud
of the fact
that you're all unhappy,
Harvard is not.
So I've invited a representative
from the law school
to see firsthand
how joyful you all are
under my tutelage.
So you want us to lie?
No.
I want you to convince
this woman
that Pearson Hardman makes you
shit rainbows.
Is that clear? Yeah.
- You sure? Okay.
- Yeah.
Anyone else have
any other stupid questions?
What are you doing here?
I'm here on behalf
of Pearson Hardman.
As much as I appreciate
a fan club,
this hearing starts
in five minutes,
which means you've got four
minutes to get out of here.
Daniel.
I'm prepared to rule on
your motion.
What do you think
it's going to be?
T.R.O. granted.
Finally, you rule one for me.
Don't give me any grief
about the Feinberg suit.
Your precedents sucked.
This one's legit.
It's good to
have you back, Daniel.
Thank you for moving me up
on the docket, Judge.
- What the hell was that?
- I believe it was a victory.
Hey, you don't reschedule
my hearings.
Were you in there?
'Cause I do.
The truth is
you should be thanking me.
Well, would you like me
to thank your face
with my fist?
If you would have consulted
with me first,
like I offered,
I could have told you.
Garvin Steiner was never going
to grant an injunction.
Not when his Wednesday
golf buddy shows up
and hijacks the courtroom.
Say what you will.
I know the man.
0% chance he gives you
what you want.
Daniel, maybe you don't know
how it works these days.
When I'm on a case,
the only thing
there's 0% chance of
is me losing.
Harvey, I said I've changed.
Don't mistake that change
for weakness.
I told you,
my name's on the door.
Didn't get there by me taking
shit from the likes of you.
You want to work together
on this,
I'm open to it.
You don't,
this is how it's going to be.
So let me get this straight.
The judge ruled
against your idea,
and so you went with my idea?
Not exactly.
Hardman got the T.R.O.
Okay, so you told me
I was wrong,
and yet I had the same idea
as a managing partner.
That's funny, that kind of
makes me wonder
what else you've been
wrong about.
Hiring you?
Daniel and I wouldn't
concur with that.
Hey, handsome.
Your bearded buddy
was already here.
You can shut us down
for 48 hours,
but we can still prepare
to strike.
Actually, I came over
to extend an olive branch.
Why don't you go ahead and
start your strike right now?
You looked into our finances,
I looked into yours.
Your strike fund has enough
to last a week.
We're not even going to have
a meeting about it for a month.
We know what
we're getting into.
We're prepared.
Well, prepare yourself
for this:
Our last offer's off the table.
The new offer is the one
we gave you before that.
And every day you strike,
it's going
to keep getting worse.
Harvey, you do realize
you just littered, right?
They can pick it up.
They're not working.
It'll give them
a sense of purpose.
Wow.
You don't think you're being
a little harsh?
I just put an end
to a situation
our client can't afford
and those nurses can't either.
Trust me, they'll cave.
Everyone.
I would like you to meet.
Ms. Sheila Zass from
our beloved Harvard Law.
While I appreciate
the introduction,
I would have appreciated
even more
a little discretion.
I'm here to make an assessment,
which would have been aided
by anonymity.
Fly. Wall.
Loud and clear.
And by the way,
it's Sazs. S-a-z-s.
Yeah, that's what I said.
Sheila Zass.
Never mind.
Do you see what I see?
There's two of them.
I think Louis is attracted
to female Louis.
Do you think that
if they touch,
the world would cease to exist?
I don't want to think
about them touching.
There's my favorite
litigation girl.
Olivia, what's up?
James, Gordon brief,
just going to say,
it was a gift to the law.
See, this is what I like to do,
basically.
I like to, uh, you know,
sit here
once a week,
make myself accessible,
get to know the troops
on a, you know, personal level.
Okay.
And what has
that process yielded?
Well, Harold has a mother...
Aunt.
Who tragically died
of heart disease.
Cancer.
We're all with him.
I think I've seen enough.
Clearly, you don't know
that person very well.
So unless you want
to find yourself
recruiting SUNY Binghamton,
you'll treat me with
a little more respect.
Wow, you really cut me
to the quick.
Yes, I do not know him
on a personal level, thank God.
But I don't think
that's relevant.
I have 20 underlings.
I don't know
a single person's last name.
God, I admire you.
What do you need from us
to keep our privileges?
What do you think I need?
Talk to each one of them
individually.
Bingo. Pick a man.
That one.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
People say
I'm emotionally unavailable.
I got us 48 hours,
and you threw it away.
No.
You gave them two days
to negotiate
with the threat of a strike
hanging over our heads.
I took the only bullet they had
out of the chamber.
And now that bullet
is headed right at us.
They have an offer in front
of them,
and they're going to sign it.
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do.
Well, you better be right
because if either one of us
picks up the phone right now,
we'll be the ones who caved.
Then we might as well tell them
they can have everything.
Finally,
we're on the same page.
Welcome to the team.
We're not on the same page.
You backed us into a corner.
I didn't do shit.
Nell Sawyer put us
into that position.
I gave her the best offer
we could afford.
And if this strike drags on,
Prescott goes down.
And none of us can afford that.
This strike never
would have happened
in the first place if
I had gotten an injunction
instead of the T.R.O.
By the way,
that piece of genius,
same idea my associate had.
Kid's smart, but he's never
been around the block.
You have.
Stop thinking like a rookie.
Okay, let me guess.
The reason that you haven't
signed up yet
is that you want me to help you
take some sexy pictures
for your profile.
You're hoping that one thing
leads to another and...
♪ Bow-chicka bow-wow
No.
The reason I haven't
signed up yet
is because they have
you fill out this form,
and it asks you to write down
who you are.
And who I am is a paralegal.
Rachel, I am a legal secretary,
and I am proud of it.
But when somebody asks me
who I am,
that is not the first thing
that comes to mind.
Yeah, but I don't have
anything else, you know?
I kidded myself about becoming
a lawyer,
and I kidded myself about Mike.
So the truth is I am just
a lonely paralegal.
And that's a tough thing
to write down.
Well, you're not
a lonely paralegal tonight.
We're lawyers. Pearson Hardman.
I'm Harriet Specter,
and this is my associate.
Michelle Ross.
I've got a photographic memory.
Pretty much a legal superhero.
I'm a closer.
I'm the best goddamn closer
this town has ever seen.
What are you looking at?
I can recite the constitution
forwards, backwards,
and sideways
'cause I read it once
when I was seven.
I don't buy it.
Recite it right now.
- Cheers.
I'm a flame thrower.
- Surgeon.
- Acrobat.
Professor... of law.
I'm a Rabbi.
- Ooh.
Oh, my God.
What the hell did you order?
Uh, you wanted to see me,
Mr. Hardman?
Please. Call me Daniel.
Sit down.
First of all,
I want to tell you
Harvey speaks very highly
of you.
He does?
Well, it's Harvey.
So you have to read
between the lines.
What did he say?
That I'm...
I'm not a complete idiot?
Something like that.
He also told me that you and I
had the same idea
to go after a T.R.O.
He told me that too.
Why did you think
it was the right move?
It put a clock
on the negotiations
and kept both sides
at the table.
I thought so too.
But whether I agreed with him
at the time or not,
I'm not going against him now.
But he and I do agree
on this point:
His decision puts us in a bit
of a pickle.
Because we can't go back
to Ms. Sawyer
and ask exactly what she needs
to close the deal.
Harvey and I can't.
But I can.
So you are smart.
I'm afraid so.
You'll have to forgive me
for not completely trusting
Harvey's assessment,
but I needed to make sure
that our back channel negotiator
was up to the task.
That's why he's not here.
Coach doesn't let dad
come to the tryouts.
What do you need me to do?
They sent you?
Which means they're not serious
about talking.
Ms. Sawyer, please.
Listen to me.
You are on strike,
and they are never
going to flinch.
So what harm is there
in talking to me?
Why should I trust you?
Well, that's why I wanted you
to meet me here.
Nell,
this is my grandmother,
Edith Ross.
Hello.
A proud resident
of a Prescott nursing home.
This is not just
another case for me.
Yeah, and he didn't just
stick me
in here last night
to make that point.
He locked me
in here months ago.
- Grammy.
- Now, easy, Michael.
I'm helping you out here.
By the way,
you're a bit of a hero
to my favorite nurse.
Really?
Well, that's nice to hear.
He never shuts up about you.
I can't take one pill in peace.
Edith, I'm glad
you brought up the topic
of pills
because I need to give
your grandson a little lesson.
You mind? No.
Let's see here.
Plavix, Zestril,
Hygroton, Atenolol.
You know what happens
when they're not kept straight?
Not good.
Who do you think does that?
Doctors?
Nurses.
Imagine
your grandmother's nurse
just finished a 15-hour shift.
She needs her medicine
in exactly two hours.
We're understaffed.
That nurse is going to stay.
He won't even sign
a time card for it
because he won't get paid.
But if his name shows up
on this chart,
he stayed.
Happens every day.
You ask me what I want?
I want enough money,
so it never happens again.
That one's a dud.
- You have no idea.
- Mm.
Ms. Sazs.
Mr. Litt.
- Louis.
- Sheila.
I feel as though
I'm talking to a...
Kindred spirit?
- Yes.
- I know.
Me too.
Level with me.
I'll be brutally honest.
That's the only language
I speak.
I'm going to allow you
to maintain
your recruiting privileges
because of the man
I believe you to be.
And I believe myself
to be that same man.
But you've got bigger problems.
Your associates
don't respect you.
They think you don't work
as hard as they do.
What?
They think you make them
do your work.
You realize
I'm only telling you this
because I think
that they're wrong.
They are wrong.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
- I did it.
- Did what?
You and Daniel are going
to be so proud of me.
Why don't you let me be
the judge of that?
Judge all you want.
Judge away because I saw Nell
on my own,
even used my grandmother...
not used.
She was on board with it...
that's weird.
Maintaining your integrity,
I like it.
Continue.
So it turns out
that the nurses are consistently
staying late
to give the patients
the right meds
even though they're not
being paid for it.
- And you bought that?
- Yeah, I bought that.
Because I checked
my grandmother's chart.
If it's true for her,
it's true for others.
Oh, you didn't let me finish.
Turns out, that all they want
is enough staff
so that nobody ever has to work
more than
a 15-hour shift again.
And how much is
that going to cost?
10% of the new equipment fund.
Nailed it.
So all we need to do is find
a legal way to get
at that money.
Yeah, so do you want me to go
tell Daniel how proud
you are of me,
or do we do that
together later?
Have, like, a group thing?
I'll give him the good news.
Wash all you want.
The lies aren't coming off.
I told you I changed.
I didn't say I became a nun.
You lied to my associate.
I never specifically said
anything that wasn't true.
People hear what
they want to hear.
You deceived your own.
You never lied
to anyone else here?
Jessica,
the other partners, me?
- Not since you've been back.
- Really?
When did Jessica assign you
this case?
You lied to me.
But I didn't come to
the bathroom and cry about it.
No, you sent my associate
to go crying
to the other side.
So he got us a final number.
He got a number,
but it's not going to be final.
We offer them $10 million,
the next day it's going
to be $15 million.
We needed to hold strong
to get them to close.
Says your gut,
and I don't practice law
based on your gut.
My gut didn't burn through
five negotiators.
Nell Sawyer did.
So you think
we should never budge.
I know we should never budge,
but you screwed that
when you sent Mike
to tell them we would.
Congratulations, Daniel.
We may be a couple of liars,
but only one of us is going
to be responsible
when this whole thing goes
to shit.
You wanted to see me?
We'll get going in a minute.
Once I start, I have to finish.
I've always hated these things.
A filthy habit.
My daughter was 15.
I caught her smoking,
and I hit the roof.
But then my wife got sick.
And then when the cancer
got to her lungs,
once a week,
we would share a cigarette.
Give it the finger.
Monday nights at 9:00.
I can't stop.
I don't want to stop.
Uh, we should really
figure out a way
to get at this equipment fund.
It's going to be a long night.
That's okay.
I don't really have much
of a social life.
Me either.
Barbaric.
Norma, the Scofield subpoena
is missing
an entire class
of subcontracts.
Please amend it
to include anything after 2010.
Oh, and send Sheila
a basket of flowers.
Thank-you flowers,
not romantic flowers.
Let things take
their natural course.
Can't you just keep a diary
like every other
12-year-old girl?
Not tonight, Harvey.
Just go home.
- What's going on?
- Nothing.
I'm just catching up
on some work.
In the bullpen?
Apparently, the associates
don't believe that I work
as hard as they do.
What?
Louis, anyone who doesn't think
you're the hardest-working
lawyer at this firm is an idiot.
You may be a dick,
but as far as I'm concerned,
the associates have it
pretty good.
Thank you, Harvey.
Dick part aside.
Remember when we were in here?
What we had to do?
Like it was yesterday.
I can still hear Hardman
reaming me out
for losing that Dunridge file.
- You were sitting right here.
- I was so scared.
I thought I'd be fired
right on the spot.
- I hid it.
- I knew it! I knew it!
I had to work 48 hours straight
just to recreate it.
Yeah, but we killed it
at trial.
Yeah, if that happened now,
I wouldn't hear the end of it.
I know.
God forbid they have to pull
one all-nighter,
let alone two.
It's like
they think there's this law
against working more than
20 hours a day.
Well, there isn't.
Prima Donnas.
I should fire them all right now
and start from scratch.
Louis,
I'm only going to say this once,
so you better enjoy it.
You're the man.
Harvey,
did you say somebody's the man?
You're the man.
Thanks. Appreciate it.
Who's the man?
You're the man.
You know it.
What did you say?
You're the man.
Damn straight.
What are you doing?
Oh, uh, God.
I'm sorry.
This... this looks awful.
I'm working with Hardman.
He needed a file, and I...
Why didn't you just send Donna?
Okay. I deserve that.
Rachel, I swear,
I didn't mean to...
Oh, don't look at me like that.
It's not porn. It's match.com.
- So you're, uh...
- Yeah.
I am. That's good.
- It is.
- I think it's, uh, good.
Yeah, me too.
Except that I have been working
on this essay
for the past three days,
and this is all I've got.
- It's blank.
- I know.
- Okay, how about you start
with something like this:
"I work at the top firm
in Manhattan."
Yeah.
See, that's not really...
"I have an office,
"which is unheard of
for a paralegal.
That shows how much
they value me."
Just hold on.
Okay, more.
"I'm passionate.
"Funny, tenacious.
Courageous."
Any more adjectives?
"Supercalifragilistic-
expialidocious.
I'm incredibly smart,
sometimes aggressively so."
You realize this is supposed
to make me sound good, right?
Why don't you let me finish?
"I'm a...
"I'm also a kind person.
"And I want someone who notices
the little things,
"like... like the fact
that I'm a foodie,
"and I love to share that
with other people.
"Or that when someone pays me
a compliment,
"I can't even look them
in the eye,
"or the fact that my parents
are obviously loaded,
but I'm still determined
to make it on my own."
I'm not going
to type that last part.
Hey, it doesn't matter.
You're still going to be beating
them away with a stick.
Well, yeah, because you write
such a... such a good essay.
No, I mean, after you post
a picture here.
Barbinger file, done.
Scofield subpoena, done.
Johnson strategy, written.
Every single one
of your assignments
was completed by me last night.
What else
do we have left to do?
- Uh, file it?
- Filing.
Doc review, spell check.
Grunt work?
Yes, grunt work.
Because that's your job.
Let it be known that
I can do your work faster
and better than any one of you
without shedding a tear
or breaking a sweat,
but I don't because
writing briefs
and recommending arguments
is how you learn.
You go out to any other firm
right now
at this stage of your career,
you won't have this opportunity.
If you don't believe me,
I will write you
the best recommendation
you have ever seen,
and you can find out
for yourself.
Go ahead.
Any takers?
That's what I thought.
Now I have ten new cases here.
Who wants in?
What are you guys waiting for?
Come and get them.
Excellent work last night,
Mike.
Thanks.
Whoa, you didn't tell me
you were bringing her in.
Who do you think
the proposal was for?
Does Harvey even know about
this meeting?
As a matter of fact, I do.
- What's this?
- It's a pink slip.
50 pink slips, in fact.
For 50 nurses. Excuse me?
It's come to my attention
these nurses have been working
past their 15-hour shift.
And they don't put it
on their time card,
but they still sign charts,
which happens to release them
from the protection
of federal labor law.
You're bluffing.
I found these 50 in one night.
How many do you think
I'll find in a week?
There's a way out of this.
Sign the contract.
Your grandmother
would be proud.
You have until the end
of the day.
- Harvey!
- Let me guess.
You're upset.
I got you that information
through my grandmother.
Your idea, not mine.
Look, I know you might have
been hatched in a pod,
but family actually means
something to me.
And I gave you that information
to help the nurses,
not strong-arm them.
Were you okay with the first
deal we presented to Nell?
- That is not the point.
- That's exactly the point.
Because this is a contract that
our client can actually afford.
- Harvey.
- Enough.
You think I was joking when
I asked if you were ready
to stick it to the nurses?
I wasn't.
I know you don't like
this part of the job,
but it's part of the job.
If Prescott gives in
to their demands,
they go out of business,
the nurses get nothing,
it's a win-win.
That's bullshit.
It's a win
because you beat Daniel.
I work with him,
I work with you,
I work with him...
it doesn't take a genius
to figure out that
you're playing each other,
and you're using me to do it.
But you know what,
I don't care what's going on
between the two of you,
but I don't want to be caught
in the middle of it ever again.
Grammy, if that's you,
I swear to God,
I'm going to have
the locks changed.
Rachel.
You hurt me.
- I'm sorry.
- No.
All those nice things you said,
those are the kinds of things
you say when you...
look, if you feel
those things about me,
why can't you be with me?
I told you,
you know, it's... it's work
and... and that guy.
It's everything, you know?
I just... I don't think
it would work.
I think it would be a mistake.
Yeah, you know what?
You did say that.
And it's a lot of bullshit
because the Mike that I know
and the Mike that I fell for...
he wouldn't do this.
And if all of your feelings
are still there,
then it only points
to one thing.
And it's that you're keeping
something from me.
I don't want to lie to you.
Then don't.
Please, just...
just tell me what it is.
I thought so.
- Rachel...
- I'm done.
Rachel. Rachel, wait!
Rachel!
Rachel, stop.
Please, let me explain.
- How?
- Look, I want to tell you.
- Then tell me.
- I can't.
Why? I mean,
what could it possibly be?
You're... you're married?
You're some kind of spy?
No, you don't understand.
Look, once I tell you,
I can never take it back.
This is my everything.
I can't.
Did you have fun?
I wouldn't say fun.
You celebrating winning
the case or beating me?
Two for the price of one.
Jessica loves a bargain.
You here for another round? No.
I'm not here to start a fight.
I'm here to apologize for one.
The partner meeting...
you were welcoming me back.
But I saw you sitting there
in my old chair,
and I just...
I'm sorry.
His words sound good.
Only one problem.
You were starting stuff
before you even got here.
Gifts to everyone,
digging into cases,
constructing a new office.
That was all part
of coming back.
Not furnishing it
with my tea set.
That's what this is about?
Don't you remember
where you got that tea set?
Alicia gave it to you.
And I took it
because I missed her.
I'm sorry.
I thought
you would understand that.
- Hey.
I need a copy
of the final agreement
the nurses signed.
Yup, got it right here.
Thank you.
You look different.
New clothes. Hair like that.
You have a date.
- Good night, Donna.
- Good night, Rachel.
Mind if I come in?
Uh, truth be told,
I was taking off
for the afternoon.
Late night?
- Nothing I can't handle.
- I believe it.
I heard your speech
to the associates.
And I just wanted to tell you
how impressed I was.
Thank you.
I always knew you were
the right man for the job,
so it feels good to see it
in action.
Something wrong? No.
Louis.
If you really heard me
in there,
you'd know that I give them
the chance to rise
to the occasion.
And I just wish every once
in a while,
you might maybe
do the same for me.
You wanted to see me?
Yeah, Mike. Sit down.
I wanted to tell you a story
that I should have told you
the day Daniel came back.
When Jessica and I found out
that Daniel was embezzling
from clients,
we confronted him.
He broke down.
He said his wife had cancer,
and he needed the money to try
and save her life.
Turns out, he needed the money
to support his mistress.
Now he's saying he's different.
But a man who would do that
is a man I find
very difficult to trust.
Do you trust me?
That's what
I wanted you to know.
Is this your first time?
No. I'm just...
trying to forget
about the other times.
Start fresh.
Look, I mean to be rude.
I just really want
to concentrate.
You have three hours
to complete the exam.
Good luck.
Your time starts now.
Three times in one week.
I might have to write you back
into my will.
What's wrong?
Plavix...
stuck in my head,
so I looked it up.
Something that you take
when you have a heart problem.
Michael, I'm 82 years old.
I have an everything problem.
Why didn't you tell me?
That getting old sucks?
You'll find out.
And I don't tell you
every little thing
because I don't want you
to worry.
And if you looked it up,
you'd know that it's...
it's for preventive purposes.
Did you read that part?
Yeah, I kind of panicked
when I got
to the heart problem part.
I hope you do
a more thorough job at work.
Okay, I make the trip down here
to express some serious concern,
and you mock me?
With love.
Okay.
Enough of your stupid
health problems,
let's get down to business,
deal with some of my real ones.
You're young.
You don't have
any real problems.
Wrong.
I am making way too much money,
and I don't have a girlfriend
to spend it on.
I know a few single ladies.
Really?
I can't go older than 70 though.
It's a ground rule.