- Mike Ross never went
to law school.
I knew it,
and I hired him anyway.
- I still can't stay, Harvey.
- You're making it seem
like I'm the one
that's taking away
your dream wedding.
- You are the one taking away
my dream wedding.
- Nothing
would make me happier
than to raise a glass
to your new life,
but I can't.
- Oh, so now I shouldn't
get married.
- No, I'm saying
you should quit.
- You tell me right now,
why are you here?
- It's not that simple.
- Why are you here?
- Because I'm afraid!
- You're calling
for an emergency vote
of no confidence today?
- Take a picture,
because tomorrow morning,
those letters
are coming down.
- Why should I believe
you would even live up
to your end of the bargain?
- Because I don't give a shit
about your war
with Daniel Hardman.
All I want to do is see you
get down on your knees and say,
"I quit."
- As of now, the company that's
been targeting our clients
is no longer represented
by Daniel Hardman.
- All in favor
of Jessica staying?
- How exactly did you get
that termination letter
for Forstman?
- I agreed to step down.
- You are not going
to step down.
- You've given up everything
for this firm.
It's time someone gave up
something for you.
- Harvey, you didn't just
give me my dream.
You gave me a family.
But I'm gonna have
a family of my own someday,
and I can't have all of this
hanging over their heads.
- You don't have
to do this for me.
- I'm doing it for us,
'cause as long
as you're with me--
- I'm with you.
[dramatic music]
- Michael James Ross.
- Yes?
- You're under arrest
for conspiracy to commit fraud.
[handcuffs clicking]
♪ ♪
[somber music]
[door closes]
- Michael Ross, I'm Assistant
U.S. Attorney Anita Gibbs,
and unlike you,
I'm a real attorney.
- I'm not answering
any questions
until I speak to my lawyer.
- I heard you asked
for him before,
but while we're waiting,
I just wanted to let you know
that I'm the one
who's gonna put you in jail.
Nothing?
Maybe you think that you've
committed a victimless crime,
but let me assure you,
you haven't.
By my estimation,
you've worked on 88 legal cases
in your so-called career,
and you committed fraud every
time you picked up the phone,
mailed a letter,
signed your name,
or appeared in court.
Each instance carries
a nine-month sentence,
and to tell you the truth,
I am too tired
to do the addition.
- Well, I'm not.
If what you're saying
is true
and there's a limit
of one count per case,
then I'll be going to prison
for 66 years.
♪ ♪
I've always been good
at math.
- Well, I haven't.
But what I am good at
is putting away
fake, cocky
tough guys like you
and seeing them break.
So here's how this
is gonna go.
You play ball,
I go easy on you.
You don't--
in my experience,
college boys,
even fake ones,
don't do well in prison.
♪ ♪
And if you think your people
are rushing down here
to bail you out,
you've got another
thing coming,
because I'm gonna keep you
in here all night.
♪ ♪
- Okay.
I'll confess.
But I want the whole thing
on tape.
♪ ♪
- Harvey, thank God.
I need to talk to you.
- Rachel, calm down.
What's going on?
- Mike's been arrested.
- What?
- Two men from
the U.S. Attorney's Office--
they just walked right up
to him, and they arrested him.
I don't know what to do.
- All right.
It's gonna be okay.
- It's not gonna be okay!
He's by himself.
We have to do something.
- I am.
I'm going down there
right now.
- No, you're not.
- Jessica, this isn't
up for you--
- Harvey, from this second,
you are an unindicted
co-conspirator,
and so am I.
And so are you,
which means none of us can
afford to be anywhere near Mike.
- I don't care.
Someone has to do something.
And if it isn't going to be you,
it's going to be me.
- You're gonna let her
go down there?
- Harvey, she can knock
on that door all she wants.
They're not gonna let her
see him tonight.
Besides, she's his fiancée.
Seeing him is not gonna
make her look guilty.
- It's not gonna make me
look guilty either.
It makes me look like
I'm standing by my guy.
- No, what's gonna keep you
from looking guilty
is you and I ripping up
your letter of resignation.
- Jessica, I just made a deal
with Forstman.
He finds out
that I'm still here,
he picks up the phone,
calls Hardman,
and the two of them
pick this place apart.
- And if whoever
is prosecuting this case
finds out you left
on the same night
they arrested Mike,
then we may as well
turn ourselves in.
- Which is why I need
to get in there
and talk to Mike
as his lawyer.
- Then this is what's
going to happen.
You are now his lawyer.
But you do whatever
you have to do
to work out of your house,
because I'm not telling
anybody you resigned.
♪ ♪
- This is AUSA Anita Gibbs
with Michael Ross.
The time is 11:05 p.m.
Mr. Ross has agreed to confess,
with the stipulation
that he do it on videotape.
- I actually never
said I'd confess.
I said I'd talk.
- You did say you'd confess.
- Oh.
Maybe I did, but then again,
I also asked to see my lawyer
at 9:03.
It's two hours later,
and I still haven't been able
to do that,
which means
anything that I've said
between then and now
is not only inadmissible,
it's also evidence
that you violated my rights.
- Oh, I get it. You just wanted
to get that on tape.
- Sure did.
And if I don't see my lawyer
in an hour,
you better be able to prove
that you've made every effort
to contact him and couldn't.
I know I'm not supposed
to know these things
because I'm not a lawyer,
but I do...
Because I am.
- Okay, you've had your fun.
Now I'm gonna have mine.
Your lawyer actually did show up
about half hour ago.
There seemed to be
a little miscommunication
about what room you were in,
but that's all been
straightened out.
So...
here he is.
[dramatic music]
- Robert.
- Oh, I see.
You thought you were
gonna see Harvey Specter
come in this room so you two
could get your stories straight.
Apparently that's not
gonna happen.
Now, normally this is the part
where I leave the room,
but almost looks like
you want me to stay.
Just so you know,
we can't watch or record
anything
that happens in here--
attorney-client privilege
and whatnot.
But if you're innocent
of these charges,
I'm sure you have
nothing to fear,
being alone in this room...
with that man.
♪ ♪
man: ♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
.
- What are you
doing here, Robert?
- Rachel called me
and asked me to help you.
- Is she okay?
- No.
She's not,
because she's out there,
and you're in here.
And so you're gonna
tell me right now,
is this shit true?
- Listen, I can explain
everything.
- I don't need an explanation!
I want an answer
to the goddamn question.
- Lawyers don't ask
that question.
- I'm not asking you
as your lawyer.
I'm asking you as a man.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- You know
what the answer is.
- God damn it.
[slams table]
♪ ♪
- You wanted the truth,
and now you got it,
but you got to tell me what
are you doing here, Robert.
- I told you, I'm here because
Rachel begged me to help you...
not because I give a shit
about what happens to you.
So you're gonna do
exactly what I say,
and I'm gonna help you
get out of this thing.
♪ ♪
- [scoffs]
No, there's no getting
out of this thing.
- Oh, yes, there is,
and you damn well know it.
That woman doesn't get anything
by prosecuting a fraud like you,
but she would love
to get Harvey Specter.
- I'm not turning on Harvey.
- Oh, he would do
the same goddamn thing to you
in a heartbeat.
- If you think that, then you
don't know Harvey.
- You better listen to me!
You better get your head
out of your ass,
because I'm throwing you
a goddamn lifeline.
It's the only chance
you're gonna get
to save what's left
of your miserable life.
- I won't do it.
- Then you are on your own.
♪ ♪
- Robert, please--
- Whatever you're gonna say...
don't say it.
The truth is,
you're doing me a favor,
because after I got you
out of this,
I was gonna tell you
to stay away from Rachel
for the rest of your life,
but I don't have
to do it now,
because you're gonna wind up
in prison anyway.
♪ ♪
[door opens, closes]
[knock at door,
door opens]
- Louis.
What's going on?
- Donna, I need to come in.
♪ ♪
- What happened?
- Donna, I need you
to sit down.
- Louis--
- I said you need to sit down.
- What happened to Harvey?
Please tell me
that he's okay.
- Mike's been arrested.
- Oh, my God.
We have to go see him.
- No, no, no.
We can't go anywhere near him.
- What?
- You can't go down there.
- Louis, so help me God,
if you turn your back on Mike
and you claim that this has
nothing to do with you--
- Just listen to me.
You're gonna want
to do everything you can
to get to Mike
and express your support,
but I am telling you,
that is a bad idea.
- Then I need to talk
to Harvey.
- No, you don't.
You need to stay the hell away
from him, too,
and count your blessings that
you don't work for him anymore,
'cause if all of a sudden
you start showing up
on his doorstep,
you are gonna find yourself next
up on the prosecutor's list.
- Louis, this is Mike
and Harvey we're talking about.
They're family.
- I am not saying they're not.
I'm saying the more contact
you have with them,
the worse it is
for all of us.
- Okay, I won't
go down there.
But I am going to see Rachel,
and if you think
you're gonna stop me,
you are out of your mind.
♪ ♪
- I am telling you,
I am his attorney.
If you don't let me see him,
I'm gonna break
through that door.
- You can bluster all you want,
but you're not getting in
because he's already
with his attorney.
- What?
- You dirty son of a bitch.
- Robert, calm down.
- I'm not calming shit.
You brought this kid
into my life.
You put my daughter's future
in jeopardy.
- Look, I know you're upset--
- Upset?
You're lucky I don't
lay you out right now.
- Robert, listen to me.
Mike Ross is a good man.
He came to me from nothing.
I saw something in him,
and you did, too,
and that's why you're here.
- No, I was here to get him
to turn on you,
but he's too stupid
to do that.
And I don't know if he's
gonna change his mind or not,
but I don't care anymore,
and I don't give a damn if
I ever see either of you again.
- Did you hear that?
He's not Mike Ross's
attorney anymore--I am.
So let me the hell in.
Robert Zane?
Really?
I'm hurt.
- Harvey, this is real.
- I know.
And the first we need to figure
out is who tipped them off.
- Why the hell do we need
to do that?
- Because if we're gonna
get you out of this,
we have to know every
damn thing they have on you.
- Are you crazy?
There's no getting out of this.
- I haven't lost a case before,
and I'm not about to start now.
- This isn't just
some other case.
They're gonna check the facts,
and when they do--
- They're gonna find
what we let them find.
- You can't know that.
- Yes, I can.
- That's bullshit!
- This is not bullshit!
Look, we can win this case.
- I don't care
about winning this thing.
- What the hell
is wrong with you?
- Harvey, I did this!
♪ ♪
- You didn't do shit
because they don't have shit.
♪ ♪
- [chuckles]
What the hell are you
talking about?
- Mike, you're
in the Harvard database.
You have a transcript.
You're in the bar.
You're a practicing attorney.
Those facts are real,
just like every case
you ever worked on
and every person
you've helped along the way.
♪ ♪
- Harvey,
this woman's not joking.
- That woman has to show
you're a fraud,
but as far as the world knows,
you're a goddamn lawyer,
and that's the way
it's gonna stay.
And don't forget--
we don't need to prove
you're a lawyer.
She needs to prove
you're not.
- Rachel, calm down.
- I can't calm down.
No one will tell me anything.
I can't go and see him.
It is the worst moment
of his life,
and I'm not there for him.
- Well, you will be
when you can.
- On top of all that,
I don't know what my dad's
gonna do when he gets there.
- You called your dad?
[sighs] Rachel, I don't think
that was a good idea.
- Well, I couldn't just
sit here and do nothing.
Mike's been arrested.
Jessica's talking about
unindicted co-conspirators.
- Okay, well then, he and Harvey
will just have to work it out.
- And what if they don't?
- Rachel, when I was
in trouble,
Harvey got me out of it.
This is what he does.
I am telling you,
he will get Mike out of this.
- It's just...
[sighs]
The thought of him...
in there all alone.
- He'll be okay.
It's just one night.
- Man, what are you looking at?
- Nothing.
- Your eyes are going
up and down on me, man.
It don't feel like nothing.
They all say, "Nothing.
Wasn't doing nothing."
You know what?
It don't matter what you say
and do once you're inside.
Little snot like you
won't last a week.
- [scoffs]
- You hear what I said?
You won't last
a week in there.
You might not last
a night in here.
- Listen, man--
- Hey! Get your hands off him,
you piece of shit.
[buzzer sounds]
- You're lucky, but
they won't be here all night.
- Yeah, neither will you.
- Hey, it's fine.
It's fine. It's fine.
Leave him in here with me.
It's cool.
I mean, unless you're
gonna let a federal marshal
beat the shit out of me
just to try and scare me
into making a deal.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Agent Ron Da'Mico, right?
[coughing]
Yeah, I saw your picture
out in the hall
getting a commendation
from the U.S. Attorney.
Of course, you didn't have
a beard in that photo,
but you look the same to me.
- You're a smart kid.
I guess that's how you got away
with what you got away with.
But you didn't really
get away with it, did you?
I am a marshal,
but the next guy won't be,
and you give him
that know-it-all attitude,
and like I said,
you won't last a night.
♪ ♪
- Yeah, well, for the record,
I'm not getting sent away,
but even if I was, it wouldn't
be a place like that.
- Oh, if you think you're
going to Club Fed...
[chuckles]
You don't know Anita Gibbs.
Sleep well, sweetheart.
.
- [sighs]
[door opens, closes]
How is he?
- He's in custody.
- And the bail hearing?
- I don't know,
because I'm not
representing him.
Now, are you done
asking me questions?
Because I have a few
of my own,
like how the hell
could you do this?
- Dad, because I love him.
- That's sweet, but you sound
like a teenager,
and right now
your mother is sobbing,
knowing what you've done
to yourself.
- Dad, Mike is the same man
that you worked with.
And you said yourself
there are things
that you did in your past
that you're not proud of.
- Don't you dare
compare me to him.
I am not a fraud.
I am not a criminal.
- [chuckles tearfully]
- Rachel...
Rachel...
I tried to get him out,
but he's living
in a dream world,
and so are you
if you think this boy is done
ruining your life.
- Why did you even come here?
- I came here to tell you
to look in the mirror
and get rid of him.
[somber music]
- [softly]
I can't do that.
♪ ♪
- Then I can't help you.
- I was wondering when you
were gonna pay me a visit.
- You know who I am?
- I know everyone
in my crosshairs.
Now pass me the cream
and tell me what you want.
- I want to know
why you arrested my associate
without just cause.
- Because Mike Ross
is a fraud,
and I'm gonna make sure
he never sees
the inside
of a courtroom again,
unless he's wearing
an orange jumpsuit.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have an arraignment
to prepare for.
- What if I was to tell you
off the record
Mike Ross
was about to resign?
- I'd say that sounds
very convenient.
- Well, it isn't.
I'm telling you the truth.
And if your interest really is
in getting him
out of the courtroom,
he was gonna do it himself.
- And why should I believe you?
- I can get you
his letter of resignation.
All you have to do
is waive charges,
and I'll get him to agree
never to practice law again.
- I'll tell you
what I'll do.
You get me that letter,
and I'll waive his bail.
- I don't need you
to waive bail.
Whatever it is,
he can pay for it.
- No, he can't.
I'll freeze his assets.
In fact, I'll make sure
that he doesn't get bail at all,
because hacking into the bar
is a federal crime,
and if he can do that,
he sure as hell
can flee the country.
- You have no proof
he hacked into the bar.
- Doesn't matter.
It's what he's accused of.
So you want to make sure
he walks out of court today,
you bring me the letter.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[line trilling]
- That better be you
calling down to my office
to explain
why your golden boy
was arrested for fraud
last night.
- My golden boy?
You're the one that
nominated him for partner.
- Because you passed him over
again and again,
and I knew there was
a reason for it,
but now I know what it was.
- Just what are you implying?
- I'm not implying anything.
You knew that kid
was a fraud,
and even if you didn't,
you should have.
So what is it?
Are you corrupt,
or are you just so stupid
you didn't know what
was going on in your own firm?
- Watch who you're calling
stupid, Jack,
'cause you were the only idiot
with his hands in his pockets
at that vote.
- I didn't have
their support then,
but I will now,
because Harvey's protégé
just got perp-walked
out of this firm.
And since then,
Harvey's nowhere to be found.
- Harvey's whereabouts
are none of your concern.
- Well, the partners
are concerned.
They need a leader
they can trust.
- And I'll bet someone's trying
to convince them
that leader is you.
- Well, look at that.
You do know what's going on
in your own firm after all.
- I'm gonna give you some advice
from the throne, free of charge.
You attack this firm's
leadership when it's in crisis
over an unproven allegation...
you're gonna look like
a bottom-feeder.
And even if they vote me out,
they sure as hell
won't vote you in.
♪ ♪
- Donna, what are you
doing here?
- Gretchen told me
you weren't feeling well,
so I dropped by
to see how you're doing
and tell you
to cut the bullshit.
- I don't understand.
- You've never taken
a sick day in your life,
and Mike just got arrested,
so I want to know
what the hell is going on.
- I can't be in
the office right now.
- Why not?
- Because I resigned.
- What?
Because of Mike?
- Because it's the only way
to get Forstman to back off.
- I don't care
about Forstman.
You're leaving the firm
when we need you the most?
- Donna, right now I have
to stay away from the office,
but I'm not leaving anyone.
I'm representing Mike.
- So you saw him.
- Last night.
- And?
- He's hanging in.
I just need this bail hearing
to go smoothly.
- What do you mean, go smoothly?
What's going on?
- The prosecutor's
playing hardball.
She's trying to keep him
without bail.
- Harvey, Rachel
is not doing well.
You have to get him
out of there.
♪ ♪
- Then I need you
to get something
from the office for me.
- [mouths word]
- I understand you've reached
an agreement to waive bail?
- We have, Your Honor.
No bail is requested
at this time.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
However, I would like
to introduce a motion
to have Mr. Specter removed
as attorney for Mr. Ross.
- What?
- On what grounds?
- On the grounds
that they conspired
to defraud the bar association,
every client they ever had,
and the people
of the United States.
- What's your proof?
- This letter showing Mr. Ross
was going to resign.
They conspired
to fabricate it.
- We had a deal.
- I don't care what we had.
The two of them
concocted a story
under the guise
of attorney-client privilege,
which they were only able to do
because Mr. Specter is both
his boss and his attorney.
- I gave you that letter
in good faith.
- You gave me that letter
in a blatant attempt
to get me to drop charges
against your co-conspirator.
- That is slander
and inadmissible.
- That's enough.
My chambers--ten minutes.
- You gave her that letter?
- I did it to get you out.
- I don't care
about getting bail
if it lands us both
in prison.
- It's not gonna
land us in prison,
and it would've come
out anyway.
We can't just destroy
every piece of evidence.
- Oh, we can't do anything
with any piece of evidence
because she's about to get you
kicked off my case.
- She has no grounds
to kick me off.
We didn't conspire
to write that letter.
- But we conspired to do
something else,
in case you forgot.
- Then we better come up
with something,
and we better
come up with it fast.
.
- I'm not in the habit
of removing counsel, Ms. Gibbs.
- And I'm not in the habit
of having an accomplice
be the attorney on a case.
- I'm entitled
to representation.
- And you had it last night.
Your attorney of record
is listed as Robert Zane.
- The only reason you want me
off this case
is so you can pressure Robert
into making my client
take your bullshit offer.
- The reason I want you
off this case
is because you're
an unindicted co-conspirator.
- If he's an unindicted
co-conspirator, then so are you.
- Excuse me?
- You violated
my client's rights
the night he was arrested,
and we have it on tape.
- That is a complete fabrication
based on the word of a con man.
- An alleged con man
with a photographic memory,
Your Honor.
- And what does that
have to do with anything?
- Because if I'm lying
about a digital tape,
then how do I know
the serial number
of the camera you use
in your interrogation?
RKZ986532.
Little piece of blue tape
keeping the battery attached.
- You want to remove
your motion,
or do I have to subpoena
that camera?
- I'll withdraw my motion,
Your Honor.
- You're free to go,
Mr. Ross,
and Mr. Specter
is your attorney.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- All this proves is that you
two were in on this together.
- What this proves is
you'll do anything to win,
and now the judge knows it,
and so do I.
♪ ♪
- Louis, put down
whatever you're doing.
- What do you need?
- I need you to make sure
there's nothing in the bylaws
Jack Soloff can use
to call for a vote
and get me out.
- Well, I can tell you
right now,
he can't do anything
for two weeks,
but after that, there's nothing
we can do to stop him.
- Then I need you
to figure out a Plan B,
because in two weeks--
- Wait a second.
Why isn't Harvey here?
- What do you mean?
- I mean it's his firm
as much as ours.
He's the one who started
this whole thing,
so there must be a reason
he's not here.
- Harvey's working
on Mike's defense.
- Oh, God damn it, that makes us
all look guilty
and puts us all
in jeopardy, Jessica.
- That was my reaction too.
And then I realized
this allows us to communicate
with Mike and each other,
and it's all privileged.
- Then I want it said
right now--
Donna stays out of it.
- That's not gonna
be a problem,
because Harvey
doesn't work here anymore.
- What?
- He resigned to get Forstman
to back off.
- Well, then
let me guess--
the prosecutor can't know
he did that,
and Forstman can't know
he didn't.
- Exactly.
- Jesus Christ, Jessica.
If Harvey's not here,
that even makes us
more vulnerable to Jack.
- Which is why I need you
to step up
and figure out a way
to keep that son of a bitch
from taking me out.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
Are you okay?
- I am now.
- [sighs]
You're out.
- And I have no intention
of ever going back in.
- Oh.
What are we gonna do now?
- I'll you what
we're gonna do.
We're gonna go on offense.
- What does that mean?
- It means finding out what
she knows and how she knows it.
- And it starts with us
getting into a room,
making a list
of every goddamn person
who knows the truth.
♪ ♪
- Donna, what are you
doing in here?
I need your help.
- Don't you mean,
"Thanks for working late, Donna.
May I ask for you assistance
with something?"
- No, I mean Jack Soloff
is crawling up our collective
asses, and I need you to--
What is that?
- It's a private matter.
- Mike Ross's
employment records?
God damn it, Donna.
You're doing work for Harvey?
- Louis--
- I explicitly told you
to stay away from Mike's case.
- And I heard you.
I just don't care.
- What did you say to me?
- I said I don't care.
- Well, I forbid you
to do this.
- Excuse me?
- Donna, I don't think
you get it.
There is going to come a time
where you're gonna
have to choose
between yourself and them,
and I am not going to let you
throw your life away
for either one of them.
- You know what, Louis?
If they're gonna come for me,
they're gonna come for me.
But until then, if Mike
and Harvey need my help,
I'm gonna give it to them.
And if you have a problem
with that,
you might as well fire me.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- Robert?
- When Rachel first told me
she didn't want to work for me,
we fought all night.
I didn't think any other firm
was good enough.
And then she told me
she was gonna work for you,
and that changed everything.
A brilliant black woman,
mentor for my baby girl,
someone who could teach her
what the world does
to people like us--
how to get down in the mud
and still manage
to keep her dignity.
♪ ♪
And look at what
you taught her instead.
- Is that what
you came here to tell me?
- I came here to tell you
to fire Rachel,
because she won't quit.
And when they come at him
to turn on you,
I don't want her within
1,000 miles of this place.
- I'm sorry, Robert.
I can't do that.
And you know why.
- I do...
♪ ♪
Because it makes him
look guilty...
which he already is.
And when they ask me
to help to get him
to turn on you, I'm gonna
recommend that he does.
- You do what you need to do,
and I'll do what I need to do
to save my firm.
- It doesn't matter
what you do.
Your firm is gonna crumble
all around you.
- Is that a threat?
- I don't have to threaten you.
I don't have to lift
a finger,
because people
are gonna come at you
from places you didn't
even know existed,
and I'm gonna enjoy
every second of it.
.
- Louis,
if you wanted to see me,
you didn't have
to send me a message
telling me to meet you here.
- I did that because
I have a foolproof plan
to stop Jack
before he even gets started.
- Well, let's hear it.
- Make me managing partner.
- Come again?
- It's the perfect solution.
I step in,
target's off your back,
and we're fine
till this all blows over.
- I don't believe this.
You want my goddamn job.
- What?
It's not like that.
No one thinks that I have
anything to do with Mike.
My ethics
are beyond reproach.
- I don't recall them
being beyond reproach
when you used Mike's secret
to get your name on the wall.
- Jessica, that--
- Louis.
You are out for yourself,
and I'm not going
to stand for it.
- How the hell could you
say that to me
after you just told me
to step up?
- You want to step up,
then do what I goddamn told you
to do and don't come to me
with some "I'm not part of this"
Mike Ross bullshit ever again.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I was wondering how long
it was going to take you.
- You heard?
- Everybody's heard.
- Scottie, I have
something to ask you,
and you're not gonna like
what it is.
- I can't believe it.
You think I would do that?
- No, I know
you'd never do that.
- Then what
are you doing here?
- Mike thought
it could be you,
and I promised him
I'd look you in the eye and ask.
- Okay, so let me
get this straight--
I keep Mike's secret,
throw a case for you,
and now you're here
taking orders from him
because you don't trust me?
- I do trust you,
and I told Mike I did.
- Oh...
which is why the real reason
you're here
is not to ask me
if I handed him in,
but to tell me to keep quiet.
- Not to tell you--
to ask you if you're going to.
- What is the difference?
- Scottie--
- Harvey, I am not
in your life anymore.
I mean, what makes you think
that they're going
to come to me?
- 'Cause you know
how this works.
They're gonna dig
into my personal life,
and when they do,
they're gonna find you.
- And how many women like me
are you paying a visit to today?
- There are no women like you,
and you know that.
- What I know is,
the last time you came to me,
I told you I never wanted
to hear Mike Ross's name again,
and once again, here you are,
asking me to do something
for the person that destroyed
our relationship.
- Scottie, I'm not here
to argue with you.
- But you still want to know
what I'm going to do?
- I do.
- Well, I guess we're just gonna
have to find that out
when they come.
♪ ♪
- I need to talk to you.
- Look, we've already
discussed all there is
to discuss about the wedding.
I can't go,
so unless you've quit...
- I was arrested.
- What?
- Two nights ago,
in my office,
two U.S. Marshals grabbed me
out of the blue.
- I'm sorry.
- You can save your sorrys.
I want to know if you're
the one who turned me in.
- What?
Jesus Christ, I can't believe
you'd think that.
- Why wouldn't I?
You've done it before,
and you also told Father Walker,
and I still haven't heard
you say that it wasn't you.
- Well, it wasn't me.
Going to Father Walker was about
making things right in my life.
- Yeah, well, I got a way you
can make things right with me.
They're gonna come to you
to put together
a case against me,
and I need to know
what you're gonna say.
- I don't know
what I'm gonna say, Michael.
Do you want to write down
my answers for me
like you used to
before class?
- Yeah, I do. And this time,
the answer's gonna be,
"I need to speak to my lawyer."
- Wow.
20 years of friendship all comes
down to "lawyer up," huh?
- Yeah, it does,
and you owe me, Trevor.
- I can't lie for you, Mike.
- I'm not asking you
to lie for me.
I'm asking you to pay me back
for every time in my life
you have screwed me over.
♪ ♪
- Okay.
But I'm not doing this
to make it up to you.
I'm doing this
to make sure my family
doesn't get dragged
into this.
So don't bother me
with this again,
or I may just have to tell them
everything I know.
♪ ♪
[rock music]
- I see you can dish it out.
The question is,
can you take a punch?
- Why don't you put
the gloves on?
We can find out.
- I don't know
if you've noticed,
but we're already in the ring,
and you're not in my class.
- What are you doing here?
- I just wanted to look you
in the eye
and ask if you still work
at Pearson Specter Litt.
- Excuse me?
- I stopped by your office
to see if you were serious
about pleading this thing out,
and you weren't there.
So I asked your secretary
when you'd be coming back,
and she got very cagey.
And now I find you here,
boxing in the middle of the day.
- I'm blowing off steam.
- I don't think so.
I think I was wrong
about you and Mr. Ross
fabricating a letter
of resignation.
And I think Jessica Pearson
found out
what you two were up to,
and rather than making herself
look like a fool
by handing you in,
she forced you both
to resign.
And now you're on your own.
- And I think if you
want to write fiction,
I hear they got
a remedial class at NYU.
- Maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe Jessica knew
about Mike Ross all along,
in which case, maybe you
would turn on her.
- Why don't you get the hell
out of here
before I turn on you?
- I will.
But if I find out
you resigned,
that's evidence
you're a co-conspirator.
And I'll not only get you
off this case.
I'll put you behind bars
along with your little pet.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[running footsteps approaching]
- What the hell is this?
- You know what it is.
It's formal notice.
Your services
are no longer required.
- [scoffs]
I don't believe this.
You're firing me?
- Yes, I am.
And I want you to pack
your things up tonight,
because you and I don't see
eye to eye on your priorities.
- Okay, Louis...
just because
we had a fight--
- No, this has nothing
to do with that.
- So you're saying
that this has nothing to do
with you lashing out at me
because of the fight
we had before?
- No, it doesn't,
because among other things,
you set your own hours,
you can't take dictation,
and to top all that,
you can't read people for shit!
- What's going on?
- You almost went to jail
for helping them once before,
and I couldn't take that.
And the thought of losing you
once again...
- So you know
that they need my help.
- Yeah.
I do.
Now you're free to go.
- What made you
change your mind?
- Jessica accused me
of not being a team player.
And she was wrong
about me, and...
I was wrong about you.
- Thank you, Louis.
- I have to go.
- No, Louis.
You don't.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- What are you doing here?
- Our conversation got
cut short the other night.
- So Anita Gibbs sent you here
to tell me
that if I go to prison,
I'm not gonna come out the same.
- You're right.
She did.
She wanted me to come here
and scare the shit out of you,
tell you about everything
that's gonna be happening
to you inside.
- And who says I'm ever
gonna be inside?
- Maybe you won't.
But if you do,
I'm here to tell you
everything that's gonna happen
on the outside.
- Why don't you get the hell
out of here?
- Listen to me. Anita's going
to come to you with a deal,
and it's not gonna be
through Harvey Specter.
And if you're smart,
you'll take it.
- I said get the hell out.
- All right, I'll go.
Just let me tell you something.
They don't have conjugal visits
in federal prison.
And even if they did,
I've seen your fiancée.
She's smart.
She's beautiful.
She has a future.
Girls like that
don't wait around,
no matter what they say.
.
[door closes]
- Hey.
- There's--
- I wanted to talk--
- Sorry.
You go first.
- My father was here.
That woman went to him
and offered a deal.
- Let me guess...
they want me
to turn on Harvey.
- They'll drop
all the charges,
and you won't have to spend
a minute in prison.
- What did you tell him?
- I told him that I would
give you the message.
- That you'd give me
the message?
Rachel, you know
there's no way in hell
I am ever gonna turn
on them, right?
You know that.
- Yes, I do.
- Do you?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- It means that you
should have told him
that I'm loyal to everyone
in my life,
and I would rather go to jail
than betray them.
- I did tell him that.
- So then why didn't you tell me
that you told him that?
- Because that's not
what you asked me.
- Tell me right now that
the idea never crossed your mind
that I should take this deal.
- Of course it popped
into my head for a second--
- So you think
that I should just turn on them
the second things look bad?
- That is not what I said.
- Is that what you're thinking
of doing to me?
- How could you even
ask me that?
- I never even thought
for a second
that you would even
consider an idea so disgusting
as turning on Harvey.
- The only reason
I thought about it
is because I am
scared to death
of you going to prison.
- Scared of me going to prison
or scared that you can't
stick around?
- Are you...
[knock at door]
Mike, don't.
We need to talk.
[door opens]
- We got a problem.
- Yeah, we do...
'cause it wasn't Trevor.
- It wasn't Scottie either,
but that's not our problem.
Gibbs came to see me earlier.
She knows I'm not in the office.
- What does that mean?
- It means she's gonna
try to use it as evidence
of Harvey being
a co-conspirator,
and if she does that,
Harvey can't represent me.
- [sighs]
[dramatic music]
- What's going on?
- They offered Mike a deal.
They want him
to turn on you.
- Ah.
Then you're in good company,
'cause they offered me a deal
to turn on Jessica,
but that's not our problem.
Our problem is figuring out
how to get me back
without Forstman finding out.
- Wait a second.
It doesn't matter if Forstman
finds out or not
if he doesn't have someone
on the inside working for him.
- What are you saying?
- I'm saying
that if they want me
to point the finger
at someone,
that means I'm holding a gun.
♪ ♪
- It's still alive.
- Did you think I would
let it die?
- No, but I thought
you might give it away.
- Well, I'm more sentimental
than you think.
How'd you get in here?
- Jessica told me how
when I told her
what I was coming here to do.
- And what is that?
- You need me...
because as good as Gretchen is,
she can't be a part of this,
and you know it.
- You're saying
you're coming back to me?
- Yes.
I am.
- Good.
- Then we'll see you back
in the office tomorrow.
- What do you mean?
- I mean I'm coming back.
- How did you swing that?
- Hasn't happened yet,
but I got a little secret weapon
called Mike Ross.
- Well, then...
[sighs]
See you tomorrow.
- Donna?
How did Louis take it?
- Believe it or not,
it was his idea.
♪ ♪
[knock at door]
- Surprised to see me?
- As a matter of fact, I am,
but as long as you're here,
I have a question for you.
- Oh.
You want to know if it's true.
- Oh, I know it's true.
I want to know
why you haven't tried
to deal your way
out of this.
- You mean why haven't I turned
on Harvey and Jessica?
- That's exactly what I mean.
- It wouldn't have
anything to do
with you wanting
to use all of this
just to get your name
on the door, would it?
- Oh, I'm getting my name
on the door
whether you cut a deal or not.
- Well, if you don't stop
coming after Harvey and Jessica,
the only door
you're gonna be looking at
is gonna have bars on it.
- What the hell
are you talking about?
- Let me tell you
what I just got finished telling
Daniel Hardman.
They're coming at me
left and right
to admit that someone
around here knew
what was going on with me
the whole time.
So, if you don't back off
trying to take over this firm
once and for all,
I'm gonna tell them
that someone was you.
- Bullshit.
You didn't even know me
until a few months ago.
- Well, yeah, but then
you and I worked together
so closely on that case.
And then I confided in you.
And then you
made me partner
so that you would
always have an ally.
- There's no way
that holds up in court.
- Good luck telling that
to the judge.
And this prosecutor...
[chuckles]
She--she's a real beast.
She's gonna come after you
with everything she has.
- I never did anything to you.
And I'm not leaving my firm.
- I don't give a shit
whether you stay or you go.
But Harvey is coming back here
tomorrow morning,
and if you pick up that phone
and call Charles Forstman,
then I am gonna pick up
the phone
and tell that prosecutor
all about me and you.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- I always wondered
what it was like in here.
It's nicer than I thought.
- Jessica, how'd you
find me here?
- You always go mudding
when you're upset.
- I always go to the gun range
and the ballet.
- You go to the range
when you're angry,
the ballet
when you're depressed,
but mud...
- Heals the broken heart.
- I know.
And I heard
about what you did with Donna.
And I'm here to say
I'm sorry.
You weren't just out
for yourself.
- But I was out
for myself, Jessica.
Donna showed me that.
- Are you saying
you were after my job?
- Of course I wasn't.
But who the hell
am I kidding, you know?
I mean, I'm not Frodo.
Once I got that ring of power,
we all know
it would've consumed me.
- That's what I like
about you, Louis.
You may not be self-aware,
but if someone holds up
a mirror,
you are not afraid to look.
- Thank you, Jessica.
And the truth is,
Harvey needs Donna
more than I do.
- Well, it was a selfless
and noble act.
And as far as I'm concerned,
you may not be Frodo,
but you are Samwise Gamgee.
- Get the f--
You read "Lord of the Rings"?
- Four times.
I mean, it is about power.
- That's funny.
I always thought it was
about friendship.
- Good night, Louis.
- You sure you don't want
to have a quick mud?
- Maybe next time.
- Really?
- No.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[elevator bell dings]
- How'd it go?
- Let's just say Jack Soloff's
not gonna be a problem anymore.
- That's one thing down.
- Yeah, it is.
Look, Rachel--
- I'm not gonna leave you.
♪ ♪
- How can you know that?
- All I can tell you
is that we've managed
to stay together with this thing
hanging over our heads
for as long
as we've known each other.
And if we can get through that,
we can get through this.
♪ ♪
- But I still might go
to jail.
- And if you do,
you'll get out...
and I'll be there.
And it won't be hanging
over our heads...
ever again.
♪ ♪