You took a case on contingency
where every plaintiff
is dirt poor.
Dump it.
One of the victims
was my uncle Keith.
Please, these people
need your help.
They need someone like you
to fight for them,
and I can't do it.
Then what do you say
we do it together?
I'd like to propose a change
to the current
compensation formula.
How many partners
do you have in your pocket
if we put your proposal
to a vote?
I can get 45%.
I'm gonna get you
the difference.
This is Harvey's
last three income statements,
and I found them sitting
in the copy machine.
You came to work for me,
so now it's time
for you to decide.
Are you with me or not?
I just called
for a vote tomorrow,
and I hope you've been
saving your money,
because your gravy train's
about to leave the station.
Oh, hello.
- I was just...
- Working.
I see that,
but it's 7:30 in the morning.
What are you doing here
so early?
I like to get in
before the chaos starts.
Tell you the truth,
I was under the impression
that you wouldn't get in
till much later.
I wanted to get a jump
on the day.
Then maybe you should get
a jump on this.
Why am I paying
Louis's laundry bill?
Because if you pay it,
he won't know
that we triple-starched
all of his shirts.
- We?
- Yes, we.
He came after us.
We're coming after him.
Did you think
I wouldn't have your back?
You want the truth?
I thought
you'd be asking for a raise
after seeing how much I make.
I didn't look
at how much you make.
And as far as I'm concerned,
anyone who did should be fired.
You're all right, Gretchen.
But for the time being,
don't play any more jokes
on Louis.
Mind if I ask why?
Because I only play jokes
on people
to express my affection
for them,
and right now I have
no affection for Louis Litt.
Looks like I got here
just in time.
And why is that?
Because I'm going
to ask you to do something
you're not going to want to do,
only this time
you're going to do it.
What didn't I do last time?
I told you to apologize
to Louis.
And I did, right before
he held hands with Jack Soloff
and cut my earnings
in front of the entire firm.
And if you hadn't have been
such a dick to Jack
in the first place,
Louis would have had
nowhere to go.
This isn't about Louis, is it?
No, it isn't.
I want you to bury
the hatchet with Jack.
You mean you want me
to kiss his ass.
I mean I want you
to figure out a way
to make peace with a partner
whose influence is on the rise.
That's kissing his ass.
Well, if that's how
you want to look at it,
then pucker up,
because that man is a threat,
and he's aligned with Louis,
and I am in no mood
for a power struggle.
- Hey.
I didn't hear you leave today.
That's because I left
at 5:00 in the morning,
trying to get an early start
on this case.
Mm.
Uh, about that...
I didn't want to say
anything last night
because you were so excited...
But you're worried about me
working with your father.
- Yes.
- Hmm.
Mike, you're the two most
important men in my life.
Neither of you back down
from a fight,
and I'm just...
I'm afraid you're gonna
end up hating each other.
Rachel, do you hate your father?
Of course not.
I love my dad.
And don't you have conflicts
with him all the time?
Yes, I do, but it's different.
He's my family.
Yeah, he's gonna be
my family too.
And if I'm lucky,
I'm gonna fight with him
about a lot of things
over the years.
So why not start with a fight
where we're both
on the same side?
Okay, I trust you.
Good.
[upbeat music]
Jessica, you have a minute?
I do if you're here to tell me
why Robert Zane
is sitting in the lobby
with an appointment to see you.
'Cause I'm pretty sure
he's not taking time
out of his busy morning
to talk about centerpieces.
No, he's not.
He is here to co-counsel
the Kelton case.
You mean the case
I explicitly told you to drop?
I mean the case that you said
would cost a fortune to fund
and you didn't wanna lay out
that kind of money for.
I didn't want to lay it out
because this case is a loser.
And I'm telling you it's not.
And even if it is,
I just took away our downside.
By going behind my back
to our biggest competitor.
Are you telling me that
you're scared of Robert Zane?
I'd be a fool if I wasn't.
And you're a fool if you're not.
We let that man into our house,
there's no telling
what he'll do.
You know what, Jessica?
If Harvey had done this,
you'd be pissed,
but you'd let him do it anyway.
And you may be as cocky as him,
but you are not Harvey.
No, you're right.
I'm sorry.
I guess I'll just go tell Robert
that we won't be working
together on this after all.
You know damn well
if we tell him that now,
I look weak.
So maybe I am as good as Harvey.
Well, sometimes
that's not a good thing.
Where are you going?
To get
some goddamn strength back.
Then go ahead and do it.
I won't just take you
to the woodshed.
I'll leave you there, dead.
Well, looks like you're
making yourself comfortable
in my offices.
About as comfortable
as possible in these chairs.
You ever hear of lumbar support?
I get it.
You like stodgy and functional.
But these are my chairs,
just like this is my case.
What exactly are you
doing here, Jessica?
I'm here to tell you
we're taking
half the contingency.
And I'm here to respond.
I'm giving you 1/3.
We brought this case to you.
After you found it in a box
crying for its mama.
Plus, I'm footing the bill,
which means
this fee discussion is over.
Well, this fee discussion
may be over,
but the power discussion
is just getting started.
You don't give a shit
about the money, do you?
On this particular case,
all I give a shit about
is keeping you in check.
Which means, for the duration
of this matter,
you will be treating
Mike Ross like a partner.
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
That boy barely shaves.
I don't care
if he's still in diapers.
He's representing my firm,
which means
he's representing me.
You look at him, you see me.
You're asking
for a hell of a lot.
Then take your wingtips
off my table
and walk 'em out the door,
because this is my case
and you either do it my way
or you don't do it at all.
Mm.
I love you.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ Suits 5x03 ♪
No Refills
Original Air Date on July 8, 2015
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
[music box plays]
♪ ♪
Louis, it's not my birthday.
I know, but I know
that you weren't happy
with the position I put you in
regarding Harvey's compensation,
so I just wanted to make sure
that you and I were okay.
Actually, you wanna
know the truth?
Right at this second,
I'm not okay.
Then please tell me,
what can I do to make it okay?
You can start
by never putting me
in a position like that again.
I won't.
Jack, I need to talk to you.
Sure, Louis,
what can I do for you?
Well, you can consider me
out of your war with Harvey.
What are you talking about?
I'm saying that I don't like
what I did,
and from now on, I don't want
anything to do with it.
Fine by me, Louis.
As far as I'm concerned,
I won my war with Harvey.
This is your office?
Why do you say it like that?
- Like what?
- With disgust.
'Cause Harvey's got
autographed basketballs
and vintage records,
and you've got a photograph
of a guy's shoes.
Well, you better be careful
or Sergeant Hulka
with the big toe
is gonna see how far
he can stick it up your ass.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Stripes.
I'm just quoting Stripes.
It's a movie.
Harvey and I do this
all the time.
Look, I don't know
what kind of teenage nonsense
you got going on with him,
but I don't do that shit.
Okay.
I'm going to visit the facility.
Meet you down in the lobby
in ten.
I take it that means that
things went well with Jessica?
Yep, she signed off,
and all I had to do
was agree to treat you
as a full and equal partner.
Whoa, that must have hurt.
Eh, it didn't hurt a bit, 'cause
I didn't mean it with her,
and I'm not gonna do it
with you.
See you in 10.
Better make that 15.
Heard you're looking for me.
I was, because I wanted
to give you this.
What's that?
Directions to
Westchester Country Club.
Why are you giving them to me?
Because I don't want you to be
late to your 11:30 tee time
with Charles Barkley.
I'm playing golf
with Charles Barkley?
If you get there on time,
you are.
If not and he starts whacking
at shit with his big club,
he might kill someone.
You'll miss the whole thing.
You think I don't know
what you're doing?
You're sucking up to me
'cause all of a sudden
you realized I'm someone
to be reckoned with.
That is what I'm doing.
But you're a big golfer
and a bigger Barkley fan,
and I thought we could use this
to get off to a fresh start.
Here's the problem, Harvey.
I don't give a shit
about Charles Barkley,
and you don't give a shit
about me.
Listen to me.
This is a gesture.
Take it.
I'm not gonna take it,
and I'm gonna tell you why.
Because you've never
treated me like a peer.
You've only ever treated me
like competition.
I'm trying very hard here.
Well, you can stop trying,
because I'm not interested.
Mr. Specter,
I swear he told me
he was
a huge Charles Barkley fan.
I'm sure he did,
but the problem is he lied,
and you should've known it.
Whatever you're doing,
put it back.
- I need you.
- I can't.
What do you mean, you can't?
We're about to go to war.
I mean, I'm about
to go to war myself.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm taking a case
against Kelton Insurance.
I gotta go meet the client
right now.
Who the hell authorized that?
Jessica.
You went to Jessica
instead of me?
I didn't go to anyone,
all right?
She came to me after I took it.
Well, I'm telling you, you're
gonna have to postpone it.
Harvey, this case is important.
I'll tell you what's important.
I got a partner at this firm
coming at me.
Well, I didn't know that
when I committed to this.
What the hell? I thought
we were meeting in the lobby.
You gotta be kidding me.
Your case is with him?
You're damn right it's with me.
And we have
a first impression to make.
I don't know what kind of law
you're teaching around here,
but where I come from,
you show up on time.
Let's go.
You wanna go?
Go.
Jessica, what can I do for you?
You came to me
for some legal advice.
Now I'm coming to you for yours.
Do I get to charge you for it?
You already do,
unless you suddenly
started paying for law school
out of your own pocket.
Free of charge it is.
I want you to look this over
and tell me if we have
any exposure.
Okay, but this isn't a deal.
This is a speech.
I'm aware of that,
but Gwen Barnes
is quite opinionated,
and I don't want her
to say something
that might get her sued.
Dr. Gwendolyn Barnes?
Do you have a problem with her?
No, not at all.
How much time do I have?
Take as long as you want.
Just make sure
whenever I come back for it,
it's done.
(Harvey)
What are you doing in here?
I came to apologize.
You don't need to apologize.
I was out of line.
Soloff's an asshole,
and it wasn't your fault.
No, you were right.
It was my fault.
Well, what's done is done.
If you don't mind,
I need to think right now.
I'm sorry, Mr. Specter,
but what's done is not done.
What are you talking about?
I told you, I got your back.
What the hell is this?
It's the bio of that asshole's
third biggest client.
- And?
- Look where he's from.
I appreciate you coming
all the way down here,
but the last time
you came to me,
you told me to sit tight,
and that was a week ago.
Emma, I don't understand.
What did you expect?
I expected you to understand
what it feels like
to be left hanging.
Because if we can't
understand that,
what's to stop us
from cutting and running
when things get tough?
And what is gonna stop you?
I know what's gonna stop me.
First year... you think
about it every day.
You relive it.
Doesn't matter what you do.
You can't get it
out of your head.
People tell you
it's part of God's plan.
Maybe they're right,
but it doesn't stop you
from wanting
to punch them in the face
every time they say it.
Then time passes,
two, three years.
Maybe you even start
to feel normal.
Maybe you start to believe
that maybe this thing
won't actually scar you
for the rest of your life.
But then one day,
something reminds you.
A song or a...
or a smell.
And it touches that nerve,
and all of a sudden,
it's the day you got that news
all over again.
So you have gone through
something like this yourself?
I haven't just gone through it.
It's the entire reason
that I became a lawyer.
And as far as it taking
as long as it did,
it took a while
to work out the particulars.
But I can assure you,
it's worth the wait,
because this right here,
this is an all-star team,
and we're playing for you.
Well...
Where do I sign?
All right,
we got that taken care of.
Next step?
Set up a settlement conference.
Got that right.
You mean "You got that right,
partner."
What the hell
are you talking about?
You're the one
that said it yourself.
You and me,
we're the all-star team.
I meant I was the all-star.
You're the team.
Oh, so I guess in this case
the team just hit
the game-winning jumper.
I got news for you, team,
the game hasn't
even started yet.
Mike, seriously, back there,
about your childhood,
I didn't really get it before.
You got dealt a bad hand,
and you pulled yourself up
by your bootstraps,
and I respect that.
Thanks, Robert.
- You can call me "Dad."
- Really?
No.
So you know we're talking
about my father, right,
who's no longer alive?
- Yeah, I forgot that.
- You forgot that?
The basis of your compliment
in the first place?
You suck the fun
out of everything, don't you?
You did this quickly.
You gave me a job to do,
and I did it.
And why did you leave it
on my desk
instead of bringing it
to me directly?
I just wanted to give you
a chance to look it over.
And does that have something
to do with the fact
that I asked you
to check it for exposure
and not rewrite it?
I know, I may have
overstepped my assignment.
It's just Dr. Barnes
is the first black female
chief of surgery
at a major New York hospital.
She faced discrimination
at every turn,
and she still got the job done,
so she doesn't need soaring
language to communicate that.
I'll tell Dr. Barnes
you said that.
So you're accepting my changes?
I'll present them to her
with my blessing.
We'll see what she thinks.
Jessica, um...
if you ever have a case
with Dr. Barnes,
I would love to be a part of it.
I have a better idea.
Why don't you come
to the speech with me?
That is exactly why
we need to figure out a way
to get you on the board
of directors of Comcast.
From your lips to God's ears.
Jack, I'm sorry.
Can I speak to you for a second?
Uh, we're kind of
in the middle of something.
It'll only take a minute.
It's firm business.
I'm afraid it's not optional.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Harvey Specter, by the way,
of Pearson Specter.
This will only take a second.
You think I don't know
what you're doing?
You're trying to poach
my client.
What makes you think
I'm trying to do that?
Please, "Harvey Specter
of Pearson Specter."
Let me tell you something,
guy's been my client
for ten years.
He's not leaving me
for the likes of you.
Then I guess
our business here is done.
What the hell is going on?
Nothing's going on.
You're free.
In fact, I'll walk you back.
Oh, look at that.
Is that Charles Barkley
taking a selfie
with your loyal client
who happened to have grown up
in Philadelphia
during the Barkley era?
Look, you might not
give a shit about Charles,
but he sure as hell does.
You son of a bitch.
I'm sorry, Jack.
Could you repeat that?
I couldn't hear you
over the sound
of me taking your client.
Then let me say it louder.
This isn't over.
It better be, because you've got
four other clients
from Chicago, Boston,
Los Angeles, and Houston.
And you may not know
who those famous ballers are,
but I do.
Will, Jennifer, thank you for
seeing us on such short notice.
Well, you did serve
our client with a lawsuit.
Nevertheless,
we have an offer for you.
You've gotta be kidding me.
You called us all the way
down here for this?
I wouldn't wipe my ass
with this.
Well, Robert, we don't
look at it that way.
How exactly
do you look at it, Will?
We look at it as a gift
to a couple of vultures
trying to pick the flesh
off the bones of an old case.
That is what every lawyer
who has had something to hide
has ever said.
And it doesn't change the fact
that your client
killed 200 people.
Then we're gonna tell you
what we told the last attorney.
You go to trial,
you'll be buried in paperwork
for the next ten years.
Well, if this were yesterday,
then we might be rattled
by that.
But since then, new information
has come to light.
And what new information
is that?
This is a list of everyone
who works at my firm.
And this is a list
of everyone that works at mine.
You see, we're not
some solo practitioner
with a part-time paralegal
working out of a mall.
What my associate is getting at
is we're two huge law firms,
perfectly designed
to kick your ass.
I don't care how many people
work at your firms.
Someone needs
to pay their salaries.
And if you're working on this,
you're not doing that.
Then doesn't it come in handy
to have a $20-billion hedge fund
footing the bill?
So you can either add
a bunch of zeroes
to this bullshit offer,
or we'll see you in court.
Mind if I ask you a question?
If it's about
using my connections
to get Stevie Wonder
to play at your wedding,
I already tried.
Why didn't you tell me
about the hedge fund?
Well, what difference
does it make
where we get our money from?
It doesn't make a difference,
except for the fact
you didn't tell me.
What are you getting
so bent out of shape for?
We landed a punch back there.
We landed a punch or you did?
What's that supposed to mean?
First you call me "associate"
in front of opposing counsel,
and now I find out
you're keeping things from me.
Look...
I'm just saying,
are we a team or not?
I called you
what I called you in there
because they want to see
someone in charge.
And looking at the two of us,
they're gonna think it's me.
And I didn't think
about telling you about Arcadian
because I came up with that
when you weren't there.
For the record,
I had the same idea.
I went to a hedge fund
before I even came to you.
Well, congratulations.
If you had closed them
like I closed my guys,
I wouldn't be standing here
explaining myself.
So let's talk when we hear back
from these clowns.
And put a smile on your face.
You kicked ass in there.
[door opens]
Jack, what can I do for you?
You can get your dog on a leash.
Excuse me?
Harvey just stole
one of my clients.
I want him back.
Do you have proof?
Yeah, he orchestrated
some bullshit run-in
with Charles Barkley,
and miraculously my client,
he needs to make a change.
Well, that's not proof.
I don't need proof.
I know what the hell he did.
Just like I know
what you and Louis did
to pass
your compensation resolution.
And if I had proof of that,
we wouldn't be having
this conversation.
We'd be having
your exit interview.
You gonna sling
accusations at me,
or you gonna get your dog Harvey
under control?
'Cause if you can't control him,
maybe you shouldn't be
in control of this firm.
Control him?
Let me tell you something, Jack.
When you went after Harvey,
you went after me,
which is why I'm the one
that sent him after you
in the first place.
And I just put more money
in every other partner's pocket,
which means you better
listen to me when I talk.
There's only so many times
you can pull some shady shit
to get something done
with the partners.
So you want to take me on?
I'm right here.
[door opens, keys rattle]
(Rachel)
Hey.
What are you working on?
The Kelton case.
Ha.
I've been meaning to ask you,
how's it going with my dad?
It's fine.
It's, uh...
It's going fine.
Mm-hmm, it's fine.
I know what "it's fine" means.
"It's fine" means it's not fine,
and you're realizing
that I was right
and you were wrong,
and he is a giant pain
in the ass.
Rachel, I never said
there wouldn't be arguments.
I just said ultimately
they'd bring us closer.
I know, you did.
I'm not trying to cause trouble.
I was just trying to be
charming and delightful.
Thanks.
Mm-hmm.
[sighs]
It's just...
It's important to me
that your dad respects me.
If there is one thing
that I am certain of,
it's that my father
respects you.
Okay?
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
Harvey, you were right.
That's one of the best steaks
I ever had.
How about you tell me why
you actually brought me here?
Can't a man just take
his client out to dinner?
A man can,
but you need something,
and I just did you
that little favor.
That wasn't a favor.
I took 15 minutes of pictures
with some dipshit
from Philadelphia.
That's not a favor?
That was an appetizer.
I need you to get Magic,
Bird, Hakeem, and Michael
to do the same thing.
You're a funny guy.
You're kidding, right?
Did I ask you
if you were kidding me
when you called me that night?
You asked me to sign with you,
and I did.
And I also said that
I would need something
from you someday,
and taking selfies
with some dipshit Sixers fan
isn't gonna cut it.
Harvey, you need to chill
with this Soloff thing.
If not, every single day
you go into the office,
he's gonna be trying
to stab you in the back.
I'm not here to get
your advice, Charles.
I'm here to get you to help me.
I'm not getting
the Dream Team back together.
It can happen
if you make it happen.
It's not gonna happen.
And the Harvey I know
would never ask me to do it.
Listen, leave a big tip.
People think
I'm paying for the meal.
Put down whatever you're doing.
We need to talk.
You're talking
to a name partner,
so I suggest you do it
with a little respect.
I'm showing respect
by coming to you
to hit Harvey where it hurts.
I told you,
I don't want anything to do
with your war with Harvey.
You already have something
to do with it.
And you said you didn't care
if I backed out.
I don't give a shit what I said.
You picked a side.
There's no going back.
Absolutely not.
I'm not doing it.
This is way too far, Jack.
No, it's what we should have
done in the first place.
Well, you know,
it doesn't even matter,
because you can't introduce
a resolution like this,
'cause it violates the bylaws.
Then you need to do
some underhanded shit
to make it unviolate the bylaws.
And I already told you
that I'm not doing anything
like that again.
Too bad,
because you did it once.
And if you don't want me
telling anybody about it,
you'll do it again.
Good morning, Louis.
Well, looks like
you've been busy.
I have.
Here's the Crenshaw depo,
and this is
the Kirsch itinerary,
and here's your music box.
Why are you giving my gift back?
Because it was a gift
you gave me with a promise
never to put me in a position
like that again.
- And I haven't.
- But you will.
And don't tell me you won't,
because I overheard
your little scheme
with Jack Soloff.
Then you obviously heard me
tell him to go to hell.
No, Louis, I heard him tell you
that you're in this war
whether you like it or not.
And then he walked out
that door,
and you didn't say a damn thing.
I swear I'm gonna
keep my promise.
I am not going after Harvey.
You think this is about me
protecting Harvey?
This is about me protecting me.
What are you talking about?
Harvey came to me
the other night
to get me to admit
that I knew what you did.
He came to you?
In my home.
And I had to stand there
and lose my integrity
in front of him for you.
Oh, my God,
he's really doing it.
Doing what?
After the compensation vote,
Harvey and I got into a fight,
and I told him that
I'd just taken away
the one thing he values most:
his money.
He then tells me
that he's gonna come
after the one thing
that I value most.
Me.
Yes.
Told me that one day
I would come to this office,
you'd be gone,
and I'd know that it was him
who took you away from me.
He said he was gonna
take me away?
Listen to me.
I swear I will never
do that to you again.
But please do not leave me.
I'm not leaving you, Louis.
You get this?
Sure did.
Motion to dismiss.
Yeah. You know
what this means, right?
We got 'em on the ropes.
They're scared.
Which is why
I scheduled a hearing
with Judge Hernandez
for tomorrow morning.
She's gonna dismiss
this bullshit,
and I'm gonna get her to move
straight to trial.
Uh, Robert, that's a bad idea.
What are you talking about?
They throw a jab,
we answer with a right cross.
Yes, if we go to trial now,
we get a decision,
but if we go in three months,
we get a knockout.
What the hell
are you talking about?
There's a bill
on the governor's desk
waiting to be passed.
It lifts the cap
on punitive damages.
There's a reason
he hasn't signed it yet.
The AMA is up his ass.
We go now.
The CEO of Kelton Insurance's
contract is up.
He doesn't want
to be renegotiating
while he's on the front page
of the Journal
being accused of killing people.
That threat takes these people
from $1,000 per person
to $5,000,
but if we actually
go to trial...
If we go to trial,
we may get nothing.
And I'm finished having
this conversation.
So now I see where we stand.
We're not partners.
I'm just the associate.
You're the one
calling the shots.
I thought I made that clear
from the second
we started this thing.
Now answer this motion,
get my motion done,
and be in court
tomorrow morning,
because this is gonna happen
whether you like it or not.
Oh... what the hell?
What the hell what?
You spilled my coffee.
You ran into me.
I don't care who ran into who.
This is my office.
How about a little "excuse me"?
Oh, okay, Harvey.
Excuse me.
Feel free to send me
the bill for dry cleaning.
I'm paying
for everything else around here.
Donna, now is not a good time.
I don't care.
I'm not a prize to be used
to get revenge on Louis.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Are you gonna deny you told him
that you were gonna
take me back?
That is not what I said.
No, do not lawyer me,
because it may not be
exactly what you said,
but don't try to tell me
it wasn't what you meant.
Donna...
And another thing,
what makes you think
if I were ever to leave Louis
that I would ever,
ever come back to you?
Mr. Specter,
I know this is a bad time,
but I have to remind you that...
I know!
Jessica wants to see me.
Donna, hey, can I talk
to you for a second?
It's actually not a good time
right this second.
- It's important.
- [sighs]
I just need to know if Harvey
is still tight
with Judge Hernandez.
Why?
I need her to postpone
a hearing for me.
You know what, Mike?
If you want something
from Harvey,
you're gonna have
to ask him yourself.
(Harvey)
You wanted to see me?
That was 12 hours ago.
I was putting
some things in order.
What things in order,
stealing more
of Jack Soloff's clients?
As a matter of fact, yes.
God damn it, Harvey.
Jessica, I went in there.
I tried to make peace.
He spat in my face.
I tried again.
He did it again.
And I said,
"Enough is enough."
Then you walk out the door.
You don't steal his clients.
You know what?
This doesn't concern you.
This is between me and Jack.
Oh, it was between you and Jack
until he came to me,
and I had to cover for you.
You covered for me?
Goddamn right I did.
I told him sending you
after him was my idea
in the first place.
That's not covering for me.
That's covering for you,
because that should have been
your idea in the first place,
instead of welcoming
every competitor we have
into our offices behind my back.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm talking about Robert Zane
and you bringing him in here
without consulting me.
I didn't bring in shit.
Mike Ross brought Zane in
without asking,
and I had to pretend to be
on board with that too.
And now you're hoping this leads
to what you always wanted.
This thing's over, Zane goes,
and Mike heads
out the door with him.
That's enough.
You need to get yourself
under control right now.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm talking about
you have a problem,
and it doesn't have
anything to do with me.
And you just expose it
by bringing up
some paranoid bullshit
about Mike Ross
going with Robert Zane.
Because this all started
when Donna left you,
and now you're afraid
that Mike's going to do
the same thing.
So you better get
your abandonment issues
under control,
because Jack Soloff
is gonna keep coming,
and now you're gonna
have to put him down.
[heartbeat thumping]
[indistinct voices]
[slow motion]
Mr. Specter,
Mike Ross is waiting for you
in your office.
Hey, I need to talk to you.
Not now.
I know you're mad from before,
but I need a favor.
I said not now.
Harvey, what's going on
with you?
Nothing's wrong.
I need a glass of water.
What the hell is going on?
[heartbeat thumping]
Okay, I'm dialing 911.
No, you're not.
Yes, I am. You could be
having a heart attack.
- It's not a heart attack.
- You don't know that.
It's a panic attack.
Oh, hate to interrupt
a special moment,
but I thought you might wanna
take a gander at this.
What the hell is that?
If you recall, our last proposal
reduced contingent compensation.
This one wipes it out
altogether.
What's the matter?
No snappy comeback?
I've read the bylaws.
You can't do that.
You doing his fighting
for him now?
I don't care
what the bylaws say.
I have Louis's backing.
So either you
give back my client,
or good luck
billing 2,500 hours a year
like the rest of us.
You go right ahead
and put your proposal to a vote.
But by the time
this thing passes,
I'll have
your other four clients.
Bullshit, you couldn't have
gotten to them already.
Go goddamn check.
They're already in play.
You pass this thing,
you won't be billing
anything at all.
You're not gonna
get away with that.
Wrong.
I didn't start this.
But I'm gonna finish it.
And when you said I only ever
looked at you as competition,
you were wrong.
I never looked at you
as anything at all.
Are you all right?
No.
Is it true what you just said
about his clients?
No, which is why I need you
to do anything you have to do
to convince him
this is happening.
I'll get it done.
[knocking]
What are you doing here?
This is my home.
It's also your office.
And that entrance
is right around there.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I'm in the middle of my dinner.
I called to set an appointment.
You didn't call back.
Because I had patients.
And what the hell am I?
You're an ex-patient
I haven't seen in weeks,
who ignored me when I said
that your panic attacks
wouldn't stop
until you accepted the fact
that your secretary
wasn't coming back.
I did accept it,
and I had another one anyway.
That's why I'm here.
You mean you're here
to get more pills.
Yes, I am.
And what happened
to the ones I gave you?
I threw them out.
Bullshit, you didn't
throw them out.
You ran out.
No, I didn't run out.
I'm telling you the truth.
Okay, well, it doesn't matter,
because I'm a psychiatrist,
not a pharmacy,
and if you want my help,
you do it my way.
You make regular appointments,
and you commit
to doing the work.
And you show up at my house
unannounced again,
I'm calling the police.
Do you have any time available
ten minutes from now?
I want to give you time
to finish your dinner.
[upbeat music]
Is the car ready?
It's downstairs
warming up, like you.
What do you mean?
Well, I received the invitation
and couldn't help but notice
that Dr. Barnes
is in the program,
and you're in the program too.
Look at that, I am.
Why didn't you tell me
it was your speech?
I wanted your honest opinion.
But you didn't ask
for my opinion.
You asked me to check it
for exposure.
If there's one thing
I've noticed about you,
it's that you give your opinion
whether it's asked for or not.
And why does my opinion
matter to you so much
that you would
go through all this?
Your opinion
doesn't matter to me.
Your development does.
What are you saying?
Oh, you're gonna make me
say it out loud?
You remind me of me.
And what do I have to do
to get to be like you?
Well, you should know.
You read my damn speech.
You mean I rewrote
your damn speech.
Oh, shit, I said it.
I'm going to show you mercy,
considering your dress choice.
What's wrong with my dress?
Oh, you don't know.
Come on, this is really special.
[Jessica laughs]
You wanna know the truth?
I think you bottled up
your anger at Donna,
let it out at Louis,
and then when
it came back at you,
you pushed it down again.
That's bullshit.
The clinical term
is displacement,
and the cure for it is letting
your anger at Donna out.
Well, I'm not gonna do that,
because even if I would,
Donna's not here.
No, I didn't say you had
to let it out at Donna.
You can let it out at me.
- That's stupid.
- No, it isn't.
If she were here right now,
what's the first thing
that comes to your mind?
Hey, Donna,
what are you doing here?
What if I said,
"I'm here for you"?
I'd say, "Shouldn't you be
at Louis's desk?"
And what if I were?
How would that make you feel?
It would make me feel like
role play is stupid,
because you're not Donna,
and I don't give a shit
what your degree says.
I'm not gonna
go through this again
just to get more pills.
Well, I may not be Donna,
but I'm beginning to see
what it's like to be her.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm talking about I'm a woman
who you've been bullying
to get what you want.
Bullying?
I'm paying you.
And that doesn't mean
that I exist
to serve your needs.
Well, it goddamn should.
If you spoke to Donna that way,
no wonder she left you.
Because you don't just
pay people to be loyal.
How dare you?
I don't give a shit about
the money, and I never did.
No, you didn't.
It was just a way to get me
to do what you wanted.
So when your life
was on the line
and I was there for you
every step of the way,
it meant nothing?
It wasn't every step of the way.
You bailed out
the second I wanted more.
That's when you decided
to betray me.
How the hell is moving on
and putting myself first
betraying you?
Because you went
to Louis to do it,
and that's not moving on.
That's sticking a knife
in my gut and twisting it.
Yeah, Harvey, it is.
How does it feel to be
on the receiving end for once?
Harvey, did you hear me?
I said, how does it feel
to know that
you've taken the first step
towards regaining control?
When someone twists
a knife in your gut,
I feel like I want
to twist one right back.
Mr. Zane,
you scheduled this hearing.
We've been waiting ten minutes.
I'm not waiting any longer.
Uh, you don't have to,
your honor.
My motion is here.
It better get up here fast.
Where the hell were you?
I'm standing up here
with my dick in my hand,
and you're out having a soda.
I had something to do.
Yeah, well, whatever it was,
I hope it was worth
almost losing this case over.
Motion to expedite trial.
I thought this was a hearing
on their motion to dismiss.
Well, if you expedite our trial,
that takes care
of their motion to dismiss.
Your Honor, they just got
this case two days ago.
They're using the timing of
our client's contract expiration
to try to shake us down.
I have to say, Mr. Zane,
I find it hard to believe
that in two days
you've found out enough
to know you need
an expedited trial,
let alone
care about these people at all.
Your Honor, four years ago,
a mail carrier named
Stanley Powell
felt tightness in his chest.
He thought it was nothing,
but his wife insisted
he go to the hospital.
When he got there,
doctors couldn't find
anything wrong,
but they wanted to keep him
for one extra day.
Now unfortunately,
Kelton Insurance refused to pay.
So Mr. Powell went home,
crawled into bed,
and one day later, he was dead.
In front of you,
you have a complaint
that's over 5,000 pages long,
which tells the stories
of another 189 victims.
Pick a page at random,
tell me the number,
and I will tell you exactly
what their client did to them.
Your Honor, are you
actually buying that?
Page 627, Mr....
Lawrence Green.
63-year-old grandfather,
admitted to St. Vincent with
complaints of lower back pain
and excessive weight loss.
He thought it was stress.
Turns out it was lymphoma.
Only they didn't find out
until it was too late
because their client
refused to pay for the MRI.
So please, rule against us
if you have to,
but don't tell me we don't care.
Motion for expedited trial
granted.
Jury selection starts Monday.
[bangs gavel]
For your information,
that's what I was doing.
And it only took
as long as it did
because I was also doing
something for the one person
who has the right to treat me
like his associate
but treats me
like his partner anyway.
Well, if you can forgive me,
what do you say
I take my partner out to lunch?
[soft music]
♪ ♪
Mr. Specter...
Gretchen, whatever it is,
it can wait till tomorrow.
I'm afraid this can't wait.
This is your resume.
I wanted to explain
the two-year gap
in my employment history.
You don't have to do that.
My husband passed away.
My children were grown.
I had no purpose, I felt alone,
and I started
having panic attacks.
And why would I need
to know that?
Because I don't
have them anymore.
Good night, Gretchen.
What was that all about?
Getting to know
my new secretary.
Did you come by just to brag
about helping me with Jack?
I take it that means
he backed down.
Like Roberto Durán
against Sugar Ray.
No más.
Seriously...
you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Thanks.
Want to get a bite or something?
Sure.
I got to warn you,
my stomach's still full
from my lunch with Robert Zane.
Oh, we're lunching now, are we?
Why, you jealous?
No, I just thought
you guys were working a case,
not picnicking in a park.
Let me tell you,
it was no picnic.
You ever try to go
toe-to-toe with that guy
over all-you-can-eat shrimp?
(both)
No más.
Hey, give me a few minutes.
I gotta take care of something.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
You ever take sides with
Jack Soloff against me again,
I will bury you.
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man