Previously on Suits:
We're suing you and your
entire firm for fraud.
I never saw this thing
in my life.
That document
never came into this office,
or you would have seen it.
A lot of people are gonna think
I buried that document.
How can you bury
what doesn't exist?
You think that I don't know
that there's a power struggle
going on between Jessica
and Hardman?
This guy gets one whiff
of what we've been hiding
from Hardman...
I know, we can't trust him.
Louis, is there anything
you want to tell me?
Let me explain
something to you.
That memo doesn't hurt me.
It helps me.
It's gone.
Your actions
have left me no choice
but to terminate your employment
at Pearson Hardman,
effective immediately.
Ray, I need you
to pick me up in an hour,
and I need you
to bring me a tux.
That's thrilling...
I'm not here.
God, what...
what are you doing here?
Are you watching
Diff'rent Strokes?
Uh, yeah, well,
it's the touching story
of a couple of orphans, so...
Don't.
It's a nice building.
How long ago was it condemned?
Oh, great, so did you come
all the way over here
just to criticize
where I live, or...
That's a side benefit.
You've got to be kidding me.
What?
Ah, that... sentimental value.
So just put that away.
- Nice panda.
- Thank you.
Grandmother. Christmas thing.
Get your tux on.
We got a situation.
A situation
that requires a tux?
Where... where
is this tuxedo situation?
Atlantic City.
Can you get dressed now?
- Yeah, I could.
- But?
I don't have a tux.
I'm not Bruce Wayne.
Don't I know it.
Wow.
Rachel.
Louis, hi.
At the ballet.
Are you an aficionado?
Since I was a girl, yes.
Me too. I mean, a boy.
I got that.
So are you...
you here with someone?
You know, Donna was supposed
to come with me,
and then she cancelled
at the last minute.
Oh, you talked to her?
How is she?
No, I haven't.
I keep calling,
but she just won't...
Answer. I know. I tried.
You tried?
Yeah.
Are you here with someone?
Oh, I'm alone.
I feel it's a better way to
experience the dance, you know?
Too distracting
to have to talk about it.
I just want to... To feel it.
No, I know.
- Yeah.
I should probably get going.
Wait. I have an extra ticket,
third row.
Yeah, I like to buy
a seat to my right
just as a precaution.
Yeah. I would love to.
- Great.
- Yeah. Okay.
You just carry around
an extra tux
for the random occasion?
Something told me
you'd need it.
And by "something,"
I mean common sense.
And by "need it,"
I mean you're an idiot.
Haha. So can I ask why
we are going to Atlantic City
instead of just messengering
these contracts? No.
You know, I'm sensing
a little hostility,
and you know what I think?
I think that you're still stung
about Donna,
and you see a chance
to blow off some steam,
and you need a wingman.
Easy, Dr. Phil. We're here.
There. How's that?
That's right.
We're not in Kansas anymore.
Let's move, Dorothy.
You didn't tell me
you were bringing me here.
And that's a problem how?
I'm sort of banned from here.
For smoking weed?
Counting cards.
I mean, I was smoking weed,
but they banned me
for counting cards.
What? My brain just does it.
I can't help
that it keeps track.
And that's your defense?
It was three years ago.
I was broke.
Well, which is it,
your brain just does it,
or you were broke?
What are you,
some kind of lawyer?
Get inside.
You're wearing a tux.
They're not gonna know
who you are.
Speaking of which,
this isn't Havana in the 1950s.
Why do we have to wear tuxes?
What are you, Moe Green?
Moe Green lived in Vegas.
I know where Moe Green lives.
Complimentary champagne?
You think this happens
if you walk in here
in a T-shirt and jeans?
You have a guest, Keith Hoyt.
Can you let him know I'm here?
Mr. Hoyt left a message
for you to meet him
in the Poker Room, Mr. Specter.
The floor manager assured me
that he'd be kept away
from the tables.
I'm sorry, I have
no record of that here, sir.
Double down.
Okay, so let me
get this straight,
he has a gambling problem?
And drinking.
Why is he in Atlantic City?
Because he's
the keynote speaker
at a clean energy conference,
and he promised me
he'd stay out of trouble.
And you took the word
of an addict?
He's been clean five years.
No drinking, no gambling.
So that's why you're here.
You're concerned about him.
- Yes.
- But you also want to gamble.
He has a problem.
I do not have a problem.
Uhhuh.
Holy shit.
Look at this guy.
Those are $25,000 chips.
That's three stacks of four...
by seven...
That is $3,125,000.
That's Keith.
Well, at least we don't have
to worry about him losing.
All in.
- Or...
- Keith.
Harvey.
This is a bad idea.
You haven't seen my hand.
I call.
Straight.
Full house.
- He's got one out.
- Yeah, we're fine
- unless the river's a...
- 10 of clubs.
That is some tough luck
right there.
Tommy, please,
just give me 48 hours.
Sorry, Keith. Deal's a deal.
- Tommy.
- That was insane.
You just lost $3 million.
Who the hell's that guy?
It's worse. That napkin...
Harvey, I just lost my company.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right
♪ all that time imagine this ♪
♪ The greenback boogie
Explain to me,
how you sell your company
on a cocktail napkin
at a poker table.
I didn't sell it.
I just put it up as collateral.
On a cocktail napkin
at a poker table.
I had aces full of kings.
The odds were with him.
Come on, you saw it.
It was bullshit.
The guy rivered me.
No, what's bullshit is,
you should have
never been at that table
in the first place,
much less drunk at that table.
I gave
the keynote speech, Harvey.
They toasted me.
I had... one drink.
You're an alcoholic
at a casino.
You don't get any drinks.
I'm not an alcoholic.
I'm a compulsive gambler.
And those dots
aren't connected?
Let me explain.
You had a drink.
You gambled.
You lost your company.
I know, it was stupid.
Is there anything we can do?
What I should do
is walk through that door
and make you live with this.
Well, you won't, will you?
Because you owe me.
What exactly was on the napkin?
I don't remember exactly,
but the deal was,
he was gonna give me
$3 million to back my bet,
and when I won,
I'd give him his money back
with an extra $1/2 million.
And if you lost,
he'd just get the company.
I didn't think I could lose.
We need to get
a look at that napkin.
Need to get
You need to keep an eye on him
and make sure he doesn't
touch a drink, a chip,
or a deck of cards.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm at Atlantic City.
I'm in a tux.
You want me babysitting?
I'm supposed to be
your wingman.
I'm trusting you with him.
That is being my wingman.
No, th...
- Magnificent.
- Superb.
- Riveting.
- Outrageous.
Insulting.
Disgusting.
Don't let it ruin your evening.
- I'm... I mean, I won't.
- No.
- I won't.
- Yeah.
I wo hey, asshole.
Why don't you have
a little more respect for the...
oh, my God, it's you.
- Yes, it is I.
- Sergei Baskov!
I profaned at you.
I'm so sorry.
No, no, no, please,
you're defending the ballet.
I was defending the ballet.
Our rehearsal space...
two ballerinas
sprained their ankles.
Well, that's why Katya
didn't dance tonight.
- Of course.
- Sadly, yes.
The Royal Hall is
beautiful, magnificent,
but behind the scenes,
they look with a blind eye.
Well, if I may be so bold,
please, it would be my honor
to right this wrong for you.
Oh, I could not impose.
Thank you so much though.
Please, allow me
to be your Nutcracker
and join in the battle
against the Mouse King.
The Mouse King.
Well, in that instance,
then I would be in your debt,
Mr... Light.
- It's actually Mr...
- Wonderful.
Thank you. Wonderful.
Oh, excuse me,
I'm terribly sorry.
You know what
a napkin's good for, Tommy?
That's what
a napkin's good for.
Peter Lawford called.
He wants his tux back.
Let me tell you something.
Steven Spielberg
did a pre-nup on a napkin.
Didn't hold up,
which is why Amy Irving
is the richest out-of-work
actress in Hollywood.
That's because
his napkin didn't meet
the minimum requirements
of a contract.
My client's does.
Why did you ask me what exactly
was written on the napkin?
'Cause no matter
what it was written on,
for a contract to be valid,
it needs to have three things:
An offer, acceptance...
And consideration.
- What's consideration?
- Quid pro quo.
You both get something.
Like I get his chips
and he gets my...
Company. That is a valid...
Contract, yes.
You forgot one thing:
Competence.
My client was drunk,
and you knew it.
Do you have proof of that?
How many drinks did he have?
- I don't remember.
- That's a good start.
Well, here's
what's gonna happen.
We're going to give you
your money back
and throw in the $500,000
you would have
gotten had Keith won,
and then we're never
gonna hear from you again.
Sorry.
My advisors tell me that that
company's worth $30 million,
and I'm keeping it.
Well, when you show up to
open the door with your napkin,
it's not gonna fit in the lock.
So if he wants
to take your company,
he's gonna have
to do it in court.
And then,
you'll be playing at my table.
I need a list of everything
that's wrong
with the rehearsal space.
For example,
the creaky floorboards,
they're affecting
certain dancers' attitudes.
Oh, they shouldn't
let that get them down.
"Attitude" is a pose.
Oh, yeah,
like striking an attitude.
Whatever, I do that
all the time.
Okay.
I also need a list of
the ballet company principals.
Okay, um, integrity, fidelity,
patriotism...
Not that kind of principle.
- Okay, we're done.
- How am I supposed to know?
Rachel, you've
just been drafted.
Oh, but she's not even a...
Not what?
She's not what, Harold?
Ms. Zane not only knows
more about ballet than you do,
she also knows more about law.
- But...
- Zip it.
My mind's been racing ever since
we met Sergei yesterday,
so I dictated a to-do list
for you to handle.
I'm on it.
Okay.
- Jessica.
- Where are you?
- In a meeting.
- Do people often yell.
"I hit the jackpot"
in your meetings?
If you know where I am,
why are you asking?
Because the answer tells me
I should be worried.
It's just poker.
Harvey, I know
losing Donna's been hard.
I'm fine.
You haven't hired
her replacement.
She's irreplaceable.
- I'm assigning you a temp.
- Excellent.
Not for you. You should fold.
- Damn it.
- I swear I'm listening.
No, no, the judge
assigned to your fraud case
just denied our motion to seal.
What?
That motion's a slam dunk,
and we need it.
Who's the judge? Ella Follman.
Don't know her. You?
I'm about to.
We're already being sued,
but I guess she decided
my headache wasn't big enough.
Now come home before
you wind up in trouble.
I'm doing just fine.
I had nothing.
Are you trying to impress me?
With nothing?
I don't remember you
impressing that easily.
I don't remember
being impressed at all.
I need copies of last night's
poker room security footage.
- I can't give you that.
- Yes, you can.
And you will.
Thank you.
Hello, Jessica.
Ella... Ella Medeiros.
Ella Follman. Married name.
- I haven't seen you since...
- Your little prank?
Oh, the things we do
when we're young.
- What can I do for you?
- You denied our motion.
I have to say, I'd assumed
it was a formality.
Well, you know what
they say about assuming.
- Ella...
- It's Judge Follman.
Judge Follman...
These allegations are serious.
I know how serious they are,
and I also know how important
this case is to your firm.
Then you also know that,
until proven,
they have no business being
placed in public record.
I see what you're saying.
Humiliating someone for no good
reason doesn't seem fair.
Do we have a problem?
No, not at all.
I just happen to be
of the opinion
that trials are about truth.
And truth requires openness.
Rest assured, Jessica,
those who have done wrong
will get what's coming to them.
There's one thing
I'm not clear on.
Go through the security footage
and count the number
of drinks Keith had.
We establish his state of mind,
then file a motion to dismiss.
How hard is that?
Not the thing I'm unclear on.
I don't have time to explain
where babies come from.
How exactly did you
get this footage?
Head of security owed me one.
Which brings me
to my next question:
Everyone always owes you one,
but Keith says you owe him one.
Why?
Why don't you just ask him?
- I did. He wouldn't tell me.
- Exactly.
Because if he had,
I wouldn't owe him one anymore.
Mr. Specter, I'm Cameron,
your new assistant.
- Where are my...
- Messages.
Urgent to normal,
top to bottom.
I also took it upon myself
to fan the folders
on your desk
in alphabetical order.
Wow, look at that, Harvey.
He fanned your folders
in an order of some sort.
I also reorganized
your filing system
and redid your calendar.
Ha, that is not going
to be a problem at all
because Harvey loves change.
- It was a train wreck.
- Yep.
He's in mourning
over your predecessor.
Her filing system,
her calendar...
it's probably best
if nothing else
is different in there
this morning, okay?
- Uh-oh.
- Mike...
Yeah.
You might want
to take an early lunch.
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
Harold, can I get the rest
of the files on the ballet case?
Sure, let me grab them for you.
Thank you.
What is it about ballet?
I just... I don't get it,
you know?
There's no words,
there's no story,
there's no action.
It's just all...
and...
and like... I don't...
Please tell me
that Louis isn't behind me.
Louis isn't behind you.
Hi. Hi.
Penelope Cruz, Zoe Saldana,
Audrey Hepburn...
what do they
all have in common?
- They're all hot?
- No, dumb-ass.
They all owe
their success to ballet
because it gives them
discipline and grace,
it embodies our emotions,
it's breathtaking in its beauty,
and most importantly,
it expresses what cannot
be put into words.
You want
to get ahead here, Harold?
Take ballet, because right now,
the only thing
that's breathtaking about you
can easily be put
into words: Nothing.
Now releve your ass
back to work.
I need everything you got for me
first thing tomorrow.
- I'm on it.
- Good.
Yes, immediately. Thank you.
What happened
with Judge Follman?
There might
be a slight problem.
What did you do?
Why do you assume
I did something?
- What did you do?
- There was a prank.
How bad was it?
We went to law school
together, and I got her drunk.
- So?
- So she woke up in front of
the entire con law class.
- It's recoverable.
- She might have been naked.
- "Might have"?
- Was.
- We're screwed.
- Come on, Harvey.
She was uptight.
I just straightened her out.
It's what you do
with uptight people.
Why don't you
ever do that to Louis?
I did.
That was you? He blamed me.
You can be uptight
sometimes too.
That's why I let him
think it was you.
- Told him it was me.
- That's what I said.
- It's okay, I deserved it.
- What?
Do you remember
when he was so mad
when his cat peed
in the corner of his office?
- Mm-hmm.
- That wasn't his cat.
You know, this is no joke.
We're being sued.
I'm in trouble.
- I know.
- What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna get her off our case.
Hey.
You're studying up
to break the house?
Counting drinks.
Don't most people count cards?
It's a thing.
Ah! Right there. You see that?
Drink number 15.
Your client? That's awful.
No, no, no, it's good.
We're even putting him in rehab
to help nullify his contract.
Touching.
Harvey truly cares
about his clients.
Uhuhuh, my idea.
Well, you're really
coming along.
What are you
doing here so late?
Working with Louis.
I'm sorry? With Louis?
Associate work.
He, um... he replaced
Harold with me.
Good for you.
Looks like you're
really coming along.
Thank you, Mike.
And that was
the last drink of the night.
16 drinks in 11 hours
in a 180-pound man,
and that's a blood
alcohol level of .16%,
double the legal limit.
Your Honor, you've heard
the expression "beer goggles."
Well, when my client was looking
at that dirty napkin,
all he saw was Angelina Jolie.
Your Honor, my client
entered into a contract
with a man that was
aware enough to realize
that he had a good hand,
aware enough to ask for help,
aware enough to sign
a piece of paper
for the sole purpose of winning
a large pot of money,
and now he's mad he lost.
Our client has
a history of drinking
and has agreed
to be placed into rehab.
That has nothing
to do with this.
That tape clearly shows
that Keith didn't
make any of those decisions
while he was sober.
Maybe not. But you did.
What?
The next morning,
you came to my client
and offered to pay him what
you'd owed him if you'd won.
I don't care what he says
about his client's
state of mind,
he was stone-cold sober.
Which clearly demonstrates
they were perfectly happy
with the terms of the contract.
Your Honor,
those were settlement talks,
not subject to disclosure here.
Mr. Specter, you're asking me
to dismiss this contract
without a trial.
Let's have it.
Yes, I made an offer.
Then I'm sorry, counselor,
I'm not ruling for dismissal.
This goes forward to trial.
This guy is pissing me off.
Yeah, he's really good.
Kind of inspiring, actually.
You trying to piss me off more?
Yeah, it focuses you.
It's what you do to me.
Yeah, I do that
because you don't have
a natural killer instinct.
Yes, I do.
Good, because
I need you to use it.
See what I did there?
Yeah. What's our end game?
Interim control of the company.
Possession is 9/10 of the law.
Whoever is in control
in the interim
is likely to be
in control in the end.
Plus, if we're
in the driver's seat,
we can drag
this trial out forever.
And we can do anything
we want in the meantime.
By the time this is over,
he won't even get back
his $3 million in chips.
What do you need me to do?
Find out everything
there is to know
about this Tommy guy
and get his ass in here
for a deposition.
On it.
Louis, I finished.
You were here all night?
You said you wanted everything
by this morning,
so here's everything
on the lease agreements
and all of the financials.
Oh, no, Sergei waltzed me
through the financials earlier.
Did you know that
he danced with Nureyev?
I did. Um, also...
I found this.
Lead paint?
Okay, this is... excellent.
- You can use it?
- "Use it"?
We are gonna pas de deux
all over their asses with it.
"We"?
- Get out.
- Okay.
Here to buy me a drink?
That didn't go so well
for me last time.
No. No, I'm here
same as everyone else,
to contribute to
your reelection campaign.
Actually, I already did.
Pearson Hardman is
now a platinum-level donor.
Go, Follman.
I know what you're doing.
Of course, you don't have
to disclose this,
and neither do we,
but I am of the opinion
that elections are about truth,
and truth requires openness.
You think
you can get me to recuse
by implying
a conflict of interest?
You know,
I hadn't thought of that.
I'll simply return the money.
That is certainly
your prerogative.
But it could look like
you took money for favors
and then got scared.
No one forced liquor
down your throat, Ella.
You got drunk,
we played a bad joke,
but that was a long time ago.
You know, a man's reputation
is at stake,
and I'm not
joking with you now.
Cheers.
Lastly, section 5,
page 30 states
that the Royal Hall
is responsible
for all maintenance and repairs
of the rehearsal space.
I'm aware of what
the lease says, Mr. Litt,
having drafted it myself.
Okay, well, then
how do you explain this?
The Royal Hall's
knowing failure to fix
the air conditioning system
has created a toxic environment.
Lead-based paint.
See, your disregard
for the safety of your charges
takes it from a tenant dispute
to a criminal action,
a fact that
I will happily bring
to the attention
of the district attorney
unless repairs
are made yesterday.
Then you'll be exposing
the ballet itself
because the terms require
they cover all repairs
from a special fund they
stopped paying into a year ago.
No, no, no, no, payments have
been going out every month.
Then perhaps
you should figure out
where they've been going in
because it's not here.
I'm sorry. I don't understand.
Our financial records say...
Mr. Litt,
we were willing
to look the other way,
but since you have come in here
and threatened me,
I'm going to take
legal action of my own.
We'll be filing for eviction.
It's time the ballet moves on.
Can you tell me what
this is exactly, Mr. Walsh?
I don't know.
If I told you
it was a yaw drive,
would that mean
anything to you?
A yaw drive keeps the rotor
facing the right way,
even when
the wind direction changes.
If you have a problem with this,
you're not getting any power.
I'm sorry, where exactly
did you study engineering?
I didn't.
But you're suggesting that
you can run an energy company.
My client's
gonna be running it,
not designing parts.
Well, does your client
have any idea
how to protect the company
from the numerous allegations
made by the Jarvis
Homeowners Association?
Are you even
aware of these allegations?
I haven't taken over
the company yet, Mr. Specter.
Well, let me explain
something to you.
My client's company
needs to remain viable
during the course
of this trial,
and these allegations are
a threat to its very existence.
And I don't think someone
who doesn't know the difference
between a yaw drive
and a carburetor
is the man for the job.
He's right.
I don't know
anything about energy.
And I'll tell you
something else:
I also know very little
about ice cream.
Yeah, I mean, I enjoy vanilla,
but beyond that, nothing.
Vanilla... could've guessed.
I assume you have a point.
I don't know anything
about any of the companies
that I've turned around.
But I don't have to
because I hire experts
to advise me on operating them.
And the one thing all
these experts have in common
is that none of them
has a drinking problem.
- Your Honor...
- He raised the issue.
His client... and I quote...
"has a history of drinking"
and was, in fact,
so intoxicated that night
that his own lawyers
had to place him to rehab.
He disputed that.
That is not
the subject of this hearing.
- Your Honor, he's trying to...
- I know what he's trying to do.
He's using
your words against you.
But they are your words,
Mr. Specter.
The issue of the napkin contract
will be heard at trial,
but in the interim,
Thomas Walsh
will assume control
of the company.
Thank you.
This is just wrong.
I know, this ruling
doesn't make any sense.
No, I meant this.
- The hot dog is wrong?
- It's a truck.
This is New York.
I want a cart, a vendor,
or a vague sense of danger,
that the hot dog might
be made of anything.
Okay, well, I think
I saw some cats
lurking out behind the truck.
Stop trying
to make me feel better.
Not so bad.
All right, street meat,
you wanna talk
about what just happened?
No, I don't.
You said whoever's in control
in the interim...
- I know what I said.
- So what's the other 1/10?
What are you talking about?
You said possession
is 9/10 of the law.
So I figure we need
the other 1/10, right?
- We're not gonna win this.
- What?
- We don't have him.
- It's a 10% chance,
but it's still a chance.
I mean, the odds are...
I'm not talking about the odds,
I'm talking about the man.
Wow, I've never heard you say
another lawyer's
better than you before.
He's not,
he's just got a better hand,
and he knows it.
- What if we play a new hand?
- I'm listening.
You're always talking
about this gun
being pointed at your head.
What if we take off our jacket
and show them that we have
a bomb strapped to our chest?
It's a metaphor, metaphor.
- You wanted to see me?
- It was Sergei.
He lied to me.
The money went
into his account.
There's no way
that you could have...
What, known?
It's my job to know.
God, I never take anyone
at their word.
You know I was eight years old
when I saw him perform
The Nutcracker?
Eight.
Everybody else was into sports,
and I was this rebel,
gliding down my own path.
He inspired me.
That's why I'm
so light on my feet.
I just can't do it to him.
I cannot do it to him, Rachel.
He is the ballet.
No, the ballet
is bigger than Sergei.
It embodies our emotions,
it is breathtaking
in its beauty,
and most importantly,
it expresses what cannot
be put into words.
- Yes, but...
- No buts.
The Louis I know wouldn't be
defeated by something like this.
He is ruthless. He is mean.
And if someone wronged him,
he wouldn't hesitate
to tear them apart
limb from limb.
You ruined everything.
I took your help,
and now we're evicted!
I want to...
Shut up, Sergei.
- How dare you?
- Me?
You, you brought disgrace
on my beloved ballet.
- I am the ballet.
- You were the ballet.
And now you're done,
and the Royal Hall,
they've been paid.
How?
I reorganized accounts,
moved money.
I did what I do.
I showed them how
they can pay for everything
by eliminating
your bloated salary.
Well,
the board would never agree,
so it's ridiculous.
Oh, please, stop.
It's why they're here, Sergei.
This isn't about the eviction.
They know what you've done.
They want to see your face
when they tell you you're fired.
But I'm giving you one chance
to avoid scandal.
My leaving is a scandal.
Your leaving is a gift.
Take it before
I change my mind.
You wanted to see me?
That was a good speech.
Got me right here.
The only thing is,
you said, "we played a joke."
There was no "we." It was you.
You targeted me.
What do you want me to say?
I was young, I was stupid,
and I'm sorry.
You were young and smart,
and I don't believe
you're sorry for a second
because it was no accident
that the classroom you chose
belonged to the Professor
who was conducting
the interviews
for the job we both wanted.
- I had no idea.
- You sabotaged me.
There were
dozens of applicants.
No, we both know
it was you or me.
- I didn't know that he...
- Objection.
Bullshit.
What do you want, Ella?
I want to recuse myself.
On one condition:
Admit you know what you did.
I wanted that job.
I know what I did.
I'm not sorry I did it.
And I'd do it again.
You look confused.
I am.
About what?
I...like Louis.
Trust me, I've been there.
Doesn't last.
Oh, my God. Is that...
is that Louis' dictaphone?
Oh, yeah, I needed it
to transcribe the notes
for the ballet case.
Do you have any idea
what this means?
Rachel, this is a window
into the mind of Louis Litt.
It's a dictaphone.
That he treats
like his best friend.
- Mike.
- Ahh... come on, gotta try it.
Goal number seven:
Perfect the British accent.
Hey, top of the morning, mate.
Would ya like
some tea and crumpets?
- Yes!
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
We really...
we really shouldn't.
Oh, no, but I think
we really, really should.
Come up with a catchphrase.
Injunct this.
Hey, Harold, injunct this.
This is insane.
Insanely awesome.
You just got Litt up.
Excuse me, Miss Zane,
you just got Litt up.
- Oh, no, Rachel.
- No, no, no! Enough.
- No, you just got Litt up.
- I feel dirty.
Wait, wait,
this is a gold mine.
One more, come on.
They're settling?
You wanted that?
Wanted it?
I goddamn orchestrated it.
CM plays what they should have
in the first place,
and the suit
against us goes away.
And Daniel Hardman's
none the wiser.
Where the hell is Donna?
He recorded us.
He must have planted this
in Harvey's office.
No, th... that's horrible.
- That's why he turned on me.
- Wait a minute.
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
But if I tell Harvey about this,
he is gonna kill Louis.
Come on, let's go.
They're in the conference room.
- Okay.
- Everything all right?
Uh, yeah, no.
Did you get
that power of attorney?
Yeah. Let's go
set off that bomb.
Thanks.
By the way, where did you
find that yaw drive anyway?
Pulled it out
of the back of a photocopier.
Gentlemen, as you are
now in control of the company,
we thought it best to bring
a problem to your attention.
How selfless of you.
These are amended copies
of the allegations
against your company by the
Jarvis Homeowners Association.
Nice try.
I looked into those allegations.
Not a single expert has backed
one of their claims.
- Well, one has now.
- Keith Hoyt.
Who better to speak
to the harmful effects
than the man who designed
the wind farm himself?
No, no, if he
goes through with this,
that company
goes out of business.
There's no way he kills
his own company.
You're right, he wouldn't.
But I would,
and as you pointed out,
Keith's judgment
has been impaired lately,
so I convinced him to let me
make the decisions
going forward.
I now have power of attorney,
and I'd rather see
this company worth nothing
than let you have it.
- This is bullshit.
- Let him finish.
Something's coming.
We have three choices here.
We move forward with the suit...
lose-lose...
we can give you your money back,
plus the $500,000,
or you and I
can play poker for it.
And I'm not giving you
your money back.
Are you crazy?
You're gonna gamble
a man's company?
What, no, you're gonna
gamble for $30 million?
It was your idea.
No, it was my idea
to make him take the $500,000.
But it's not $500,000,
it's $3.5 million.
Why give him that when
I could take it for free?
Okay.
But let me take it.
What? A minute ago,
you were ready to fold.
What are you gonna do
if he goes all in?
Harvey, I know
the odds of every card
in every hand
before it's even dealt.
Pick a card in your mind,
any card.
Wh.
Okay, what, now you're gonna
tell me what the card is?
I'm gonna tell you
what it isn't.
It's not one of
the 52 cards in a deck
because you think
you're smarter than me.
It's a baseball card
or football card or...
It's the joker.
I told you this before.
I'm gonna tell you again.
I don't play the odds.
I play the man.
Well, let me
tell you one thing.
- What?
- Louis bugged your office.
He heard our whole conversation
about Tanner's lawsuit,
and then he ran,
and he told Hardman.
You just saying that
to make me mad, so I can focus?
You're not the only one
who can play the man.
You really think
you can handle me?
Oh, I think I'll be just fine.
'Cause this isn't
Sunday afternoon bridge
with your grandmother.
I don't see how that's
an insult to a person.
I'll just keep dealing.
Look, we're supposed to play
until one of us is busted,
even if it takes all night,
but you know what?
I don't have all night.
Who's the grandmother now?
Better.
He can't help you.
But I do know why
you're looking to him.
You see, I looked into you.
You say you're a self-made man.
Your ex-wife
had a different story
when she told me
why she left you.
She said you had
a chip on your shoulder
because everything you ever got
came from daddy.
Now, you may not think
this is true anymore.
You said yourself,
you're not an expert.
But you hire them
to advise you,
run your companies,
and fight your battles.
Tonight, it's you, me,
and that stack of chips.
Let's play.
You think you can
bait me into calling you
when you got me beat?
You're gonna have
to do better than that.
You're right, Tommy,
I do have you beat.
But these shity cards,
they don't have
anything to do with it.
After that, he was on tilt,
never recovered.
Took me 20 minutes to bust him.
Are you out
of your goddamn mind?
How fast did you
want me to beat him?
That's not what I meant,
and you know it.
You're out of control.
I'm fine.
Fine? Let me
connect the dots for you.
Donna's gone.
You took Mike to a casino,
and two days later,
you're gambling
with a client's
$30 million company.
I wasn't gambling,
I was playing poker.
- Harvey, save it.
- Save it?
Gambling is what you do when
you're playing against the house
and hoping to get Blackjack.
I'm playing against people,
and against people, I win.
In a back room card game,
that might be true,
but you didn't know
anything about this guy.
He could've been Phil Ivey
for all you know.
You're gonna beat Phil Ivey?
No, I did know,
and I was right.
This time.
But you know what else gambling
and what you did
have in common?
This.
You think I didn't remember
your "Life is this,
and I like this" speech?
When you get that from your job,
it's one thing,
but then you start chasing it.
No, I wasn't chasing it.
We were going
to lose this in court.
- Then lose.
- No! I am not...
You're not what? A human being?
We're people,
and sometimes we lose.
Sometimes?
Look, I don't know about you,
but I feel like that's
all we've been doing lately.
Hardman's back, Donna's gone,
we're being sued...
I mean, we're fighting
for our goddamn lives here.
I just had a huge win,
and I am not in the mood to hear
why it might have
turned out as a loss.
Harvey...
you're right.
We are being sued,
and our backs
are against the wall,
and I need to know
that this bullshit
is out of your system
and that you can focus.
Can you do that?
I'm focused.
I was...
I don't give a shit
what you were doing.
You know, Harvey, you can
make fun of me all you want,
but watch your tone.
What the hell is that?
That's not yours.
This is a violation
of my privacy.
You know what,
I have a right to know
what's going on at this firm,
just as much as you.
Okay. Did you tell Jessica?
There's gonna
come a day, Louis,
when I need something from you,
and when I do, you're gonna
remember that I let this pass.
Daniel Hardman
is not the answer.
You owe me.