Uh...
What is that,
three in a row?
That would be four,
actually.
Oh, God.
Come on. What do you say?
We go five out of nine?
So you can keep abusing me?
No, thank you. I'm done.
Oh, come on.
I'll spot you three.
Game time's over, Wyatt.
They're here.
They're here?
Get set up in the conference room.
Yeah.
No, I'll just, uh...
Get set up
in the conference room.
You did let him win,
right?
It wasn't easy. The guy has
the coordination of a two-year-old.
I know. The last time
these venture capitalists came in,
I took him boxing
to calm him down.
I basically had to punch myself
in the face to let him win.
I don't get it.
I mean, if he's such a genius,
why does he get so nervous
around a bunch of investors?
Well,
you spend two years
working on a satellite phone
that fits in your pocket
and then bet
the company on it.
You'd be a little nervous, too,
I bet.
The prototype. I can't find it.
I don't know where I...
You mean this?
I don't know what I'd do without you.
- Fail miserably.
- I would.
- Is that the, uh...
- $20 million prototype, yes.
And you don't even get to look
at this bad boy
until after we close
the deal today.
Wow.
They're like storm troopers.
Storm troopers
don't write checks.
All you've got to do
is walk in there,
show them
how the phone works.
Right.
And Suntech Digital
will be a new force
in global communications.
Let's knock them dead.
All right.
Whoa, whoa.
Where do you think you're going?
Into the room.
With the people.
Wrong.
That's the adult table in there,
and you haven't earned
the privilege yet.
But I...
I played air hockey with him.
You need to go back to the office
and file the patent for the phone.
A patent?
I don't know how to file a patent.
- Figure it out.
- Can't we do that after...
No. And you keep talking,
I'm going to start billing you.
And my time
runs $1,000 an hour.
"But isn't this our time,
Mr. Hand?"
I stand corrected. Your
Fast Times at Ridgemont High quote,
that proves you belong
at the adult table.
Right. That's a great movie,
and it spoke to a generation.
Hey. You busy?
Okay. Have you ever
filed a patent before?
I just got back
from this meeting with Harvey,
and he wants me
to file this patent,
but I have no idea
what that paperwork looks like. So...
You know, any help in this arena
would be really...
Did Harvey call you
and tell you to do that?
If it isn't the golden boy.
You're, uh, Harvey's project, right?
What's your name?
Mike. Mike Ross.
Gregory Boone.
So what are you doing here?
Weren't you signing some big deal
this afternoon downtown?
Well, evidently,
I haven't earned the privilege yet.
You get
the adult table speech?
Instead of watching the deal close,
I get to file the patent.
Yeah, those suck.
Wait. You...
You've done one of these before?
Like, a hundred.
Why?
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
Oh. It's okay.
You don't have to apologize.
I took care of it.
The patent claim?
I negotiated a deal to get it done.
What are you
talking about?
Gregory.
He agreed to file it for me.
And all I have to do
is proof his Bainbridge briefs.
Ah. That explains
why he said to give you this.
And why he called you
a sucker.
He called me a what, now?
Mike Ross, allow me
to introduce the Bainbridge briefs.
- Which stack?
- All of them.
Wait a minute.
Are these all...
Still printing?
Yeah. I give it about a half hour.
Oh. It's six printers,
23 pages a minute, 30 minutes.
That's 4,140 pages.
Plus all this.
Which means the next time
you negotiate a deal,
I would suggest
you get your facts straight.
Ugh! I am a sucker.
Mmm-hmm.
When did that happen?
See the money, wanna stay
for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
Nice of you
to join us this morning.
For your information,
Mr. Sunshine,
I've been here all night proofing.
That belongs to... Okay.
Where's my confirmation?
Your what?
The fact that you don't know
already concerns me.
Oh, you mean
the patent thing?
The patent thing
is the only piece of paper
that's holding up our deal
from yesterday. Where is it?
On my desk.
Well, if it's not on mine
by the time I get back,
I'm going to
feed you to Louis.
No problem.
Please tell me
that you filed that.
Patent? No, not yet.
I gave it to you yesterday.
The same time I gave you
my Bainbridge briefs,
which you
haven't finished.
I was here all night
and I barely got through half.
And I was on hold
for almost 11 minutes
before I gave up on your patent.
So what's your point?
Look. I swear
I will finish those filings.
But you have to give me this patent
confirmation before Harvey gets back.
Sorry, Golden Boy.
A deal's a deal.
What do you think
you're doing?
Uh, I'm proofing briefs.
Why? Is there a problem?
Yeah, there is.
That's Gregory's responsibility.
Why are you handling it?
Oh, I volunteered.
He didn't
pawn it off on you?
No. No. I mean, he didn't even
want me to do it,
but I... You know,
I had some extra time, so I insisted.
Congratulations.
You've shown loyalty
to your fellow associates.
I know Gregory tricked you
into doing his work.
I wanted to see how you'd react
when pressed about it.
You held up.
I respect that.
Thanks?
You see, but I don't understand
something, though.
If you didn't know
how to file a patent,
then why didn't you
just run to Harvey?
He was busy.
But you see, Mike,
that's why you come to see me.
Look, Mike,
I know I can come across a bit
prickly.
But we're
a team here.
That means
I'm here to help.
Okay. All right.
So, can you help me now?
I already have.
All right.
Thank you, Louis.
Donna. Blue is your color.
Is Harvey back?
No.
Can I put this
on his desk?
Yes.
Will you tell him
I put it there hours ago?
What time
you want me to say?
11:00 a.m?
Absolutely.
And then maybe I can use my access
to his bank accounts
to buy myself
a house in the Hamptons.
- 12:15?
- No.
You wanted to see me?
Sit down.
I looked through your work
on the Bainbridge briefs.
Spectacular.
You caught
the discrepancies between
"listed assets"
and "potential assets."
That had a huge impact,
Mike.
Yeah. I know. Millions. But anyone
would have caught that, right?
Um, out of the 50 associates
that are under my purview,
not one of them
would have caught that.
You just have
this eye for detail, Mike.
I mean, no wonder why Harvey
is so crazy about you.
It's amazing. I mean, I really,
really, seriously appreciate that.
Hey, thank you, Louis.
That...
That's nice.
You know that I pick
a pony out of the herd every year,
don't you?
- A pony?
- Oh, yeah.
Someone
who shows potential.
Stamp my own little brand
on him.
Mmm.
Are you that pony,
Mike?
I work for Harvey.
As you should.
Good.
Well, listen,
I have some work to get to.
So, maybe we can,
uh, meet for lunch
tomorrow at the club,
say 1:00 p.m?
Uh, you know,
tomorrow...
I know I just posed that
as a question,
but I really
didn't mean it that way.
Hey. What's up?
I just heard from Wyatt. He got
a response from the patent office.
And?
It's been denied.
What?
Evidently,
there was a similar claim.
Wait. What do you mean?
Somebody beat us to it?
No,
someone beat you to it.
They filed
less than 24 hours ago,
which means you filed a day later
than you said you would.
I tried to tell you
that I didn't know how to do that.
And I told you
to figure it out.
And I did
and it got filed.
After you lied
and said you'd already followed through.
Okay.
What's going to happen now?
I suggest you get on the phone,
call the patent office,
and find out
who beat us to it.
Then you're going to have Donna
find any judge who will listen
so we can get an injunction
and stop whoever it is
from launching their product first.
Okay. Got it.
Now I've got to call Wyatt
and calm him down.
You think that's going to be
a walk in the park?
Hey. Harvey.
Did you tell him
it was me?
Why would I do that?
I'm responsible for you. It was me.
They signed the paperwork, Wyatt.
They can't pull out.
The patent dispute is not an issue.
Okay?
No, they cut the check.
End of story.
I'm at court right now.
Let me call you back.
So, it's Velocity Data Solutions.
Did you serve them
with notice of the hearing?
They're a billion dollar company.
The bigger they are,
the harder they fall.
Did you not see
the sign outside?
Just putting it away,
Your Honor.
It should already be
in your pocket.
But you were running late,
so perhaps that's why it wasn't.
Let the record show
that Counsel is fined $1,000
for failing to follow
the posted rules of the court.
- Your Honor, I didn't mean to...
- And for mouthing off.
Mouthing off?
Another outburst like that,
and you will be escorted out.
Wow.
Mr. Salinger.
Your Honor,
this is a waste of your time.
The U.S. Patent Office
is the only judicial body
that should be handling
this dispute.
Velocity Data Solutions
requests dismissal.
Your Honor.
If I may.
- This injunction request is...
- Counsels, approach.
That's the exhibit filing?
Why wasn't I given
a courtesy copy?
Given the expedited nature
of this hearing, I assumed...
Hand it to me.
Hand it to me?
And I would have assumed
that a lawyer appearing before a judge
would come on time,
with his mouth shut,
and prepared
with a courtesy brief.
My apologies.
Request denied.
Court adjourned
for the morning.
Better luck next time,
Harvey.
From now on, I want him
when I go against you.
Wait here.
- Your Honor? I have...
- Send him in.
Counselor?
You asked to see me.
You must have something to say.
Excluding friends, associates,
and the clients that I represent,
there are very few people
that I'm on a first-name basis with.
And I've never had anyone,
let alone a judge I've never met,
address me as Harvey
in open court.
But if you're going
to screw me,
I guess it's only fair
that you call me by name.
I could have you brought up on review
for talking to me like that.
Then we can get it
all on record.
Get what?
Whatever it is that you seem to have
against me for no apparent reason.
I have a solid argument for any
reasonable judge to grant my injunction.
So solid,
it begs the question,
why do you
have it in for me?
And I don't even know
your first name.
Really?
My wife never mentioned it?
Your wife?
The woman you had an affair with
last month?
Hey, wait.
What happened in there?
Donna. The address for that fundraiser
at the gallery last month?
I need you to text it to me
and clear my afternoon.
Hey.
Where are we going?
You're going
back to the office
to file an interference claim
with the Patent Office.
Okay. Wait.
What's that?
It's how they determine
who wins these situations.
It's not always who filed first,
so we have a chance.
So why didn't we do that
in the first place?
Because it takes longer and I wanted
to head Velocity off at the pass.
Hey,
where are you going?
To iron out a wrinkle.
If you're really interested,
come back tomorrow around 1:00.
The afternoon light
really makes this canvas come alive.
Pardon me.
I was wondering,
would I get a discount for being the guy
you cheated on your husband with?
Can you excuse me
for a second?
What are you doing here?
I had a hearing
in front of the judge this morning.
It didn't go very well.
Why did you lie to him?
I'm sorry.
I mean,
I recall you being tipsy that night,
but I'm finding it hard to believe
that your memory is so cloudy,
you forgot
I sent you home in a cab.
After humiliating me.
Well,
I was a perfect gentleman.
Yes, exactly.
I fall all over myself
making a pass,
and you do the right thing
and send me home.
Okay.
I'm sorry you felt humiliated.
But I told you
I don't sleep with married women.
Right.
The moral code.
No. It's too big
of a pain in the ass.
As evidenced by my experience
in court this morning.
What do you want from me,
Harvey?
I need you
to tell him the truth.
- I can't.
- Yes, you can.
Why didn't you
just tell him?
He's never
going to believe me.
And what makes you think
he'll believe me?
Because he'd want to.
Our whole marriage, Donald's only ever
cared about one thing.
His sterling reputation.
Never overturned.
I was...
When he found out you and I had...
He changed.
Looked at me for the first time again.
Like I mattered.
I'm sorry.
I can't tell him.
No, this is a request
from the applicant for...
Yes, but I have up to a year
before you...
Hello?
No, I can't hold.
You ready?
I can't go to the club.
I have to do this for Harvey.
Yes, the person before you
said that I had to file the blue form.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
We have a court reserved in 30 minutes.
We have to go now.
Yes, I'm trying to file
the oral hearing.
But what you people keep doing
is transferring. Hello?
Hello?
You work for me, too.
And that means
when Harvey is not here,
you've got to listen
to what I say, Mike.
Louis, this claim needs
to be filed today. Harvey's orders.
- In that case...
- Gregory?
I'm on your side, remember?
Watch this.
- Yes.
- Hi.
Patent interference claim? Can you
have it filed before we get back?
Cool? Thanks.
Let's go.
Just with a...
Who's winning?
You need to warm up?
No, I'm good.
You serve first. Come on.
Show me what you've got.
Fifteen-love.
All right.
You want to play like that?
Let's do this thing.
Come on.
Oh!
Wait. Wait.
Hey, Tom.
Game. Hey, Tom.
I mean, I've seen your pro shot, man.
You have really improved.
I'm not kidding.
You know, maybe you can play now.
Me and my associate
were just starting up.
How about you two against me?
I'll just play...
Tom, seriously. I'll even...
I'll spot you three sets.
All right.
I'll see you later, then.
Isn't that, uh...
That's Tom Keller.
Yeah. The Premiere Fantasy Sports guy,
right? That's him.
Yeah,
I play that every year.
Yeah, you and five million
other fantasy footballers.
I mean, the guy generates
200 million per annum, right?
And he still uses his
fraternity brother as a general counsel.
I mean, someone with that many assets
just makes me sick.
Okay, so,
is it my serve?
Let's hit the showers.
But we...
- Sorry, sir, but...
- No introductions necessary.
We're on a first-name basis.
I brought you a present.
Yours to keep.
After you sign
my injunction.
- A pen?
- It's custom.
French. Le Bic.
My earlier ruling
wasn't clear enough for you?
Crystal. But I didn't want you
to suffer for it.
You see,
if you don't sign my injunction,
there's going to be
a lawsuit.
And when the next judge
sees all the facts,
he's going to overturn
your ruling.
You may be right.
But by then,
your clients will have dumped you.
You may be right,
but that sterling reputation
that you value so highly?
Down the tubes.
Which would matter,
except for one thing.
I've decided
to leave the bench.
Try my hand
at litigation.
And I'm your last case.
Divorce will do that.
Make you want to change your life.
You filed for divorce?
Soon enough.
Perhaps we could discuss
a little quid pro quo before I do.
I'm listening.
You sign a document
that says you slept with my wife.
I'll give you
your injunction.
And why would you want me
to do that?
To prevent her from taking me
for half of everything I own.
So, what you're saying is,
you'd like to blackmail me.
I'm saying
we could both benefit.
And since you're the one who screwed me,
I'd say you owe me one.
Harvey Specter.
What are you hiding from me,
Harvey?
Wyatt. Do you remember six months ago
when you got all nervous
and thought everything
was falling apart?
Yeah.
Yeah, but this is a little different.
That's what you said then.
And a year ago, and 18 months ago.
And we agreed
that when this happens again,
I'll remind you
of those times
- and I'll hang up.
- Okay. Harvey...
Trust me,
it's for your own good.
Harvey,
please don't hang up...
Hey, Tom. You just missed a great game.
We were, uh...
We were just...
I was beating him.
You know, 10 years ago,
before these dot-com millionaires,
there were men of substance
in this club.
You know, men who understood
how business gets done.
Well, maybe he's just not interested
in talking business
while he's in a towel.
Mike, he's not interested
because he doesn't think I'm cool.
And he's a pot-head
who thinks that
anybody who doesn't smoke is a nerd.
I mean...
So I treat my body
like a temple.
Does that make me uncool?
I don't think so.
No.
But on the other hand,
you kind of seem his type.
- Why do you say that?
- Because you're young.
And you think of yourself
as hip.
Whatever, I guess.
You know, I'm sure you enjoy
the occasional bong hit.
No. No.
I don't smoke.
I mean,
that's just a little strange.
Why is it strange?
I mean, because, you know,
the drug test that you took...
Well, that I made you take,
would indicate otherwise.
You're not going to dispute it now,
are you?
Relax, Mike.
Relax.
I'm not offended.
I'm not even surprised.
Matter of fact,
in this instance,
we could use this
to our advantage.
What are you talking about,
Louis?
I'm just saying.
You know, back in the day,
to woo a client,
you would take them to dinner.
You would buy them a drink.
But that's not going to work with Tom.
Not in a million years.
Not with me, anyway.
But if someone
of his generation
who shares
the same proclivities...
Are you saying you want me
to smoke pot with him?
I'm saying you can help me
land him as a client.
That's the only reason I'm here,
isn't it?
No, Mike. Stop.
Just stop, okay?
I assure you, no one
was more disappointed than me
when I found out the results
of your drug test. Okay?
But then, I had to say to myself,
"Louis, do what you do.
"Make lemonade."
And if I don't?
You're a smart kid.
And I really
want to see you succeed.
Ball's in
your court.
Hey, Tom.
I was just going to tell you I wanted...
Dude creeps me out,
man.
And he never wears a towel.
Ever.
Yeah,
tell me about it.
Hey, uh, I know you must hear this
all the time, but...
Totally addicted
to your website, man.
All right. Who placed sixth
in passing yards last year?
Carson Palmer.
3970.
How many sacks did James Hall have?
Eleven?
Uh-uh.
Ten-and-a-half.
Yeah, I know.
I rounded up.
Well, your league doesn't,
or I'd have come in better than 20th.
You're Ross' Raiders.
Right?
Yeah. Mike Ross.
Tom Keller.
Yeah.
Good to meet you.
Congratulations, man.
You've got a nice little team there.
No, if Roethlisberger
hadn't let you down,
you would have been top 10 for sure.
I'm telling you.
Yeah, well,
that's what happens
when you get high
before the draft, right?
You get high?
How's it going
with Harvey?
Me?
Uh, it's...
You know, it's good.
I'm learning.
A lot of learning.
Bye.
What's black and white
and going to cost you dearly?
Whoa.
Took me all morning to file this,
Golden Boy.
You owe me.
And I won't forget it.
Oh, God. Thank you.
You smell papery.
Wyatt, it doesn't happen
immediately. The paperwork is coming.
Don't worry about it,
okay?
Boom. There you go.
Look at that.
Wyatt, let me call you back.
Okay?
Five minutes. Bye.
What's this?
What is this? That's confirmation
of the interference claim,
which I proofed.
Up top.
What, you think
you're working in a fraternity?
You don't barge in here
when I'm on the phone.
And why are you so flush?
Why am I so what?
Your face is red.
Looks like you've been in the sun.
Um, yeah, I, uh...
This morning, Louis,
uh, took me to the tennis club.
He didn't give you the speech
about the ponies, did he?
Oh, my God.
How he likes to cut one
from the herd?
The ponies.
Was he wearing
the headband?
You know about the headband?
With the...
Oh, my God.
Are you kidding me with that guy?
Hey. If you guys were playing tennis
all morning,
how did you have time
to file this?
Uh...
He... It was...
This morning, actually,
I was on the phone
with them,
uh,
and Louis helped me.
Look at me.
And he did this snapping thing,
and Gregory...
Look at me.
You're high.
Get out.
Harvey,
you don't understand. Louis...
Out.
Donna?
Get Wyatt
back on the line?
What are you doing in here?
It's the ladies' room.
I'm sorry.
Can you do me a favor?
Can we, um...
Can we just keep this
our little secret?
Why are your eyes so red?
I need some air.
- You took Mike on a field trip today?
- Yeah.
Aside from subjecting him
to you in a towel, what happened?
I beat him in straight sets,
if that's what you're getting at.
Don't play dumb, Louis.
Tell me what you did to him.
What are you, jealous?
Harvey, come on.
The kid is starving
for a mentor.
Someone to give him
some advice.
So, maybe if you just
took the time...
I'm telling you right now.
You try to move in on him...
Harvey,
where is this coming from?
Harvey, I've got the outside
council for Velocity on the line.
Put him through.
What happened
after you smoked with that guy?
I just got paranoid.
I felt bad for lying to him. And I...
I told him
that Louis put me up to it
and that he couldn't trust him.
So what did he say?
He said that Louis
gave him the creeps, anyway.
And he was never
going to hire him.
Okay.
You have to tell Harvey.
I tried.
He wasn't listening.
So then go home
and tell him tomorrow.
God, you should have seen his face.
We had a deal.
What deal?
Thanks for hearing me out.
No, what are you talking about?
What deal?
It's nothing.
I just promised that I wouldn't
do anything stupid and let him down.
And I did.
Wait.
You let him down?
No. The way I see it,
he let you down.
What?
He's got to know
what Louis is capable of.
So if he didn't listen
to what happened,
it's 'cause
he didn't want to.
Mike,
you need to tell him.
I don't know how often
you've come across Harvey,
but he's not exactly
the listening type.
Right. But he's also
the first person that would tell you
never to take no for an answer.
From anyone.
Harvey,
how are you doing this fine day?
I'm ready to hear
your settlement offer, George.
Cutting to the chase.
I like that.
What's the number?
Ten million.
That's half what we spent
developing the prototype.
And 10 million more than you'll get,
the way the wind is blowing.
Yeah, well,
winds can change.
And you and I both know the injunction
will get overturned on appeal.
I don't know
anything of the kind.
Then why are you calling
with an offer at all?
Fifteen.
That's as high as I'll go.
Okay, I'm hanging up now.
Twenty million.
That's it.
The offer's good
for 24 hours.
And I'm sure
I don't have to remind you
that you're legally required
to present this to your client.
Is he free?
Not for you.
How much
did he tell you?
He didn't have to tell me.
I read it on his face.
- You hurt him.
- Maybe he did the same to me.
Get in there.
And be careful.
Harvey.
We talked about this, right?
Barging into my office?
I'm not leaving
until you hear me out.
- You want to bet?
- You owe it to me.
- Oh, I owe it to you.
- Yeah.
Look, this is not my fault, all right?
Louis made me do it.
Louis did. Right.
He put a gun to your head,
made you smoke pot.
Yeah, he did.
He pulled out the drug test,
which I failed,
by the way.
And then he told me
that if I didn't smoke pot
to help him land this new client,
that he'd fire me.
It's not so different than asking
someone out for drinks, is it?
You and I had a deal.
I'm sorry.
And if next time Louis asks you
to do something
that I told you not to do,
what then?
I told you
that I did not have a choice.
- Oh, because he had a gun to your head.
- Yes.
And what are your choices
if someone puts a gun to your head?
What are you talking about?
You do what they say, or they shoot you.
Wrong.
You take the gun.
Or you pull out
a bigger one.
Or you call
their bluff.
Or you do any one
of 146 other things.
If you can't think
for yourself,
maybe you aren't cut out
for this.
No. I can and I am.
Look, I did what I had to do.
I made the best
out of a bad situation.
Which is
what I am good at.
Which is what you hired me to do
in the first place.
Yeah, I hired you,
and I expect your loyalty.
So if Louis asks you to do
something like that,
you come
to me first.
Oh, right.
Like when I came to you
and, uh, you told me
that I couldn't sit at the adult table.
Right,
I remember that. Or...
Or when you told me to go file
the patent by myself. Like that?
Excuse me?
You know what? Maybe it's time
you showed me some loyalty.
Do you know how long it was
before I got to sit at the adult table?
It was when I brought in
my first client.
Which I don't recall
you having done.
And when you screwed up that patent
and Wyatt went apeshit on me,
I didn't put that on you.
I took it on myself.
Because that's my job.
And it's your job to do
what I say when I say it.
So if you're talking
about loyalty,
you better goddamn
earn it.
You're right.
I said I'm sorry,
and I meant it.
Harvey.
I want you to trust...
I need you to trust me. Okay?
And I will work
as hard as I can,
as long as it takes,
to make that happen.
I mean, you... You don't
even have to pay me, all right?
I'll work for free.
For free.
Well, I meant...
Not forever.
Just, like, as a probationary thing.
But...
Donna, tell Wyatt
I'm on my way over.
You never have to press
a button on that thing?
Got it. And Jessica wants
to see Mike in her office right now.
Louis told me
what you did at the club.
I bet he didn't tell you
the whole story.
He told me enough
to impress me.
New business is hard.
People will promise
you the world.
But until they sign
that engagement letter,
it means nothing.
Now, I don't know
what you told Tom Keller,
but bringing a client in
at your age,
that reminds me
of Harvey.
Jessica.
Before we get started,
there's something in the retainer
that Tom pointed out.
It's not a big deal, really.
We were just...
No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
Like I said,
we're here to make you happy.
Right?
I thought you wanted nothing
to do with him.
I didn't.
But then, I thought about it.
He might not be
a very good person,
but a little deviousness is the sort
of thing you look for in a good lawyer.
I mean, the other guy I was with,
he was too nice.
We were buddies.
We went to school together.
It's time I grew up.
You know, got a real shark.
Well, I had no intention
of being that way to get your business.
That's exactly why I insisted
that you be my point man.
I want someone being devious for me,
not to me.
What?
It's just... Louis never
would have told Jessica that I existed,
let alone
that I helped him,
if you hadn't done that.
Hey,
the way I see it,
the three of us stick together,
we'll make a pretty good team.
You know,
I've got a better idea.
$20 million?
They claim it's their final offer.
That's what it cost
to make the prototype.
Not to mention my entire savings
and two years of my life.
Wyatt.
They know we're stalled
on our injunction.
Which means, to them,
they're giving you a fair price
as an insurance policy
against the risk
of possibly losing
the interference claim.
I don't care
what it is to them.
It's not fair.
Well, fair or not,
it's their final offer.
You think
I should take it?
I think you should tell them
to shove it up their ass.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm
terribly sorry, but we have a problem.
What problem?
We came down here
because you led us to believe
that your client was ready
to accept our settlement agreement.
And I thought he would.
Look,
I took him the offer.
I presented it to him
and recommended that he take it.
In fact,
I urged him to take it.
You know
what he told me to do?
He told me to tell you
to shove it up your ass.
Now, I know you didn't have me
come all the way down here
just to tell me that.
You're right.
That's not all Wyatt said.
He said, rather than spending years
fighting this out in court,
in 48 hours,
he's going to put this online.
It's a little rough,
but you get the idea.
What are you showing us?
Is this a website?
Available
at the Suntech domain name.
All the design plans and calculations
have been uploaded.
- Is this online now?
- It can be.
Which means the whole world
will have access to my designs.
There will be
10 knock-offs of that phone
before you can catch a cab
back to your headquarters.
We could file
an injunction.
Not before tomorrow.
And once that technology
is out there,
good luck
putting that genie back in the bottle.
Well, then we'll sue.
But my client
won't have any money.
What he will have is credit
for the initial design.
Which, after he incorporates
under a different name,
will be worth
a hell of a lot more money
than the $20 million
that you're offering.
And you're saying
that this was all your client's idea.
Yes.
That's what I'm saying.
That's good.
I think so, too.
But, uh...
I'll see you tomorrow.
Good night.
Thought you
weren't coming.
I had to settle
a case first.
You have the paperwork
we talked about?
What is this?
It's a copy
of the judicial conduct codes.
A friend of mine works
at the Attorney General's office.
He gave it to me.
We had a nice chat about you.
I told him if you were
willing to blackmail someone once,
chances are,
you've done it before.
He's very anxious
to meet you.
You think you can get away
with screwing my wife
and then
have me investigated?
You actually have it
the wrong way around.
The only thing I've done so far
is have you investigated.
What?
I never actually
slept with Lauren.
But I knew
you'd never believe me,
so I kept
my mouth shut.
But now that she's getting
a divorce,
my policy
no longer applies.
And, of course,
she's free to date whoever she pleases.
And she pleases me.
Enjoy your evening,
Donald.
I always heard
about this place.
Which room
is Hoffa buried in?
Not sure.
But the Ark of the Covenant
is just down the hall on the left.
When you're finished down here,
I'd like you to come upstairs
and start putting together
a settlement memorandum.
They went for it?
Thanks to your idea.
Well, I mean,
it wasn't really my idea.
They're settling
for 400 million.
Okay.
Yeah, that was my idea.
So, does this mean
I get to keep my job?
- I want to talk to you about that.
- Before you do, Harvey...
Do we have to have a conversation
about how you keep interrupting me?
Ah.
Look. Sometimes,
when someone pulls a gun on you,
instead of bullets,
it's filled with blanks.
What's this?
It's a copy
of your drug test results.
But this says I passed.
You did.
Louis showed me a fake?
I'm going to go
have a talk with him.
You know what?
Why don't you let me do it?
You think
you're ready for the adult table?
Well, didn't you hear?
I just landed my first client.
Why do you think
I'm showing you this now
and not going
straight to Louis?
Go easy on him.
No.
Good boy.
You lied.
That other drug test
you showed me was a fake.
How did you
figure that out?
Someone once told me
I have an eye for detail
when it comes to important paperwork.
Well, maybe you're not as good as
you think you are,
or you would have caught it sooner.
Okay. So this was all some sort of test?
You blackmail me. You jeopardize my job.
Mike, stop.
Stop.
We all came out ahead, didn't we?
That new client
is going to bring us millions.
Jessica knows your name now.
It's a win-win.
You're right.
She does know my name.
Which is why she'll listen
when I tell her exactly what happened.
Okay.
But before you do that,
it is that time again,
isn't it?
What time?
"Pee in a cup" time.
And now,
you know I'd fail.
Of course,
you can run to Mommy,
tell her your story,
and take your chances.
Or you can
take the test
and trust that I'll keep it to myself
as my way of thanking you.
Oh, you know,
I actually did some reading
of the Pearson Hardman drug policy,
as well.
It turns out
that you have to wait three months
before you can request
another drug test.
It's a little detail you might
have missed. So, drink up.
Oh, and, uh,
I spoke to Tom Keller.
He says that he feels
he'd be best served
with the combination
of me and Harvey.
I think you'll get
that call in the morning.