Previously on... Suits
Tess, there is such
thing as right and wrong.
You're married.
What if I wasn't?
What you're doing,
it only ends one way.
I wasn't the only senior
partner who voted for Hardman,
and I don't see you
giving anyone else shit
the way you give me.
And by the way,
when the chips were down,
I backed you, I ousted him.
Tell yourself
whatever you want, Louis.
But tell it to yourself.
I can't go away
with you, Harvey.
Why not?
The next time I have an option
to cross the line to save you,
I'll send you packing
and not think twice.
Now get your shit together.
You need to go,
and I need to get
my shit together.
[Vacuum hums]
How nice,
greeting me at the door.
When are they gonna take
that down?
Pearson...
Just doesn't have the same ring.
Pearson Paulsen
sounds pretty good.
Okay. No, it doesn't.
How's my day?
How was your night?
And by night, I mean weekend,
and by weekend, I mean Zoe.
It was fine.
That's it?
No fun banter?
No witty repartee?
And you're in the office
at exactly 8:00.
Not early, which would mean
it went badly,
and not late, which would mean
it went great.
But exactly on time,
which means...
[gasps]
You and Zoe never went away
for the weekend.
What happened?
Do you want to talk about it?
I have ice cream.
It's 8:00 a.m.
Which is why God made
chunky monkey.
It has chocolate and bananas.
Bananas are part
of a healthy breakfast.
And who cares
about the bananas?
It has chocolate.
Okay, you caught me.
I don't even eat the bananas.
8:00 a.m. means the business
day has already started.
I'd like to conduct
some business.
Well, in that case,
Trent Devon would like
to see you.
So schedule an appointment.
Okay, you have
an 8:02 with Trent Devon.
Well, I didn't meet you
at the elevator
just to chat
about your weekend.
Fine. Get Mike.
From home?
You gotta be kidding me.
My client is here,
and my associate is not?
Well, I'm sure...
Donna, I don't want to hear it.
The minute Mike Ross sets foot
in this building,
I want to know.
I think it's a bad idea,
Harvey.
We'll double the share price
by the end
of the first quarter.
That's not what I meant.
I'm just...
I'm not sure going public
is the best move right now.
That's why I'm here.
Trust me, these aren't
valid reservations.
You're just getting cold feet.
Harvey.
I'll have Donna send you
some fuzzy slippers.
You'll be just fine.
Are fuzzy slippers gonna stop
the Title 16 ruling
that came down Friday?
You don't even know
what that is, do you?
No, I don't.
But what I do know is
it's not gonna change
the value of your site.
You've tripled your reach
in the past ten months.
Everyone is talking about you.
Now is the time.
Come on, we agreed on this.
What's this really about?
It's about the changes
around here.
Nothing's changed.
I'm here. Harvey.
I may be a tech head,
but I'm not oblivious.
This firm just went
through a battle, and I know it.
Are you telling me
that you don't trust me
to put your needs
above the firm's?
No, I've always trusted you,
Harvey.
I'm just saying I don't...
I think you might be
too distracted
to give me the best advice.
- Trent.
- I have to consider my options.
About the IPO
or Pearson Hardman?
Both.
We have a problem.
Yeah?
Bernie Carillo is
thinking of leaving us.
That's absolutely not true,
and I would know.
I have it on good authority.
So let me guess. It's my fault.
Louis, I didn't come here
to blame you.
I came here to give you
a heads up.
You want to spit out
what you're chewing on?
Yeah, you order me
to rescind an offer
due to
a firm-wide hiring freeze.
I stake my reputation on it.
Two minutes later,
you hire a fifth-year.
You went back on your word,
and you made me look
like a fool.
I also gave you my word
that there'd be
no coming back from your vote.
And I'm ready
to go back on that.
We're losing clients, Louis,
and I can't have that.
So today is day one
of the Louis Litt
rehabilitation program.
Take it. Move on.
It is time to heal the wounds.
I'll take care of Carillo.
[Banging on copier]
Come on!
Out with it. What'd you do?
I think I put in
too much toner.
With Carillo, you imbecile.
He's considering
a change of counsel.
Now, I want to know
what you did
or more likely did not do
to cause this.
[Stammers]
[Mockingly stammers] What?
- I don't know.
- What a shocker.
If you want, I can go back,
and I'll retry...
No, no, no, no.
What I want is for you
to finish
drafting the contracts
and deliver them to Rachel Zane
by 8:00 a.m. tomorrow morning.
Then wait
for further instructions,
politely seated,
with your hands crossed
on your lap.
Uh.
And if anything goes wrong,
I swear to almighty God
that you are gonna rue the day
that you decided to become
the embarrassment
of a lawyer that you are.
Louis Litt
does not lose clients.
Is that clear?
[Stammers]
About the Carillo contracts
or the fact
that you don't lose clients?
Get out.
[Paper rustling] Oh, sorry.
Uhoh. Wait a minute.
What is this?
Is that a triple nonfat
sugar-free mocha latte?
- Oh, you sweet, sweet...
- Mmm.
Wait a minute.
What did you do wrong?
Okay, I'm offended.
You're questioning my motives?
- Actually, Mike...
- It's okay.
You haven't had
your second triple latte yet.
I forgive you
because I'm in a forgiving mood.
- Right, but Harvey's...
- I love the smell
of litigation in the morning.
Not.
It's 8:30.
Yeah, in the morning.
It's 30 minutes past
when you were required
to be here,
which means it's an hour past
when you should be here.
Okay, since when
do we use a time clock?
What are the new FTC
Title 16 requirements?
Oh, they're nothing.
It's a nuisance.
Trent Devon's worried
about them.
Okay, well, all it is
is another form to fill out.
So if that's what you're worried
about, it's fine.
What I'm worried about
is the fact
that I could've told him that
had you been at the meeting
this morning at 8:00.
What? I checked the schedule.
There was nothing on it
for this morning.
It happened spontaneously,
as things do.
And I was there.
You were not there.
[Tapping keys]
Did you not hear me
when I told you to get
your shit together?
No, I did hear you, and I did
get my shit together,
by the way.
That's why I'm late
this morning.
Deciding to be late
to get your shit together
is not getting
your shit together.
Get it through your head.
We just went
through a civil war,
and the world knows it.
We're weak.
And the law of the jungle says
the weak get eaten.
Okay, Harvey, I'm sorry,
but you need to ease up here.
[Shouts] Ease up?
You're telling me to ease up
when our clients are leaving?
That's right,
Trent Devon might leave.
People don't leave me!
- I-I...
- Enough!
Your job is to help me,
not to screw me.
If I tell you you did that,
I don't want to hear
that you didn't.
I should've fired you
last week.
You know what,
I should fire you right now.
But I cut you slack
because your grandmother died.
Well, you've used up the rope.
You keep it up,
I will fire you tomorrow.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right
♪ All that time imagine this ♪
♪ The greenback boogie
"People don't leave me"?
- Donna, I don't...
- I do.
- He deserved it.
- He deserved a slap.
You knocked him
across the room.
[Sighs]
What happened with Zoe?
She's leaving New York
to take care of her niece
whose father is dying.
Oh, my God.
Harvey, I'm sorry.
Is there anything...
No.
Just one thing.
I don't think kicking
the dog is gonna help.
Wow, you look like hell.
Jimmy.
You here to pick a fight
with me?
'Cause I'm really
not in the mood.
No, no, Mike.
It's not like that, man.
Oh, yeah?
You're not still pissed at me?
You gave me an out.
I might not have respected it
at the time,
but I do now.
As far as I'm concerned,
I owe you one. Okay.
Yeah. Let me buy you a drink.
Two conditions.
One: You still owe me one.
Two: You still owe me one.
As long as I still
don't owe you one.
Bartender.
It's good to see you, man.
You too, buddy.
So what's going on?
You had a bad day? Yeah.
Okay. So give it to me.
Well, evidently,
getting in at 8:30
can only mean one thing.
Yeah, that you had
your head up your ass
from 7:00 to 8:15.
- How'd you know?
Are you forgetting
I used to work for Louis too?
And unlike you, I didn't have
Harvey there to protect me.
No, this was Harvey.
Whoa. Ain't that some shit.
Anyway,
here's to the wonderful world
of being an associate, right?
[Glasses clink] Yeah.
Pearson Hardman.
What does that mean?
I'm at Bratton Gould, my man.
And I'm happy. No!
Associates don't get
to be happy, Jimmy.
No, you do at Bratton Gould.
I got an office.
- Shoot me now.
- [Laughs]
That's great.
Listen, Mike.
When I said
that I owe you one, I mean it.
'Cause you didn't hear it
from me, but we're expanding.
So if you want to jump,
just let me know.
I'll put in a word for you.
- I can't leave Harvey.
- Screw Harvey.
I mean, what's he done for you?
More than you know.
Okay, maybe.
But a year
under Harvey Specter,
they would kill to have you.
And you wouldn't be
the only one.
There are people
from Pearson Hardman
going to Bratton Gould? Who?
I can't tell you that.
Jimmy,
you have to tell me that.
Mike, come on.
If they knew it came from me...
They won't.
I saw Clark and Owens meeting
with our partners.
If you're here to give me
your letter of resignation,
I'll accept it in the morning.
Oh, that's ironic.
I was offered a job tonight.
- Congratulations.
- I passed.
You want credit for that?
No, I want to do the job
I already have.
Apology accepted.
Bratton Gould
is poaching our associates,
Clark, Owens,
but he's also coming after...
Our clients. Trent Devon.
Someone's whispering
in his ear.
Allison Holt.
She was brought in
about a month ago.
She was ready to throw you
under the bus.
And Jessica threw her out.
So you think
she's in this for revenge?
Maybe.
But we both know
who brought her in.
Hardman.
You think this is him?
Hell of a view.
Clark and Owens
don't deserve this.
Which one is Owens,
by the way, the redhead?
You don't even know
who your associates are,
but you're here to complain
about losing them?
You bitter
because you were fired?
I'm not bitter, Harvey.
Unlike you, I don't take
things personally.
And by the way, I was right.
I advised you to settle,
and you settled.
Your advice was for us
to settle,
and I lose my law license.
And my question is,
was taking that deal
your idea or Daniel Hardman's?
You think Daniel's behind this?
You met with him six days ago.
I'm not even gonna ask
how you know that.
I told you before, Jessica.
I'm a straight shooter.
Daniel wasn't dictating
my actions then,
and he's not now.
Either way,
we are filing a claim
for tortious interference.
You're using
privileged information
to target our clients.
You really want to cry
foul to the ref?
You know who went to the ref
more than anyone?
Michael Jordan.
He did it quietly.
And he got six rings,
and he's my client.
Maybe I should call him too.
You're not getting Trent Devon.
You can't keep people
who want to leave, Harvey.
Everybody knows
about your civil war.
Pearson Hardman
is falling apart.
And I'm telling you,
the avalanche
has already started.
The Carillo contracts,
they should be signed
and on my desk. I know.
Well,
since you're so in the know,
perhaps you can tell me
why I don't have them yet.
- Because they're not signed.
- Not signed?
I called earlier to have them
to have them messengered...
The story's already
taking too long.
And they said
they didn't need to see them.
Still waiting.
They said
they're no longer a client.
Harold.
No. Harold didn't...
Louis,
Harold didn't do anything.
Harold never does anything.
He got me the contracts
first thing this morning.
He worked all night.
They were really quite...
[grunts] Excuse me.
- "Quite" what?
- Good, actually.
Uhhuh. And how many
citations you correct?
- None.
- You're lying.
- No, I'm not.
- I don't care.
Wow. Yeah. That is a tattoo.
- It's cool, right?
- Yeah.
Manatee... the slow,
gentle cow of the sea.
Uh, no. It's a shark actually.
Totally. No... yes.
That's a shark.
That is a big, wide, fat shark.
You're fired.
- You can't fire Mike.
- You.
You moron. You can't
even get your firing right.
- I'm fired?
- Louis, come on.
Pack up your things and go.
Now.
But I did everything you asked.
I delivered
the Carillo contracts.
I don't care.
The client fired us,
and now I'm firing you.
Times are tough, people.
We can't afford mistakes.
We can't afford incompetence.
You can't cut it, get out.
There is no place
for mediocrity here
at Pearson Hardman,
and there's certainly no place
for someone like you.
Everyone else get back to work.
You know, I didn't just do
what he asked for Carillo.
I went way beyond.
I didn't make any mistakes,
and I know that they're not
leaving because of me.
So why didn't you
say that to him?
Because he makes me freeze.
[Sighs]
You know, sometimes I wish
we would've known each other
at Harvard.
Yeah. Yeah. Harvard.
You probably hung out
with Duncan and those guys.
I hung out with the library.
I'm such a loser.
No, you're not, Harold.
Look, for the record,
Duncan was a douche.
He was a douche.
- Totally.
- Like a douchy-douche.
Do you remember that thing
he used to do with the...
- I know.
- You know what I mean?
[Laughter]
See, that's what I mean.
If you would've known me there,
then at least
someone here would know
that I wasn't always like this.
People used to come to me
for help on their essays.
We'd sit in the quiet
of my apartment
where no one was yelling at me,
and I could think and write.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Here.
This is the first essay
I wrote in law school.
Look
at the Professor's comments.
Holy shit.
Louis is right.
I don't belong here.
No, he's not.
- Thomas.
- Poconos weekend.
- With the girlfriend.
- Which one?
- Doesn't matter.
- Done. Winters?
- Lunch with the mayor.
- Campos.
- Lunch with me.
- Benson?
- Box at the Garden.
Have Lundqvist meet him
pre-game.
Does the king do that?
He does for me. Siebertz.
- Tickets.
- Super Bowl.
- Broadway.
- Really?
Beneath that lumberjack chest
beats the heart of a songbird.
Fine. Anything but Cats.
Cats closed over a decade ago.
What took 'em so long?
That's it then. We're done.
Closed them all.
That's just foreplay.
We didn't close shit.
I want to have talked
to every one of my clients
by the end of the day.
You stay on Trent Devon
until he takes the call.
I will.
And, Harvey...
No one is leaving you.
[Knock on door] Okay.
Harold is totally freaked out.
I think he's gonna have
an ulcer,
but the good news is he'll never
disappoint you again,
so you can go and magnanimously
hire him back now.
Why would I do that?
Um, I don't know,
because you made your point.
You think that was a show?
Look, I know Harold can be...
Harold.
He's an idiot savant
minus the savant.
He tries hard.
He's a good person.
Yeah, well, then tell him
to join the Peace Corps.
Why don't you just give him
a second chance?
I did, Mike.
It was called his second day.
You realize you need cause,
right?
You want a cause?
He left a zero off
the Hopkins settlement,
which cost the client $360,000.
He filed a motion
with the appeals court
instead of the superior court,
which accidentally triggered
a death penalty review.
And then the one and only time
that I take him to court
with me, his fly was down,
and he called the judge
"Your Owner."
[Laughs]
You know why he does
those things, right?
Because you intimidate him.
You brutalize him.
You're always talking
about how great
you are at grooming us.
Well, you were not great
at grooming him.
If he can't take
a drill sergeant yelling at him,
how can he handle
people shooting at him?
People don't shoot at us,
Louis.
Don't they?
Okay. You know what?
You want him to stay...
Fine. He can stay.
Thank you.
One condition.
You personally guarantee
every piece of work product
that Harold sends
out of this office
just like I have.
You check everything he does.
You cross every "t,"
dot every "I,"
and still do everything
you have to for Harvey.
People may not be shooting
at us, but we are at war.
So how does that work for you?
Do we have a deal?
Harold.
I was just coming by
to wish you well.
Thanks, Rachel,
but I think it's gonna be okay.
Mike's talking to Louis
right now.
Really?
That's great.
Well?
There was nothing I could do.
It's okay.
I know you tried, Mike.
If it'll make you feel better,
you're not the only person
being let go this week.
Well, Clark and Owens
are only getting let go
because someone found out
that they're moving
to Bratton Gould
with McKinney and Kline.
- They are?
- Yeah, I overheard it.
I guess some people
will choose any port in a storm.
Harold, good luck.
You too.
[Sighs]
This sucks. It does.
He didn't deserve that.
Allison's not done.
We know.
We're working all the clients.
No, it's more than that.
She's taking McKinney and Kline.
It's just two more associates.
No, it's more than that.
I tell you
the rats are jumping ship,
and you say it's fine,
but Donna nods,
and you're busting out
life jackets?
You have a history
of panicking.
He's not panicking.
Clark, Owens, McKinney, Kline...
these aren't just fifth-years.
They're the best fifth-years.
They're Louie's
first class of associates.
He gave her a report card?
Harvey, you do not know that.
Well,
I'm gonna goddamn find out.
[Laughs] Stop.
Just cut it out.
All right,
I'll talk to you later.
Bye.
I never liked you, Louis.
You're a vindictive,
sniveling rat,
but I never thought
you'd betray your own firm.
I never betrayed this firm.
What do you call helping
Allison Holt
poach our associates?
I had nothing to do with that.
I love this firm, Harvey.
You were a traitor
when you voted for Hardman,
and you're a traitor now.
Like I've told you before,
I'm not the only one
in this firm
who voted for Hardman.
And I voted to oust him
once I knew.
Once you knew you had
to save your own ass.
All right, you know what,
Harvey, just get out.
Get out.
Ri... I did nothing wrong.
Jesus!
You bugged my office.
You ran to Hardman
about the CM lawsuit.
You sold your soul
for senior partnership.
And once you got it,
you created a drug policy
with the sole purpose
of firing me!
I did it for Hardman.
Maybe Hardman wanted me dead,
but you're the one
who went out,
got the gun, aimed it,
and fired it at my head.
And it blew up in my face!
And what would have happened
if it didn't?
I was under orders.
Were you also under orders
when you ran
to Hardman about Monica Eton?
How do you know it was me?
Because I set it up!
Because I know who you are!
Are you still gonna tell me
you're not helping Allison?
Harvey, I swear to God
I did not do this.
Maybe not.
But now that you've done
what you've done,
I will never trust you.
Pearson Hardman is my life.
Well, here's what's
gonna happen from now on.
You and I, we're done.
Don't drop by my office.
Don't ask Donna
for information.
You're the guy
that nobody wants
but we can't get rid of.
I'm a senior partner.
So I can't make you leave.
But as far as I'm concerned,
you don't even work here
anymore.
[Clatters]
That glass
does not look half full.
You're cherry-picking
Pearson Hardman associates.
I only want the best cherries.
Then why not go
after the gardener who grew 'em?
You want to leave
Pearson Hardman.
I'm a proven commodity who
delivers outstanding billables.
With an unparalleled knowledge
of finance.
Yeah, I'm well aware
of who you are, Louis.
But how do I know
that Harvey Specter
didn't just send you here?
'Cause I'm the last person
that Harvey Specter would trust.
Just ask Daniel Hardman.
I did.
He said you betrayed him.
Like I said,
I am well aware of who you are.
Well, if you spoke to Daniel,
then you would know
that he lost Pearson Hardman
not because of my betrayal
but because of his own.
My loyalty does not sway
with the wind.
I'm leaving Pearson Hardman
because there's no room
for me there anymore.
You could go anywhere.
Well, I've done my homework.
You guys are expanding.
You are hiring well.
You're gonna have a young staff
that needs guidance.
You know
that I'm the right fit.
And I want to move now.
You have a non-compete clause.
Jessica is gonna waive
the non-compete
as long
as I don't take clients.
- I wouldn't if I were her.
- Well, you're not.
Harvey wants me gone,
and he has a way
of getting what he wants, so...
There might be
a partnership position
for you.
Senior partnership.
That, you're gonna have
to earn.
I have earned it.
And I'm not giving up
what I've worked for
my whole life.
Louis, you have made
a tactical error.
You've shown me all your cards,
you can't offer any clients,
and you're being forced
to leave a place
that doesn't want you.
You are a very good fit for us.
But if you want to join us,
you're gonna have to prove
how much you want it.
Please don't do this.
Do what? I'm just negotiating.
You have an empty title.
If you come with us, I promise
that you will be truly valued.
Well, that's it.
I've talked to every client
except Trent Devon.
Well, I know why he's returning.
Allison's calls
instead of yours.
Because he thinks
we're not focused.
That's not enough.
Come on. You taught me
to always ask...
What's in it for him?
"If we're looking
to expand our reach,
"then Trent Devon's
data platform
provides the perfect symbiosis
with our search algorithms."
Page 23,
the CEO of flash-start.
Allison doesn't represent them.
Google bought Meebo
for $100 million.
Allison is trying to do
the same thing
with Flash-Start.
Allison doesn't represent them.
Pretend she does.
Trent gets $100 million,
but his company
gets swallowed up,
and that's not what he wants.
Well, what if they let him run
both companies?
That's too good to be true.
It's happened before.
So if that's true,
all we need to do
is figure out a way
to beat that deal.
We can't beat that deal.
Okay. So what do we do?
Why didn't you just tell me?
Allison said you had a history
and that it might get in the way
of what she was offering.
- Flash-Start.
- Very good.
But Allison
doesn't represent them.
No, but she does represent
a hedge fund
that's about to buy
a controlling interest.
And let me guess.
They want you
to run the whole thing.
We'll take on Google.
And let me guess.
You're here to try and beat it.
No, I'm here to tell you
to take it.
If I were you, I would,
and I would hire the lawyer
who brought it to me.
Thanks, Harvey.
You're welcome.
There's just one thing.
I wonder, what's in it for her?
What are you implying?
Let me look over the deal.
My own time.
If it is what she says it is,
I'll tell you.
If it's not,
you'll want to know.
- Harvey, I already told you...
- Look.
You said we weren't focused,
and I'm not here to try
to convince you that we were.
But you also said
you've always trusted me,
and I'm telling you,
trust me one more time.
[Knock at door]
Louis. Do you need something?
Actually, yes.
I need you to waive
my non-compete,
so I can take a position
at another firm.
Bratton Gould.
I had nothing to do
with Allison Holt's poaching.
What did she offer you?
I went to her.
Why?
I got Harvey's message.
What message?
You don't know?
It doesn't matter.
This is what he wants.
And this is what you want?
You know
you can't take clients.
Oh, I wouldn't even if I could.
I have no desire
to hurt our firm...
your firm.
Do you know why I instituted
the Louis Litt
rehabilitation program?
Because I was seduced
by Daniel Hardman once too.
He made me feel special
and smart and valued.
The problem was
he really didn't give
a shit about me.
But I will give him one thing.
He was right about you.
You deserve
a senior partnership.
[Scribbles]
I'm gonna let you go, Louis.
Just for the record,
I am not on the same page
as Harvey.
I don't want you to go.
What?
Were we really quitting,
or was that just a move
to get to the contract?
You don't think I have
his best interests at heart?
That's not what I asked.
If it's a good deal,
he should take it.
But you said
it's too good to be true.
What else did I say?
That it's my job to help you.
So what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna go find out
what's too good about it.
Goodbye, Mike.
Hey, you can quit all you want,
but Trent Devon is not leaving.
Okay. Good talk.
[Groans]
Yeah.
You know who I am, asshole.
- I'm sorry. Okay?
- For what?
Sleeping with my wife?
What, you didn't do it
on purpose?
It's over. Okay?
I swear to God.
You think it's that easy?
[Groans]
Keep your goddamn apology,
and stay the hell away
from Tess!
[Coughs]
[elevator bell dings]
Oh, my God.
What the hell happened to you?
Oh, I don't want
to talk about it.
Ow. With me. Now.
This isn't the first-aid kit
from the kitchen.
Use other people's
antibacterial cream?
Please, I might as well
give myself a staph infection.
It's antibacterial.
That's what
they want you to believe.
- But you're using it.
- Shh.
Looks like it's gonna bruise.
Oh, look, I'm sure
it's gonna be fine, it's...
[winces]
How do you know how to do this?
Bruno used to get
into these fights
with this Maine coon
on the 37th floor.
Pumpkin.
[Groans]
- No, I don't need it.
- Here you go.
- I don't need tissues.
- Are you sure?
Put them down.
Are you gonna tell me
what happened?
It's New York. I got jumped.
Didn't you call 911?
To have the police come
and ask a million questions
about a guy
who they're never gonna catch?
No, thanks.
You knew him.
Let's just say
that actions have consequences.
Okay.
I get it. Yeah, I get that.
We gonna talk about that box
you were carrying?
Oh, man. What box?
The box full of personal things
from your office?
Like you said,
actions have consequences.
- Jessica fired you.
- Mm-mm.
She asked me to stay. She did?
Yeah, because she knows
that I would never sell out
this firm.
Well, then I don't
understand, what are you...
Mike, do I have
to spell it out for you?
You're Harvey's right hand.
He hates me.
So? Jessica's the boss.
Come on,
Harvey's always hated you.
No, actually.
Harvey hasn't always hated me.
We were never Elmer and Bugs.
We were... Ralph and Sam.
Who?
Ralph Wolf and Sam Sheepdog.
The cartoon characters?
Yeah.
They came to the meadow
every day to work, friendly.
But then when they punched
in the time clock,
Ralph would try
to steal the sheep,
and Sam would stop him.
I mean, it was brutal.
And then
they'd punch out again.
Friends.
And that was me and Harvey.
Harvey's not punching out
anymore.
And I can't walk in here
every day
knowing that I'm gonna
be working side by side
next to somebody
who despises me.
I just... Mike, I can't.
Louis,
if actions have consequences,
then maybe actions
can redeem you.
No, it's too late for that.
Die's been already cast.
Here.
You can send me
a new tube of Arnica
at your convenience.
You don't have to stay,
but I have
some merger projections
that I have to go through
for Harvey.
And I'm pretty sure I'm gonna be
out of my depth.
[Exhales]
Morning.
Thought I'd get in early
and destroy Allison Holt.
How's that going?
- It's a work in progress.
- Mm-hmm.
Louie's letter of resignation.
Found it on my desk
this morning.
- Good.
- No.
Not good, Harvey.
We can agree to disagree.
We're not agreeing on anything.
You pushed Louis out the door.
It was not your call to make.
Louis may or may not have
helped Allison,
but he has betrayed you, me,
and this entire firm.
We're better off.
If you really believe that,
then something's
got you off your game.
- Jessica, I'm not off my...
- No.
Not you. Me.
Your job is to help me.
And when I say
you are off your game,
you say,
"how do I get it back?"
I went to Louis
to get him back on board,
and you made an end run
around me.
When does it stop?
We can't let Trent go
with Allison.
He's gonna... get screwed.
I'm... I'm sorry.
It's nothing. [Stammers]
It's just some stairs.
[Mutters]
[Chuckles]
Oh, God.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't see her there.
Who did this to you?
- I'm fine.
- You're not.
And after I'm done
kicking his ass,
the guy who did it
isn't gonna be either.
- Harvey, just let it go.
- That's not who I am.
I deserved it.
- What did you do?
- I don't want to tell you.
I wouldn't call this
getting your shit together.
I don't want to tell you
because of the story
you told me about your mom
and your dad.
You got off easy.
I know.
It's a bad deal.
What, you're reading
between the lines?
'Cause I couldn't find anything
in the contract.
Because the problem's
not in the contract.
You said it yourself.
The deal's too good to be true.
The financials
don't support it.
What, you get your MBA
overnight?
No.
You went to Louis?
We worked all night.
He didn't betray us, Harvey.
He found the problem.
They never wanted anything to do
with Trent's company.
After the deal,
they're just gonna sell it off
for spare parts.
That won't get them
what they paid for it.
But it'll get them
what they wanted.
- Trent.
- Exactly.
Louis figured this out?
Trent's contract
has the same problem as Louie's.
He's got a non-compete.
They couldn't get him
to run the company
unless they bought his.
Now Louis wants back in.
No, he doesn't.
This is just his way
of saying he's sorry.
It's not on the menu,
but might I suggest
the "I got my ass kicked"
Martini?
It goes well
with the "second-tier law firm"
potato skins.
Those come with bacon?
I don't know, never had 'em.
I take it
my client's not coming.
He was your client,
but then you offered him
a deal too good to be true.
You got the paperwork.
Because he trusted me.
Well played, Harvey.
No. Here's the play.
He's gonna take
his company public,
like I told him to months ago.
A deal my new client,
a certain hedge fund,
just agreed to underwrite.
You know Edelson Investments,
don't you?
I do.
Apparently,
I used to represent them.
Ah, you're taking this well.
What do you want me to do, cry?
Harvey, we play the game.
Sometimes we win,
sometimes we lose.
Not me.
Which brings me
to a suggestion of my own.
Come work for Bratton Gould.
Come work for you?
With me.
Did you not hear what I said
about the potato skins?
You're second-tier.
What about you?
There's blood in the water,
Harvey.
You may have fended off
this attack,
but we're not
the only ones circling.
We fended you off,
we'll fend off the rest.
With who?
I got all
your best senior associates,
your future, and I'm not done.
We'll see about that.
Lunch is on us.
After all, we just landed
a huge, new client.
You say "we," but I don't see
your name on the door.
Mike, Mike, Mike.
I got your call.
You said you owed me one,
right?
Yeah, and I meant it too.
Well, you're gonna pay me back.
I'm happy to,
'cause listen to me,
when I bring you in,
and you kick ass,
I look kick-ass.
Got your resume? Right there.
You gotta be kidding me.
Oh, you didn't think
it was gonna be easy
to pay me back, did you?
Harold?
I'm not gonna look kick-ass.
I'm gonna look ass-kicked.
Look at how he did.
Are you kidding me?
You keep saying that.
Man, we talking
about the same Harold?
I know.
Seriously, Mike, man,
if this doesn't work,
I'm gonna look like shit.
Jimmy, he needs a second chance
just like you did.
[Sighs] All right, all right.
You won't regret it.
Harold's great.
You're gonna love
his new tattoo.
He's here, isn't he?
Right over there.
Not only do you retain
one client,
you landed another.
I knew there was a reason
why I kept you around.
And a reason Allison Holt's
trying to steal me away.
Congratulations.
I'm sure you'll be very happy.
What could possibly go wrong?
Congratulations.
That's what I said to Mike.
Him too? She's after everyone.
Don't worry. He's staying.
Loyal as a basset hound.
Oh.
Are they particularly loyal?
I turned her down.
But?
I want my name on the door.
I don't want to end
around you anymore.
I want to discuss things
with you as an equal.
It's a little late for that,
don't you think?
How long are we gonna walk
by his name on the wall, huh?
They're coming after us,
and they're not gonna stop
until we send them a message
that we are whole.
I'm not gonna just slap
someone else's name up there,
Harvey.
- "Someone"?
- I told you once.
You don't make decisions
when you're reeling from a loss.
And your response was,
"let's quit today."
Not quit. Fight.
Without any thought
for the consequences.
With my gut,
which serves me well.
As a closer, not a leader.
Jessica.
Watson, Klyman,
Gallo, Goldberg, Specter.
The first five senior partners
you named.
The first five major moves
I made.
All success stories.
Last week,
you had me steal someone
from the D.A.'s office
for reasons you won't say.
We won't even go
into what you did to Louis.
And then
there's the cherry on top.
- Mike.
- Who showed up this morning
beaten to a pulp.
He also beat Hardman to a pulp.
One day, what he is
isn't going to be enough
to make up for what he isn't.
Which is how you feel about me.
Harvey, what was
Michael Jordan's record
on the Bulls?
664 wins, 285 losses.
More than twice as many wins
than losses.
Do you know what his record was
in the front office?
- No.
- 185 to 291.
Almost twice as many losses
as wins.
You know how I know that?
Because you knew one day,
I'd come in here
asking for this.
Because I look at the future
like an adult.
Are you saying it's a no?
I'm saying
I'm not rushing this decision
and that your judgment
that day was wrong.
Thank you.
[Clears throat]
- Hey.
I thought you'd like to know
that Harold got a job
at another firm.
Good.
Look, Rachel...
He found out, didn't he?
I just want you
to know that it was
after I ended things with Tess.
I want you to know
that I just don't give a shit.