Previously on... Suits.
Less than
1 out of every 12 people
who applies gets in.
What if I'm not one
of those people?
I don't know. Maybe you'll
get in somewhere else.
I don't want to go
to law school.
I want to go to Harvard.
I got 100% faith in you.
[Softly] I didn't get in.
I promised her.
Louis, I liked her.
You're just going to have
to tell her the truth.
Sometimes good
isn't good enough.
I want my name on the door.
So if you deliver a huge win...
I get my name on the door.
Are you talking
about joining forces with her?
Not just with her,
with her firm...
her infinitely
deep-pocketed firm.
Edward and I are merging.
I had to show him the books.
You don't want your name
on the door.
You want your name on my door.
I want to see our names
on the same door.
This is exactly
what you've always wanted.
Get over your pride.
I'm not getting over anything.
And this merger
isn't happening.
- Those are your clients.
- Who Harvey is using.
- That's a bullshit argument.
- And so is that file.
- I won't.
- You will.
Harvey will never forgive me.
Right now your problem
isn't with Harvey.
Your problem is with me.
Champagne?
- Depends.
- On what?
On whether or not
there's a roofie in there.
I wouldn't need a roofie.
Jessica, uh, might I have
a private word?
Actually, Harvey and I were...
Don't mind me.
My date just got here.
Edward. Harvey.
Hell of a party.
You look...
Beautiful. I know.
Actually, I was going
to say "sophisticated."
- No, you weren't.
- I can now.
You seem different.
I feel different.
What's going on?
You know, why don't you
get me a drink?
It's a party.
Okay.
Harvey.
Rachel.
You look nice.
Thank you. So do I.
Now I see what
you're always talking about.
What was that supposed to mean?
What do you think it means?
It means you're a dick.
Fair point.
I just didn't know
that she knew that.
Everyone knows that.
- You bring it?
- Right here.
You sure you want
to do this to her?
You're supposed to be
on my side.
I am. I've got your back.
Then why are you giving me
such a hard time about it?
Not only am I not giving you
a hard time,
but I am giving you this...
and this and this.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
Where are you going?
Oh, I'm going to go get a drink
while this is still a party.
- Hi, may I...
- Excuse me, good sir.
Would you be so kind
as to prepare me...
A frapin cuvee?
Easy, Prince Charles.
Where I'm from,
you wait your turn in line.
Oh, I'm so sorry,
but I thought
you'd been served.
The barman is patiently
waiting on you,
so I'd stop standing there
like some sort of baboon
and order your Miller Lite.
Macallan 25, neat.
Why don't you put a banana
in it for my man here?
With a drink like that,
you might as well be in a zoo,
playing about in the mud.
Oh, you wouldn't know
anything about mud.
It's not for playing.
It's for cleansing.
You mud?
I've taken mud in more places
than your snooty little mind
can fathom.
Calais.
- Cliffs or Harbor?
- Both.
Me too. Sedona.
- Isle of Wight.
- Joshua tree.
- Dalyan.
- Baden-Baden.
That isn't mud. It's wet dirt.
You know, I don't know
who you think you are...
My moniker is
Nigel Alexander Nesbitt.
Well, Nigel, when you impugn
the life-affirming muds
of Baden-Baden,
you're on the precipice
of the equivalent
of someone taking a shit
on the royal muds of England.
How dare you?
Oh, I've already dared...
To do... What I've done.
Ah, Harvey.
I was hoping we might have
a moment alone.
So was I.
I wanted to run something
by you.
- This is a lawsuit.
- Three lawsuits.
What have I gotten up to now?
Not you, your clients.
Looks like one of their hobbies
is fixing prices.
I take it this means
you've discovered
we're in merger talks?
And what are you going
to do about it?
- What would you have me do?
- I'd have you kiss my ass.
Tempting.
However, what I can do
is enjoy this glass of wine,
finish this lovely party,
and proceed to make you
permanently regret
the hostile action
you've just set in motion.
What, are you going to kill me?
Nonsense.
I'll simply do what I've done
to so many before.
I'll defeat you in open court.
The way I work, it's never
going to get to open court.
You'll be on your steamer
back to London,
wondering what happened,
and you'll know
that you picked a fight
with the wrong guy.
Are you suggesting a wager?
I'm not a gambler,
but in this case,
I'll make an exception.
You lose, we don't merge.
I've heard your terms.
You win, I go.
Care to hear mine?
Don't need to
'cause you're never
going to win.
Well, it looks like you two
are getting along.
Mm.
Harvey...
Look at what they can give us.
How do you know
what they can give us?
Because he showed me
their books.
- Why did he do that?
- Because I showed him ours.
Why didn't you tell me?
- We needed their help.
- To beat Hardman.
And I didn't want you worrying
that we would owe him
for the rest of our lives.
You don't marry someone
just because they knock you up.
All right, Harvey, here it is.
You lose,
you embrace this partnership
with no reservations.
He can beat me,
I'll welcome him
with arms wide open.
He can't,
we send him back to England,
and he can spend his time
fixing his teeth.
Fine.
You beat Edward,
we don't do this.
And since you didn't want
to hear Darby's terms,
these are mine.
You win, you get what you want.
You lose, you stay,
you extend your noncompete,
and you get a chance
to earn your name on the door
because it's not
going up there now.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece oj pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right
♪ all that time imagine this ♪
♪ The greenback boogie
Get in the car.
I prefer to walk.
Since when?
Doctor recommended it.
Helps me work out the kinks
since I got stabbed in the back.
You?
Last night was
a personal attack on me.
Oh, that's funny
because Jessica seemed to think
it was a personal attack
on her,
yet both of you knew
about the merger
and chose not to tell me.
You should get lunch... seems like
you have a lot in common.
Harvey. Harvey.
Can you stop being so defensive
for one second?
You put me on the defensive.
And I'm not just going to stand
here and listen to you
because I went on the attack.
Harvey...
No, don't "Harvey" me, okay?
You made your bed,
and now you're going to sleep
in it alone.
What did I do
that was so terrible?
For the past nine months,
I have been fending off attacks
from Daniel Hardman,
Allison Holt, and Robert Zane.
I told you before.
You want to get your name
on the door,
get it
at your own goddamn firm.
Okay. Fine.
If it's not personal,
you're not going to hold it
against me when we beat you.
0 and everything, Scottie.
That's your record against me...
0 and everything.
I won't have
to hold anything against you
because there won't be
anything to hold.
- Hey.
I never got to buy you
that drink last night.
- They we free.
- I know.
You left.
- I did.
- It was a nice party.
- It was.
- Mm-hmm.
Mmhmm.
Okay, so I see you're still
not going to tell me why...
I didn't get into Harvard.
Don't look at me that way.
With sympathy?
- With pity.
- I wasn't. Rachel...
Listen to me.
There are other schools.
Don't.
Yeah. I won't.
It wasn't
that I wasn't good enough.
I know that.
- It was Louis.
- What?
The interviewer...
um, apparently she and Louis
had a history, and...
Wait. She didn't let you in
because of him?
That's... I know.
- Not right.
- I know.
[Scoffs]
Tell me about the day
you found out.
- Rachel, come on.
- No.
I need to hear how it felt
from someone who got in
because I'll... I'll never hear
that for myself.
You're looking at me
like that again.
I'm not.
Then what?
It's just not right.
Yeah.
It was a pleasure meeting you.
- [Mouthing words]
- [Chuckles]
What the hell was that?
What was what?
What were you doing with Donna?
I was caressing her lovely hand
with my lovely lips.
You know what I mean.
What are you doing here?
Oh, that.
I was being treated to a tour
of your little outpost.
I'll grant you this,
you've got quite
the spectacular view...
Though truth be told,
my favorite spot
was inside
Ms. Paulsen's cubicle.
[Elevator bell dings]
How could you?
- How could I what?
- Don't.
You let that man
inside your cubicle.
Inside my what?
Nigel Nesbitt...
I mean, you let him...
I have never crossed
the boundary of your cubicle.
And should that honor
ever be bestowed on me,
at least I'd be gentleman enough
to keep it between us.
I mean, I have
too much respect for you.
Louis, he leaned over
to get a file.
He's doing an efficiency list.
Oh, thank God.
Wait a second. I've been asked
to do an efficiency list.
- So do one.
- No, you don't get it.
It's inefficient to have two
people doing efficiency lists.
It's a test.
- To see who's better.
- How dare they?
Man, you know, it's bad enough
that smug bastard thinks
he's higher up
on the mud chain than me.
Is he?
- Uh-oh.
- Again?
Didn't you tell him
about Cartagena?
I was on tilt
after he nullified Baden-Baden.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
I let him out-mud me.
What am I going to do?
Okay, I'm going to tell you
exactly what you're going to do.
You're going
to pull your shit together,
and you're going to kick
his limey ass.
You're goddamn right.
Louis, I know you.
Harold is gone.
Do not take your frustrations
out on somebody else.
Oh, Donna, remember,
I told you.
I am not that man anymore.
I would never let any...
what the hell
are you looking at, asshole?
Right.
[Clears throat]
Uh, can I help you?
No, no. I'm fine.
Just had a mochaccino.
Waiting to see Harvey.
He's making you wait?
Oh, I don't actually believe
he's aware I'm here.
So why don't you go in?
Well, his secretary
isn't present to announce me.
It wouldn't be proper.
- What year is it?
- Hmm?
- Huh?
- Mike?
- Yeah?
- What's going on out there?
Um, it's kind of hard
to explain.
Have you ever seen
Downton Abbey?
What?
I haven't caught it,
but I've heard great things.
Yeah, it's terrific.
- Really?
- Yeah.
May I present
Mr. Edward Darby of...
- Get the hell out of here.
- Okay.
- Oh, I'll Netflix it.
- You should.
I don't mean to pry,
but is that how you treat
all your underlings?
What?
Well, just being curious,
but how would you like
to be spoken to that way?
Listen, Benny Hill,
I'm a little busy
preparing a motion
to kick your ass.
You mind getting to the point?
Well, that is the point.
You may have
to expediate that motion
a little faster than you think.
Tomorrow I'll be freezing
your assets.
What?
Hmm. It seems that one
of the three companies
you picked a Dickens with
has a cousin
who happens to be the president
of a consortium of banks,
whereby...
Well, you get the picture.
I'd move as much money
as possible forthwith.
Let me get this straight.
You're coming in here
to warn me
that you're going to freeze
my client's assets?
Of course.
This way, you'll have time
to transfer a bit of currency
to fund your legal battle.
It wouldn't be sporting,
otherwise.
- "Sporting"?
- Certainly.
One doesn't hunt the fox
while it's still in its den.
One sounds the horn
and allows the poor creature
a head start
before giving chase.
You think I'm the fox?
Think it?
The only one
who doesn't know that is you.
You and me...
Right now...
Game of efficiency list.
I'm afraid I don't have
my files with me.
Files are for pussies.
Right you are.
I was just trying
to give you a way out.
I looked into you.
And I you, Louis Marlowe Litt.
You, as everyone else
in your firm,
graduated from Harvard Law.
And you, as everyone else
in your firm,
graduated from either
Harvard or Cambridge,
which waters down the purity.
However, I graduated from both.
That's inefficient.
[Softly] Not when done
in three years.
[Softly] Well, this isn't
about your efficiency.
This is
about your efficiency list.
[Normal voice]
My list isn't science.
It's a work of art.
Performance reviews
versus projected billables...
child's play.
I ain't no child.
I begin with life expectancy.
I begin with nutrition.
How do you think
I determine life expectancy?
Number of sexual partners.
- Relationship to mother.
- Pet ownership.
The three things
are inextricably linked,
and I have the formula
right here.
Yeah, well, I...
Just remembered
that I have a deposition
that I have to go to
in conference room "D."
There is
no conference room "D."
They're re-lettering.
Where are you off to
in such a hurry?
Uh, I have to finish
this page-turner.
Harry Potter?
No, but it is
by a British author.
Well, I've got something else
for you to read.
- What?
- A letter.
Oh, sweet.
It's not even my birthday.
It's not to you. It's from you.
This is to Harvard.
I'm going
over Sheila Sazs' head
and telling them
everything that happened.
Well, you are.
- Rachel, you can't...
- No, come on.
You said it yourself.
It is not right
that I'm being denied admission
because someone's
punishing Louis.
It's not,
but I can't sign this.
- Why not?
- Because it's not my place?
- Well, then whose place is it?
- I didn't see what happened.
It's hearsay.
Mike, I'm someone
who wants to go to Harvard.
You're someone
who went to Harvard.
Who do you think
they're going to listen to more?
Are you going
to help me or not?
I'll help you.
Whatever it is,
I'm not in the mood.
I know about Rachel
and Sheila and Harvard.
How?
Rachel told me.
She wants me to send this letter
going over Sheila's head,
but it can't come from me.
Yeah, it can't come
from anyone.
[Sighs]
She didn't get in
because they didn't think
she was good enough.
- You lied to her.
- No, I never lied to her.
I told her she was good enough,
which she is,
but I let her down because
I couldn't persuade Sheila,
which is the truth.
Louis, you have to tell her
the real truth.
Mike, I saw the look
on her face,
and I took it away.
I do not want to put it back.
She is going to pursue this.
She's going to find out
one way or the other.
I'm not going to let her
find out from Harvard.
I can't tell her.
You'll regret it.
Look, I'll give you another day
to think about it,
but after that,
I have to tell her myself.
[Sighs]
Gentlemen, I'm glad
you stopped by.
I wanted to inform you
I'm leaving town on the morrow.
I'll be having my number two
handle the case for me.
I expect you'll do the same.
Why would I do that?
It's tradition.
I leave it to you.
Honor it or don't.
I say we honor it.
Oh, by the by, Downton Abbey...
got it in my briefcase.
Plan to watch it on the plane.
Oh, my God. You are going to...
Please, please.
I abhor spoilers.
Episode three...
that's all I'll say.
Oh.
Why don't you two
watch it together
over a game of Tiddlywinks?
You seem to be upset
over my game
of "let's put the peacock
in its place."
I'm glad you mentioned that.
I brought a little
going-away present for you.
This is a biscuit
and a bottle of water.
It's what I assume
they serve in English prison,
which is
where your client's going
for freezing
our client's assets.
It's a violation
of international law
to intimidate a litigant
into settling
by choking their funding.
You seem to think you've
got me by the short hairs.
However, if you turn
to page 693 in this tome,
you'll find an exception
to that very law.
No, I won't.
I've memorized this book.
Yes, I was told
of your prowess,
which is why I chose a law
not published in any book,
but a long-standing provision
honored in England for decades.
We can do what we like,
as long as notice is given.
You don't give a shit
about being sporting.
You just wanted
to skirt the law.
Nonsense. I wanted to do both.
By filing this action,
you have opened your clients up
to a charge
of malicious litigation.
Which is
why you froze the assets
in the first place.
You baited us.
In any case, you seem to be
backed up against the wall.
I'm comfortable there.
Gives me back support
for when I come out swinging.
Well, you'd better
do something quickly.
Your clients
don't have the funds
to proceed beyond, I'd say,
this week's end.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
Hey.
Episode three...
Lady Mary and the Turk do it,
and then the Turk dies.
Sorry.
Jessica, you wanted to see me?
I thought you were supposed
to be announced.
You summoned me.
That supersedes an announcement.
How can I help you?
I understand
you're leaving town tomorrow
and putting Dana Scott
in your stead.
Yes, I have some business
to attend to on the coast.
Yes, your business
with Bayne-Powlen in Los Angeles
and Tillson-Tuttle
in San Francisco.
Do you really think
you could take meetings
with other firms
and I wouldn't know?
- Why would I not?
- Because we have a deal.
That deal presupposed
that you could control your man.
I can control him.
Then why the hell
did you allow our wager?
For the same damn reason
you made it.
If I can't beat him,
he won't respect me.
And if he doesn't respect you,
he won't respect me,
and he will eventually leave.
And he's too valuable an asset.
I didn't just fall
off a turnip truck.
No, I don't suppose you did.
The truth is,
you're afraid you might lose.
I'm afraid of nothing
of the sort.
Then why are you taking
meetings with other firms?
You gave me your word
on this deal,
so either you're going
to win and break it,
or you're afraid.
I never break my word.
Then there it is.
I'm not afraid,
but I didn't get where I am
without taking
some precautions.
Then go ahead and take them.
But you're wasting your time
because we're not losing
this case.
Hey, can I, uh, talk
to you for a sec?
What is it, Louis?
I'm just a little busy now.
I just wanted to say
that I know you've been taking
a lot of heat
from Jessica, and...
I'm glad you did what you did.
That's not supposed
to be public knowledge.
Well, no, Donna told me
because she knows
that I support you 100%.
Do you?
Nigel Nesbitt...
my British counterpart.
What about him?
He out-mudded me.
Didn't you tell him
about Cartagena?
Oh, would we be having
this conversation if I had?
Louis, relax.
I know how seriously
you take your mudding,
but that's personal.
It doesn't mean
he's a better lawyer.
Yeah, but he didn't
just out-mud me, Harvey.
He out-listed me.
He out-educated me.
He...
out-me'd me.
And if this guy
out-finances me...
I understand.
I mean, but really, do you?
Because I fought tooth and nail
to become one
of 30 senior partners,
and I'm the best at what I do.
But if this merger
goes through,
I'm going to be one of 150,
and I'm not going to be
the best of anything.
Harvey, I'm scared.
Please tell me
we're going to win this thing.
Our backs are against the wall.
What do you need?
Right now I need
to buy some time.
- That's easy.
- What?
You once told me what to do
when your back's
against the wall.
Break the goddamn thing down.
That's right.
- You have access to that shit?
- All of it.
They needed me
to do an efficiency list.
We got 'em.
You're not
Mr. Chong's Chinese food.
Oh, I ran into him
on my way in.
I just sent him away.
Why would you do that?
M.S.G... It's terrible for you.
Plus, I ate it.
[Sighs]
What's this?
It's what you're going to use
against Scottie
tomorrow morning.
Me?
You're going in as number two.
I don't want to give Edward
any excuses.
You mean you don't want
to deal with Scottie.
Well, that's just
a side benefit.
Right.
Whoa, wait a second.
This is confidential information
from the merger.
Which you're going to use
to get us a reprieve.
You broke the Chinese wall?
Why do you think I'm here?
Harvey, this is
inadmissible stuff.
And it's in the ballpark
of what Tanner accused you of
with Coastal Motors.
You think I don't know that?
Are you sure
you want to do this?
No, I'm not.
But it's the only way I see us
getting a little breathing room,
and I'd rather cross my own line
than sign their dotted one.
Okay.
Then it looks
like I have a date
with your girlfriend
in the morning.
[Elevator bell dings]
Weren't you supposed
to be announced?
I don't play by those rules.
Hmm. Somehow
that doesn't surprise me.
What are you...
Doing here? You're not Scottie.
And you're not Jimmy Smits,
but we make do.
Are you making
an L.A. Law reference?
No, I'm saying I wish
I had a date with Jimmy Smits.
- Ah.
- But instead I'm here...
To tell you that Edward's
in another league.
You're going to lose.
Well, there's only one problem.
Words are coming
out of your mouth,
which means
the real story isn't.
Okay, you want the real story?
Your clients
are running out of funds.
You have a window. To do what?
- Give up.
- [Chuckles]
No, I don't think
that's going to cut it for us.
Why not?
Because...
We have this.
[File thuds]
Harvey, we still have
to work together after this.
I am giving you a way out.
We can still both
be name partners.
No, we can't.
I made a deal with Jessica.
I win, you're out.
I give up,
you're going to be name partner
all by yourself.
That's not what I want.
Harvey, don't you get it?
Wait a second.
If you're here,
who the hell's in with Mike?
Get out.
You're angry.
This isn't funny, Harvey.
You just broke the law.
It's a civil law.
No one's going to go to jail.
Justify it all you want,
but you cheated.
Like you,
subbing in for Scottie?
I see what you're doing.
You know damn well
Darby plays by the rules.
So if you win by cheating,
you win.
And if you lose,
then they think you're dirty,
and they won't want to merge.
You really want to merge
with a man
who's asking
for your help to win?
He didn't ask.
I insisted.
On being his number two.
I guess that's a preview
of things to come.
And is that little stunt
you pulled
a preview of things to come?
Holt, Zane, Hardman...
we just fought them off.
We won. We're strong.
We've got money.
And if we do this,
we go to the next level.
We'll be the biggest,
baddest fish in the sea.
Those three names
you mentioned... fleas.
Not only can't they bully us,
they can't touch us.
And what's going to happen
after I beat Darby?
You think I'm playing with you?
That stunt you pulled...
fruit from the poison tree.
I will have that reversed
on Tuesday.
You think I'm not going
to find anything
between now and Tuesday?
- I know you won't.
- Is that a threat?
It's a prediction.
I can go.
Where you going to go?
Hmm?
Even if I let you out,
it's the same out there,
only worse.
And you'll be a winner,
but not a leader,
and you won't have me.
You don't know these people.
I know they said
I couldn't control you.
You're going to learn
that I can.
The merger
hasn't gone through yet,
so technically,
you're not allowed to be lurking
around our files.
I'm not lurking.
I'm looking for you.
And here I am.
I think that you lied to me.
I think that you're wrong.
You don't even know
what I'm talking about.
I know I'm not a liar.
You told me you never said
a bad thing about me.
And I never have.
But you don't like me.
I don't like people
who lie to Harvey.
Are you in love
with him, Donna?
I am so frickin' tired
of people asking me that,
and it is none
of your business.
But, no.
And I did like you,
until you walked in here
with that bullshit agenda and...
It's not bullshit.
Okay, then what
would you call it?
Why do you think
I came back last time?
I brought us in on Folsom?
I don't know
how to get his attention
unless I sue him.
You're in love with him.
He's he's just so angry at me,
and I-I don't know
how to make him believe it.
Well, why would he believe you?
All you've ever done
is lie to him.
This is not...
This is not a lie.
Look, Dana, if you want
to break through his anger,
you're going to have
to do something.
The merger.
Walk away.
[Scoffs]
From my name on the door.
If you want him to hear you,
you're going to have to make
a sacrifice.
So I just...
Risk everything
with no guarantee.
That's what sacrifice is.
I got your message.
Why are we meeting here?
You sound like
you don't trust me.
Well, you did sandbag me
with Jessica.
Jessica sandbagged you
Still doesn't explain
why we're meeting here.
Baby Harvey.
[Scoffs]
That's a huge compliment.
- Call it like I see it.
- I meant for him.
Like I said, baby Harvey.
[Clears throat]
We're meeting here because you
will never find this.
If this checks out,
it'll win the case for us.
I know.
And why am I the one
you're giving this to?
Because there are
some things in life
more important than winning.
That's not what I asked.
Why are you giving it to me?
When we were in law school,
Harvey's brother got sick.
He needed money.
His father didn't have any.
His mother
wasn't in the picture.
Don't tell me.
Harvey found a way
to help him out.
He used his tuition.
Anyway...
When his mother found out,
she contacted him.
Harvey wouldn't take a nickel
from her.
So she gave his brother
the money.
Who used it to pay him back.
I didn't even know
Harvey had a brother.
You'd like him.
He's like you.
So are you saying
that I have to tell Harvey
I found this on my own?
You don't have to.
But it'll definitely increase
your odds of him using it.
- I found something.
- Let me see.
It's not done.
We have to hurry.
But I can get it done
before tomorrow morning.
This is good.
I know.
Get on it. Where'd you get it?
You know where I got it.
The question is,
are you going to let me use it?
- Get out.
- Harvey, we can win with this.
Here's what you don't get.
You can't trust her.
If it came from her,
it'll come back to bite us
in the ass.
Tomorrow morning is coming,
and we don't have anything else.
- Then go find me something.
- Okay.
Pardon me. Excuse me.
Do you mind
if I have a little more lemon?
Thanks.
You were at the show?
Seat 4-A. You?
Seat A-4.
Shakespeare well performed.
Indeed...
Though not improved
by the yammering
of that battle axe.
Well, thank God she stopped
after the first act.
Thank you.
Well, she didn't
precisely stop.
You had her removed?
Told her
the baby-sitter phoned,
and the children were on fire.
What's that?
One row up...
some douche bag was texting.
Took it from him,
didn't even know.
Oh, uh, please.
Incidentally, excellent use
of the word "douche bag."
Well, I've had a lot
of experience with them.
As have I.
I don't make friends
very easily.
That's funny.
When I was a kid...
There was a bunch of them.
And, uh, every day
there was something new,
meaner and meaner.
Most of them
were just followers,
but there was that one...
Kirk Breslin.
Julian Hunt.
And then one day
I decided to be mean.
I just told
that bully piece of shit
that he'd never be anything,
do anything,
or amount to anything.
After that, they never made fun
of me again.
In fact, they, uh...
They never talked to me again.
Right.
I shouldn't have impugned
Baden-Baden.
It's just that when I asked you
if you took mud,
I was...
Offering a warm,
muddied hand of friendship,
and you took that hand
and wiped it clean.
Well, I didn't recognize
the gesture.
I understand.
It's a lonely job,
being the hatchet man.
Yeah, well, I guess
it's, uh, our cross to bear.
Hmm.
Can I be honest with you?
With the results
of my efficiency list,
I keep arriving
at the same conclusion.
There's no room for both of us.
[Sighs] Unless...
We made room for each other.
I leave you off my list.
And I leave you off mine.
Well, would you be willing
to sacrifice the integrity
of your list?
[Sighs]
I would...
For a friend.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
I have a feeling
you're about to tell me.
Are you for this merger
or against it?
I'm against it.
Why? Never mind.
I'm going to tell you why...
because of Scottie.
If I can't trust her,
how can I trust any of it?
She's showing you you can
by throwing it all away.
That folder
is a wild-goose chase.
Oh, my God. For somebody
who's usually three steps ahead,
you are a mile behind.
She is in love
with you, Harvey...
Only she can't tell you that
because she,
like everybody else,
knows that it will only
drive you away.
- Donna.
- If she had shown up here
and asked you
to start a relationship,
would you have said yes?
No, you wouldn't have.
It's not that simple.
Was it not that simple
with Zoe?
What the hell
does that have to do with it?
You let her go.
She left me to raise her niece.
- Did you ask her to stay?
- It wasn't on the table.
She wanted you to fight.
That poor girl
was losing her father,
and I wasn't about to try
and replace him
while it was happening.
Bullshit! You let her go!
And I am so sick
of watching you fight like hell
for everything
that happens in here
and nothing
that happens in here.
- Is this about Zoe?
- No.
Is this about you?
No.
This is about Scottie.
You don't know what she did.
I do know what she did.
She cheated on her fiance,
so you think that that means
that there
will always be a chance
that she will cheat on you.
The difference is,
she didn't love him.
She loves you.
Look, I know
that your mother hurt you,
but you need to get over it.
You think
that's what I'm worried about?
She made me
make a fool out of him,
a man I'd never met,
a man who'd never done
a wrong to me.
How am I going to trust someone
who made me a man who did that?
Maybe you can't trust her.
But if you want to end
this merger,
you better trust
what she gave Mike.
Give him the file.
What do you think
I did four hours ago?
You wanted to see me?
That request went out
two hours ago.
Uh, yeah, I was
in the middle of something.
What were you in the middle of?
Excuse me?
You said you were
in the middle of something.
I assume it's Harvey's case.
I can't tell you that.
You're on the other side.
Is there some rule
against my checking
on my own employee?
I'm confident that,
after tomorrow,
you'll either settle or lose.
And why is that?
Because I've prepared a motion
based on a file
dated September 14th.
Darby didn't tell me
about that.
He didn't know about it.
Where'd you get it?
[Sighs]
Hmm.
What does it say?
It says you're going to lose.
Then that's too bad...
Because you're going
to throw it away.
- What?
- You heard me.
You're going to go home.
You don't call,
you don't answer,
and you don't come back
until that deadline is passed.
Wait a minute.
These are your clients.
Who Harvey is using.
- That's a bullshit argument.
- And so is that file.
- I won't.
- You will.
Harvey will never forgive me.
Right now your problem
isn't with Harvey.
Your problem is with me.
You don't do this,
who's to say
you don't end up in a cell
for practicing law
without a degree?
And who's to say you don't
share that cell with me
for knowing about it
the whole time?
You don't want
to take that tact.
- I didn't start it.
- I will beat you.
The last time
you said that to me,
you thought
you didn't need a computer.
You were wrong.
That was
about demonstrating knowledge,
and the stakes were nothing.
This is about my power,
and the stakes are everything.
This is a letter
to the district attorney,
saying that it's come
to my attention
that you are breaking the law.
I believe you've met him...
not the type to let it slide.
You file your motion...
I'll file mine.
[Footsteps approaching]
Okay, look, Harvey...
shut your mouth!
I risked everything for you.
Then I did it again and again.
- Wait. You weren't there.
- I didn't have to be.
- Jessica...
- You don't work for Jessica.
You work for me.
I know I do,
but I was just trying
to get you what you wanted...
your name on the door.
No, you got
Edward Darby's name on the door.
My part of the deal is gone.
What? You never told me that.
I didn't think I needed
to tell you that
because I didn't think
you would ever betray me.
Harvey,
look at what we've done...
you and me.
You broke the Chinese wall.
I got information
directly from Scottie.
That's two ethical violations
that six weeks ago
would have made
your stomach turn.
- That's not why you did it.
- Fine.
But look me in the eye and
tell me it's not true anyway.
You know what,
it doesn't matter
because you don't get to make
my decisions for me.
Isn't that what you
were trying to do for me?
This is a private conversation.
You want to have it out,
let's have it out...
right now.
You might want to go.
I'm sorry.
You're back
in the associates' pool.
Harvey, come on.
Turns out you're not
the best lawyer I've ever seen.
In fact, you're fired.
No, he's not.
Oh, you going to overrule me
on that too?
You can go.
I didn't overrule you
on the other.
I beat you fair and square.
- No, you didn't.
- You're right.
I cheated, like you.
You jumped to the other side.
You put me on the other side.
I had a deal
that put your name
right next to mine.
And it wasn't even
up there yet,
and you started acting
like it was on top of mine.
- To protect you.
- Bullshit.
This wasn't
about protecting me.
This was about advancing you.
That's what this whole thing
is about.
What?
Hardman said it.
I didn't think it was true.
He said you don't trust me.
He meant you're afraid of me.
Afraid of you?
Boy, I just kicked your ass.
And you didn't just want it.
You begged me for it.
So now you're going
to stay here,
be humble,
and learn your goddamn place.
[Elevator bell dings]
You could have just told me
that you didn't love me
instead of selling me out.
I didn't sell you out, Scottie.
Well, somebody did
because Darby found out
what I gave Mike,
and I just got fired.
It wasn't me.
Well...
At least there's that.
Good-bye, Harvey.
And then we just toasted to it,
one hatchet man to the other.
Wow, Louis.
That's the sweetest story
I've ever heard.
- I broke my word.
- What?
I put him on the list,
and I handed it in.
How could you do that?
I realized I couldn't do that
to my list.
I wouldn't be able
to live with myself,
which means he couldn't either.
Yes, he could.
Meaning?
He didn't put you on his list.
I have to do something.
You can't. It's too late.
Not that.
I couldn't be a good friend
to Nigel,
but I could've been a good
friend to Rachel, and I wasn't.
What are you talking about?
I missed the deadline
to tell her something,
but I can still try
to make it right.
- I'm a man of my word.
- Huh.
And what word is that?
I'm here to officially
welcome you to the firm
with open arms.
I'm not much of a hugger.
Good.
One more thing...
Jessica was wrong.
Scottie didn't give me
anything.
I took it.
You say you're a man
of your word,
yet you're lying for her.
I am.
Honorable nonetheless.
What would you have me do?
Give her her job back.
What reason
would I have to do that?
Whatever she did,
you wouldn't have this merger
without her.
Fair enough.
Would you have her work here
or in London?
Rachel, look, I'm sorry,
but I am not...
When did you send that letter?
Um, I was, uh...
I'll tell you when... never.
Okay, look, let me explain.
When I went to see Louis,
he told me
what really happened...
I know. He told me too.
And I get it.
I'm not good enough.
What I don't get, Mike, is why
you didn't have the courage
to just come
and tell me that yourself.
Look, he lied to you.
I thought he deserved a chance
to tell you himself, all right?
When I went to his office
to get him to sign the letter...
Wait.
You went to him
to sign the letter?
You told me you were going
to sign the letter.
- No...
- No, so you lied to me.
No, I didn't. I told you
that I would help you.
That is such bullshit!
That's not what you meant,
and you know it.
You've been cagey with me
since the second I came to you
about the letter,
and you're being cagey
with me right now.
You are. You're lying to me.
Not today, Rachel.
Please, stop.
Then what day, Mike?
Because it's always something.
It is always some secret
or some story or some lie...
- You don't understand...
- I don't understand what?
You don't understand
what I have been through!
what I have lost!
Because it's everything,
everyone that I love...
Trevor, my grandmother, Harvey,
now, probably this job!
I am not ready to lose you...
Not today!
Then tell me.
I never went to Harvard.
What?
I'm a fraud.
Rachel, I...
Rachel...