Ross. Triple double. Courtesy
of America's favorite burger chain.
Louis won
the class action suit?
Ten thousand men of Harvard
Want vict'ry today,
For they know
that o'er old Eli
Fair Harvard holds sway
So then we'll conquer
all old Eli's men
My favorite part.
You don't know the lyrics,
do you?
I don't even know the lyrics,
Louis.
Now,
are we practicing law down here
or auditioning
a chorus line?
It's called
esprit de corps.
And I just got a $100 million
jury award overturned.
I don't have
to overturn awards like that
because I've never lost one
in the first place.
So, what is this? A new cologne?
Or just a hint of jealousy?
I'm surprised you, uh,
don't recognize your wife's perfume.
I know.
You're not married.
It's still funny.
You do realize we're celebrating
making fat people even fatter, right?
If you wanted to do good,
you should have been a fake doctor.
Business cards.
- Yep.
- My mistake is now official.
Come with me.
And learn the goddamn lyrics
to the Harvard song, will you?
Oakhurst Capital has agreed
to a $200 million licensing deal.
We are at the goal line.
How are we
on brand protection?
The contract is airtight.
The only issue here is to get
the Joyful Toy Company to close.
I'll go over it with
Joy one-on-one.
Protocol in a meeting
is to put your phone on silent.
Oh. Uh...
If it does ring,
you answer it.
Not in here.
Don't feel the need to rush back
when you're done.
Who is this?
Dude, it's Trevor.
Don't hang up.
Look, I only get one call.
I'm in jail.
I tried to hop this bus
at Port Authority. I was drunk.
It's all messed up. Look, I know
we haven't talked since we fought.
But I didn't know
who else to call.
I'm sorry, man.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
I'm going to
pay you back.
Good. Your bail
cost me everything I had in the bank.
The thing is,
I don't have the money.
What are you talking about?
You were clearing $10,000
a month selling weed.
It went out
as fast as it came in.
Came in?
I quit.
I'm not dealing anymore.
Bullshit.
I'm serious.
After we fought,
things just started
to fall apart.
Jenny broke up with me.
I didn't know.
Well, I just realized
I needed to make a change.
I even sold my bong.
What have you done
with my friend?
You should talk.
Look at you.
You look like
Gordon Gekko's little brother.
- Okay.
- Are you working on Wall Street, man?
Why did you call me, Trevor?
You're the one person
I knew would show up.
You want to ask me
for anything?
Else?
Look. All I care about right now
is keeping my record clean.
You don't happen to know
any good lawyers, do you?
No. I don't.
See the money,
wanna stay for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
Why the rush now?
You've already wasted
ten minutes of my life.
Please tell me you didn't wait
ten minutes just to scold me.
I've been waiting for you
to bring the paperwork down
so I can close
a nine-figure licensing deal.
If your phone rings
while I'm talking to Ray,
I'm throwing it out of the car
while it's attached to your hand.
Eddie Hope
and the Mannish Boys.
1959. Three guesses.
Guesses?
Won't be a fool no more
You insult me, Harvey.
Don't worry, we won't be late.
Okay. What was the name
of the record label?
Marlin Records.
Who covered it
in the late '60s?
Ah, I want to say
The Stones, but...
You need some guesses?
Oh!
Oh, my God.
Just like
a private car service, huh?
Thinking you don't
have to yield?
What? Yield?
You ran a red light.
That light was yellow.
- No, sir, it was not.
- Are you calling me a liar?
- Back off.
- Mind your business, okay?
Oh, I'm minding
my business.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Anyone throws a punch, I'm going
to introduce you to Mr. Taser.
Trade insurance.
I'll take reports one at a time.
As much as I'd like to help you out,
I'm late for a meeting.
Oh, no. You're not going anywhere.
I need a statement from you, too.
Here is my information.
I need you to babysit the client
until I get there.
Don't mention the deal.
She asks any questions,
just nod your head
and look pretty.
Ms. McAfee. I'm Mike Ross.
I work with Harvey.
Oh. You're the protégé
that he's been gushing about.
He was gushing?
Well, he mentioned
that you existed.
For Harvey, that's gushing.
Uh, he's running
a few minutes late today. Car trouble.
I was just about to
have tea with the girls.
Would you care to join me?
- I'd love to.
- Good.
And for heaven's sakes,
call me Joy.
Okay, Joy.
These are the girls.
Susie, Sarah, Stacy,
Sinclair, and Sabrina.
Susie, where are your manners?
Shake hands with this nice young man.
Just kidding.
I know they're dolls.
Oh.
They're named
after my daughters.
I started the company
because of them, really.
You know, dolls didn't used
to be these cheap, plastic bimbos
from China
that we have today.
Your mother made them
for you by hand.
I wanted my girls to have
that same experience.
And here we are,
thirty years later.
Every parent's
worst nightmare.
What do you mean?
These little angels,
they sell for $90 a pop.
I wasn't born with a butler,
you know.
I've got to say,
this is amazing.
Taking on a project
like a licensing deal.
Why is that amazing?
Well, my grandmother
could never pull this off.
She's been retired
for ten years.
How is that
treating her?
She lives near my apartment.
I get to see her once a week. So...
That's very sweet of you.
No. No, it's not.
You know, whenever I needed her,
she was there.
No matter what.
She'd give me a hug.
She'd tell me everything
was going to be alright.
Even if it wasn't.
And now that she needs me,
I am always at work.
And I'm...
I'm so sorry. Yeah.
Never answer your phone
in front of a client.
- But it's you.
- What's happening?
Well, actually,
we're in the middle of a tea party.
I knew you were
the doll-playing type.
Put Joy on.
Ms. McAfee. It's Harvey.
Oh.
Oh. Joy, I'm sorry.
I have to reschedule.
No need to apologize.
I like this one.
I'll send him back after tea.
Tell me you didn't ask
our client for a doggie bag.
What can I say?
Stacy insisted.
I just got off with
Joy McAfee's general counsel.
It seems
she had an epiphany.
She wants less on her plate,
not more.
I thought you were
going to close her.
We need that doll money.
I'm on top of it.
Harvey, it took five months
to structure that deal.
Please don't make me
set fire to your desk.
I...
All you had to do
was have tea with the dolls.
Donna, schedule another tea party
with Joy as soon as possible.
And text me
the names of her girls.
Oh, what a shock. You can't keep
girls' names straight in your head.
Just yours, Debbie.
See, that's funny because
your name is Donna.
Harvey Specter.
I got your order right here.
I didn't order a pizza.
You've been served.
The cab driver who hit Ray
named me as a witness in a civil suit.
I need to pay
Travis Bickle a visit.
Harvey, if you let me
go talk to Joy,
- I know I can fix this.
- No.
You don't send a puppy
to clean up its own mess.
Optimally,
you don't even have a puppy.
Ross. Rumor has it you talked
a client out of $200 million.
The deal's not off the table, all right?
It's just a speed bump.
Dude, I think we just found
him a new nickname.
Speed Bump.
I feel like I'm back
in high school.
They called you
Speed Bump in high school?
Kidding. But if you need
any boxes to pack up your office...
Ah. Wait a minute.
There.
I think that belongs to you.
It wouldn't hurt so much
if you had thicker skin.
What do you want?
I want to pay you back
for posting bail.
Trevor, you've owed me forty bucks
since fifth grade.
I wrote it off. Okay?
Look, I want a clean slate.
Okay?
So, you don't want to see me,
I'll mail you a check.
Okay.
Yeah. Let's hang out
tomorrow night.
Nothing crazy, though, all right?
I have to be up early.
We can crochet pantyhose
if that's what it takes to be cool.
I think we can do
a little better than that.
Why don't we, uh...
Why don't we say Rex's, 7:30?
First six rounds are on me.
If you're serious
about paying me back,
the first hundred rounds
are on you.
Oh, it's the tough guy.
This is a matter
for insurance.
Not a frivolous lawsuit.
You know, for your information,
I suffered emotional pain.
Emotional pain?
Rub this
on your emotional pain.
You condescending
son of a...
Look at me.
I am going to warn you once.
Do not pursue this matter.
You know, I have been
held up at gunpoint three times.
So, do you think a fancy suit
and a $500 haircut,
that's going to scare me?
You take my driver to court,
I'm going to
represent him myself.
And when you lose,
you'll be covering my fee.
Which is going to be
a hell of a lot of haircuts.
Mmm. So you weren't
a one-way fare.
Ray's worked for me
eight years.
Then you don't have to worry
about being a witness.
Because as his employer,
you're liable
for his actions.
You know, I think you've seen
way too many reruns of Ally McBeal.
You know, I immigrated here
after September 11.
And they shut the doors
on everybody.
I couldn't pay
for a lawyer,
so I had to take them
to court.
I sued for my citizenship.
So I have a very special appreciation
for the law.
I appreciate
a good single malt.
I don't pretend
I can make one.
I wiped the floor
with the US government, Counselor.
I'm going to do
the same with you.
Ray.
Donna.
What are you doing here?
I don't have you scheduled.
Uh, I need to see Harvey.
Oh, come on.
You know the rules.
No one sets foot in there
without a warrant,
a Papal edict,
or my say-so.
I just got named
in a multi-million dollar lawsuit.
The accident
wasn't my fault.
Can I get in to see Harvey,
please?
Okay, say no more.
I will get you in.
You are so beautiful
when you're forceful.
I know you meant that
as a compliment,
but I don't appreciate limitations
being placed on my beauty.
Harvey. I'm already losing money
with the car in the shop.
A trial means
I can't work.
And how do you think my name is going
to play in front of a New York jury?
Rahim Benghazi?
I may as well buy
a one-way ticket to Guantanamo.
Not going to happen.
If I lose, I won't even
be able to afford a livery license,
let alone my insurance.
That's why I'm going to be
defending both of us.
Ray, this goes against
every fiber of my being.
I'm taking your case.
Pro bono.
I don't know what to say.
Absolutely nothing.
I've got a reputation to maintain.
Besides, it's not going
to take long. Okay?
I'm going to get
it dismissed.
Donna, call the court.
We need priority status on the docket.
Yeah. I already tried.
You drew Judge Palermo.
You know what you have to do,
don't you?
Yeah. The other thing that goes against
every fiber of my being.
Louis, has anyone told you
you're an exquisite soprano?
What do you want, Harvey?
You're right.
Why prolong my suffering?
I need you to get me in
to see Judge Palermo.
You need my help,
and you're not going
to pull rank on me?
Your case has nothing
to do with firm business, does it?
What's it
going to take?
A mani-pedi?
Tickets to Celine?
I'll see what I can do.
And your pound of flesh?
I need my back scratched,
I'll let you know.
Louis, unless that's a metaphor,
the deal's off.
Huh.
Joy, when I told you that
my grandmother didn't have much time,
I didn't realize that
she's 15 years older than you.
Now how do you know
how old I am?
That is a very closely
guarded secret.
I did some research.
Very resourceful.
I did it to assure myself
that you can handle a heavier workload.
I appreciate that.
But I'm not worried
about my health.
Is it the money?
Because I can guarantee
$200 million upfront
is just a tenth of what you stand
to make on this deal.
Michael, my dolls eat better
than most people.
I've got plenty of money.
This deal meant staying on for five
more years and doubling my workload.
I am going to take my grandchildren
on a cruise to Tahiti.
Tahiti?
You know the licensing agreement
includes a theme park.
You could take them there.
It's not about the deal.
I have had this same view
for 25 years.
I need a change of scenery.
I'm going to speak to Harvey
and I'm going to tell him
that I want to sell the whole business.
So I just spoke to
Judge Palermo.
And because he thinks
I'm a good guy
and I told him
I'd owe him one,
your case is going to be moved up.
Way ahead.
Back scratch.
I don't have a first born,
you know.
So what exactly
do you want for that?
- No, you're not getting one of my ties.
- No.
Your shoulder?
What... Your lapel...
Donna?
God.
Norma is going to Istanbul
for two weeks.
And you know that
I'm not good with temps.
My God.
Ask me for something else.
Harvey,
this is non-negotiable.
You owe me now.
Donna is one thing
that I can't give you.
Why not?
For one thing,
she'd never agree to it.
You're her boss.
You just tell her to do stuff.
I don't tell her
to do anything.
She just does.
All right, fine. You know what?
That's just not a problem.
I will call Judge Palermo,
and I'll tell him I was mistaken.
And then,
your hearing will be in,
I don't know,
maybe six months?
I tell you what.
If you can convince
her yourself,
you have my blessing.
She's going to love me so much,
you're going to fight to get her back.
Hi, Donna.
Harvey and I were just
talking about you.
No.
You don't even know
what I was going to say.
Yes, I do.
And how is that possible?
I read lips.
I know body language.
And I talk to Norma.
I'm not some token
you win at a fair, Louis.
You... I know you're not.
You're not a token.
- I'm a human being, and I just...
- Yes, you are.
I'm sorry. I just...
You know what?
That just made me feel really... cheap.
No, I'm just trying to tell you
that you're really good
at what you do, Donna.
So I'm going
to ask you...
It's like my soul hurts now.
No. Donna, listen.
Even if your soul hurts
a little bit...
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's going to be fine.
Don't cry.
Please don't cry, Donna.
Oh, shit.
I think I owe you one for that.
That was fun.
Wait a second.
The time that you cried
and then I let your parents
stay at my condo?
Yep.
So you don't want
to talk about it?
What is there
to talk about?
I did exactly
what my boss told me not to do,
and it blew up
in my face.
Dude, I told you
I'm taking care of this.
For my last few hours of employment,
please, I should pay.
Put the wallet away.
Ooh.
Dude, this is epic.
This is the scam
we always talked about.
God, I bet you're getting
laid left and right.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You lose appreciation after a while.
Come on.
Why did you put a phone number
on there?
It's a real firm.
Oh, yeah? Huh.
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm just calling
the employee directory.
- It's part of the scam, man.
- They'll check your story.
- Stop it.
- What?
- Trevor, stop. Hang up the phone.
- No.
- Trevor, hang up the phone. Stop.
- What?
All right? I'm working there.
Oh, yeah.
What, as a lawyer?
Are you...
Dude.
It's a long story. Okay?
But you can't tell anyone.
Ever. Okay?
That is awesome.
Man, I always said that if you quit
smoking pot, you could do it.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, that's right.
Yeah, you did.
Right before
you passed me the bowl.
What?
No, I just...
I wish you trusted me enough
to tell me.
I mean, all I did was
set you up on a drug bust.
Oh, God.
That was too soon.
I'm sorry.
Hi, ladies. How are you?
Um, I want to
let you know,
if you, either of you,
ever get arrested for anything,
you call this guy.
He's the best attorney in the city.
What would we
get arrested for?
Um... I don't know.
What are you thinking
about doing?
Uh, as your attorney,
I would definitely
advise you to do that.
Uh, four more.
Yeah.
I must warn you that representing
yourself at trial is not the...
What's he doing here?
You think you can schedule a meeting
without me knowing it?
Oh, no. I'm privy to all communication
between you and the court.
Well, if your driving matched
your legal knowledge,
we wouldn't be here.
Your Honor.
This case should be dismissed.
It's a matter for insurance.
Insurance only
covers repairs.
It does not deal
with my losses.
What losses?
Because of that accident, I missed
my chance to get my Taxi Medallion.
Can't you just
buy it next year?
The loan I got
expires in one week.
On top of that, a Medallion costs
$300,000 this go round.
Next year, $350,000.
So his entire claim
rests upon the assumption
that he would have won
this year's Medallion.
The hallmark of America is that
the little guy gets to see justice done.
We are all equals
in the eyes of the law.
That is why, out of all
the countries in the world,
I chose to come here.
What do you have to say about that,
Counselor?
I say Atticus Finch makes
a good speech here.
But this is a fender bender,
not a multi-million dollar law suit.
Vicarious liability
applies to discrimination,
harassment, and accidents.
Employers are responsible
for their employees' negligence.
The court finds
a reasonable suit here.
Trial starts tomorrow.
Thank you, Your Honor.
You're getting a good kick
out of this, aren't you?
I am. But I'm taking
this on its merits.
And you better bring
your A game tomorrow,
because he's got
a legitimate claim.
He wants a trial,
I'll give him a goddamn trial.
Your Honor.
So, how many cases
have you won?
I only remember
how many I've lost.
None.
Well, what happened
to the drinks?
I got a better idea.
Let's say we get a bottle
and take the party back to your place.
Make it a bottle of Dom,
and you're on.
All right.
How about four bottles?
Come on.
You guys want to get a cab?
Definitely.
Cab, four bottles of Dom...
You want to spend
any more of my money?
Just relax. Okay?
It's an investment in the evening.
And, uh, I just said
the thing about the bottles
to get the girls
out of the bar.
Really? Because it looked like you were
trying to get away from those guys.
Taxi! What guys?
The guys in the back.
You know what I'm talking about.
Come on. Who are they?
Look. Those two?
I... I... I don't know.
Where are all the cabs?
Well, it looked like
they knew you.
And not
in a very good way.
I... I don't know. Maybe they were,
uh, flirting with our dates. Okay?
I'd be pissed, too, if I watched
those legs walk away from me.
How we doing, ladies?
My feet are killing me in these heels.
- I'm sorry.
- Hey. Trevor. Come on.
- Taxi!
- Seriously. Stop playing with me.
What was that about back there?
Look, I'm not playing with you.
All right?
But just, if you play your cards right,
maybe you and, uh...
Maybe Marcella will...
Maybe she'll play with you.
Okay.
Now, it's going to be a tight
squeeze. Who wants to sit on my lap?
We don't go after him?
No, we're going to get
to him through this guy.
A-ha, just like
the good old days, huh?
Are you kidding me? This is
way better than the good old days.
I'm actually missing a shoe.
Hey, where are we?
Uh, I think we're in Hoboken.
You wanted to see me?
Did you go to see Joy
after I told you not to?
How did you know?
I didn't. Until now.
I told you.
A puppy can't clean up its own mess.
Mess? All I did was tell her
about my grandmother.
Your job is to
make my life easier.
If you can't understand that,
why did I hire you?
Police report summarized.
Traffic signal analysis.
Medallion bids,
attendees, and results.
That's why you hired me.
I thought you were all over
the Joy situation.
Instead,
you're all over page six.
You wanted me to do pro bono work.
This is it.
Pro bono enhances
a firm's image.
This makes us look like wealthy bullies
against an everyman cabby.
Does that seem like it
enhances our image to you?
I refuse to answer that
on the grounds that I don't want to.
Someone had a fun night.
Answer another call
you shouldn't have?
I... I... I didn't...
I was...
Piece of advice. When the big dog
asks the puppy something like that,
it's a rhetorical question.
Got it.
Before you go...
The phone call. The other day
when you answered it during the meeting?
Yeah. I'm sorry about that.
It won't happen again.
Who was it?
Um, it was just a friend.
You know, an emergency.
- What kind of emergency?
- Um...
Was it the friend who almost
got you busted for drug trafficking?
That friend? Trevor?
He's not dealing anymore,
Harvey.
So, it was him.
He called you from jail?
You know, I make a living
learning how to read people, Mike.
So if I saw it,
Jessica did, too.
Is that the kind of impression
that you want to leave around here?
This guy
is not your friend.
He is an anchor dragging you down.
Get rid of him.
He is my oldest friend,
Harvey.
I wasn't just going
to let him rot in jail.
What's going to happen
the next time?
Because there will be
a next time.
You going to bail him out?
Put yourself in jeopardy?
You know, if it weren't for Trevor,
you and I never would have met.
Cut him loose.
We're here to see Mike Ross.
He's an associate.
His friend, Trevor, referred us.
Thank you.
It looked like they knew you.
And not in a very good way.
Hey!
Excuse me. Officer.
Is Central Park that way?
Yeah,
just go right there.
I'm sorry.
I'm really terrible with direction.
Is it this street
right here?
This street, yes.
- Right here.
- Yeah.
Okay.
Trevor, it's Mike.
Call me back. I need to know
what the hell is going on.
Did you get
the red velvet cupcakes?
Yes. Three dozen.
Extra icing.
How the hell
did that happen?
Okay. You know what?
There. Problem solved.
I asked you
how'd you get that tear.
A couple of guys
came to the firm.
They were looking for me.
I don't know
what they wanted,
but I'm pretty sure it has something
to do with some shit Trevor did.
And that big brain of yours
doesn't remember me saying
to cut ties with that loser?
You know what? You've been
blowing off Joy's deal all week
for your friend, okay?
So, please.
First of all,
Trevor is not your friend.
You want to know
why I'm loyal to Ray?
I was taking a limo,
and I left $3,000 in it.
Ray happened to be
the driver.
He found it
and tracked me down.
Not a nickel of it
was missing.
And his first reaction
when this accident occurred
was to ask if we were okay.
Now, what would
Trevor's have been?
Cut him off.
And as far as
the licensing deal goes,
just because you think I'm blowing
something off, doesn't mean I am.
Now watch and learn.
Everything's set
for you to walk away.
We're selling
your stake as a block.
Your headhunter is lining up
your replacement as we speak.
Well, Harvey, this was
the most wonderful surprise.
You're a long-time client
who wants to be with her family.
It was the least I could do.
And you'll have...
...all the free time in the world
to spend with them.
Joey broke the lamp.
Oh, that's great.
Now, how soon
can we send them home?
They're booked on the first flight out
tomorrow morning.
So when you had Donna
text you the girls' names...
I was talking about
her daughters.
And you were
going to fly them out all along.
Do you remember when I said you don't
send a puppy to clean up its own mess?
Yes, Harvey. I do.
I'm not a puppy.
Court will come to order.
Mr. Santana,
your opening statement, please.
Driving a cab
isn't glamorous.
But it's
an honest day's work.
Ever since I started,
I've looked forward to a time
when I could tell customers
that they were riding in my cab.
That I was
an owner-operator.
So, I scrimped and I saved
until I finally had enough
put away to buy a Medallion.
But because of the actions
of these men,
I've lost that opportunity.
So make no mistake. This trial
is not about a busted headlight.
This is a trial
about a broken dream.
Forget the case.
They're going to make him President.
Statements are like free throws.
Easy.
Nobody's playing defense.
Are we good at defense?
You would agree that chauffeured drivers
cause more accidents?
- Objection. Badgering.
- Sustained.
Objection. Argumentative.
Leading the witness.
Ambiguous.
Privileged. Inflammatory.
Sustained.
Anything further,
Mr. Santana?
Yes, Your Honor.
I would like to call to the stand
Mr. Michael Ross, please.
What time had you called for the limo
on the morning of the accident?
We were supposed to leave
at 8:30.
And what time
did you get to work?
Objection. Irrelevant.
It's highly relevant,
Your Honor.
It speaks to the psychology
of the driver, Rahim Benghazi.
Overruled.
Answer Mr. Santana's question.
8:40.
So unless Mr. Benghazi
made up for that lost time,
you were going to be late
for that meeting. Correct?
Yes.
No further questions,
Your Honor.
When the accident occurred, you were
on your way to the Medallion auction.
When and where was this auction
to take place?
9:00 a.m., City Hall.
According to
the police report,
the accident occurred
at 8:53 a.m.
That means you only had seven minutes
to get downtown in rush hour traffic.
Objection. Irrelevant.
I believe when I made
the same objection,
you told his Honor
it was highly relevant.
Overruled.
You were running late.
Only the stakes for you
were much higher, weren't they?
These things
never start on time.
Then, why was the first Medallion
sold at 9:03 a.m?
You were scared your chance
at a Medallion was going up in smoke,
and you ran a red.
Then, you used the accident
to paint me and Ray Benghazi
as a couple of scapegoats.
You can't prove that.
What color was the light?
I take the Fifth.
You can't take the Fifth,
Mr. Santana.
This isn't a criminal case.
What color was the light?
He cut me off.
You claim to love
our legal system so much,
answer the question.
What color was the light?
- Your Honor?
- Answer the question, Mr. Santana.
It just meant so much to me.
Your Honor?
Can I sidebar with opposing counsel?
We can roll the dice with the jury,
but I'd rather settle.
- How much would I have to pay?
- Nothing.
You take responsibility
for the accident,
and your insurance company
makes Ray whole.
In return,
I waive my right to collect legal fees.
I don't know what to say.
Don't say anything.
I've got a reputation
to maintain.
That goes for you, too,
Judge.
Damn it, Trevor.
I left you, like, five messages.
Good to know your boy's flaky
with everyone. I was taking it personal.
What do you want?
Well, Trevor owes us $50,000.
He's never paid,
so you're going
to bail him out.
Listen, I don't have that kind of money.
Okay? I can't.
Well, if you're not down here
in an hour with it,
we're going to take it out
on Trevor.
Tell him where the money is.
Whatever you do,
don't show up.
Trevor.
You have one hour.
Hello? Hello.
What do you think you're doing,
leaving in the middle of a trial?
I've got some things
to take care of.
You mean someone
You never cut Trevor off,
did you?
No, I didn't. My friend's in trouble,
and I'm going to help him.
You know what?
This is what addicts do.
The second they start making progress,
they screw up.
Because deep down, they think it's
only a matter of time until they fail.
They'd rather fall from
the third floor than the penthouse.
Nothing you say
can stop me.
Then tell me
what the hell is going on.
He's clean. No wires.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Remember what happened
with the guy.
He was 300 pounds.
Now who did you say
you were again?
Trevor's lawyer.
Trevor didn't
mention a lawyer.
He doesn't know
he hired me.
Come on.
Open the briefcase.
Where's the goddamn money?
That photo is a screen-shot
taken from my firm's security video.
We know what you look like.
And if Mike Ross doesn't
hear from me in the next five minutes,
he's calling the police.
No, man. You're not coming
in here and threatening us.
You're looking at kidnapping,
extortion, and drug dealing.
And the District Attorney happens
to be number three on my speed dial.
Well, if we're looking at all that time,
you might as well add murder.
I've got a better idea.
Retainer agreement.
If you sign right here,
you'll become one of my clients.
And I won't be able to testify
against you even if I wanted to.
What about the money?
This envelope
contains $10,000.
Consider it a down payment
on Trevor's debt.
Only here's the thing.
I don't do pro bono work.
And my retainer agreement
requires a down payment of $10,000.
Now, as your attorney,
my job is to give you advice.
So, here's the deal.
Sign the agreement.
I thought I said
not to come.
Remember that forty bucks
from the fifth grade you owe me?
If you were dead,
how would I collect?
Oh, man.
I'm sorry. I just put you in trouble
just by hanging out with you.
So, why did you do it?
Because I'm a dick.
I bet you didn't think
you'd have to save my ass
so soon after bailing me out.
I wasn't the one
who saved you.
Yeah. Wow. As a friend,
that guy puts me to shame.
Harvey's not my friend.
Trust me.
Well, he didn't put his ass
on the line because of me.
Listen, I pled you down to a
misdemeanor, drunk and disorderly,
and I paid the fine.
I think it might be a good idea
if you got out of town for a while.
Montana.
You said you wanted
a clean slate.
I figured 20 hours on a bus
ought to do the trick.
Oh, yeah.
It will do me good.
Wait.
When I get back, you know who
the first person I'm going to call is.
Yeah. The one person
you know who'll answer it.
- For you.
- What's this?
I'm very happy
you took Ray on pro bono.
You, on the other hand,
can afford our services.
You want me to pay me
to represent me?
Mmm-hmm.
Ten hours at a $1,000 an hour.
Yeah, I'll let you
do the math.
You can't be serious.
I'll tell you
what I am serious about.
I hear you're finally
mentoring the kid.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Really? Because I understand that
you dropped the puppy analogy on him.
Which is exactly
what I used on you.
It may have slipped out
by accident.
On accident, on purpose...
The really important thing
is that I'm taller than you.
Yeah.
Yep.
You look much thinner in that.
You planted that story.
Be man enough to own it.
I don't traffic in the tabloids,
Harvey.
But I can see how whoever
planted this might find it amusing.
The great Harvey Specter
bullying a humble cab driver?
I mean,
it's a no-win situation, really.
Well, maybe you didn't hear.
I won the no-win situation.
Did it ever occur to you
that if you hadn't done that to me,
I actually
would have owed you one?
Maybe if you didn't humiliate me
in front of the associates.
Louis,
for an average attorney,
a $100 million
is a career case.
If I'm mocking you,
it means I think you're above average.
But stress balls?
You're making it too easy.
You put Trevor
on the bus to the boondocks?
Yeah.
Can I ask you a question?
After all this,
you really think I'm still buying
the Mr. I-Don't-Give-a-Crap thing?
Joy sent a little token
of her appreciation.
She got your hair
just right.
Did she ever
make one of these for you?
Not that you'll ever see.