Donna...
Donna.
You know, in all the years
that we worked together,
you've been over
to my place exactly twice,
the God-awful
dinner party and...
the other time.
I have been gone three weeks,
and you've been here
that many times. What?
I had a good time
at that dinner party.
Oh, my God, it is
just like you to make a joke.
And ignore the other time.
I brought you your bonus.
Really? You thought that
would make it all better,
handing me a check?
Look, I know that
you're pissed.
- Oh, what gave it away?
- Donna...
You just had to jump in there
at the trial, didn't you?
You just had to fight
my battles for me.
Yeah, I did that because,
the last time I saw you,
you were pissed that
I didn't fight for you.
Well, congratulations, Harvey.
All you managed to do
was make it look
like I love you.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Oh, my God, you think I do.
I have actually never met
such a self-important...
Donna, about that time,
you once told me...
I don't care what
I once told you!
That wasn't
what Louis was asking.
He was asking if I love you.
And you wouldn't answer.
Because he was forcing
a yes or no answer
to a complicated question.
I am not in love
with you, Harvey.
I love you like a brother
or a cousin, somebody that
you really, really look forward
to seeing at Christmas,
and then you're really,
really glad to see leave.
And as far as
you and I are concerned,
Christmas is over.
I didn't just come here
to give you a check.
I came here to get you back.
What, Cameron not working out?
I heard that little shit
redid my entire filing system.
Cameron's fine.
Look, I need you.
- Need?
- Need.
- Well, what about Jessica?
- Already signed off.
How did you get her to do that?
Because I told her
I can't be me without you.
- No, you didn't.
- Well, I thought it.
And she knows it.
Okay, I will come back
on two conditions.
One is you replace that check
with a bigger one.
And the other?
Harold...
Is that porn? No.
Well, yes, but that's not
what I'm using it for.
Okay, I'm about 150% sure
that I'm gonna
regret this, but...
What are you using it for?
I'm looking at tattoos.
I told you, it's what
I'm getting with my first...
Bonus time, boys and girls.
Too much. Way too much.
Oof, multiply this by zero,
and it's still way too much.
O'Neil, Racine,
Sabbatini... no Ross.
- Very funny, Louis.
- I'm not kidding.
It looks like
you came up empty.
You have the file for
the Solis motion to dismiss?
Yep, all set.
Main citations are tabbed.
Good. Go. I'm busy.
Okay, I was just, um...
you know, before, um... you...
Are you having a stroke?
What? My bonus.
Louis didn't have it.
Well, at least, he said
that he didn't have it,
so I thought
that maybe you, uh...
Maybe Jessica thinks
you don't deserve one.
You know, because...
you're not a lawyer.
Right, right.
No, that's true, so I guess
these won't be
doing you any good.
Jessica thinks
you're not a lawyer.
I don't think that.
Um... wow.
Your Monica Eton
performance worked.
You switched Carson,
Gallo, and Fogerty.
Wait, is that why
you're giving me so much?
Yes. We're up one.
You might want to
hold onto it for a bit.
- Why?
- Hanson.
Took a job at
the Justice Department.
Our lead is gone.
Now we're even.
Well, the vote's in four days.
The tie goes to the incumbent.
So we're good.
- Probably.
- Nice.
Uh, you do realize that
"hold onto it for a bit" thing,
that's just a figure of speech.
Yeah, okay, I'm just...
You wanted to see me?
Saw you handing out bonuses
to the associates earlier.
They must all
be feeling grateful.
The firm was quite generous.
It's not just the associates
who should be rewarded.
Well, for me personally,
it's the satisfaction
of the work that drives me.
Although the money
does help keep score.
You misunderstand me.
I don't have a check
for you, Louis.
I was hoping
you had one for me.
I'm sorry, I'm confused.
Jessica is the one
who handles the bonuses
for the partners.
I'm not talking
about a bonus check.
I'm talking about a buy-in check
for a senior partnership.
As founding partner,
I'm entitled to name
one new senior partner a year.
I'm naming you.
You're making... you're...
- you're making me...
- Yes.
I can't wait to tell everybody.
My mother, my father,
Rabbi Shimkoff...
Yes.
Oh, my God, the look
on Harvey's face!
Louis...
It's official
as of this moment.
But I think we should
make the actual announcement
at the next
senior partners meeting.
Sure, the meeting where
the managing partner
will be voted on.
I believe that is
on the agenda.
Best to do these things
face to face, don't you agree?
It's our secret.
Tomorrow's just like
any other Tuesday.
Exactly.
Hey, congratulations.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right
♪ all that time imagine this ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
Get out.
And take your color-coded
filing system with you.
It's a system. How do I...
I'm trying to give the moment
some dramatic flair.
Jeez, now he ruined that too.
God.
That's it?
That was worth making
a whole condition?
I've never fired anyone before.
You know he's
a floating temp, right?
I mean, he'll be on somebody
else's desk by the end of lunch.
Does everyone
have to rain on my parade?
First of all, you just
have to look at the statistics.
I mean, this guy Solis
could barely crack
20 homers a season
a few years ago.
And now he's banging out
over 40 a year?
What's that supposed to be,
the wisdom of age?
And you don't even
have to look at
what he's doing on the field
to wonder if
this guy is juicing.
Just take a look at him.
Now, look, I might not
be a scientist,
but I do have common sense,
and it says this guy is doping.
But hey, that's just
one man's opinion.
Your Honor,
if being an asshole
was a criminal offense,
I'd say lock Mr. Zielinski up.
In fact, if they want
to call him that, be my guest.
But they better use the word
"opinion," like he did,
because unless I woke up
this morning in Nazi Germany,
that's my client's right.
- Nazi Germany?
- Making a point.
Ja, gut one.
Your Honor, his client
blatantly declares
his rants are
merely his opinions
for the sole purpose
of skirting libel law.
I drive 65 for the sole purpose
of avoiding a speeding ticket.
Doesn't make me a criminal.
But Mr. Specter doesn't have
malice against other drivers.
- What does he have?
- I don't know.
Your Honor, we have
a little recording
of Mr. Zielinski of our own.
This is what Mr. Zielinski
sounds like
when he doesn't know
the cameras are rolling.
Solis? The guy is
a goddamn fraud.
He's juicing, I know it.
I don't care what evidence
he or the league claim to have.
When I say things,
people listen,
and I'm gonna run his ass
out of the game.
- Your Honor...
- Save it, Mr. Specter.
Case goes to trial.
You really only drive 65?
In a school zone.
Solis doesn't need the money.
What do you want?
Three years' worth
of random tests by the league
plus independent tests
we had run to quash the rumors.
As you can see,
my client is clean.
- Zielinski doesn't have these.
- Oh, he does, and I know it
because we sent them to him.
But he chooses not
to reveal them on his show.
What if I get him
to air these results
plus your side of the story?
Too late for that.
We want an apology
from your client.
In person?
Nice try.
We want an on-air
complete retraction,
and that's non-negotiable.
Louis.
Hi, Donna.
I heard you were back. I am.
Yeah, see that.
Look, you know, I, um...
I never... I never wanted to...
To... what?
I never wanted
to do what I did.
And I-I just
don't have the words...
Find them.
I'm sorry.
I'm so, so sorry.
Then let us never
speak of it again.
Mm... you're kidding, right?
Did you mean
what you just said?
- Pfft, and more.
- Then it's done.
- No, it isn't.
- Did you hear what I just...
Season pass, Lincoln Center,
front row every show.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Do I have to go with you?
- Hell no.
- Thank you, Louis.
- You are welcome.
God, could this day
get any better?
"Any better"?
What was so good
about it before?
- Huh, what happened?
- Something.
Nothing, no, can't I
just be glad you're back?
You look like
you have 80 teeth.
What kind of suit is that?
Brioni. Why?
Oh, shit.
Welcome back, Donna.
Thank you, but there's
something I need to tell you.
- No need to apologize.
- Uh, that's not what it is.
You're not getting a raise.
Daniel just made Louis
senior partner.
How do you know?
Four years ago, Norma told me
that Louis had a suit
picked out for the day
he made senior partner.
He is wearing it.
Son of a bitch.
Hardman bought another vote.
What are you gonna do about it?
Get it back.
Donna... Yes?
How'd the suit look?
Dated.
Thank you.
Can't believe that asshole
put us in this pickle.
I'd think you'd admire him.
He's cleaning up
the game you love.
He's been throwing accusations
around with no proof,
and I've had about
enough of that lately.
Well, proof or no proof,
anybody can see
that Solis is juicing.
That's not
what those tests say.
People can find ways
to pass tests, trust me.
Michael!
Grammy? Rachel. Oh, no.
Um, Harvey...
This is
your famous grandmother?
Oh, you were right.
He is sharp.
What are you doing here?
Mr. Specter,
pleasure to meet you.
Your grandson says
nice things about you.
Oh, he tells me
you're quite the hardass.
Can be a hardass.
"Hardass" isn't
really the word he uses.
Okay, grammy,
I see lip runs in the family.
It's nice meeting you.
Yeah, um...
what are you doing here?
And... and... and why
are you in Rachel's office?
Oh, we bumped into each other
downstairs in the lobby.
I thought we could eat.
Might as well have brought it
to me in Star Wars lunchbox.
Don't give me lip, Michael.
It's been two months.
I thought maybe you'd want
to see I'm still alive.
She's got a point,Michael.
Plus I wanted to meet
the people you work with.
Like Rachel.
She's even more lovely
than you said.
- "Lovely"?
- Okay, we're done here.
Bye, dear.
I hope to see you again soon.
Me too.
It was lovely to meet you.
Okay, did you really
have to tell Rachel
that I said she was hot?
Oh, fine, just let me meet
that Harold clown, and I'll go.
You planned this whole thing
from the beginning, didn't you?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You got Hanson
that job at justice.
It was a loss for us,
but a gain for justice,
don't you think?
And making Louis Litt
a senior partner behind my back.
Is that all part
of the new Daniel Hardman
era of transparency?
It's within my rights
according to
the bylaws you wrote.
Ah, yes, and how much
did buying his vote cost you?
Cost me?
It was earned years ago.
And your failure to promote him
is a perfect example
of how your judgment
has harmed this firm.
My judgment and my discretion
are the only reasons
your ass didn't end up
in jail five years ago.
It wasn't discretion,
it was self-interest.
You ousted me and got the firm.
- I saved you and got the firm.
- You did.
But you didn't steal the ball
from me five years ago.
I dropped it.
My lieutenant was all
you were ever meant to be.
I'm going to offer you a deal.
Take Porter, Feldman,
Gallagher...
I'll let you walk away,
set up shop wherever you like.
I'll waive the non-compete.
You don't have the votes.
I put you out once.
When I beat you this time,
they're gonna have
to peel you off the wall.
It's nice to see you
doing your own dirty work
for a change.
Unfortunately, this time,
you can't have Harvey threaten
to tell my dying wife
or my teenage daughter
about my indiscretions.
You didn't even know
about Sarah, did you?
He did what I told him to do.
No. You can't even control
your own attack dog.
Well, get this.
I wasn't even planning on
coming back after Alicia died.
Then you sent him,
and I had no choice.
Bullshit.
You do what you want to do.
You always have,
and you always will.
Well, water under the bridge.
We are where we are.
And I like where I am.
And we'll see who peels whom
off the wall.
Let me get this straight.
You realized that Daniel
was pulling a move,
and you confronted him?
How many times have you told me
not to poke the bear?
I didn't just poke.
I made him an offer.
Which he refused.
And now he knows
we're on to Louis.
If I lose this thing
because of Louis Litt...
You're not losing.
You have a card to play
that Hardman doesn't have.
- No, no.
- Yes.
Partner bonuses
haven't gone out yet.
I'm not using the bonuses
to buy people off.
You might be ethically
against playing politics
with our firm's money,
but he isn't.
This isn't about ethics.
If I give Louis
an extra $100,000,
how's that gonna play
with Gallo, Klyman, Reeger?
Then do what Daniel did.
Make another senior partner.
We get one each per year.
I named you.
Read the bylaws just once.
You've got to be kidding me.
Louis is going to be
the deciding vote.
And he better vote for me.
- No, no!
- Yes.
Harvey, this is
your chance to prove
you learned something
from that mess you made
with Paul Porter.
I have nothing to offer him.
Harvey, you've treated that
man like shit at every turn.
You are the thorn in his side.
It is time that
you pull that thorn out.
Here are your interrogatories.
- Thank you.
- Oh, and remember, Michael,
you have to finish your homework
before you can watch TV.
Oh, right, because
my grandmother brought me lunch,
that makes me... A little boy.
And this is really fun for you.
It really kind of is.
Are you thinking about moving?
Uh, no, actually I was
looking into getting
a place in Manhattan
for my lunch lady.
- You'd really do that for her?
- I am doing it.
It doesn't even come close
to paying her back
for everything
she's done for me.
That's, um...
that's really amazing, Mike.
You wanna know what's amazing?
- What?
- This place.
Right here, check it out.
It's pretty sweet, right?
Off 10th Avenue.
Mmhmm.
Does it come
with a bulletproof vest?
Um... okay.
There, how about this one?
- A six floor walk-up.
- Great views.
Move over.
Okay.
Wait a minute. Yeah?
You set all this up,
so I'd help, didn't you?
Oh, I may be a little boy,
but I'm not
a stupid little boy.
- You're a sneaky little boy.
- Show me another.
Partner, senior partner...
it all sounds the same to me.
No, Mom, how many times
do I have to tell you?
Senior partner
is the inner circle.
It just makes you sound
like an old man.
Stop it.
And what would you know
about it, Dad?
Well, you are losing your hair.
- It's the cut.
- It is not the cut.
It's the cut!
And by the way, Dad,
if you're not going to bother
to figure out
where the camera is,
maybe you should
put some freaking pants on.
I know where the camera is.
I'm not ashamed of my body.
If you felt the same way,
maybe there'd be a Mrs. Litt.
Louie, I don't want to die
before I see my grandchildren.
Mom, you have
two grandchildren.
Esther's children
are not Litts!
Is that your mom
and dad on there?
Get out, Harvey, I'm Skyping.
Is that Harvey Specter?
Let me speak to him.
It is about time
I met your best friend...
Was that your mom and dad?
What's up? No.
What's this?
The address of my tailor.
Donna said you asked for it.
And what would
really happen to me
if I show up at that address?
You get a nice suit,
one that you could wear tonight
when I take you out to dinner.
Donna.
What's the fun
of being senior partner
if you have
to keep it a secret?
And why exactly
should I dine with you?
Because you've been waiting
a long time for this,
and I want to congratulate you.
You want to congratulate me
on becoming your peer.
- Yes.
- Say it.
I'm your peer. You're my peer.
- We're exactly the same.
If two girls saw us
walking down the street,
they'd say, "hey,
those guys are twins."
Identical."
Okay, I'm cancelling.
Okay, no, I'm in. I'm in.
I'm in. What time?
7:30.
Are you gonna be there at 7:30?
Yep.
Donna tells the woman,
"I don't care who you are,
you're not getting
my grapefruit."
- Then what did you do?
- What could I do?
I gave her my grapefruit.
Thank you.
This is great, Harvey.
We're like two fingers
on the same hand.
As long as I'm the index.
I'm serious,
this is nice, you know?
Colleagues. Equals.
Friends.
Well, as a friend,
I want you to see something.
What do you got?
Five years ago,
I asked you for help
to look
into another firm's books.
Well, they were our books.
I helped you prove
Hardman was embezzling.
You also tried
to set up a fall guy.
Me.
"A schmuck," I believe, was
the term you used at the time.
This was five years ago,
and you're just getting around
to telling me now?
I wonder why that is.
I didn't see the need
for you to be hurt.
Right, 'cause I'm your friend.
A friend tells you the truth,
and the truth is, Hardman
used you to hide his embezzling,
and he's using you again.
And how exactly
is that different from
what you're doing right now?
You can't trust him.
But I can trust you?
- Yes, you can.
- Oh, please.
Did I tell Jessica about
your little dictaphone maneuver?
No, you know what you did?
You lorded it over my head,
said that I'd owe you,
and now you've come to collect.
Well, you know what? Go ahead.
Run to mommy. Tattle.
I mean, this was about my vote?
If I do vote for Daniel,
what is Jessica
gonna do about it?
I found this one
that faces away from Lex,
so she won't get
all the street noise,
and I checked into the doormen.
Raul's been here 14 years,
and Jimbo 17.
Jimbo?
People open up to me.
So what do you think?
I think...
Grammy's gonna love it
when I tell her
she has a new place
to live tonight.
Come on, you haven't
even seen the bedroom yet.
- Holy shit.
- I know.
It's perfect, right?
All you need are
some new curtains right here.
No, the first thing I would
do is put down a nice rug.
You wanna cover the hardwood?
- Not all of it.
- So you mean an area rug.
No, I mean, cover an area
of the hardwood with a rug.
I can live with that.
Like an 8x10 Sisal.
- A whatsal?
- The beige, scratchy kind.
A scratchy rug defeats
it wasn't my idea
in the first place.
Fair enough, but the bed...
The bed goes here.
Oh, my God, you're such a guy.
If the bed doesn't go here,
then what's the point
of even having the window?
Yeah, but your curtains
cover up the light anyway.
No, that would be shades,
which this room
will never, ever have.
Look, just come right here.
See what I mean?
Beautiful.
I should go meet Harvey.
It's really hot in here.
Yeah.
Nice of you to make it.
Sorry, I had
this thing with Rachel.
Oh, a date. Isn't that special?
Not as special
as your date last night.
So how is Louis?
What did he wear?
Did you get any? Shut me down.
What?
This is serious.
What are we gonna do?
I don't know,
but I'll tell you one thing...
I'm not taking
no for an answer.
No way! You want me
to apologize on the air?
Why don't I just drop my pants
and paint a clown on my ass?
Save that for sweeps.
I have a reputation,
Mr. Specter.
And by the way,
I don't appreciate
you bashing it in court.
Look, I went to court
to win the case,
not protect your reputation.
Yeah, well, turns out
you didn't do either one.
Here's a suggestion.
Next time, make sure
you're actually off the air
before shooting your mouth off.
I stand by what I said.
Solis is doping.
Roger Maris got
an asterisk next to his name.
This guy deserves
an asterisk next to his name,
and I want him
out of the league.
You're not
the commissioner of baseball.
Yeah, well, the commissioner
could never get my ratings.
- Mr. Zielinski...
- See, finally,
someone who treats me
with respect.
We can't claim
that you're just
offering up opinions anymore.
If you don't apologize,
we have to show
that you have a factual basis
for accusing Solis of doping.
- Of course I did.
- Then give us your source.
What kind of career
do you think
I'd have if I give that up?
I'll tell you what...
nonexistent.
Exactly like your source.
- Harvey, please, could...
- That's it.
Instead of bugging me
to give up my guy
after I already told you no,
why don't you do your damn job
and win this case?
Well, looks like good cop,
bad cop didn't work.
- Actually it did... on me.
- What are you talking about?
If he's full of shit
and has no source,
he knows this eventually
goes against him in court.
I think Solis is doping.
Welcome to the party.
And Zielinski may have
some integrity.
I thought you said
he was a dick.
If he's actually
protecting his source,
he's a dick with a code.
His code is our problem.
If we can't find that source,
we can't fix it.
Forget the source.
We need to figure out
how Solis passed those tests.
How are we supposed to do that?
Not us, you.
I'm like Zielinski,
you're like Solis.
- An all-star.
- A cheater.
You're not gonna
tell the bar association
that I deserve
an asterisk, are you?
You just gave me a good idea.
I hope it doesn't involve
you telling the bar association
that I deserve an asterisk.
Oh, a bat.
What, are you gonna hit me
if I don't vote for Jessica?
No, I just wanted you to hear
a story before you decided.
Ah.
More dirt on Hardman.
The story's about Roger Maris.
Yeah, what,
did he work for Hardman?
He used to play
for the Yankees.
He beat Babe Ruth's
home run record
with this bat.
You brought a prop.
That's really cute.
Maris did it
in a longer season,
so no one really
gave him credit for it,
and it went down in
people's minds with an asterisk.
I see, so it's a parable.
How literary of you.
Becoming senior partner
is your life's work, Louis.
You really want to buy it
with your vote?
Daniel did not condition
my partnership on anything.
Maybe, but it'll always
have an asterisk.
You know what?
It's like you just
can't fathom that
I actually earned it.
Whether you earned it or not,
that's not the point.
It's everything.
All I am saying is,
you vote for Hardman,
everyone will see this
as quid pro quo.
Yeah, because
you're gonna tell them.
No, I won't tell them.
They'll wonder about it
all on their own,
just like you will.
Do me a favor right no..
Take your bat and go.
Go.
Louis...
you were right at dinner.
I was using you,
and I was wrong.
But this decision,
it isn't about me.
You came up under Hardman.
You hated him.
You always hated him.
Don't let him do this to you.
What's my alternative, Harvey?
Jessica didn't even
have the courtesy
to court my vote herself.
So she sends you.
Well, guess what.
You failed.
So go back right now.
You tell her,
Harvey Specter,
the great closer,
couldn't close me.
Aren't you supposed to be off
accepting the award
for world's best grandson?
Uh, I had to cancel.
Weren't you taking her
to dinner
to tell her about the apartment
you bought for her
to make up for the fact that
you don't have time
to take her to dinner anymore?
For your information,
she was happy when
I called to reschedule.
Happy to be stood up.
Happy that I have
a job that fully engages me.
There was a time she was
worried that wouldn't happen.
Despite Harvard Law School?
No, I mean, when I was younger.
She's right that
you're really lucky
you get to do something
that challenges you.
I hope I have that someday.
Rachel, I told you,
whenever you want help with...
holy shit, you took the LSAT...
you took the LSATs?
I did.
How did you do?
Um... I don't know.
Rachel, you already
did the hard part.
You took the test.
Opening the envelope is easy.
No, every other time
I've had to open the envelope...
This isn't every other time.
Do you want me to open it?
- No.
- Yes, you do.
Okay, um, if I score below 160,
then I just want you
to throw it away.
And don't tell me.
I don't want to know, okay?
- Okay.
- Um... Rachel, I'm...
172.
- 172?
- You got a 172.
- Oh, my... I did?
- Yes.
That's... oh, oh, my God!
Oh, my God, don't you ever
do that to me again.
Rachel, you're
gonna be a lawyer.
Look, look at it. Oh, my God.
Go.
Bam. Oh, my God.
I'm gonna be out of a job.
Harvey, I think
I found something.
And by "something,"
I assume you mean
how Solis was cheating.
Um, maybe,
but I definitely figured out
who Zielinski's source is.
Well, that counts as something.
They used a hot mic,
I used a hot mic.
What are you talking about?
I found some footage
from a segment
that Zielinski taped
at spring training.
Uh, the crew is setting up,
he's in the background,
having a very
intense conversation
with Ruben Hernandez.
Mediocre catcher. So?
Zielinski's a sportscaster.
Talking to athletes
is what he does all day.
This conversation
took place in Winter Park.
Hernandez should have been
practicing with his team in...
St. Pete.
He never should have
been there.
Then I remembered the roster of
every single team
Solis ever played on.
- They never played together.
- Wrong, they did.
Ten games, three years ago,
Hernandez's rookie year.
So he got Hernandez
to take the test for him.
Or at least approached him
because Zielinski's accusations
began
one week after
that tape that I watched.
Enough time for Zielinski
to look into
whatever Hernandez told him.
And call him six times from
a company-issued cell phone.
Boom!
Look at you! Hot mic,
using their tricks against them.
Yeah, it's what we do,
no big deal.
Remind me to stop
teaching you my tricks.
Well, you're gonna need
one of your tricks
because what good does
Zielinski's source do us
if he's not going
to let us go public?
Who says we have to go public?
Here's what I need you to do.
I couldn't close him.
Are you trying to tell me
you couldn't be nice
to Louis even for this?
No, I'm not.
You said
I'm a thorn in his side.
I tried to take it out,
but you're the one
who's had what he's
wanted all these years
and didn't give it to him.
Senior partnership.
You need to tell him
he deserves it.
That's what I sent you to do.
He needs to hear it from you.
You know, I send you to do
this one thing and you can't...
Fine, I'll talk to him.
Wait a minute.
You know him. You knew this.
This is where
it always ended up.
- You got me.
- Why send me first?
Because if Louis didn't have
to work to get me there,
he wouldn't believe me
when I went.
You're playing chess
while everybody else
is playing checkers.
Are you just getting that,
Mr. I'm-the-best-closer-
this-city's-ever-seen?
Hey, you're the one
who always calls me that.
Well, maybe I shouldn't.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have to tell Louis he deserves
to be senior partner.
You know what, I am the best
closer this city's ever seen,
and I didn't even make a dent.
Do you have a point?
He needs more than just words.
I told you,
I'm not bribing him.
That's not what I meant.
His anger is deep.
He wants us to feel pain. How?
Give him my office.
You're willing to do that?
Remember when you questioned
if I could put
your needs above mine?
Here's your answer.
Mr. Solis, big fan.
Can I get an autograph?
Sure, buddy.
Can you just sign it
"Roberto Solis, steroid user"?
What?
I represent Tony Zielinski.
You can't talk to me
without my lawyer.
Ah, you're right, I can't.
You go ahead and turn me in.
When you do,
I'll tell them all
about Zielinski's source
inside your clubhouse.
Bullshit.
Baseball is a brotherhood.
Nobody on my team would
go public against me.
But Ruben Hernandez isn't
on your team anymore.
If Ruben tries ratting out
a former teammate,
no ball club in this league
will forgive him.
He might not have a choice
when we subpoena him.
No, no way.
If Zielinski's giving up Ruben,
he'd have done it already.
He might not, but I will.
You're in a rundown, Roberto.
Drop the suit and announce
your retirement from baseball.
- Are you out of your mind?
- You do it,
Zielinski will never mention
your name on air again.
You don't, Hernandez outs you,
and the whole world
knows who you are.
Louis, got a minute?
I'm a little busy, but sure.
I deserve that.
A little payback among
senior partners is fair play.
I'm listening.
I'm not going to insult you
by beating around the bush,
so let's talk about
the elephant in the room.
What's it gonna take?
My dedication to this firm
knows no limits.
And what I ask in return...
all I ask in return...
is to be valued,
for someone
to make me believe that
they think that
I'm great at what I do.
Then we're all set
because I've always
felt that way.
That's not the way
you made it seem
to everyone at Harvey's trial.
Louis, we were at trial.
I was trying to make my case,
same as you.
Well, you did a good job.
Because that, Jessica,
I got no trouble believing.
But the Jessica that
kept stringing me along,
telling me, one day,
my time would come...
her, I've come to doubt.
I've always been
straight with you, Louis.
My message has never wavered.
Does that include the message
that you sent to me
through Harvey?
Harvey came to you first
because I wanted you to know
that you are valuable
to both of us.
No, there's only an "us"
when you want something from me.
The rest of the time, it's me
on the outside, looking in.
Well, you're
a senior partner now.
You're as on the inside
as it gets.
That's right,
thanks to Hardman.
You think he's valuing you.
He's buying you...
with this one thing
at this convenient time.
You don't get it.
Hardman actually sees me.
With you, I'll always
be this mushroom
in the shadow of Harvey's tree.
What are you saying, Louis?
I'm saying it's time
you put Harvey in my shadow.
And how exactly
would you like me to do that?
You know, I don't know.
You figure it out.
Otherwise, maybe
one of these days,
you'll see what it's like to be
in someone's shadow
for a while.
You know what, Louis?
Harvey told me that
I should give you his office,
and I came in here
prepared to do just that.
But I don't respond to threats,
and I'm not
going to buy your vote
because that's not who I am.
But know this:
I will win.
And tomorrow, after the vote,
if you are on the wrong side,
there'll be no coming back.
When you stole from this firm,
did you do anything
to cover your tracks?
I should have known
they had this in their pocket.
So you don't deny it.
I wouldn't insult
your intelligence.
I'm sure they came to you
armed with proof,
and you followed the numbers
better than I ever could.
- Why?
- The best I can offer you
is that it wasn't personal.
It was just that, given
your financial expertise,
I thought you
would seem plausible.
"Plausible."
Obviously my plan was that
nobody would notice the money
was missing in the first place.
- So I was plan "B."
- I suppose so, Louis.
I'm sorry. You're sor...
Do you realize you could have
destroyed my entire career?
Maybe even sent me to prison.
And you know what?
I didn't care.
That's the truth.
And you want me
to vote for you?
Did you like me back then?
I didn't.
The man I was five years ago
shouldn't be managing partner.
He shouldn't even work here.
But I'm not that man.
If you think otherwise,
don't vote for me.
Right.
And if I don't support you,
what happens
to my senior partnership?
Do you think my making
you senior partner
is conditioned
on my having your vote?
- Wasn't it?
- Louis, I'm disappointed.
I'm disappointed you think
so little of yourself.
I saw the way you dominated
Jessica at Harvey's trial
and lost because of some trick.
You thought I dominated?
I offered you what
I thought you deserved,
no more, no less.
I ask for nothing in return
but that you vote
your conscience.
Louis...
don't doubt yourself.
I've got good news.
Solis has not only
agreed to drop the suit,
but to retire
from the game as well.
Well, maybe you're not
the asshole I thought you were.
I'm not done yet.
In return...
you're never gonna talk
about him again on the air.
So he walks away
with his reputation intact?
- That's the deal.
- No, no, no, no.
You know I'm right,
and you want me
to step off the gas
right when I got him?
Screw that.
You want to know
how I know you're right?
Mike?
I believe you know
Ruben Hernandez.
You promised you wouldn't
tell anyone I was your source.
I didn't tell them. I didn't.
- Bullshit!
- Mike, get him out of here.
I promise we'll fix this.
Come on.
You son of a bitch, you're
supposed to be on my side.
This is me being on your side.
You make me win this in court,
I'll have to do it
by making Ruben testify.
So the cost of
ruining Solis' reputation
will be that kid's career.
And by the way, everyone will
think the same as he does.
You gave him up
to save your own ass.
- That's a lie.
- Doesn't matter.
They'll think it anyway.
But hey, that's
just one man's opinion.
You want to protect
your source?
Take the deal.
- So?
- He took the deal.
We're done with that asshole.
"Asshole"?
Come on, he's just protecting
the church of baseball.
You going Bull Durham on me?
Oh, yeah, yeah,
I'm Tim Robbins,
the hotshot pitcher
who's destined for the Majors,
and you're that old man
who never really made it there.
You know Robbins wore
women's underwear
in that movie, right?
Yeah, after he slept
with Susan Sarandon.
Good one.
But if you ever call
Kevin Costner an old man again,
you won't get another bonus.
Okay.
Whoa, my God, bonus.
Harvey, I'm sorry, I've got
to go see my grandmother.
Fine, go, I wouldn't want her
to think I was a hardass.
Did you get rid
of that libel case?
Score one for free press.
Good to see you back in stride.
When was I ever off?
Jessica, do you have a moment?
Of course, Louis.
Harvey, will you give us a sec?
Oh, please, what,
are you kidding?
Not like there's any secrets
between you two.
Well, we're listening.
I'm presenting
my partnership buy-in check
to you in your current capacity
as managing partner.
"Current."
Oh, is that your cryptic way
of asking about my vote?
You kept me waiting five years.
You can wait another 24 hours.
Surprise!
Rachel... hey,
what are you doing here?
Come in.
Mike, someone kept calling
the office for you.
It was the nursing home and...
I guess... I guess that's
the emergency number they had.
Um... what?
It's your grandma.
She passed away.
No. No, she's...
I am so sorry.
But...
she didn't even
get to s... to see...
I know.
I-I'm...
I'm so sorry.
Wh...