You took this case
without running it by me.
- Jessica...
- That's enough. Dump it.
Or I will.
You think this case is a winner?
I do.
Then what do you say
we do it together?
(rachel) I'm afraid you're gonna
end up hating each other.
If I'm lucky, I'm gonna fight
with him about a lot of things.
Why not start with a fight where
we're both on the same side?
This is harvey's
last three income statements,
And I found them
sitting in the copy machine.
You came to work for me.
You knew who I was when you did,
So now it's time
for you to decide.
Are you with me or not?
You always said,
once you pick a side,
If you're not loyal
to that side,
Then who the hell are you?
You should've thought of that
before you picked someone
Who would do something like this
in the first place.
You ever take sides with
jack soloff against me again,
I will bury you.
[elevator bell dings]
- well, you look happy.
Becky just tell susie
she like-likes you?
Eh, more like kelton insurance
just told robert zane
They're scared-scared of us.
You got a settlement offer?
Just like he said we would.
I got to hand it to him,
he played them perfectly.
Did he now?
What?
Nothing.
Look, I take it back
about becky.
The only one with a crush
around here is you.
Sounds like someone's worried
that robert zane
Might be better than him.
Nice try, tiger, but did magic
ever worry about bird?
First of all, yes, he did.
Second of all, you realize
You're the white guy
in this scenario, right?
I know I'm the bigger badass
in every scenario.
Okay, mr. Badass, which one
are you, magic or bird?
I think we both know I'm...
(both) jordan.
Hey, why don't you go meet
your boyfriend robert zane?
I think I just left something
at security.
Oh. Look who like-likes
someone now.
Ma'am, the last time
I let someone up
That he wasn't expecting,
He threatened
to have me executed.
I'm sure he did,
but I'm telling you that...
That gretchen obviously forgot
to phone down, carl,
Because we have a meeting
scheduled for right now.
That isn't what she just...
Carl.
A meeting with you. Really?
I promise
I'm much better-looking
Than whoever
you were supposed to meet.
You have no idea
how right you are.
But I could have sworn
you were just on your way out.
Oh, that's not a problem.
The mayor can wait.
But I'm not sure
the governor can.
Are you trying
to out-name-drop me?
If I were, I think I just did.
But I'll let you in
on a little secret.
I don't really care
about names that much.
Well, if you don't care
about names, why don't we
Skip the introductions
and just get down to breakfast?
What if I already had breakfast?
I'm talking about
tomorrow morning, in my kitchen.
Or yours, I mean, you look like
you have a nice place.
As tempting as that is,
maybe another time.
Good luck in your meeting.
So how's my favorite
pain-in-the-ass lawyer?
I thought louis was your
favorite pain-in-the-ass lawyer.
He is, but louis
isn't responsible
For me getting to work on this.
You're doing the grunt work
on our case?
I pulled some strings...
Thought it might give us
A chance to work together.
You know I'm engaged, right?
Yes, mike, that's my plan,
To steal you
from my boss's daughter.
It's a thing. It's been done.
Well, I didn't come here
to steal you.
I came here to thank you.
For what?
Come on, mike.
I get fired,
And two days later, I get
an offer from rachel's father?
Whatever you did, I owe you one.
Actually, you owe rachel one.
No shit.
Shit.
(both as clay davis
from the wire) shiiit.
By the way, you're
in the wrong conference room.
Okay, esther,
what are you doing here?
What, a woman can't stop by
To see her brother,
who she loves?
Please, you know damn well
we don't love each other.
In that case, I need a lawyer.
[laughs] you? For what?
Did you give someone salmonella
with your stupid muffins?
I'm getting a divorce.
Well, good.
I knew that guy was dead weight
the second I met him.
I know, I think that was
your speech at our wedding.
And your sympathy is touching,
But I didn't come here
to vindicate you.
No, I know you didn't.
You came to get me
To slaughter jeffrey for you,
and I will.
When I'm done with him,
he won't have a pot to shit in.
It's "piss in."
And, louis, I don't want you
to slaughter jeffrey.
Why the hell not?
Because I want
harvey specter to.
Come again?
You said he was
the best attorney in the city.
No, esther, I told you
he was my best friend.
Which is exactly what you said
about jeremy henschell
In tenth grade,
which really meant
You worshipped him from afar,
You wrote in your diary
about him,
And you never actually hung out.
Okay, you swore
you never read my diary.
And you swore you didn't spy
on me and jeremy.
Oh, please, that was one time.
I was on my way
to get a glass of milk,
And for your information,
I've been lactose intolerant
ever since.
Louis, are you gonna
get me harvey,
Or do I have to get him myself?
Harvey is not taking on
any new clients right now,
And he's out of town
for the next few years.
Louis, I know what you're doing.
You think I want harvey
because I don't think
You're good enough.
You're wrong.
I know how good you are,
But this is personal for me,
Which means
it will be personal for you,
And I can't have that.
So please,
will you get me harvey?
I'll make it happen.
Thank you, louis.
That was esther?
Yes, I know what you're gonna
say... we look exactly alike.
That actually wasn't...
I get it... it's like
looking at me in a wig.
I've heard it a thousand times.
Yeah, the resemblance
is uncanny.
What?
I'm just wondering why you're
not getting up to go ask harvey.
Because I'm not gonna ask him.
I'm gonna save some time
and tell her he said no.
Louis...
Donna, we all know
that harvey's furious at me.
There's no way he's gonna do it.
Maybe not.
But, louis, she's family,
And if there's one thing that
harvey understands, it's that.
Where the hell have you been?
Sorry, I got stuck
in really bad traffic.
So you were
in the wrong conference room.
For about 20 minutes.
So what did we get?
Want to take a guess?
$90 million.
Want to take a real guess?
That was a real guess.
Son, what planet
are you living on?
The planet where you called
To say we got
a great settlement.
$25 million is
$25 million?
Robert, after fees,
That's less than $70,000
per person.
[laughs] then what do you
suggest we counter with?
I suggest we counter
with a trial.
Are you nuts?
You don't go to trial.
You turn up the pressure,
and then you settle.
Going to trial is
turning up the pressure.
The second we finish
opening arguments,
That offer is gonna triple.
Look, I've sat across the table
from these two
Four times
in the last six years,
And when they say
this is their best offer,
It's their best offer,
and we're recommending it.
Well, you can recommend
whatever you want.
I'm recommending we reject it.
You don't give clients
conflicting opinions.
You work it out
behind closed doors.
Well, maybe that's the problem.
You want to do things
behind closed doors.
I actually want to be honest.
Hey, watch yourself, mike.
You tell me this,
would $70,000 per person
Be a great settlement
if we were talking
About laura's life or rachel's?
You get out of here!
You don't come back
Until you wrap your head
around recommending this offer.
And don't you ever
use them against me again!
(man) ♪ see the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
.
Don't tell me
he wasn't in here either.
He was in here, all right.
What happened?
Did the settlement fall through?
No, it didn't, but it should've.
They gave us a shitty offer.
Robert's ready to take it.
Come on, if it's really
that bad, why would he take it?
Because he knows his clients
will jump all over it
And it's the easy way out.
So you think robert doesn't care
about his clients?
It sure seems that way.
Mike, I've only been here
a few months,
And there are a lot of things
you can say about robert zane,
But what you can't say
is that he doesn't care
About his clients.
Go away, louis.
I would, but then
I couldn't tell you
About the $50-million company
I'm giving you.
And why would you do that?
'Cause I want to make up
for our little misunderstanding.
We didn't have
a misunderstanding.
You went after my money,
so if you're giving me a client,
There's some other
misunderstanding
That you're too chickenshit
to tell me about.
It's my sister's company.
I'll give you her business.
All you have to do
is handle her divorce.
I don't want
your sister's business.
Now get out.
Harvey, this is my family.
My sister, she... Has never
asked me for anything
Her entire life, not once.
Now the one time she does,
I just can't let her down.
Louis, I'm not
a divorce attorney.
When has a shitty detail
like that
Ever stopped you before?
All right, I'll do it,
on two conditions.
First, you stay completely
out of this case.
Done. Second?
I'll let you know
when I think of it.
How do I know it won't be
something I can't stomach?
You don't, but those are
my two conditions.
Okay, harvey, you have a deal.
One thing.
Promise me you won't
sleep with esther.
Believe me, louis,
the last thing I want to do
Is sleep with your sister.
(robert) I'm glad you agree.
I'll let you know
when the paperwork's finished.
I know you didn't wrap your head
around this deal
In the last ten minutes,
So what are you still
doing in my office?
Exactly what you'd be doing
in my place.
Robert, I know you said
that you know these two lawyers,
But I don't.
I need to see for myself
what they will or won't do.
And you still want to counter.
I want to at least try.
Except you don't want to go
by yourself,
You want me to go with you.
Yes, I do.
Because you and I both know,
if we don't go together,
We don't stand a chance.
I know we don't stand a chance
either way.
And if I do go, it makes me
look like a fool.
Robert, I saved you from looking
like a fool in that courtroom.
I came through for you.
Now I'm asking you
to come through for me on this.
You and rachel are
peas in a pod.
[chuckles]
Can't believe she's really
worth $50 million.
I can't believe you've never
heard of her company.
Do I look like I buy
a lot of potholders?
She doesn't just sell
potholders.
She has a brand
like martha stewart.
Look, I get that you think
she's impressive,
But to me,
she's just louis's sister,
Which, as far as I'm concerned,
is strike number two.
What's strike number one?
The fact that
she's louis's sister.
Oh, come on, harvey, listen.
Are you gonna take this
seriously or not?
I'll tell you what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna go walk there.
I'm gonna shake
this woman's meaty hand.
I'm gonna get this over with
as quickly as possible.
You?
You've got to be kidding me.
You two know each other?
So you weren't meeting
the governor.
You're telling me you were
really gonna blow off the mayor?
The mayor.
You don't know the mayor.
I'm so sorry, let me introduce
my soon-to-be former associate.
[chuckles] rachel zane.
Esther edelstein.
It's nice to finally
meet the man
I've heard
such good things about.
It's nice to meet the woman
I've obviously heard
nothing but lies about.
Let's get to it.
Yes.
I just have to know,
Were one of the two of you
adopted?
I've been asking that for years.
Hey. Get out.
Shit.
Come on, speak up, narcissist,
it's not a freakin' library.
Reminder to thin the walls
In the conference room/
make a peephole.
What do you think you're doing?
What happened?
Oh, I was just checking
the sound-proofing,
Making sure
they thicken the walls
In the conference room.
So if I walk out this door
and I turn to the right,
I won't see harvey
in there with esther?
Esther's here?
I didn't know that.
Louis, listening
through the wall
Is not staying out of her case,
And if harvey finds out,
he's gonna drop her.
Look, it's my sister, all right?
I just want to make sure
he does right by her.
And you never would have
asked him to take this case
If you didn't trust
that he would do just that.
So put the glass down,
go back to your office,
And let him do his job.
You know it'd be easier
for both of us
If you were wrong
every once in a while.
When we decided to get divorced,
jeffrey and I agreed
He would get 20% of the company,
no need to involve lawyers.
The next thing I knew,
I got a letter from a lawyer.
Jeffrey doesn't think
20% is enough anymore.
No, he doesn't.
Esther, I'm gonna ask you
a question,
And I want you
to answer me honestly.
Who's leaving who?
It's mutual.
It's never mutual.
So I'm gonna ask you again.
Who's driving this decision?
I am.
Then the answer to our problem
Is for you to stay away
from the negotiations.
What? No, I'm not staying away.
Listen to me.
He's going back on your deal
Because he wants
to prolong the fight.
I don't care.
I spent 12 years
building the company.
I'm not gonna sit back
and let someone else decide
How much I'm allowed to keep.
Then what'd you come to me for?
Because you're supposed to be
the best.
I am the best,
and I didn't get that way
Letting someone else
call the shots.
So you're either gonna
let me do that,
Or you're gonna get yourself
another lawyer.
.
All right, here's what
I need you to do.
You can tell me what you
need me to do in a minute.
First we're gonna talk
about what happened back there.
What happened is,
I laid down the law,
She accepted, I'm the man.
Yep, uh-huh.
Okay, I'm not talking
about that.
I'm talking about how the moment
you walked through the door,
You looked like you were struck
by a bolt of lighting.
- I did not.
- You most certainly did.
In fact,
before you started fighting,
I was afraid the two of you were
gonna go at it on the table.
Afraid or hoping?
That's unsavory.
And you making lewd comments
about our client isn't?
Lewd comments about what client?
Harvey likes louis's sister.
That's funny, 'cause that's
exactly what I came in here
To talk to him about.
You like louis's sister?
Not enough to fight you for her.
Well, you should reconsider.
She's lovely.
And I'm leaving.
Harvey, why are you
all of a sudden
Taking on esther edelstein
as a client?
And don't tell me
it's because she's lovely,
Because I'm not sure
I believe that.
I took her on
because louis asked me to.
And the last I heard, you and I
were both pissed at him.
And I still am.
But he told me this was family,
And... I thought
this might be a chance
For us all to get back on track.
I like that, harvey.
You just might turn out
To be a half decent name partner
after all.
I doubt it.
So do i.
Well, frankly, robert,
I'm surprised
You called for another meeting.
Surprised by a routine counter?
When the first offer is
as generous as ours, I am.
Just hear the man out, will.
Campbell v. State health.
Wilson v. Genrx.
Friedman v. Medfirst.
Those are
identical class actions
In which the average payout
Was $1/2 million per plaintiff.
They were jury awards,
and two of them were reduced
For being excessively punitive.
Dollar amount was still higher
than what's on the table.
After seven years of appeals.
Yeah, and like we said,
we don't care how long it takes.
We want triple
what you're offering.
And I want to skinny dip
with sofia vergara,
But no puedo hacerlo.
That's spanish for "we're not
giving you another nickel."
And what's spanish
for "we'll see you in court"?
Bring it on.
That's enough. Come on, will.
We're just having
a conversation.
Conversation?
I gave you a fair offer, robert,
Because I respect you,
And I thought that
you respected me enough to know
That I meant it when I said
it's the best I could do.
Then he comes in here
threatening a trial.
Well, you know what?
You don't like
what's on the table,
We can pull
the whole damn thing.
I told you
he wasn't messing around.
You were right about that.
Now I'm right
about taking this to trial.
You aren't right about anything.
I owed you. I paid up.
We're done.
No, we're not done,
and I'm still not
Recommending this offer
to my clients.
Well, that's too bad,
because they already signed off.
What?
You talked to our clients
before we even went in there?
You're damn right I did.
We took a shot,
and it didn't work.
Now, in the meantime,
we had an obligation
To show their offer
to our clients, and I did.
Don't give me
some bullshit justification.
You went behind my back.
I didn't go behind your back.
I went over your head.
What the hell
are you talking about?
You know what the hell
I'm talking about.
I went to your boss's boss,
and you know what?
She and I see things
the same way.
And as far as I'm concerned,
this case is settled.
Why don't you two have a seat?
I suggest we get right to it.
Wait a second, where's esther?
She won't be joining us,
but I've been authorized
To negotiate on her behalf.
No. No, I'm not agreeing
to anything without her here.
That's because you don't really
want to negotiate,
You just want to stay
connected to her,
And that's not gonna happen.
I don't know when you decided
to become a divorce attorney,
But that's not how it works.
I didn't become
a divorce attorney
Because it's the minor leagues,
But this is how it works
with me.
What the hell is this?
That's our new offer, nothing.
This is bullshit.
You thinking
you deserve even 20%
Of our client's business
is bullshit.
So you're either gonna
accept the terms
That you and esther agreed to,
or you can take our new offer.
You can threaten all you want,
but my client has a right
To what's his,
and that's half the company,
Because 12 years ago, that's
what your client agreed to.
See, I wasn't just gonna be
esther's husband.
I was gonna be a doctor,
but I put that on hold
While esther got her company
off the ground,
And when I said
I was willing to do that,
She said I'd get half.
Which constitutes
an enforceable verbal contract.
(jeffrey) so I don't care
whether esther's here or not.
She promised to spend
our lives together,
And she's breaking that promise.
There's nothing I can do
about that one,
But I'm sure as hell gonna
hold her to the other one.
You have no proof
she ever made that promise.
Ask your client about it,
because when we depose her
Under oath,
you can rest assured we will.
.
You authorized the settlement?
You want to change that tone?
No, I don't, because you told
Robert zane to treat me
like a partner,
And then you turned around,
and you cut my legs out.
I told him that
because you were my proxy,
But you're not my proxy with me.
And I don't appreciate
my decisions being questioned.
Did you even look at that offer?
Mike, I'm going to explain
something to you that,
Based on your approach
to this conversation,
You clearly don't understand.
This trial will cost millions.
And arcadian has deep pockets.
And they're not looking
to empty them on a gamble.
So this is all
just about the money.
Were you born yesterday?
The clients are looking
for money.
We're looking for money.
The insurance company's
looking to keep money.
It's always about the money.
And if you had some balls,
we'd get a whole lot more.
Listen to me,
I don't know what you thought
Marching in here was going to do
other than piss me off,
But you're going to march
the hell back out
Because I have better things
to do with my time
Than to explain to you
how the world works.
[scoffs]
Hey, I got your message.
Jeffrey signed the agreement?
He did.
All it needs
is your john hancock.
Wait, this doesn't say 20%.
It says 50%.
Oh, I'm sorry,
did I forget to mention
That he said you promised him
50% of your company
For putting off medical school?
Because you sure forgot
to mention that to me.
[laughs]
You have got to be kidding me.
How could you not tell me that?
Because it was
a throwaway conversation
We had 12 years ago
on the new jersey turnpike.
Well, it wasn't throwaway
to him, and he's gonna use it
Because he's feeling betrayed.
Well, I don't really care
what he's feeling
Because he's the one
who had the affair.
You wanted to know the
circumstances of our divorce.
Well, that's what they are.
That's why I'm leaving him.
I am sure you wouldn't
understand what's it like
To experience infidelity.
I would, and I do,
But that doesn't change the fact
that you made a contract.
What about our other contract?
20%.
The original agreement
supersedes it,
And an affair
doesn't change that.
Except he doesn't have any proof
I ever made
the original agreement.
Esther, they're gonna
put you under oath
And ask you point-blank
if this happened.
And I'm going to say it didn't.
That's perjury, and I'm not
gonna let you do that.
What are you, some white knight
Who never crosses the line
to win?
No, but I'm not gonna let you
make a decision
In the heat of the moment
That you'll regret
for the rest of your life.
Well, then you better find some
other way to void this deal,
Because there's no way
I'm giving my shit bag husband
Half of everything I own.
I need you to find
every loophole there is
Around verbal contracts.
So jeffrey was
telling the truth?
Yes, and she'd rather
slit her wrists
Than give him 50%,
and I don't blame her.
Yeah, but she's the one
who's leaving him, so...
He cheated on her, didn't he?
Well, that's between our client
and her soon-to-be ex-husband,
And I have no intention
of letting him
Get the better of her.
What?
You're being protective.
It's sweet.
Okay, listen to me,
we're protecting esther
Because it's our job
to protect her.
And if we don't figure
a way out of this,
She's gonna lose
millions of dollars,
So you want to make observations
about the two of us,
Do it all you want
after we've won.
I'm on it.
Okay, so final deal memos here,
check authorizations here.
Now all we need to do is get
kelton to sign, and we are done.
Mike, I know you think
this deal sucks,
But there is a silver lining.
We got to work together again.
What?
I was just thinking
about when we started.
Who would've thought that
working with you
Would ever have been
a silver lining?
Me?
[laughs] yeah, you.
What about you?
What are you talking about?
I have been a gentleman
since day one.
- Really?
- Yes.
Remember the whole
airplane incident?
Do I?
Yes, you were the one who...
Wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait a second. Delta financial.
What about them?
There was a brochure
for delta bauer financial
On robert zane's desk.
And on top of that,
they were listed
As a subsidiary
on arcadian's annual report.
As are 50 other funds.
50 other funds that don't have a
brochure on robert zane's desk.
Mike...
Katrina, I need to know
if they're one of your clients.
You know I can't tell you that.
Okay, well, you just did.
Now I need to know
if they own shares of kelton.
I don't know if they own shares,
and I'm not gonna find out.
You don't care if robert zane
is manipulating a case
To service a hedge fund?
It doesn't matter if I care.
I can't violate
attorney-client privilege.
You said you owe me.
And you said I owe rachel.
Katrina, please.
You said that robert is
doing right by his clients.
Well, I just need to know
which clients
He's doing right by.
[sighs]
Hey. Do you have a minute?
The last time I asked you that,
you told me the answer was no.
And I still gave you the minute.
Well, I happen to be
in the middle
Of trying to get louis's sister
out of a huge mess, so...
That's what I wanted
to talk to you about.
Louis promised
to stay out of this.
And he is, and I'm not here
because he asked me to be.
I'm here because I care
about him and...
That's not my problem.
Harvey, I'm not the enemy here.
And louis is your partner
and your friend,
And right now, he needs
a little reassurance.
And I told you before,
I'm not the guy
That gives you a hug
when you're scared.
I'm the guy that wins
when you need it the most.
Why can't you for once...
You know what, donna,
when I came to you for help,
You said that I don't
get to do that anymore.
Well, you don't get
to do this anymore.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have work to do.
You know what, harvey?
Louis was afraid to let you
take this case,
And I told him not to be
because I trusted
That at the end of the day,
You'd remember
that we're family.
But maybe I was wrong.
Because I spent 12 years
putting you first,
And the day I finally decided
to do something for myself,
You didn't just stop
treating me like family,
You started treating me
like a stranger.
And for your information,
that is a thousand times worse
Than if you treated me
like your enemy.
Louis, did you need something?
I need you to know
how proud I am of you,
'cause seeing you working
like this
Just reminds me how
you persevered with the lsats
And how you got into law school,
and now...
Louis, I'm not telling you
about esther's case.
Well, then what the hell
good are you?
Louis, you promised harvey
you would stay out of it.
I just need to know
what happened.
What happened with what?
What happened with them.
I mean, it's no secret
that I hated jeffrey,
But esther, she loved him,
And for them to just...
I need to know why.
He cheated on her.
Well, then you promise me
that the two of you...
Stick it to that sack of shit.
What do you think
I'm working on?
.
We're all squared away
on the paperwork?
No, we're not squared away
on shit
Until you tell me
whether or not you knew.
You want to run that
by me again?
Delta financial, your client.
Did you know they were
heavily invested in kelton?
Are you accusing me
of something, mike?
Because you better watch
what you say.
You still haven't answered
my question.
Did you know a subsidiary
of the hedge fund
Backing our suit just purchased
a huge block of kelton shares?
I am their lawyer,
not a stock analyst.
Then maybe you can
explain to me why you have
One of their brochures
on your desk?
Okay, listen to me,
mr. Photographic memory.
Underneath this brochure
are another 35
That have been piling up there
for a year and a half
Because I'm looking
to invest my money
That someday may be going
to your children.
Wait, you think we want money
that comes from some stock
That went through the roof
because you authorized
A settlement
lower than street expectations?
Okay, you've said your piece.
Now I'm gonna say mine.
I have been a lawyer
and an officer of the court
Longer than you've breathed air,
And I'm looking you
straight in the eye
And telling you
that I am an honest man.
You know as an honest man that
now that we've discovered this,
We have to disclose it
as conflict of interest.
Then bury it,
deep in the fine print,
Because it had nothing to do
with my recommendation,
And I'm not gonna let it
blow this goddamn deal.
Since when did this become
a deposition?
It didn't, but since you seemed
so anxious to ask esther
About what she said in the past,
I thought I'd just save us
all the trouble
And get it on the record myself.
What? I never agreed...
You promised jeffrey
50% of your company, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Then it's settled.
Well, not quite.
Now that our client has admitted
that she made the agreement,
We'd like to discuss
the circumstances
Under which she did.
What do you mean
the circumstances?
She promised me 50%, period.
No, she promised you 50%
because you forfeited
Your admission
to medical school.
That's right, and instead
of going to stanford,
I stayed home
and took care of our family.
(rachel) then why is
there no record of you
Ever being admitted to stanford?
Or any school, for that matter?
Just a pile
of rejection letters.
You lied to me?
This is ridiculous.
Lots of people
don't get into medical school
On the first try.
You were gonna take half
of my company on the first try.
30%.
He's not getting another penny
Of the business I built myself.
(jeffrey) you want to talk
about doing things yourself?
Who do you think stayed home
and kept our family together
While you were too busy
baking muffins
To make dinner for your kids?
(esther) don't you dare
attack me as a mother!
You cheated on me!
Esther, I'm sorry.
I made a mistake.
But I did give up everything
for you.
I put my life on hold.
I sacrificed my dream for yours.
I'm never gonna get
those years back.
(esther) no, jeffrey.
We had everything,
And you ruined it.
All right, that's enough.
You have our final offer.
This better not be
about robert zane again.
- Just give me one minute.
- God damn it.
One of his clients purchased
shares of kelton,
And if they acted
on privileged information...
I know the law.
Well, then you know
it's unethical at best
And illegal at worst.
What do you want from me?
I want to know
if you think he knew.
What the hell difference
does that make?
It's the difference
between a legitimate settlement
And stock manipulation.
You mean it would make him
a fraud?
This isn't the same thing,
and you know it.
I'm not trying to screw over
my clients.
Why would you even bring that up
right now?
Because you begged me
for this case
And a chance to work
with that man.
And if he colluded with them,
We can stick a better settlement
down their throats.
Do you really think robert zane
is dirty enough to do that?
I don't know,
but I find it hard to believe
That he's dumb enough
not to know.
My dad's not dumb.
- And he's not dirty.
- Rachel...
And the last time
someone called him shady,
It was louis, and you
almost punched him over it.
This is different.
This is the same.
You were gonna punch him
because an attack on me
Is an attack on you.
Well, attack on my father
is an attack on me,
And you're the one
who's doing it.
Nobody's attacking anybody.
Mike, you once came to me
Asking me to give you
the benefit of the doubt,
And I gave it to you.
So the least you can do
is give it to him.
I was hoping you had good news,
But you're not pouring that
drink because we have a deal.
We don't, but we can.
What are you saying?
I'm saying they offered 30%,
and I talked them down to 25%.
And why should I take it?
Because he's not the one
dragging this fight out anymore.
You are.
And whether or not you believe
He gave up everything for you,
he does.
Tell me I don't have the right
to be angry.
Do you know why
I never even considered
Becoming a divorce attorney?
Because it's beneath you.
Because there are children
involved.
When people get caught up
in divorce...
They forget
there are some things in life
That are more important
than money.
Okay, harvey.
25%.
You know, you're not exactly
The harvey specter
I was expecting.
Is that a good thing
or a bad thing?
A good thing.
You're not exactly the
louis's sister I was expecting.
Is that a good thing
or a bad thing?
A good thing.
Definitely a good thing.
Would you like
to take me home tonight?
I would.
But I need you
to sign that first.
Why is that?
Because then you won't be
my client anymore.
A man with a code.
Maybe you are a white knight
after all.
Come on, let's get out of here.
.
Louis, it's midnight. What's...
Harvey's screwing esther.
- What?
- Look at this.
It's an agreement
that esther signed
That agrees to give jeffrey 25%.
That's 5% more than she needs
to pay that son of a bitch.
Where did you get this?
Well, I was walking
down the hall.
I saw two glasses,
a bottle of scotch, and that.
He got her drunk,
so he could screw me over.
Okay, there is no way
harvey would ever do that.
You woke me up in the middle
of the night to tell me that?
Donna, 5% extra is $3 million.
How do you explain that?
- I can't.
- I can.
He's trying to get me back
about his compensation
By trying to screw over
another litt.
So what I need you to do...
Louis, the only thing
that I need to do
Is tell you you're crazy
and go back to sleep.
And if you do anything
between now and tomorrow
Other than confront harvey
face-to-face, so help me god,
You will not have a secretary
in the morning.
Hey.
I'm letting it go.
Does that have something to do
With where you've been
so early in the morning?
Yeah.
You went to see my dad?
I went to see emma powell,
Asked her how she felt
about the settlement.
She said it would
change her life.
You said it wasn't enough money.
She didn't even
mention the money.
She said, for her,
the settlement was proof
That kelton didn't do right
by her husband,
And that was all she needed.
[chuckles] okay.
So because the plaintiff
was happy,
All of a sudden, you think
my dad's an honest man.
No.
I went there to see
if I could let it go.
I know your dad is an honest man
Because he's raised
someone like you.
You were right.
I never should have
questioned his integrity.
I was also right
That you never
should've taken this case.
No, you were wrong about that.
I told you we might fight,
But it would bring us
closer together,
And it did.
And not just me and your father.
What does that mean?
I mean you and your father.
[chuckles]
I have never seen you leap
to his defense like that.
I did leap to his defense,
didn't I?
You sure did.
You think our daughter
will leap to my defense
Like that one day?
She sure will.
Louis, what are you doing here?
I'll tell you what
I'm doing here.
I'm coming to you face-to-face
about screwing my sister.
Excuse me?
I saw the terms, harvey.
They're a joke.
No, they're what esther wanted.
And you swore
you'd stay out of this.
Well, it's a good thing I didn't
Because there's no way
she wanted to give away
Millions of dollars.
It's called being charitable
in order to move on.
It's called
jeffrey's a piece of shit,
Not the march of dimes.
He should be getting nothing.
Instead of being focused
on what he gets,
You should be focused
on what esther gets,
Which is to be happy.
Wrong, litts are never happy,
And you're using her
to get to me.
How the hell am I doing that?
You think
I went after your money
By changing the firm's
compensation structure.
You did come after my money!
And now you're going after
esther's to even the score.
If I wanted to even the score,
I wouldn't come
after your sister.
I'd be coming after you.
And for your information,
I convinced her
To be forgiving by telling her
That there are
some things in life
That are more important
than money.
Bullshit!
You don't believe that.
Louis, I didn't take this
to get back at you.
I took it because it was
a chance to bury the hatchet
And move on.
So either let these terms stand,
Or do what you always do
and screw everything up.
Robert, I'm glad you're here...
What the hell did you do?
What are you talking about?
I went to see emma powell,
But I swear to god, I did
not undermine the settlement.
I'm not talking about that.
I'm talking about you going
behind my back to arcadian.
I didn't do that.
Oh, you expect me
to believe that
After all the shit you told me
the last time I saw you?
You can believe it or not,
But I'm telling you
I didn't do anything.
- Then who did?
- I did.
You said if he colluded
with arcadian,
Then we could shove a bigger
settlement down their throats.
But he didn't have to collude,
Because arcadian already had
access to that settlement.
Which makes it
insider trading anyway.
And I pointed out to them
That if they were
to divest their shares
To our clients who don't
have insider knowledge,
Then they've done nothing wrong.
No harm done.
The harm is
you lost me my client
And made me look like a fool.
No, robert, they did that
By not telling you
what they did.
Which means the client you lost
Was breaking the law.
And worse than that,
They were lying to their lawyer.
So you think this is funny?
No, I don't.
I think your future son-in-law
Trusted you had nothing
to do with it
And then saved your ass
from committing a crime.
You're... Welcome?
Thank you.
And you have my condolences.
- For what?
- For having to deal with him.
Oh, you have no idea.
Hey, right here.
I'm standing right here, guys.
- Can I buy you a drink?
- Mm-hmm.
If you guys, you know,
need anything fixed or saved
That no one else seems to be
able to do, I'll be right here.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to tell you
how grateful I am.
- You don't need to do that.
- Yes.
I do.
This whole mess
Has been the hardest thing
I've ever gone through.
And I wouldn't have
gotten through it
Without you reminding me
what's really important.
Thank you for that.
Take care, harvey.
Good luck, esther.
Oh, by the way,
Louis wanted me to tell you
How grateful he is too.
- Harvey.
- Louis.
What can I do for you?
Remember when I said,
if wanted you
To make up
for the compensation vote,
I would come to you directly?
Well, now I am.
Well, what happened to
"some things in life are
more important than money"?
This isn't about the money.
This is about
making things right.
I'm sorry, harvey.
For what?
I act like I don't know
esther's beautiful,
But I do.
It started when we
were in junior high
And all the cool kids
would hang out with me
Just so they could
get close to her.
Sometimes it worked,
and sometimes it didn't,
But either way,
when it was over...
They all acted like
they didn't know me at all.
So when I thought
You were using her
to get to me, I, uh...
I wasn't doing that, louis.
I know.
I'll take care
of the compensation issue.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
What can I do for you, harvey?
I wanted to thank you.
For what?
For 12 years.
♪ ♪