Lucille.
Hey!
Hey, it's looking good.
Tell me you've got good news.
I do.
Stable Shelters' bridge loan
has just been approved.
Harvey pulled some
strings at the bank.
Oh. Good to see you,
Harvey.
I figured you was allergic
to manual labor.
Oh, I'll get my hands dirty
if I have to, Lucille.
But I believe
charity begins at home.
Yeah.
Based on that Rolex you wear,
I'd say that your favorite
cause is doing pretty good.
We're going to need
your signature here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, 15% interest?
They're worried about
Stable Shelters' solvency.
They're worried? They should try
being Executive Director.
If you don't recover the money
that Anthony Mazlo embezzled from us,
every one of these projects
goes dark.
Unless you've got
a spare room or two
for a couple thousand families
in your condo.
I'm not really a roommate kind of guy.
- Oh.
- Harvey's deposing Elliot Perkins,
Mazlo's number two,
this afternoon.
Perkins had to have
knowledge of this,
and he's going to
give up his boss.
That's a promise. Excuse me.
Check it out.
Mazlo spent $500 a night on doggie
day care on his trip to Greece.
Greece.
What?
- Nothing.
- Tell me.
My first time
was in Greece.
Oh, my God. You're picturing
that right now, aren't you?
I have no choice.
I'm a visual person.
You two are
really adorable.
We're 48 hours from trial,
and you're gossiping like
two 12-year-olds in sleep-away camp.
Listen up.
Lucille Jackson is not just
the head of Stable Shelters, okay?
She also sits on
the Board of Directors
of several of
our largest clients.
So, if we lose this case,
I doubt that her generosity
is going to extend to us. I would...
In my office.
Bring the Clarity Drilling IPO.
Jerome Jensen is here.
Come on.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Lucille's case is all-hands-on-deck,
Harvey. You can't just...
I can. And I am.
I thought we were
working on this together.
Yeah, we are, Louis.
The same way a golfer
and his caddie work together.
Be that as it may, we are deposing
Elliot Perkins in fifteen minutes. So...
Perkins can wait.
Just make sure that my 9 iron is nice
and shiny when I get there. Okay?
Come on, Mike.
Harvey.
Jerome Jensen,
meet Mike Ross.
He's got the latest
on the IPO.
- Hello, Mike.
- Mr. Jensen.
I'm not here to talk
about my business, Harvey.
Looks like my daughter
might be getting into some trouble.
Mildred Wisnewski.
What's Lola doing
with a fake ID?
Well, that's what I hope
you can find out.
It slipped out of her purse
when she was ordering a drink
at a friend's bar mitzvah.
Any idea what it's about?
My relationship with Lola
has been rocky for a few years.
If I asked her,
she'd just lie.
The truth is, I don't need to know.
I just need you to take care of it.
Thank you.
What the hell is Harvey doing? He's
supposed to be deposing Elliot Perkins.
He's with a client.
I don't care.
We have a deposition.
Don't even try it, Louis.
I'm sorry.
Let's just start over. Okay?
Hi, Donna.
Hi.
You know I like you. Right?
But in the firm's
food chain,
I am a humpback whale
and you are phytoplankton.
June 3rd, 1997.
That date means
nothing to me.
Doesn't it?
- Who told you?
- Is the important thing how I know?
Or that I know?
Does Harvey know?
He can.
I am going to pay you.
I just don't have
cash on me right now.
So I'm going to just tell Norma to run
her old ass out to the ATM,
- and bring it back in a jiff.
- Hmm.
- All right?
- I don't want your money, Louis.
I just want you to...
I was not here.
All right.
Let's get started, shall we?
Isn't Harvey Specter
leading this deposition?
He sent me.
Now, Mr. Perkins,
my first question to you is
do you sleep well at night?
Of course you do. Because you have
a roof. And a bed. And running water.
And by contrast,
thousands of families
are going to be sleeping
on the street
when Stable Shelters is forced
to suspend their operations.
All because of
the money that you stole.
I never stole anything.
You're Mazlo's number two.
The money was embezzled.
Do you deny that?
- Absolutely.
- Please.
Robert, I know as General Counsel,
you just basically push paper.
But will you please warn Mr. Perkins
of the penalties of perjury?
Look, I'm not aware
of any perjury.
We know about your account
in the Caymans.
- Twenty million dollars.
- Are you... Are you kidding me?
That transaction
was legitimate.
Oh. When I take this public,
you're going to be disgraced.
Your wife, your children,
your whole family, disgraced.
- Would you show my client some respect?
- And... And that transaction
had nothing to do
with the firm.
Bullshit.
You either took your cut from Mazlo
or it was hush money.
Either way, you're going to live
the rest of your life as a pariah
or you give up Mazlo now.
Is this a deposition
or an inquisition?
This is ridiculous.
I can show you the records.
Oh, sure, you can.
Because you're the guy who invented
losses in mortgage-backed securities
when you never
even bought them.
I had no part in that.
But you were aware of it
and you did nothing about it.
Come on. Louis.
Could I... Could I get
a glass of water, please?
You can't get any water.
We don't have any.
You give up Mazlo now,
and this all stops.
All right, look.
My client needs a break.
We can continue this
in ten minutes.
I'm just getting started.
I don't get it.
She looks so sweet.
Don't let the photo
fool you.
She's less girl-next-door,
- more girl-with-the-dragon-tattoo.
- Hmm.
Look, my plate is full
with Stable Shelters.
I need you to look
into Jerome's daughter.
Why didn't he just hire
a private investigator?
Because if there's a problem,
an investigator can't fix it.
I'm not just a lawyer
to Jerome, okay?
I'm... I'm more like...
Robert Duvall in The Godfather.
His consigliere.
Okay.
What?
Uh, nothing. Just if you're
his Robert Duvall, you're coming to me,
so, technically,
I'm your Robert Duvall.
You're my Fredo.
Fredo? No.
Clear the hall, please.
Robert,
what the hell happened to Perkins?
Ask that pit bull of yours.
Oh, no. Actually,
I prefer a female masseuse.
Is that... Can I call you right back?
Right back. Okay. Bye.
Perkins just got wheeled
out on a stretcher.
Well, he couldn't handle the heat.
He's probably faking it.
What were you thinking,
starting that deposition without me?
I don't know.
Maybe if you were doing your job...
Oh, no.
What?
It's from Geller.
Perkins wasn't faking anything.
Our best chance to nail
Anthony Mazlo is dead.
See the money,
wanna stay for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
Well, he blew off the deposition.
So I was just picking up the slack.
I was letting
Perkins sweat.
It was a tactic.
Which you completely undermined.
Well, I believe I made
him sweat and then some.
Are you actually proud
of what you did?
As far as I'm concerned,
whatever happened to that guy
was a result of his own guilt.
And I will not apologize for deposing
a criminal in a vigorous manner.
Losing Perkins
is a complication.
We're just going to have to work harder
to unearth Mazlo's money trail.
As for what happened,
I've spoken to the hospital.
And the cause of death
was a pulmonary embolism.
It was nothing you did.
Would it be okay
if I took the credit?
Louis, I need to have
a word with Harvey.
Okay.
Financial crime
is that man's forte.
Yes, he over-stepped
his rank.
But I'm not about to throw
the baby out with the bathwater.
Louis is the bathwater.
Believe it or not, Harvey, you can be a
real pain in the ass to work with, too.
Oh, I get along
with me just fine.
Yes, well, I'm not about to tell
Lucille Jackson that we didn't win
because we couldn't
work together.
You need to figure out
how to collaborate with Louis.
So the name on
Lola Jensen's fake ID
wasn't just pulled
from thin air.
It belongs to an assistant controller
at Clarity Drilling.
And you're telling me this why?
You wanted me
to look into it.
I didn't ask you to
explain the problem to me.
I asked you
to fix it for me.
Hey.
Did Louis really kill a guy?
Is that what the associate rumor mill
has been churning out?
Actually,
I think he started it.
Yeah, he also claims to be 6' 2"
with a full head of hair.
Louis with hair.
That's good.
How did you
get past Donna?
You waited until she peed,
didn't you?
I mean,
the woman retains water like a camel.
I see that the greatest band of all time
is conspicuously absent.
And who would that be, Louis?
Oh. I don't know.
A little British band called Queen?
Should have seen that coming.
You know, real musicians,
they don't wear eyeliner.
Oh, really? Why don't you tell that
to the artist formerly known as Prince,
who is once again
named Prince?
What do you want, Louis?
Well, I think,
now that we're working together,
we should set some ground rules.
First rule.
Never touch my records.
Or anything else
in this office.
Fine.
That includes the furniture.
I'm trying to build
a rapport with you.
Okay? I mean, I think
our relationship needs a little work.
Let's hold off the couples counseling
until our fifth anniversary.
Don't you think?
Look, Mazlo's lawyer moved
to push up the trial.
They know we need time
to cultivate another witness.
Well, I say we bluff.
I mean, Perkins implicated Mazlo
the minute his lawyer
walked out of the room.
It's hearsay, Louis.
Not if it's
a deathbed confession.
Maybe while Geller was
making the 911 call,
I had a little conversation
with Perkins.
So you want to lie about
what Perkins said and how he said it?
Well, what's your brilliant solution,
Harvey?
I'm having the money
in Perkins' account traced as we speak.
And I have
another witness in mind.
I get Anthony Mazlo across that table,
you know I'll break him.
The way you broke Perkins?
- Yeah, if need be.
- You're not hearing me.
We need to hold off
on any meeting.
- I just want to know why that's...
- That's final, Louis.
Question.
Why would someone
named Lola Jensen
ever want to be known
as Mildred Wisnewski?
Who are you?
My name is Mike Ross.
I'm a lawyer.
Let me guess.
Pearson Hardman?
You know, forging a government document
like this after 911
is next to impossible.
God, there must have been
a glitch at the DMV.
Why did you come here?
Your father came to us
because he's worried about you.
If he was that worried,
he'd be here himself.
He wouldn't have sent
an empty suit.
You don't know
anything about me.
I, on the other hand,
know that you used this ID
to funnel payments from Clarity Drilling
to some fake company that you set up.
Locksley LLC?
You're stealing money
from your father's company.
A couple million so far.
I don't need to know why.
But I do need you to return it. Now.
Actually,
you do need to know why.
This is groundwater from Clarity's
fracking operation south of Tulsa.
It's got elevated levels
of dibutoxyethanol,
methane, and benzene.
This compares samples
taken pre-drilling
to levels taken last week.
How did you get that?
That's classified company data.
I'm good with computers.
Wait a minute. Locksley LLC. As in
Robin of Locksley. As in Robin Hood.
These toxins are known to cause kidney
failure, liver cancer, and infertility.
The EPA fines
were a slap on the wrist.
But the settlement that your firm
negotiated with the victims...
It doesn't matter
how pure your motives are.
You're committing
a very serious crime.
Threaten all you want. Okay?
There is no way that my father
is going to let this go public
right before his IPO.
I'm not giving
the money back.
I'm giving it away.
In terms of living relatives,
I didn't find anything.
But when I looked into the estates
of relatives who'd passed away,
the holding was originally
in the name of the aunt.
Your theory on Perkins
was right.
Harvey, what are you doing?
Rachel's services
are under my purview.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to change that.
Anthony Mazlo and his attorney
are in the conference room.
At whose invitation?
Oh, what,
you think I called them?
You... I... I didn't.
Then Mazlo feels
he has an advantage
and he's pressing it.
Hey, fellows. Thanks for meeting us
on such short notice.
I figured you'd be
on a flight right now, Mr. Mazlo.
Somewhere
with no extradition agreement.
Let's get to the point.
Without Perkins,
you don't have a case.
This report summarizes
an internal investigation we conducted.
What Inez has just handed you
is hard evidence
of fraudulent investments
and fake losses perpetrated by Perkins.
You guys have a real penchant
for fiction, don't you?
No, he duped all of us.
As CEO, he betrayed me
just as much as the investors.
We found an offshore
account worth $20 million.
Just hold on a second.
Lucille Jackson trusted you
to manage $150 million endowment.
If Perkins takes 20,
where the hell is the rest of it?
In light of these findings,
we'd like to offer a settlement.
- Yeah.
- Fifteen million.
Ten cents on the dollar?
That's a slap in the face.
Well, we advise all our clients
that investments carry risk.
You want a risk free return,
buy treasury bills or...
I don't know,
hide your money under the mattress.
While you were writing
the great American novel,
I've been checking facts.
The $20 million that Perkins
had overseas was legitimate.
He was innocent.
The money your firm embezzled
is still out there.
And this so-called
investigation,
it isn't worth the paper
it's printed on.
Well, Lucille Jackson
may beg to differ, counselor.
A bridge loan means
she's desperate.
Our offer is non-negotiable.
I won't accept this offer today
or a year from now.
Now, since you've all invited yourselves
over, feel free to see yourselves out.
So, first, you attack me
for wanting to lie about Perkins.
And then, you turn around
and do the same exact thing?
I wasn't lying.
What are you saying to me?
Harvey, what the hell
are you saying to me?
That Perkins had no
involvement whatsoever?
That's exactly what I'm saying, Louis.
He was innocent.
Huh?
It's no surprise
that Mazlo low-balled us.
I'm just passing along
this offer as a formality.
Fifteen million dollars
is not insignificant.
But now is not
the time to settle.
We have to
strengthen our hand.
All right, here's my problem.
Best case scenario.
We go to trial,
the jury awards us a settlement.
Obviously, Mazlo appeals that.
It's three years
before I see any money,
and my foundation
is long gone by that point.
No. I'm not going to let Mazlo pocket
the lion's share of your endowment.
I'm not interested
in a Pyrrhic victory.
Neither are we.
And to prove it,
we're going to forego our usual fee
and return to you the money
you've already paid.
I grew up sleeping
in my mama's car.
And in and out of more halfway houses
than I can count.
And one thing I realized
is that every penny matters.
So thank you.
What you going to do?
Perkins may have
been innocent,
but he was still
Mazlo's direct report.
I'm going to find out
what he knew.
Thank you.
Your job is to verify every detail
of Mazlo's internal investigation.
It is not about the crime now.
It's about the cover-up.
This says
Perkins acted alone.
Well, he's the perfect scapegoat.
He can't defend himself.
You want to go
to the bathroom?
You don't bother coming back.
By the way, that goes for
personal phone calls,
emails, and texts.
I detect a whiff of slacking,
you are done.
Get it?
You find anything,
I'll be in my office.
Louis.
I'm still working on Harvey's case.
Jerome Jensen can go screw himself
for all I care.
But Harvey
explicitly told me...
I don't care
if a burning bush told you, Mike.
The only commandments you need
to focus on right now come from me.
There is something wrong
with Louis.
That's not my problem.
I answer to Harvey.
...sitting home alone
with your kids and no job.
Harvey.
You solve Jerome's problem,
yet?
Uh, about to.
But I need your corporate card first.
What for?
Well, I thought you didn't want me
to explain it to you.
You're right. I don't.
Okay.
It's killing you, not knowing what
I'm going to use this for, isn't it?
Nope.
Please let me tell you?
If you bring that back to me and
it smells like stripper, you're fired.
I don't...
I don't go to places like that.
You had to send someone?
You couldn't just call me?
If you wanted this to be private,
you should have just robbed me.
You robbed the company,
I had to involve other people.
Okay. Why don't we take a seat?
I think that we could probably...
Why are you here?
I want to tell you
my side of things.
Okay.
I'm not proud of the fact
that we contaminated people's water.
But we apologized.
We implemented safeguards.
We negotiated a payout
that was more than generous.
If that's what you think,
then you are lying to yourself.
I think that we
could keep this civil.
No, she's right. It's true.
I am lying to myself.
I thought this was a phase. That, uh,
it was hormones. That it would pass.
But the truth is...
I raised a thief.
Okay. I think we're going
to need a minute. Thank you.
A thief. My research
is making the planet more habitable.
Okay? You are making money
destroying it.
You have no respect for me,
that's fine.
But at least respect
the workers.
You're stealing from them,
too.
You think I'm such a criminal?
Arrest me.
So, I organized this
so that you two could clear the air.
But it seems we've gotten off
on the wrong foot.
You know what?
It's the same story as always, Dad.
You duck
your responsibilities.
Lola. Lola.
What if I paid the company back
with my own money?
I don't think that
would be a very good idea.
It would make you
a conspirator.
I'm not turning
my daughter in to the police.
This is not about
the company image.
Well, the good news is
she hasn't distributed the money, yet.
The money is irrelevant.
I came to Pearson Hardman
to take care of this.
Instead, my daughter and I
are further apart than ever.
I can't imagine
how hard it is right now.
People are saying
the most horrible things about Elliot.
They must think
I've gone deaf.
Anthony Mazlo has been dragging
your husband's name through the mud
to make him a scapegoat,
Mrs. Perkins.
I'm here to help.
I don't understand.
You work for the other side.
I work
for a charitable organization
that had all
its money stolen.
I'm on the other side of Anthony Mazlo,
not your husband.
And I don't want to see his memory
painted with the same brush.
What would I have to do?
- This isn't the time or the place.
- No, it's okay.
What would I have to do?
I'd like to know everything Elliot
has ever told you about Mazlo.
Any details would help.
Mrs. Perkins.
Uh, I'm Louis Litt,
and I just want to let you know
that I'm going to do whatever it takes
to clear your husband's name.
His name?
My husband would be alive
today if it weren't for you.
We don't know that.
I know what happened
in that room.
Well, at the time,
we didn't have all the facts.
But now, we do.
I can't believe that
you have the audacity to come here.
I don't ever
want to see your face again.
And you can forget about
me helping you.
What the hell are you doing?
I was deposing the widow.
Just like you.
I came here
to pay my respects
and initiate a relationship,
not aggravate
a grieving woman.
I brought flowers.
You just cost us
a potential witness.
Oh, really? Well, maybe,
maybe if you'd shared
your game plan with me...
Oh. The same way that you shared
your game plan with me?
How do you expect her to react
to seeing you?
You need to get
your shit together
and find us a new witness.
Lola.
I wanted to apologize
for earlier today.
Can I come in?
Uh, yeah. Of course.
Nice gesture.
The botanical gardens.
Oh. Yeah. He said it was
a pretty special place for you guys.
It was.
And then, he became CEO.
But I'm not here to reminisce.
I must say, I was really impressed
you figured out what I was doing.
Especially
since you're not even a real lawyer.
What are you...
What are you talking about?
I accessed Harvard Law
School's alumni directory.
Every class that graduated
for the last ten years.
No record
of Mike Ross at all.
Yeah, the Dean's office
was supposed to fix that.
They... They put my name wrong
in the system.
I checked your Social
Security number against the database.
How did you get
my Social Security number?
Easily.
Here's the deal.
Leave me alone,
or I expose you.
You don't really
seem that worried about this.
Threats like hers
are a tactic.
They're effective
because they distract you
from what you're supposed to be doing.
Are you crazy? What we should
be doing is backing the hell off.
And how would that go, huh?
"Jerome, you came to us
with a problem.
"We discovered that your daughter
stole $2 million from your company.
"And our conclusion
is you're shit out of luck"?
I don't really care
how it would go.
All I care about is my life
and keeping our secret.
I told you
it's a distraction.
She won't pull that trigger.
Why do you think
she hasn't distributed that money, yet?
Why do you think Jerome
doesn't want us to go to the police?
I don't know.
It's because they both
want to bury the hatchet.
And if any of that stuff happens,
they can't.
Then, what?
Figure out a way
to make him reconcile.
It's easy.
Yeah. It's easy.
Inez, right? Louis Litt.
I know who you are.
So, is this what you do
for Mazlo?
You clean up
his dirty laundry?
Leave me alone.
You know, you have
your whole career ahead of you.
When Mazlo goes down
and you're part of this cover-up,
- no one is going to hire you.
- I can't help you.
Listen.
Can I just tell you something, Inez?
In my experience,
people respond to two things, okay?
And that's the carrot
and the stick.
Now, I prefer the stick.
And if you do not help me,
I will devote my considerable expertise
to sticking it to you.
The same way
you stuck it to Perkins.
Inez, stop.
Let's go with the carrot.
Inez. Harvey Specter.
I appreciate
you coming forward.
I should have
done this sooner.
What changed?
I can't be a part
of a company like that anymore.
Are you ready to testify
against Anthony Mazlo in open court?
I am.
I assume you've documented
his malfeasance.
Because otherwise,
it's "he said, she said".
The entire paper trail.
From the beginning
all the way to last week.
Harvey asked me to fix
this problem with Lola, but I can't.
Because your daughter's
not the problem, Mr. Jensen.
You are.
Are you trying to get fired?
No. I'm not.
I'm your attorney.
It's my job
to give you advice.
But you're her father.
It's your job to raise her.
Now, you can go
to another firm,
but there's not a lawyer in the city
that can do that job for you.
Please don't lecture me
on parenting.
Mr. Jensen, I had a
difficult relationship with my father.
So, trust me
when I tell you
that Lola
wants to forgive you.
But she needs you
to take the first step.
Well, we tried it your way.
We went to lunch,
and you saw how well that worked out.
My daughter is not a child.
She's an adult.
She made these choices
as an adult.
- If you just found a way to...
- You're my lawyer.
This is a legal problem.
My daughter brought this
on herself.
Now, I desperately
do not want her to go to prison.
But if she doesn't return the money,
she will.
Thank you.
Where's Mazlo?
He was afraid to face us himself?
What do you want?
We know about
your entire scheme.
What scheme?
Oh, the scheme where Mazlo
is laundering money through Dubai.
How do you know about Dubai?
We cultivated
another source.
What kind of settlement
are you looking for?
One that includes
punitive damages.
Send Inez in here, please.
I don't think
you'll find her at her desk.
- Why not?
- Because she agreed to testify for us.
I doubt that.
When your colleague approached her,
she came straight to us.
He even tried to bribe me.
He said if I ratted
out Mr. Mazlo,
he'd get me a job as an
assistant to Jessica Pearson.
Everything she told you
was a complete fabrication.
There is no Dubai.
I seem to recall you
mentioning something about
penalties for perjury
at our last meeting.
Well, the penalty for
bribing a witness is just as severe.
And we're willing to overlook
that indiscretion
if you convince your client
to take our settlement offer.
Well,
our revised settlement offer.
- Revised?
- Yes.
Exactly half
of what it was before.
What the hell
were you thinking?
We needed a new witness.
You didn't think to look
into her story?
I don't know.
Did you look into it?
You were the one who brought her in.
I assumed you had.
Like any halfway
decent lawyer would.
We were under the gun.
And I was under strict instructions
from my golf pro to get another witness.
No, I told you to get another witness,
not bribe one.
That's enough.
As for the threat against Louis,
no money changed hands.
I'm not concerned with Louis.
He brought your name into it,
okay?
The offer was to be
your assistant.
Now, you're exposed
because of what he did.
- Is that true?
- She is an executive assistant
to the head
of a major investment firm.
She's not going to work
for a junior partner.
So you tried to bribe her.
No, it wasn't a bribe, Jessica.
It was an incentive.
I thought she'd be more likely to talk
if she wasn't worried about being fired.
I want you to go to Mazlo
and take their offer.
I'm not ready to do that.
I'm not, either.
I waived Lucille's fee
because a certain senior partner
said we'd never go to trial.
I said that before
you stuck me with Louis.
Not the point.
She can't afford it, and neither can we.
Give me time.
Give it to me without Louis,
and we'll see who can afford it
and who can't.
You have until
the end of the day.
You come up empty,
I'm taking the offer to Lucille myself.
Jessica.
I went to Perkins' widow.
Not another word.
You try something like that again,
and it will be
your last day at this firm.
You said Jerome wouldn't pull
the trigger. You were wrong. He's ready.
I don't have time
for that right now.
Harvey, when the police show up
at Lola's doorstep, we're done.
Has she distributed
the money, yet?
No, she hasn't.
But she's about...
She hasn't. And she won't.
Because what she wants
is her daddy's attention.
Now, sit down with me
and let's deal with this.
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
Why don't you tell me what you need?
Mazlo was in Liechtenstein the day
that Lucille's endowment evaporated.
Yeah, maybe he was skiing.
Nobody goes to Liechtenstein
for pleasure.
Why don't we subpoena the bank records?
How many banks can there be?
That place is like
Switzerland on steroids.
We'll never see
those records.
So what the hell
do you want from me, then?
What did you
just say to me?
I once suggested that we hack
Harvard's records to cover my ass,
and you laughed at me.
And now,
it turns out that you were wrong,
and it's about to cost me
my career.
Where are you going?
You told me to fix my case.
Why don't you fix yours?
I hope you came here
to tell me Harvey's backing off.
I wish I could,
but he's not.
That's too bad.
You had
such a promising career.
God, Lola. You act like
you care about a higher cause.
But of all the companies that exist,
you chose your dad's.
A company that's trying
to make amends for what it did.
I really don't need to hear
another speech from a wannabe suit.
God, you think
I'm your enemy, huh?
Well, I'm not.
I didn't even come here
to talk to you about me or your father.
New York. Iowa. Kansas.
Forty states that all have
housing projects that will vanish
if we don't find out information
that only you can help us get.
So, you can steal money
from your father's company,
or you can blow the whistle
on me if you want to.
But if you really care about people
the way that you claim to,
you're going
to do this first.
Are we close?
I'm accessing the banks
through a server in China.
Unless you'd rather me
use yours.
Take your time.
Done.
All right.
There are 16 banks in Liechtenstein.
This is every account
in every single one of them.
None of the accounts
is listed under Anthony Mazlo.
Forget about the name.
Find an account with $150 million
embezzled
from Stable Shelters on that date.
Harvey, it's time.
Unless you have something,
I'm calling Lucille to settle.
Jessica, you know how Liechtenstein
doesn't respond to subpoenas.
So I responded for them.
Just trust me.
We've got everything we need
to find Lucille's money.
It's not here.
Sounds like you need more
than just another minute.
You need another person.
Someone whose expertise
is financial crime.
No. No.
Harvey. Bring in Louis,
or I'm calling Lucille.
Donna? I need to talk to Louis.
He's not in his office.
Huh.
Norma wouldn't tell you
where he is?
Well, she didn't, um...
You didn't ask her,
did you?
That woman...
She gives me the creeps.
Oh, you're such a wuss.
What did you
just say to me?
I think we both know
what I just said.
Norma, where is he?
What? You're kidding.
- What?
- Shh.
I come here
when I need to be alone.
.44 Magnum? Really?
You feeling lucky today, punk?
You know, I understand
that me pissing the bed on this case
must be really,
really fun for you.
No, Louis, it's not.
The one thing you and I
have in common is we need to win.
I noticed that.
And I came here because,
even after everything,
we can win.
No.
I can watch while you win.
Louis,
I'm not here to give you shit.
Listen. I respect you.
I bribed a witness.
You incentivized her.
I went to see Perkins' widow.
To apologize.
I killed a man.
That you thought
had it coming.
I don't think you heard
what I said.
I respect you.
You need my help.
I wouldn't phrase it
exactly like that.
Well, if you need my help,
you better phrase it
exactly like that.
Okay, you want me to say it?
I'll say it.
I'm under the gun
and I need your help.
I've got
the information,
but you've got the financial expertise
to break this case.
Now, let's put the gun down
and go get him.
Okay.
First, just stand over there
for a second.
Don't push it.
So, what was the exact amount of money
that was lost
from Stable Shelters' account?
- Why?
- $152,375,242.18
I'm good with numbers.
Huh.
All right. What do you have?
We've compiled a printout
of every account
that had a deposit made
on the day in question
in all of Liechtenstein's
16 banks.
Okay.
Well, we are going to focus on,
excuse me,
these five banks.
How can you be sure?
Watch this.
These four banks have a history
of capitulating to subpoenas
so Mazlo would know.
These six have
US corporate parents,
which would expose their accounts
to federal scrutiny.
Once again, Mazlo would know.
And then, the one that he's got
right there is low in reserves.
Therefore,
its solvency is in question.
And there is no way in hell
that Mazlo would take his stolen money
and put it
into some shaky bank.
So, we can be sure.
Every person who embezzles money,
they do it in their own way.
But the one thing
that they all have in common
is that they never put
all their eggs in one basket.
So we are going to be looking
at a combination of accounts.
- Across banks.
- Well, I mean, maybe across banks.
Maybe the same bank.
But we're definitely looking
at more than one account.
Ooh. How do we figure out
which accounts are his?
Because they're all going to add up
to the same exact amount of money
that was lost from
Stable Shelters' account.
Well, how do you know?
When the account was drained,
it had to go somewhere.
What goes out from Lucille's
had to go into Mazlo's.
Simple law of mathematics.
So, we just have to figure out
a combination of accounts
- that adds up to...
- $152,375,242.18.
I'm good with
numbers, too.
Thanks for meeting us
on such short notice.
I assume you're ready
to take our offer.
I rushed right down.
Well, we just have a few questions
before we get to any of that.
We didn't agree to answer
any questions.
No, no, Robert. It's okay.
I'm happy to play.
Have you ever been to Liechtenstein,
Mr. Mazlo?
You know,
I've been to many places.
Among them Liechtenstein.
Really?
Well, of those many places,
did you open
seven different bank accounts,
the amounts of which add up
to exactly the same amount of money
that disappeared from
Lucille Jackson's endowment fund?
I doubt it.
What I don't doubt is that if you trace
the money that went into those accounts,
you'll find that it came
from our corporate offices in Sri Lanka.
It's completely legitimate.
I mean, I'm happy to show you
the records, whenever you'd like.
Oh, that's great.
Isn't that great? Well, after that,
can you show us the records
of the seven safety deposit boxes
that you opened
at those same banks the same day?
I don't
have to answer that.
This isn't a deposition.
You're so right.
It's more of a presentation.
We can make it a deposition.
- Or a trial.
- Up to you.
We have pictures of you
entering those banks.
And we have enough
to crack their subpoenas.
It's just a matter of time, Tony.
All right.
What do you want?
What do I want?
Well, it's not about me.
It's about Lucille.
She wants your head on a stick.
But she'll settle
for her money back.
And your resignation.
We agree right here,
no criminal prosecution.
Done.
If Lucille doesn't get
her money back today,
nothing's done.
Great. That's perfect.
You are back in business.
The wire transfer just went through.
Girl. You came through.
That is what we do.
Harvey? Harvey, get in here.
Lucille wants to thank you
in person.
I've always got time
for gratitude.
Harvey,
you didn't let me settle,
and I appreciate
your tenacity.
The truth is,
I didn't do this on my own.
Have you met Louis Litt?
You guys are doing such good work.
I just want you to know it.
Dean Waiser, have I told you
how valuable you are to this company?
Because you're not.
Just kidding.
Janice. I want you to take the rest
of the day off because you're so good.
And I really mean it.
Harold. 9:30.
Tequila shots, you and me, sharp.
Be there.
Louis. Luis.
- What's up?
- What were you just doing in there?
- What? I was just...
- Let me guess. You were cutting me out.
What are you talking about?
The little impromptu meeting
you just had with Jessica and Lucille
that you conveniently
left me out of.
- I didn't leave you out of anything.
- Man, I thought we were a team.
I thought this was
the start of something. But I...
- Louis...
- Now, I see the truth all too clearly.
Louis. I was walking by
and they called me in.
Yeah. Just in time
to take the credit for what I did.
I didn't do that.
I wouldn't even think
of doing that.
But you know what?
You would.
And that's your problem
right there.
I got your email
about Mazlo.
Not a bad way
for Locksley LLC to go out.
Looks like the firm
owes you one.
I think you owe me one.
Whoa.
Uh...
- Is this...
- The real thing?
Yeah.
I told the Dean's office
you'd lost yours.
They were happy to oblige
for one of their top graduates.
I don't know if you're awesome
or terrifying.
Also, I added a layer
of protection for you.
Uh, the Harvard Law School
alumni database.
It's all there.
Your name, class rank,
Social Security number.
You do realize you've just
made me party to a crime, right?
You can always call them up.
Report it as a glitch.
Let me guess. Untraceable.
I'm not saying
you won't get caught.
But it won't be because
your story doesn't check.
Hey. Um...
Thank you. Seriously.
You were right.
I'm working things out
with my dad.
You're not the empty suit
I thought you were.
Who was that?
Uh, client's daughter.
Really? It's kind of late. What's she
doing at the office at this hour?
You know,
she was just thanking me.
- Thanking you.
- Mmm-hmm.
How did she do that?
Easily.
She bought me
two plane tickets to Greece.
Not interested.
We leave Tuesday.