The 2011
Tesla Roadster Sport.
Offered only
to our most exclusive members.
You know your vehicles.
I promise to have her back
before she turns into a Pontiac.
- Hey, Harvey.
- Laurence.
How would you feel about taking
something other than the Tesla tonight?
It goes against my policy.
What policy?
My I-want-the-Tesla
policy.
Yeah.
Tell you what.
You know more about the car than I do,
it's yours.
Horsepower.
Really?
That's where we're starting?
Well, if it's so simple,
just answer it.
288.
- Top speed.
- 125 miles an hour.
- Zero to sixty...
- 3.7 seconds.
Yeah. You know your cars.
I'm an enthusiast.
And I've been waiting
for the Tesla for months.
Okay.
Laurence.
Knock yourself out.
So, why did you let him have it?
Because it never hurts to have a man
who runs a two billion dollar hedge fund
owe you one.
But if you were
just going to give it to him,
why bother
to compete first?
Because if I didn't beat him,
he wouldn't feel like he owed me one.
I'm suddenly feeling
old school.
Why don't you surprise me,
huh?
Are you Mike Ross?
Harvey told me to tell you
that 8:00 means 8:00.
Whoa.
Glad you showed up.
Oh. Hey, I'm sorry.
I was...
- Shut up.
- Okay.
You see these cars?
Yeah. They're awesome.
They suck.
They're nothing compared to this.
Whoa.
The engine in this car
is made by McKernon Motors.
The industry standard
in Formula One.
In fact, they've won more championships
than any other engine on the planet.
How do you
know all this?
Avery McKernon was the first client
I ever brought into the firm.
Was?
He died three months ago.
- Oh, God. I'm so sorry.
- Not the point.
McKernon's engines and his company
have something in common.
They win. Like me.
And because I win,
I've been promoted to senior partner,
which means you'll be handling
all their paperwork.
So you brought me here to give me
an appreciation for the product.
No, I brought you here
to meet Robert Stensland, the new CEO.
He'll want to put a face
with your name.
How do you know?
Because Robert's a tightwad,
and we don't bill you out for nothing.
Wait a minute.
Is this conversation right now billable?
You bet your ass it is.
Yes. Up top. Come on.
What? We're making all this money.
We can't celebrate it?
Not in poor taste.
Dominic.
Mike, I'd like you to meet
Dominic Barone,
the man responsible for the design
and production of this engine.
This is my new associate,
Mike Ross.
He's just a kid. Are you trying to steal
his soul before he hits puberty?
Okay.
Obviously, I'm long past...
You're still upset
about our labor negotiations.
Well,
my workers took a big hit.
And McKernon took a bigger one.
Both of which poised the company
to be strong for years.
I was always straight
with you about that.
Sophisticated words
for a guy who screwed us.
Look.
I'm sorry you feel that way,
but you have to admit I did have
the courtesy to do it from the front.
Wow. Yeah, he really appreciates
what you've done for the company.
Robert Stensland. I'd like you
to meet your new associate, Mike Ross.
We're not paying him
what we pay you.
Nor should you. But I assure you,
he's highly effective.
Well, I'll believe it
when I see it.
I had him read
your corporate lease last week.
Ask him anything.
That's a 300-page document.
Okay. What are the terms?
Okay. I have no idea
what you're talking about.
The named lessee was the parent
company, Glendon Enterprises.
35,000 square feet
at 19, West 57th,
$80 a foot.
Expires in six months, with an option
to extend exercisable in thirty days.
Who signed the lease?
You did.
- What's my middle name?
- The letter "L".
What happens in the event
the company no longer exists?
- That wasn't in the lease.
- How can you be sure?
Because the lease I read
wasn't 300 pages.
It was 364.
And I could tell you
what's on any one of those pages,
but I can't tell you that.
That's how I can be sure.
Excellent.
You can get him started
on the new deal right away.
New deal?
Yeah. I have found a buyer
willing to spend $200 million dollars
for the ground underneath
the flagship factory.
Where are you moving manufacturing?
Well,
that's the beauty of it.
The real asset of McKernon Motors
is the name.
We move overseas,
we save ourselves a bundle.
Upfront payout, while retaining the name
and maintaining cash flow over time.
That's genius.
- Exactly.
- We'll take care of everything.
- Okay.
- All right.
Yeah. Thanks.
Really?
Jesus.
I knew he was cheap.
I didn't realize
he was an idiot.
What are you
talking about?
The asset's not the name.
It's the quality.
He moves overseas,
he's going to kill the goose
that laid the goddamn golden engine.
Wait a minute. I thought you didn't
get emotionally attached to the client.
I'm emotionally attached
to me.
Look. I made a bet
that this company would grow
and my billables
would grow with it.
We're holding
a pair of aces,
and this asshole
is trying to fold.
So?
What are you going to do?
I'm not going
to do anything.
You're going to go
through those bylaws
and you're going to find me a way
to get rid of Robert Stensland.
No, no, no, no.
I have to go see my grandmother. Uh-uh.
She dying?
- No.
- Cancel on her.
Are...
See the money,
wanna stay for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
Hmm.
Oh.
Yeah.
Did you find anything that will help me
get rid of Stensland?
Uh, yeah. I think so.
Well, if you're not here when I need it,
what good does that do me?
What? It... It's 7:15.
Hello?
Did you get it?
Picked it up yesterday.
Did you sleep with it
under your pillow?
How I sleep
is none of your concern.
Yeah, neither is
the Yankees batting order,
but that doesn't stop me
from thinking about it.
Harvey.
Promise me you won't be cocky.
I understand what's at stake here.
I'll be perfectly humble.
Great. You ready?
You kidding?
I was born for this.
7:45.
Nice of you to show up.
Ha. Yeah, I was up
till 5:00 in the morning.
I'm kidding.
But Louis really wants to see you,
and I don't kid about that.
What does he want?
I don't know. Louis doesn't let me in
on his game plan,
and I kind of
prefer it that way.
Okay. Um... Can you tell him
that I have to see Harvey first?
Your call.
But, uh, if you're
going to be sleeping in your suits,
you may want to keep
a fresh one in the office.
- Is it that bad?
- It's worse.
Come on.
I'd just like to say
this is an honor.
I take it seriously,
and I intend to make you all proud.
Except you, Fred.
I gave up
on making you proud in '99.
Okay. There is one more
order of business.
He's not here.
No.
Where is he?
- He's at his senior partner initiation.
- Let me ask you something.
What's the difference between
a senior partner and other partners?
Isn't that something
you should've been studying
when you were pretending
to go to Harvard?
Ah.
Okay. Senior partners,
they buy into the firm.
They share in the profits,
but they also have to put up equity.
So how much does it cost
to buy in?
Half a million dollars?
Right now?
Harvey,
you knew what the buy-in was.
You knew today
was initiation.
How could you not
have the money?
I didn't think
it was due today.
It's not due today,
is it?
No. It's not.
Every man in this room
fell for exactly the same thing.
Does that include you?
No. No, it doesn't.
Thank you, gentlemen.
All right.
Peanuts, gluten,
strawberries.
What is this,
a shopping list?
No. It's just a list of foods
that I'm allergic to.
So,
when you select a venue,
these foods
are not to be on the menu.
Venue for what?
No one told you?
- No one told me.
- Oh, drats.
Well, a long-standing Pearson Hardman
tradition is the rookie dinner.
- Which means you, the...
- Rookie.
- That's right.
- Yes.
Are to host a dinner
for your fellow associates.
Oh, come on.
Don't look so blue.
Oh, it's okay.
It's really easy.
All you have to do
is just find a unique location
and then coordinate
with 50 other associates.
It's really simple.
No pressure.
And you're allergic
to chicken?
No, I just don't like it.
Oh, by the way,
what was so important that you had
to see Harvey before you came to see me?
Louis,
Harvey doesn't really like me...
Can we... Can we just...
Can we just... Shut up.
Okay.
Let me just get something straight.
Okay?
When I ask you a question,
I just expect an answer.
Uh...
McKernon Motors.
I was working on the due diligence.
And why would that require you
to look at the bylaws?
State law requires a summary be prepared
in the event of a sale.
Privately held corporations
are exempted.
Not if the sale exceeds
$150 million.
According to who?
The state's website.
I like to be thorough.
Well, put it there, buddy.
Serious? Embarrassing.
I understand Stensland is throwing
a large amount of legal work our way
with the McKernon Motors factory sale.
- How do you know that?
- I hear things.
- You taking care of him?
- I am.
By the way,
for when it is due.
What's this?
It's a cashier's check
for $500,000.
You had this
the whole time?
I've had the money
since I set my sights on senior partner.
Nice of you
to finally make it.
Why does everybody
keep saying that?
Because you're supposed to be here
when you're supposed to be here.
That doesn't seem
to apply to you.
I'm not the topic
of this conversation.
Now. What did you find me
on McKernon Motors?
The Board can't vote
for at least 24 hours
after the CEO presents a deal
involving the sale of company land.
But Stensland already
presented it to the Board.
Right.
But Stensland isn't CEO.
I wrote those bylaws myself.
He's CEO.
Hmm. Page 238,
clause 137 states,
"If the CEO dies,
an interim CEO will be appointed
"until the Board convenes
an election vote,
"which can't be called
until the next fiscal quarter."
In this case, next Thursday.
So, they can't vote him in
until Thursday?
Thursday.
Okay.
Well, prepare the due diligence
for me to take to Stensland.
But I don't want
anything ready to sign.
- Where are you going?
- Out.
I have until Thursday
to find a new CEO.
- Huh.
- What?
Oh, nothing, uh,
it was just six hours, 1500 pages,
and I, uh...
I found your mistake.
Yeah.
You found the one mistake I made
while drafting those bylaws
a dozen years ago,
when I was
two years younger than you.
A mistake, by the way, that's going
to help me get rid of Stensland.
Mistake.
Oh, uh...
Excuse me, uh, Mr. Specter?
I was wondering
if you might need a hand sometime
with one of your, uh, matters.
Uh, any one.
- Well, Allen...
- Oh, it's Aaron.
I think that says it all,
don't you?
What are you doing?
I'm looking
for a restaurant.
Where did you go
for your rookie dinner?
I came into the league
a sophomore.
And you better not be
prioritizing that over McKernon Motors.
I still need something
to stall Stensland.
It's right here.
What are you
so irritated about?
I spent the day
with the top headhunter I know,
who couldn't produce one legitimate
CEO candidate by Thursday.
What about
that Dominic Barone guy
who runs production?
You said he was responsible
for the engines,
and he clearly cares
about the workers.
No, he's not the guy.
Ah, you're scared you can't
convince him because he hates you.
I get it.
Nice try.
You know you can't
host your dinner there.
That's a
Wachtell Lipton Kline restaurant.
Okay, fine.
What about this place?
Yeah, that would be great.
If it was 2004.
Oh, my God.
What does any of this matter? God.
See that guy over there
by the fax?
Take a good look.
He's never
going to make partner.
Okay. Let me guess.
Because he threw a lousy rookie dinner.
No.
Because he doesn't get it.
Get what?
He doesn't get that doing good work
isn't the whole job.
Part of getting it is that
things like the dinner actually matter,
even when you don't think they do.
Look, you were giving me shit
this morning
because I come and go
when I want to.
You know why I can do that?
Because when I got here,
I dominated.
They thought I worked
a hundred hours a day.
Now,
no matter what time I get in,
nobody questions my ability
to get the job done.
Get it through your head.
First impressions last.
If you start
behind the eight ball,
you'll never get in front.
Hey. You busy?
It's 7:00.
I'm not here because I like the view.
And don't misunderstand me.
When I say the view,
I'm referring to your face.
That's funny.
Because I'm hideous.
- What's up?
- You're a foodie, right?
Why do you say that?
Because you're the only person
I've ever seen order
a shrimp, red pepper,
and goat cheese pizza.
Well, right,
but without the pepper,
what connects the goat cheese
and the shrimp?
I'm a foodie.
Okay. So, I need your help finding
a restaurant for the rookie dinner.
Well, that's unfortunate.
But I'm swamped, and I don't have time
to teach you about cuisine.
What? No. Don't make me remind you
that you owe me one.
How is that?
You told Louis I was working
on Harvey's case before his.
Because you told me to.
Well, now, I'm telling you
to help me with my dinner.
- Mmm.
- You... Okay.
Good luck with that.
Not going to help me
with my dinner.
Now,
I'm talking to myself.
Yeah. Grammy.
No, I told you I was coming.
I'm... I'm on my way.
Okay. Yeah.
Um... Fifteen minutes.
Okay. Bye.
Hey, what are you...
Okay.
What was that for?
If you cared about me,
you would have told me
what Trevor was up to a long time ago.
I was trying to protect you.
How is hiding the fact that my boyfriend
is selling weed protecting me?
You want to know the truth?
Your boyfriend also happens to be
my best friend. All right?
I didn't feel like
ratting him out.
If you were
really his friend,
you wouldn't just stand by
and let him throw his life away.
Let him?
Let... I never let Trevor do anything.
Have you met him?
Trevor listens to you,
and he needs you right now.
Oh, my God.
He is throwing
his life away.
And you ditched us.
Both.
Like we didn't mean
anything to you.
I'm late.
Louis.
What are you doing here?
Hi. Uh, Stensland called.
Apparently,
the diligence wasn't proceeding apace.
He called you?
Yeah, he called me. I called him.
What's the difference?
The paperwork was taking too long,
and I got it done.
I suggest you stay the hell away
from my client.
Harvey. Glad you could make it.
We are about to sign the papers.
I got word
back at the office.
I just came to see
how Louis was getting around the bylaws.
I don't know.
Ah...
I'm at somewhat of a loss.
Robert, I'm sorry. This is
what was holding up your due diligence.
Technically,
you're still interim CEO
until the Board
votes you in on Thursday.
If protocol isn't followed,
it leaves you
- with huge litigation exposure.
- That's right.
Well, I imagine we should,
uh, hold off, then.
Please don't blame Louis.
It's my fault.
We usually have senior partners
oversee transactions like this
because junior partners,
they tend to miss things.
- See you Thursday?
- One second.
Uh, just so you know, you were
a junior partner until recently.
There's a reason
I'm not anymore.
Okay. Take it easy.
So what if you took
a trip to Russia with another man?
I mean, that was before
you met Grandpa Jimmy, right?
He didn't care
it was before I met him.
Never shut up about it.
So, what was
this other guy's name?
Gregory Mind-Your-Own-Business.
Ooh.
So, Michael,
this has been fun.
Now, why don't you stop
beating around the bush
and tell me
what's going on?
Trevor.
It's Trevor.
It's always Trevor.
He's gotten himself
into some really bad... stuff.
And I think he needs my help
to get out of it.
But I've been
under so much pressure.
And I know you've always
told me to be there...
- Yeah, no. Listen to me.
...for the people in my life.
Screw Trevor.
- What?
- You're moving forward.
And he'll do
whatever he can
to keep you
where you are.
- Yeah, but he...
- But no buts.
That kid is an anchor.
You need to cut him loose.
- Whoa.
- You owe me fifty bucks.
What's going on
with Robert Stensland?
What did Louis tell you?
You're not dealing with Louis. You're
dealing with me. What are you hiding?
Nothing.
I looked through the bylaws
and precluded
potential litigation.
You looked at the bylaws
for a tactical reason,
and I want to know
what it is.
I want him out.
That is not your call.
You're an attorney. This is the
internal business of McKernon Motors.
Look. McKernon had a plan.
And I didn't spend
a decade shaping it
to let this fool
throw it away.
McKernon is dead.
So, what?
That doesn't mean the plan's no good.
You fail, we'll get fired.
He moves overseas,
our billables will be gone
in five years, anyway.
Better five years
than nothing.
You know what?
That's Stensland's attitude,
and it's a losing one.
Harvey. I don't think
you have any business
telling that man
how to run his company.
But I know you don't have any business
telling me how to run mine.
You are a senior partner.
You are not
a gunslinger anymore.
Back off Stensland,
and close the deal.
I need you to prepare the draft
CEO candidate speech for Thursday.
I thought you were
supposed to back off.
Yeah, I'm supposed
to do a lot of things.
I'll call you with the plan
on my way back.
From where?
From convincing the man who hates me
to do what I say.
Oh, right. You mean the guy I suggested
you go to in the first place.
Do you remember that whole "getting it"
thing I was talking to you about?
What, I can't even gloat?
Gloating's fine.
You just have to not suck at it.
Ah. Okay.
Thank you. So much.
That hurt.
Hey, Ross.
You left your searches
for the rookie dinner on your computer.
Why don't you just save time
and take us to Fridays?
Ooh. Ooh.
Somebody's mad.
Devon, looking on my computer
is a violation
of exactly seven hostile workplace
environment statutes.
What are you going to do,
sue me?
No, no, no, no. I'm just going
to use it as legal cover
if I decide to kick your ass.
Dominic.
Harvey, what are you
doing here?
Our contract's good
for two more years.
I need a word.
In private.
Excuse me, Joe.
Make it fast because this is a place
where people actually work for a living.
Well, keep in mind
people are watching.
Just try to keep
your expression neutral.
They don't teach deceptive tactics
where I come from.
Then, you're going to learn
under fire.
Stensland
is shutting you down.
What? Why?
For money. He's got a buyer
for the land under the factory.
Why are you coming to me?
Because the only way
to stop him
is for you
to challenge him as CEO.
What? Are you crazy?
You've got
a management title.
That I choose
not to identify with.
You run the factory.
Which I've never left because I've got
no taste for boardroom politics.
You've been here
since day one.
You know the product
inside out.
These workers...
They respect you.
Phew.
That's a lot of smoke.
How many people
did you go to before me?
- Seven.
- Right.
I never said you were
my prom queen.
Look, I want a win.
Okay?
I went to those other people
because they were better suited
to get past the Board.
Not better suited
for the job.
Those are the facts,
whether you like it or not.
- And why should I trust you?
- Because if you don't,
there aren't any jobs left
to negotiate over.
You and the factory,
you're finished.
What are you working on?
Um, nothing.
Just some stuff for Harvey. Why?
Wrap it up. Louis Litt wants to see you.
This time, he doesn't want to wait.
Furthermore,
I feel that with the proper strategic
and synergistic alliances,
moving forward, we can...
I have to actually believe
what you're saying.
They're just platitudes
that don't mean anything.
Yes, they do. Synergistic alliances
mean you form relationships
to get the costs down
and your product out.
This is never going to work.
Well, it better goddamn work.
My ass is on the line.
- What about my ass?
- If it wasn't attached
to your thick head, maybe we wouldn't
be having this problem.
I'm sorry I'm not as well-practiced
at corporate double-speak as you'd like,
but I've been busting my ass
on this for two hours.
So if you're not happy
with my progress,
then why don't you
get the hell out?
He doesn't leave
without getting it.
Son of a bitch.
You're not going
to pick it up?
Why should I?
You're never going to get it.
You're right.
Hey, can I ask you something?
What's your
engine design philosophy?
Perfectly balanced power
and durability.
Okay. Why don't you favor power,
like Bronson does?
Because drivers are limited
to eight engines a season,
and Bronson's don't last.
What, so, you would stack your engines
up against Bronson's, then?
Uh, I have stacked my engines up
against Bronson
and everyone else's in the world,
and mine win.
Why?
Because I make sure they're designed
better than anyone else's in the world
from the day that they're conceived
to the day they're born.
And that's why
people buy them.
You're goddamn right.
Then that's the speech
you're going to give.
Good lawyer,
bad lawyer, baby.
Worked like a charm.
Come on.
You know you want it.
There it is.
I told you. If someone doesn't like you,
use it against them.
Or in this case, for them.
I didn't do this
for Dominic.
I did it
to get rid of Stensland.
Wow. Have you ever considered
writing for Hallmark?
- Many times. Yeah.
- Wow.
Congrats.
You're good.
- Hey.
- I said don't be late.
Late? I'm not late.
When you host
your dinner here,
not being late means
getting here a half hour early.
Aha. So, what made you
change your mind?
The food items are samples
to help you select your menu.
So since I could never really afford
to eat here myself...
Hmm.
- Hmm.
- Okay. Start there.
- Try that?
- Yes.
- It looks kind of funny.
- So does an eggroll.
I don't accept that premise.
You want my help or not?
- Oh, what is that?
- Squid.
I think it's still moving.
That's what I'm talking about.
Mmm.
I don't get it. How do you have
no appreciation for fine food?
We didn't have a lot of money
growing up.
I don't know.
I guess I'm just comfortable
with what I'm comfortable with.
That is the exact opposite of me.
I've...
I've always loved
new experiences.
And your parents?
- They're loaded.
- Mmm.
So then what do you need
a free meal for?
I want to live on
what I make.
Hmm.
- What?
- Nothing.
I was just thinking
about Dominic for a second.
And then, I realized
this is the first time in weeks
that I haven't
been thinking about work.
That's what new experiences
do for you.
Being a foodie doesn't mean
only liking fancy food.
It means having the courage
to try it.
And then you get to serve
what you like.
Except strawberries,
peanuts, gluten, and chicken.
Okay. Why not those things?
Because Louis is an asshole.
If you can't serve things just
because Louis is an asshole,
you're not going to have
that many choices.
Good point.
So, what really made you
change your mind?
Pity.
I'll take it.
Driver,
taketh me to Williamsburg.
It's Jenny. Trevor told me
you talked to him,
and he's going to stop.
Thanks, Mike.
Hold on.
Change of destination.
- Trevor.
- What are you doing here?
Can we talk for a minute?
Yeah.
I know you lied to Jenny
about us talking.
You never should've told her
I was dealing in the first place.
I never should've had to hide it
in the first place.
Look, Trevor.
You don't need to be
dealing for a living, man.
You can make something
of yourself.
Is that what you came
here to tell me?
You've got real software clients, man.
Stick to them.
Jesus.
You believed that crap?
I don't have
any software clients.
Jesus,
you're as naive as Jenny.
Look. If you need some kind
of transition money or something...
What? How?
Does it matter?
What matters
is that you don't help me out.
Okay? I help you out.
And I'm not interested
in transitioning into anything.
Okay.
But the least you could do
is be honest with Jenny.
That's what this
is all about.
- Yeah.
- You always liked her.
I think she deserves
to know the truth.
You always thought
you were better than me.
Maybe that's because I am.
Come on.
We're done.
Don't let the door hit you.
You called Dominic?
He's waiting for us outside.
He's got the speech down?
Yeah, he's got it down.
He better.
I'm taking a big risk on him.
You're taking
a risk on him?
Look at him.
He's scared out of his mind.
He's leaving his comfort zone
because you convinced him to.
So?
So, maybe
some words of encouragement.
The best way to help Dominic
is not to let him second-guess himself.
The most important asset
an attorney has
is his ability
to always be self-assured.
Okay.
Here's what's going to happen.
It's standard for me to prep
the Board on any voting procedure.
When do I speak?
When I tell you to.
Let's go.
I suggested to Stensland
you be there to convince the Board
that production won't be hurt
by an overseas move.
It helps your credibility
that he brought you here,
and it will hurt his
when you challenge him for CEO.
Look, it's natural
to be nervous. Okay?
Just remember,
you know your stuff.
The Board's
never loved Stensland,
and I'm here to back you up.
Okay.
Robert?
Harvey.
You know, I have to admit,
I almost didn't see it coming.
Excuse me?
It was the delay in the due diligence.
It just didn't smell right.
So the only thing
it could be
was that you were going after
my CEO appointment.
So since I'm still within my rights
to move a Board meeting, I did.
I was voted in
today at noon.
And tomorrow, the Board will ratify
the sale of the factory.
And now,
I'm firing your firm.
And I'm firing you.
Try the croissants,
gentlemen.
Marmalade's fantastic.
What are we going to do?
You're going to go
through those bylaws again
and see if there isn't another way
we can stop this sale.
I'm talking about Dominic.
He just lost his job.
He's a grown man.
He made a decision.
Because you convinced him to.
Based on your idea.
Which I recall
you pushed on me at the time.
Because I thought
it would work at the time.
Well, it didn't.
What do you want me to do about it?
Help him.
He's not dying.
He lost his job.
He has to look
for another one.
Which, if he hadn't chosen to fight
for his company in the first place,
would have happened,
anyway.
Now,
show me that you get it,
go back through
those bylaws again,
and see if you missed anything.
Okay?
So this is what happens when you promote
the wrong guy to senior partner.
If you hadn't gone to Stensland behind
my back, this wouldn't have happened.
You don't know that.
And I'm a member of this firm
just as much as you.
I think we both agree
that you're a member.
For your information,
I didn't even...
Louis.
Harvey, eye on the ball.
The issue here
is you tried to torpedo a client...
The client is McKernon Motors,
not Stensland.
You didn't let me finish.
Without my consent.
That trumps the "who's the client" part.
Louis?
Go to Stensland,
repair the relationship.
Say what you have to.
Call it a misunderstanding.
Promise Harvey
is no longer involved.
Consider it done.
Wait a second.
Louis didn't go to Stensland
behind my back.
You sent him there
to hedge your bets.
Either Stensland's out
and we double our billings,
or you have
plausible deniability
and he stays with the firm.
Wow.
Am I smart enough to do that?
If I win, I look great.
If Louis wins,
he looks great.
Either way,
you look great.
You mean the firm looks great.
Harvey, what I've been trying to get
into your head is that you bought in.
You are the firm.
That's it.
Mike. Follow me.
I need you to go talk
to Dominic.
What? Why?
Stensland's already CEO.
That won't matter
if we just buy the damn company.
What?
Why are you still working?
This is one of my creations.
I'm not leaving it
unfinished.
What the hell
do you want?
I'd be happy to tell you
if you put that wrench down.
You're quick with the jokes.
I'm the guy who just got fired.
You're right. I'm sorry.
But what would you say
if I told you
we could get your job back
and stick it to Stensland?
I'm done with Harvey
and his plans. Yeah?
You were there.
We got fired, too.
You and Harvey
still have jobs?
He doesn't care
about anybody but himself.
Including you, Mike.
Yeah. You're probably right.
But he did stick his neck out
to keep your company here.
And he does have an idea
that requires your help.
So you can stay here
and call him an asshole,
or you can come with me
and we can help him.
Give me my goddamn shirt.
You know,
it goes from zero to sixty...
In the blink of an eye.
Did you bring me down here
to tell me I can drive this?
Better. For $250 million dollars,
you can own it.
McKernon Motors
is for sale?
If we act fast.
I'll need to see
the financials.
You put together a letter of intent,
they'll get you the financials.
You know,
their real asset is engine quality.
I don't want to
just buy the name.
Speak of the devil.
Laurence, I'd like you to meet
the man responsible for
every McKernon Motors engine
ever built.
Wow. Dominic Barone.
Very nice to meet you.
Good to meet you. I'd like to show
you something if you have a minute.
Absolutely.
So? How do we get an offer
to the Board
before they vote
to ratify the deal tomorrow?
You're going to go through those bylaws
and you're going
to figure something out.
I don't have to look through them
to figure it out because I just did.
Well,
what took you so long?
Are you trying
to look like me?
Wow.
Each of you had 24 hours
to review the documents in front of you.
So at this time...
Uh, excuse me. Excuse me. What...
What is he doing here?
I'm sorry.
I'm going to take care of this.
No, no, no. I will.
You gentlemen have no right
to attend this meeting.
Actually, we do.
The bylaw states
that any original employee
has the right to petition the Board
any time they meet.
Dominic Barone
has assigned that right to me.
He was fired.
He no longer
has that right.
Per section 17-5.C,
Dominic wasn't given
three days' notice.
So, technically,
he wasn't fired.
Which is why I do have the right
to urge the Board to accept
the offer for the purchase
of McKernon Motors.
Now, I can tell you
that this offer
will keep manufacturing here
and save jobs,
while retaining the flagship engine
that put this company on the map.
But I don't have to,
because it happens to be
for way more goddamn money
than the one
in front of you right now.
Hey, Bob. How are you?
It's funny how you held out on me
on that proper notice exception.
I didn't hold out.
I made that up
on the spot.
Really? On the spot?
You remember that
"getting it" stuff?
I know, right?
I'm getting it.
Well, I was going to say that,
but now, you ruined it.
That's one thing
you definitely get.
How to ruin it.
I heard that.
Nice job, Mike.
I have to admit.
You don't suck.
I wish I could say
the same for you.
Time to pay the piper.
Just so you know, I took the liberty
of ordering some really expensive wines.
Hope that's okay.
Sorry, sir. But the check's been paid
for in full by a Harvey Specter.
There, uh, might have been
some gluten in the ravioli.
I hear McKernon Motors
is getting a new owner.
We're not only
handling the sale,
but with the expansion plan
they're putting in place,
our billables should double.
Nicely done.
I did it for the firm.
What are you doing here?
You were right.
I should never have kept it from you
that Trevor was dealing all that time.
Well, I mean...
It's, uh...
It's all in the past,
right?
No.
What are you
talking about?
He's lying to you.
He's still dealing,
and I'm done with him.
Son of a bitch.
Well, thank you, uh,
for telling me, Mike.
No, don't. Stop.
We're even.
That is the last time
I am ever ratting on anyone.
So if you
fall for it again,
it's on you.
Are you angry with me?
You told me
he would listen to me.
- I thought he would.
- Look, he didn't.
I...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
No, I can't.
I can't.
- What?
- No, I... I...
I fought with him.
It's...
Oh, God.
This is too much.