- Previously, on "Suits"...
- Has ruined Clifford's life.
And if you had been our lawyer,
he never would have been
convicted in the first place.
- What do you want?
- You do two years in prison,
and I won't go after
any of your friends.
- It's the only sure way
to put this to bed
and make sure that
the only person
who is hurt by it is me.
- What about me?
All I did was love you.
- I'm not gonna rat them out.
- I'm not asking you to.
I'm just asking you to
have faith in yourself.
- Don't fall
on your sword again.
- We might not win.
- You don't always
have to be the hero.
- I'm not doing it
to be the hero.
- Then why the hell
are you doing it?
- I would never
send my friends to prison.
- They find me guilty,
they're gonna send my friends
to prison anyways.
- The jury came back.
We have an hour.
- Where's Mike?
- I don't know.
- I'm ready to take your deal.
- Which one?
So just to be clear,
this is the one
you want to go with.
You go to prison for two years,
your friends go free,
and no crying about it
once it's done.
- One stipulation.
- I'm not reducing
your jail time by one minute.
- That's not it.
I want you to write in
that once we sign,
you can't renegotiate
with Harvey.
- Oh, I get it.
You're afraid
I'm gonna use this
to get him to take
the bullet for you.
- I'm not afraid
of you trying to do that,
because I know you will.
So, either put it in,
or we go to verdict.
And just remember,
like you said to me,
tick tock.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- What did you do?
- I did what I had to do.
I pled guilty.
- Bullshit.
You didn't plead anything.
- Harvey, look at me.
It was my crime.
It was my choice to make,
and I made it.
It's done.
- Well, I'm gonna unmake it,
because the judge
hasn't ratified it yet,
and until she does,
nothing is done.
- Harvey, stop.
- No, you listen to me.
If you think I'm gonna
let you do this,
you're out of
your goddamn mind.
- Do what, Mike?
What did you do?
- I took the two years.
- No, no, you didn't.
- Rachel, Rachel,
please.
- I don't accept that.
- Please listen.
It was the only way
that I could--
- No, it wasn't
the only way.
You told me that
you'd wait for the verdict,
and I begged you
to have faith in yourself,
and you told me that you would.
- That was before
I begged Diaz to take a deal
that would rat out his friend,
and he didn't listen to me--
- Wait a second.
You're throwing away
the next two years
of our lives
for something that
some criminal said?
- Just stop. Listen to me.
- Hold on.
Harvey said he wasn't
gonna let this happen.
He went to see the judge,
didn't he?
- It doesn't matter.
He can't stop it.
- Why not?
- Because it's not up to him.
It's up to me,
and I've made my decision.
♪ ♪
Rachel, where are you going?
- Anywhere else.
Because if you're gonna rob us
of the next two years
of our lives,
I am not gonna stand here
and watch you do it.
♪ ♪
- Ms. Gibbs, I don't
appreciate being kept waiting
once the jury has informed us
they've reached a verdict.
- I'm sorry, Your Honor.
Mr. Ross and I were
finalizing a plea agreement.
- I'm sorry too,
Your Honor,
but they haven't
finalized shit.
- What did you just say
in my courtroom?
- You heard what I said.
- My chambers,
right now.
♪ ♪
- Rachel, I heard
the jury is back.
I came down
to hear the verdict.
- There's not gonna be
a verdict,
so you can turn right around,
because Mike took a deal
to spend two years in prison.
- Oh, my God.
- And they're
in there right now
signing off on it.
And I don't know what to do.
- Okay, I'll tell you
what you need to do.
You need to go back inside,
and you need to
be there for him.
- I'm not gonna go back inside
and be there for him.
- Why not?
- Because he told me
that he wasn't
going to do this.
He told me that it was
on the table,
and I begged him
not to take it,
and he promised me
that he wouldn't.
- Rachel, last night
Harvey came to me
wanting to do the same thing,
and I begged him
to have faith in that jury.
- And Harvey kept his word.
- But he might not have,
and I told myself that
if he changed his mind,
I would have to forgive him.
- Then Donna,
you're a better woman
than I am,
because Mike is my heart,
and right now I feel like
someone is ripping my heart
out of my chest,
and that someone--
that someone's him.
♪ ♪
- Your Honor, I don't
give a shit about that deal.
She took advantage
of my client.
She coerced him,
and you have
the power to stop it.
- I've had enough
of your language, Mr. Specter.
- It wasn't coercion.
It was negotiated
by a competent attorney.
It's rock solid,
and there's no basis to stop it.
- He's not
a competent attorney.
He's cutting a deal
to plead guilty to fraud.
- You want to cut
a different deal with me?
I'm all ears.
- Yeah, the only
problem with that
is you can't sign
a different deal,
because you already signed
your rights to that away.
- God damn it, Mike,
don't do this.
We can go to verdict.
- Don't give me that.
You weren't racing
over to her office
to tell her that
the jury was back.
You were going
to jump on the grenade,
and I beat you to it.
Now I told you it's done,
and it's done.
- Are you absolutely sure,
Mr. Ross?
- I am, Your Honor.
- Then, Mr. Ross,
you have 72 hours
to report to
Danbury Federal Prison.
♪ ♪
- ♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
.
- Give it to me straight.
What happened?
- Mike pled guilty,
and in exchange,
they can't go after you,
Harvey, Louis, or any of us.
- Shit.
- For someone
who just found out
she's not going to prison,
you don't seem happy.
- I was never worried
about going to prison, Donna.
- What are you
worried about?
- Losing my firm.
Now that Mike pled guilty,
every case he ever touched
has "lawsuit"
written all over it.
- So what are we
gonna do?
- I'll tell you
what we're going to do.
We're gonna restructure
this firm,
and we're gonna do it
before the lawsuits even start.
Get me Louis.
[tense music]
- Michael.
♪ ♪
- Gloria,
what are you doing here?
- I came here to be with you
for the verdict,
but they told me
you made a deal.
- I did.
- Michael, there's no way
the lord would have
put me through
two innocent men going away.
- But Mrs. Danner,
I'm not innocent,
and I did what
they accused me of.
- I'm not stupid, Michael.
I didn't mean
you went to law school.
I meant you are innocent
in your heart,
and now you've chosen
to go to a place
filled with men who aren't.
- I don't think
you understand.
I'm going to
a white-collar prison.
- There's no such thing
as a white-collar prison
once they close those doors.
You need to hear me.
- Gloria, look, I know
that you are trying to help,
but I took responsibility
for what I did,
and I'm gonna live with it.
But right now,
I need to go spend time
with the woman I love
and make things right,
so I'm sorry,
but you have to excuse me.
♪ ♪
- Robert,
I got your message.
I rushed right over.
What happened to Rachel?
- I'll tell you
what happened.
Mike Ross is going to jail,
my daughter is heartbroken,
and Harvey and Jessica
are getting off scot-free.
- Wait a second.
If you lured me down here
because you wanted
a punching bag,
I can tell you right now,
that's not gonna happen.
- Well, let me tell you
what is gonna happen.
It's about to be
open season on every case
that Mike Ross ever put his
good-for-nothing name on,
and once that happens,
it's just a matter of time
until every one of your
attorneys tries to leave.
- I see what this is.
You want to use me
to start an avalanche
that will bury
Harvey and Jessica.
Guess what?
I'm not gonna do it.
- Then you're a bigger fool
than I thought,
because I'm gonna
find someone that will.
- Good luck with that,
because have a noncompete.
- Not anymore,
you don't.
- Bullshit.
You're bluffing.
- Then why don't you go and ask
your ex-associate Katrina?
Because she's
the one that gave me
the way around it
in the first place.
♪ ♪
- Harvey, I heard
about Mike.
I am so sorry.
- Well, you can
stop being sorry
and get me the name
of that jury foreman.
- Harvey, you can't
get a mistrial.
It's too late.
Mike cut a deal.
- I don't need
legal advice, Donna.
I need the name and address
of that foreman.
- I don't think
that's a good idea.
- It's not breaking
the law anymore, Donna.
It's just a favor.
I'm not gonna ruin his life.
I just need to ask him
a goddamn question.
- Well, I'm not gonna do that
until you tell me
what that question is.
- Donna...
Mike just threw
his whole life away,
and there's nothing
I can do about it,
and the only way
that I can accept it
is if I find out
what that verdict was gonna be.
- I'll get you the name.
♪ ♪
- Robert Zane just told me
he can take away
our noncompete.
I need you to tell me right now
how he's gonna do that.
- Nice to see you too, Louis.
Can I offer you a prunie?
- No, I don't need
a damn prunie.
I need you to tell me
what he's up to.
- Louis, I'm here now,
and the reason I'm here
is that I got fired
for helping you,
and even though you promised
to bring me back
once you were named partner,
you didn't.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I wanted to bring you back,
Katrina, more than anything.
- Don't give me that, Louis.
I covered for you
after Sheila dumped you.
I helped you poach VersaLife.
I even forged
government documents for you.
- Okay, Katrina,
if I wanted to bring you back,
I couldn't protect you--
- From what?
From finding out
Mike Ross is a fraud?
Yeah, I did the math, Louis,
and you couldn't have
protected me from it,
but you could use it
to get your name on the door,
couldn't you?
Are you gonna look me in the eye
and tell me that isn't true?
♪ ♪
- It's true.
- Well, I appreciate
your honesty.
Since you were honest with me,
I'll be honest with you.
I can't help you.
♪ ♪
- Are you okay?
- No.
- Rachel...
- I just don't
understand, Mike.
You told me you'd wait
for the verdict.
- I know.
Rachel, listen to me,
all right?
I didn't do this to hurt you.
I did it because
it's who I am.
- I know that.
- Then why are you
holding it against me?
- Because I can't stand
the thought of losing you.
- You're not gonna lose me.
- Yes, I am, Mike,
for two years.
- And it could have been seven.
- It could have been zero.
- They took--
- Why couldn't you
just wait for the verdict?
- Because I have to
live with myself
for the rest of my life.
I made a decision,
and I...
I can't go back in time
and change it.
But we are here right now,
all right?
We have--we have
three days left.
- I'm gonna have to take
one of those days for myself...
Because you promised me
that you would
have faith in yourself.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
And you didn't.
[machinery buzzing]
- You remember me?
- How could I not?
I listened to you for
the better part of two weeks.
- Then I'll get right to it.
I need a favor.
- You got a truck
needs fixing?
- I want to know what
that verdict was gonna be.
- No, you don't.
- Yeah, I do.
- What difference
does it make?
- It makes all the difference
in the world.
- Then I'll tell you,
'cause I've been dying
to tell somebody,
'cause it was
"12 Angry Men" in there,
and I was the one.
Yeah, that's right.
One by one,
I put that jury on my back
and we did the right thing.
- What's the right thing?
- You think I don't
know what's what?
That kid didn't
go to law school.
You know it,
I know it,
everybody in
the goddamn room knew it.
- It was guilty.
- I didn't say that.
That woman didn't
make her case,
and I'm not letting
my country's justice system
go to shit on my watch.
- Say it.
- Not guilty.
♪ ♪
They told us you guys
cut some kind of deal.
Guess you should have had a
little more faith in the system.
♪ ♪
.
[elevator bell dings]
- Mr. Specter?
Mr. Specter.
- Mrs. Danner,
what can I do for you?
- I tried to talk to Michael,
but he wouldn't listen.
- Talk to him about what?
- About what's gonna happen
to him inside that prison.
- Mrs. Danner, I appreciate
you coming down here,
but I can't talk
about this right now.
- I don't care.
You're gonna listen
to what I have to say,
because I saw what prison
did to my son, Mr. Specter.
Michael needs to know
what his first day
is gonna be like,
who to make friends with,
what guards to stay away from,
because it's the guards
that are the worst.
- You think I don't
know all that?
- Then do something
to toughen up that boy.
- I told you, I can't talk
about this right now.
- Go ahead.
Walk away.
But you owe me.
Because you may have
gotten him out,
but you're also the one
who put him in that hellhole
in the first place.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Louis, where the hell
have you been?
We have a problem.
- You think I don't know that?
- I need you to
bifurcate the firm
into two entities,
and I need you to do it now.
- I know what
you're thinking.
If we insulate our clients,
we can hold on to our lawyers,
but that won't help.
- Why the hell not?
- Because Robert Zane
has a way to bust
our noncompete.
- God damn it.
He finds somebody
to jump ship,
it'll be a stampede
for the exits.
- That's what I'm trying
to tell you.
- All right, then forget
about splitting the firm
and work on figuring out
what the hell he's up to,
or there won't be
a firm left to split.
♪ ♪
- I need to talk to you.
- I can't, Mike,
not now.
- Harvey, I need
to know if you think
I did the right thing
taking that plea.
- God damn it,
you ask me that now?
- Rachel can't
get past the fact
that I didn't wait
for the verdict to come in.
It's tearing her up,
and that's tearing me up.
- Mike--
- Harvey, I know
that you are pissed
that I made a deal before you,
but I need you to tell me
that I made the right call.
♪ ♪
- You did.
- How can you be sure?
- Because I went
to see the foreman,
and he told me
the verdict was guilty.
- What?
- Look, the idea of you going
to prison was killing me,
and I couldn't let it go
unless I knew.
- But now you can.
- I still wish
you would have
let me take the hit
instead of you,
but yeah, I can.
Go home, Mike.
Get whatever time left
you have with Rachel.
- It's gonna be easier now.
I never thought the word
"guilty" would do that.
♪ ♪
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
- Can I get you anything?
- Yeah.
Clear your schedule
for the rest of the day.
I need you to get me
everything there is to get
from Mike's trial.
- Harvey, I don't understand.
You said if you talked
to that foreman,
you would be able
to make peace with this.
- I don't care what I said.
- And he said
that Mike was guilty,
and Mike accepted
those consequences.
- He didn't say
Mike was guilty.
He said he was
goddamn innocent.
♪ ♪
- Oh, my God.
He's going away for nothing.
- No, Donna, he's not
going away at all.
- What do you need me to do?
- I need you to get me
everything we have
on that trial,
because I'm gonna
figure out a way
to invalidate
that goddamn deal.
♪ ♪
- Jessica, do you
have a minute?
- I'm really busy
right now, Jack.
- I'm afraid this can't wait.
[sighs]
I'm officially giving you
my letter of resignation.
- Let me guess.
Robert Zane made you an offer.
- He did,
and as much as
I didn't want to take it,
I have to.
- Oh, you have to?
You begged me
for a second chance
and a third
and a fourth,
and I gave them all to you,
and now he's using you
to destroy us.
- We're already destroyed.
You just don't
want to accept it.
- No, this is a setback.
- I'm sorry.
- Jack.
I think you're forgetting
about that folder you gave me,
the one with the little
legal indiscretion
Daniel Hardman had on you.
- Let's not
soft-pedal it, Jessica.
It wasn't an indiscretion.
It was a flat-out crime.
And the problem
with you using it is,
you'll be announcing
to the world
yet another crime
happened under your watch,
and you did nothing to stop it.
And whatever clients were
willing to stay with you before
won't be willing to anymore.
♪ ♪
- I think I'm gonna
miss this the most.
- Miss what?
- Coming home to you.
Rachel, I know I should have
told you what I was gonna do
before I made that deal,
but I didn't know
I was gonna do it,
and I had, like, three seconds
to make a decision.
- And those three seconds
took away two whole years.
- Actually,
gave us back five.
- What are you talking about?
- Harvey found
the jury foreman.
They were gonna
find me guilty.
[stirring music]
- And we only had three days,
and I took away one of them.
- Hey, it's okay.
Rachel, I don't care.
As long as we're good.
- I don't want us
to just be good.
♪ ♪
I want us to be one.
I want to be your wife
before you go.
♪ ♪
- I want to be your husband.
.
- Okay, I got us
some coffees and--
- Donna, what the hell?
This isn't everything.
- What do you mean,
this isn't everything?
- I mean, she had to
have filed motions
and subpoenas and discovery,
and all this shit is nothing.
- Harvey, these boxes are--
- What?
This is his class ranking
that he wasn't on.
This is his transcript.
This is his yearbook.
Where are the things that
we can attack procedurally?
- They're over there.
- Then why haven't you
gone through them?
- Because that's
not what I do.
- Then what in God's name
are you doing in here?
- I'm supporting you, Harvey,
and right now,
I'm gonna do that
by giving you some space.
[dramatic music]
- If you think you can
waltz into my firm
and take my lawyers,
you must be out
of your damn mind.
- Let me guess,
you're suing me for inducement.
- You bet your ass I am.
You induced Jack Soloff
into breaking his noncompete.
- You don't have a noncompete
with Jack Soloff or anyone else.
- I heard you tried
that empty threat with Louis,
but it's not gonna
work with me.
- If it is empty,
then so is your morals clause
and your bylaws,
which states that if
a named partner
participates in a crime,
any partner is free to go.
And conspiracy to commit fraud
is a goddamn crime.
- You can't prove
we knew about Mike Ross.
- Well, let me suggest
that you ask Louis Litt
about his conversation with
Katrina Bennett this morning.
I got you, Jessica,
and if you want
to come after me
for hiring Jack,
or anyone for hiring anyone,
you may not go to jail,
but the world is gonna
know what you did.
[tense music]
- Why are you
doing this, Robert?
- I don't give a shit about
you hiring a fraud, Jessica,
but you never came to me with it
once he started dating Rachel.
- How could I have known
I could have trusted you
not to come after my firm?
- That picture on Robert's desk
is how you could have known,
Jessica.
Now if you'll excuse us,
we have tickets for the theater.
♪ ♪
- Sorry about before, Donna.
- It's okay, Harvey.
I understand.
And I've been thinking we're
going about this all wrong.
- What do you mean?
- I mean appealing something
based on legal minutiae
isn't what you do.
- And what exactly
is it that I do?
- You get people to do things
they don't want to
by giving them something else.
- Donna, I can't
do that with Gibbs,
because what
she really wants is me,
and Mike won't let me.
- And what if you
give her something bigger?
- What are you talking about?
- I'm talking
about Liberty Rail.
- No.
- Harvey, if we're willing
to let me be prosecuted
for what I did,
then you can give Gibbs
people who committed murder
and get Mike off the hook.
Two for one.
- Donna, I am not
trading you for Mike.
Period.
- Then what are we gonna do?
- We're gonna
give Gibbs her murderers
without giving you up at all.
♪ ♪
- Louis, tell me right now.
Did you admit to Katrina Bennett
that you knew about Mike Ross?
- The morals clause.
- God damn it.
- Jessica, she already knew.
- Her knowing
and you flat-out confessing
aren't the same thing.
- It doesn't matter.
She can't prove it.
- Louis, don't you get it?
Katrina Bennett
was your protégé.
All that underhanded
shit that you do,
she learned all of it.
- What are you saying?
- I'm saying
that she recorded you,
and if that tape
ever sees the light of day,
any partner who wants
can walk out that door
and take their clients
with them.
- No, they can't.
- Where are you going?
- To the file room.
You're right, Jessica.
Katrina was my protégé,
and she knows
all my dirty laundry,
but I also know hers.
♪ ♪
- Let me take care of it.
- I don't think so.
- After the way
we ended things last time,
it's the least I can do.
- What do you want, Harvey?
- I want Liberty Rail.
- Well, that's
never gonna happen,
and you need
to let that shit go.
- What I need
is to trade that shit
for Mike Ross's freedom.
- What the hell
are you talking about?
- You give me Liberty Rail,
I'll give you
five of my best clients.
- There's no way Jessica Pearson
allows that to happen.
- It's not her call.
They're my clients.
- Well, I don't care,
because I'm not
breaking privilege
and risking my entire career
in exchange for five clients.
[tense music]
- What's it gonna take?
- You want my price?
I want to go shopping
at Pearson Specter Litt.
Exclusive access
to hire anyone I want,
from paralegals
to senior partners
and their clients,
for the next month.
- You'd be gutting the firm.
- Do I look like I care?
- There is no way
Jessica accepts this,
and you know it.
- What I know is,
people will do anything
if they're desperate enough.
And if you're
in here doing this,
then you're desperate
to save Mike Ross.
♪ ♪
- Michael, if you're here
to see Robert,
he's already gone.
- I'm not here to see Robert.
I'm here to see you.
- Well, I'd rather you go.
- Laura, please.
- Please what, Michael?
Robert and I
were ready to embrace
the man who was going
to marry our daughter,
and it turns out,
that man is a liar.
And now you're here to get me
to convince my husband
to go to your wedding?
- It's not just my wedding.
It's also Rachel's.
- And I can talk to Robert
until I'm blue in the face.
He will never forgive you.
- He doesn't need
to forgive me, all right?
He just needs to be there
for his daughter.
- He's not gonna do that.
- Why not?
- Because you're
ruining her life.
- Look, Laura, I know that
I made a horrible mistake.
I'm going away for two years,
when I could have
gotten out of it
by turning in my friends.
Rachel knows that's
the kind of man that I am.
That's why she wants to spend
the rest of her life with me.
Now all--
all I am asking you
is that you
help Robert see that.
- I know my husband.
What you're asking
is impossible,
and I don't expect you
to understand that,
because you've never been
the father of a daughter.
♪ ♪
But I'll try.
- I don't understand.
- Of course you don't,
because you've also never been
the mother of a daughter.
♪ ♪
- Louis.
What are you doing here?
- Why'd you do it?
- Do what?
- Don't be coy
with me, Katrina.
It's one thing
to share our bylaws,
but I know you recorded me,
and I want to know why.
- I did it because
it put my name
on the map with Robert Zane.
- If you don't
destroy that recording,
it's gonna put your name
on the map somewhere else.
- This is a copy of
the document I forged for you.
- Yeah, the one you
reminded me of yesterday,
the same one that
I'm gonna give to the SEC
if you don't back off.
- You don't have to do this.
You can still
come work with us.
- No, I can't,
and even if I wanted to,
I can't trust you anymore.
- That's not fair.
If it wasn't me,
it would've been somebody else.
- But it was you, Katrina.
My own protégé
stabbing me in the back?
- I was just trying
to make a name for myself.
- And I just wanted
my name on the wall,
but let me tell you something.
If there's one thing
that I have learned,
it's not worth being
willing to do anything
to make a name for yourself.
♪ ♪
- Jessica,
I need to talk to you.
- Harvey, before you ask
whatever you're about to ask,
I'm not in the mood.
- Well, that's not
gonna cut it.
I need you to waive
our noncompetes for Evan Smith.
- Is this a joke?
- It's the only way
to keep Mike out of prison.
- There is no way
- Yes, there is.
We give Evan people
who already want to go,
and I give Anita Gibbs
murderers in exchange for Mike.
- And I've just spent
the last 24 hours
fighting to keep
our noncompetes.
- Jessica.
- No.
He cut a deal
to save this firm.
- He cut a deal to keep us
from going to prison,
and you know it.
- You know,
I don't give a shit
what he thought
when he made that deal.
- He was gonna be
found innocent.
♪ ♪
- What?
- I went to see the foreman.
The verdict was
gonna be not guilty.
♪ ♪
- Then let me see
your deal with Gibbs.
- I don't have it yet.
- Are you crazy?
You're asking me
to decimate my firm
for a deal you don't even
know she'll take?
- I'll make her take the deal.
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do.
Jessica, we have
a chance to save Mike
and let the people
who want to go, go.
- And what if it doesn't work
and we lose everything?
- Then we do.
Jessica, Harvey's right.
Mike's family.
Even if we lose half the firm,
if we don't try to save him,
who are we?
♪ ♪
- Make the deal.
.
[knocking at door]
- Da--
- Where is he?
- He's not here.
- Well, that's too bad
because I came here
to talk to him,
even though he didn't
have the balls to talk to me.
- He wasn't afraid
to talk to you.
He went to Mom
because I asked him to.
- Oh, okay.
Okay, let's down to this.
You marry him,
and that man ruins your life.
- How, Dad?
We're gonna get through
the next two years and then--
- And then what?
Because you're sure as shit
not gonna be a lawyer.
- What are you
talking about?
- I'm talking about
you graduating,
and then you're gonna
stand before
the Character and Fitness
Committee of the Bar.
And the last time I checked,
marrying a man
that defrauded them
isn't gonna get you in.
- Okay, and by the time
that happens,
he will have served his time,
and we will have paid his debt.
- What the hell difference
does that make?
- The difference is that's what
our justice system is all about,
and standing behind
the man that you love
is the definition
of character and fitness.
- Okay, you tell them that,
and they're gonna tell
you and your felon husband
to go to hell.
- That's not gonna happen.
- Oh, yes it is,
God damn it!
These are vindictive
and protective people,
and he make them
look like fools.
- This isn't about
me not becoming a lawyer
or him ruining my life
or any of this other bullshit
that you're in here saying.
This is because
he pulled one over on you.
- He can't be trusted!
[tense music]
- Dad, I'm sorry
that I kept this from you,
but he didn't
keep it from me,
and I'm telling you
I can trust him.
- And how can I trust you?
♪ ♪
- Wow, um...
Well, if you can't,
then maybe you shouldn't
come to the wedding.
♪ ♪
- Well, that about sums it up.
- I'm proud of you, Michael.
It's not easy
to resist the temptation
to make a deal
that saves yourself.
- Well, as far as
I'm concerned,
I did make a deal
that saves myself.
But I didn't just come here
to make you proud.
I came to ask a favor.
- Name it.
- Rachel and I want
to get married before I go.
I know it's not
supposed to happen
for another
couple of months but--
- You don't have
that kind of time.
- Look, I promise it's not
gonna be too much trouble.
We're not gonna
invite too many people.
- I'd be honored, Michael.
- Thank you, Father.
♪ ♪
- Michael, since you're not
inviting many people,
we don't have to
do it in here.
We could always do it
in the small chapel.
- I appreciate that, Father,
but my mom and dad weren't
married in the small chapel.
♪ ♪
- Okay, you're here.
What's so important I had to
reschedule an arraignment
to meet with you?
- Because that arraignment
wasn't gonna lead to you
putting corporate murderers
behind bars.
- Let me guess.
You got a hold of some
incriminating documents,
and you want me
to prosecute these people
in exchange for keeping
Mike Ross out of jail.
- Murder for fraud,
straight up.
- Not interested.
- Listen to me.
Compared to this,
what Mike Ross did
barely constitutes
spitting on a sidewalk.
- I know that.
- Then what the hell
is wrong with you?
- I'll tell you
what's wrong with me.
You.
You've been bending the rules
since the day you were born,
and I'm not letting you
get away with it anymore.
- Are you kidding me?
You bent rules up and down
this entire case.
- Except the difference
between you and me is,
I'm bending them
to get justice.
- Putting these people away
is justice.
- Then give them to me anyway.
That's right.
You've been keeping this case
in your back pocket
waiting for a rainy day,
because that's what you do.
So maybe the next time
you have a chance
to put away murderers,
you'll do it
instead of saving it up
for a chit down the road.
- You hate me that much?
- I don't hate you,
but you did this,
and you can try to
get out of it,
but what you can't do anymore
is deny you did it.
- I'm not trying
to get out of this.
I'd take the punishment for him.
- You had plenty
of chances to do that,
but you waited
until it was too late.
Now, you want to keep Mike
out of prison?
You have to convince him
to let you take his place.
♪ ♪
- What are you doing here?
- [sighs]
Harvey, I want
to talk to you.
- Good, because I want
- I want you to be my best man.
- What?
- Rachel and I
want to get married.
- You're less than
a day from prison,
and you're thinking about
dresses and flowers?
- Harvey--
- You know what?
I'll be your best man
on one condition.
- That ship has sailed.
- The hell it has.
We can still call Gibbs.
- I am not calling Gibbs.
- Get it through your head.
This is on me.
- No, you get it
through your head.
I am not letting you
go to prison
for a crime that I committed.
- Well, I'm not letting you go
when you were gonna be
found innocent.
[tense music]
- What did you say?
- That's right,
I lied.
The verdict was not guilty.
- No, I don't believe you.
- Then call the goddamn guy.
- Why the hell
would you lie to me?
- Because the truth
would have broken you.
- Oh, except now
you want to break me?
- Because it's the only way
you're gonna let me do this.
You think putting a ring
on Rachel's finger
is gonna make
everything go away?
- You know what, Harvey?
You want to come to my wedding,
you let me know.
♪ ♪
[glass shattering]
- You want to go to prison?
Rule number one:
never turn your back on anyone.
- I know what you're doing,
and it's not gonna work.
- I'm not trying to
take your place anymore.
I'm trying to get you ready
like Gloria Danner asked me to.
- Harvey--
- Because you're weak.
- I am not weak.
- Yeah, well, hit me.
- No.
- Hit me.
- Harvey, stop it.
- Listen.
- No, you listen to me.
- You think you're not weak?
- You're only doing this
because you feel guilty,
all right?
- Louis Litt got you
in a headlock.
- But I am not gonna
hit you just because...
- Tess's husband
kicked your ass.
- You can't handle the fact--
- Logan Sanders
hooked up with Rachel.
- Stop right now.
- What do you think
he's gonna
do with her
the second you get--
- Is that what you want?
That I hate you,
and that you made me do this?
I'm gonna lose everything
because of you!
- [groans]
- [panting]
[dark music]
♪ ♪
[sobbing]
- Mike, please.
Let's call Gibbs.
♪ ♪
- I can't.
I can't, Harvey.
I can't.
♪ ♪
- What are you doing?
- Sometimes I like
to come and just watch.
- See how far you've come?
- Oh, something like that.
- Gibbs didn't take
the deal, Jessica.
I'm sorry,
I was wrong.
- No, Louis,
you were right.
He's family,
and we had to try.
And whoever's left,
we'll be stronger,
even if we're smaller.
♪ ♪
- I'm sorry, Mike.
I shouldn't have told you
the truth about the verdict.
- I probably shouldn't have
hit you all those times.
- It's okay.
Makes me feel better
knowing you have it in you.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
I got to go.
[sighs]
I got to ask Rachel
to marry me.
- I thought you were
already getting married.
- There's something
I got to tell her first.
♪ ♪
- You come here to gloat?
Because tonight
is not the night.
- No, Robert.
I came here to make peace.
You were right.
I should have come to you,
and I'm sorry I didn't,
and I will regret that
for the rest of my life.
But I understand Rachel is
getting married tomorrow,
and I'm telling you,
if you're not there for her,
you will regret it
for the rest of yours.
♪ ♪
.
[keys clattering]
- Rachel?
- I'm in the bedroom.
Don't come in.
- Why?
What's wrong?
- No, nothing's wrong.
I-I have my dress on.
- Rachel,
come on, please.
- There are about a million
things with this wedding
that aren't going as planned,
and I'm fine with that,
but I'm not gonna jinx it
by having you
see me in my dress.
- Rachel, I was wrong
about the verdict.
Harvey lied to me.
They were gonna
find me not guilty.
Rachel,
please open the door.
- Why are you
telling me this right now?
- Because you only
wanted to get married
after you found out
I was guilty,
and I didn't want
to start our life out
with another secret.
You were right.
I should have
had faith in myself,
and I didn't.
If you don't want
to do this now,
I understand.
We can do it when I get out.
- In my mind,
you are out,
and no one knows
what's gonna happen
after they get married.
They just know
what's gonna happen
the day that they do.
And the day we're
getting married is tomorrow.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[laughs softly]
- I don't think I've ever
seen a more beautiful bride.
- That's good,
because I have never seen
a more beautiful maid of honor.
[laughs softly]
- So I don't want
to bother you,
but I just wanted to come in
and give you a little bit
of an early wedding present.
- Donna, you don't
have to do that.
- Your mom and dad are here.
- Thank you.
- Oh, don't thank me.
Thank Jessica.
- Um...I'm gonna go
and put my necklace on
before I make my mascara run.
- Okay, I'll just be outside.
- No, no, please,
I would, um...
I'd rather you stay.
Okay.
♪ ♪
- Donna, can I talk
to Rachel for a second?
- Mike, you can't.
You can't see her
before the ceremony.
- Donna, please.
♪ ♪
- Okay, Donna, can you
just help me put--
- [laughs softly]
Mike, you can't see me
in my dress.
- Rachel, we can't do this.
- What?
♪ ♪
- I just walked in
and I saw your parents.
They're here
because they have to be,
not because they want to be.
- Mike--
- It wasn't just the look
on your father's face.
It's the look
on your mother's.
They think I'm taking away
your future.
♪ ♪
- You are my future.
- Hey, hey.
I am not saying that
I don't want to get married.
I'm just saying
that if for some reason
I was responsible
for taking away your dream...
- That you'd never be able
to live with yourself.
- You go finish
law school, okay?
And you pass the bar,
and you become a lawyer,
and then...in two years
when I get out,
if you still
want to marry me...
♪ ♪
- Oh, I will.
Of course I will.
[sighs]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
How'd you know?
- I knew,
and there's no way
I'm letting you
do this alone.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- They're all gone.
- It's not your fault, Harvey.
I made my case.
I convinced you to hire me.
- I was the one
that made the call.
- You were.
But it doesn't matter.
'Cause even knowing
how it all turned out...
I'd do it again.
- I guess I would too,
'cause I never thought
in a million years
I'd meet someone dumb enough
to be willing
to go to prison for me.
- I mean,
Donna always said
you were looking
for another you.
I guess you found one.
[poignant music]
♪ ♪
I guess it's time to
get busy living
and get busy dying.
♪ ♪
- Well, that's goddamn right.
- Watch your back
in there, Mike.
♪ ♪
- I will.
[gate buzzing]
♪ ♪
[gate slams]
[dark music]
♪ ♪