Mike: Previously on Suits...
You looked me in the eye,
and told me that your hood
was rock solid?
You make it right on your own,
or I will.
You want to settle?
Let me save you some time.
We pass. You think I don't know
this was your doing?
Daniel Hardman doesn't work you.
You work him.
What did Hardman
find in those files?
I don't know, and I don't care.
I'm entitled to name one
new senior partner a year.
I'm naming you.
You think he's valuing you.
He's buying you.
Hardman actually sees me!
You kept me waiting five years.
You can wait another 24 hours.
It's your grandma.
She passed away.
No.
Either Jessica
will retain her position,
or I will resume control
of Pearson Hardman.
Well...
in a few minutes, we'll know.
Last time we spoke,
there was a lot of talk about
peeling each other
off the walls.
I just want to say...
Stop talking.
As you wish.
[Door opens]
[Clears throat]
What are you doing here?
Rachel, meet the file room.
It's where we store information
on the cases
that we're working on.
No, I-I just mean,
I don't believe that Harvey
would make you come and work
the day after...
You can say it.
[Sighs]
Okay, I'll say it.
The day after
my grandmother died.
And Harvey doesn't know.
What? Why?
'Cause,
there's a vote going on,
and he's got bigger things
on his mind.
- Mike, he'd want to know.
- Oh, really, you know that?
You and... you and Harvey
are best friends now?
Okay, then tell Donna.
Just tell somebody that...
I don't want people to know.
If you tell people,
they will understand,
and then you can go home,
and you can really deal with...
Deal with what, Rachel?
The fact that I missed
my last-ever chance
to see my grandmother
because I was too busy at work?
Oh, come on, that's not fair.
You were an amazing grandson.
You... you were buying
her an apartment...
I bought her an apartment
because I felt guilty
for not having seen her
for two months.
No, you were buying
her an apartment because...
This is not a debate, Rachel.
All right, I came to work
because I want to work.
I'm not telling people because
I don't want to talk about it.
And now I'm gonna go out
and get some fresh air,
and when I get back,
I really hope
you will be done bothering me.
The managing partner...
is Daniel Hardman.
[Murmuring]
Effective immediately.
[Clapping]
I want to thank you for
trusting me with
the future of this firm.
I won't let you down.
Let's get back to work.
Harvey...
a word.
I know that we have
a rocky history,
but I would be
a fool not to recognize
your value to this firm.
Daniel, you won.
You don't need
to blow smoke up my ass.
I'm not blowing smoke.
I told you this
from the day I came back,
that I was us to find
a way to work together.
Why say this to me
and not Jessica?
I will.
But her name is on the door.
She's not going anywhere.
I want to make sure that you're
not going anywhere either.
It's time to go.
I can name 12 partners
who will follow you anywhere.
We can have every associate
in the place.
Harvey...
we're not going anywhere.
We have a non-compete clause.
We quit, we can't practice law
in New York for a year.
Contracts
were made to be broken.
Not when they're written by me.
Well, maybe we should take
a year off.
- How would that go?
- You could teach.
- I could also kill myself.
- You could write a book.
- Next.
- What about travel?
You have the means.
See the world.
Teaching, writing, traveling.
You know what
you're talking about?
Running.
I'm not running.
We can't stay here.
Not working for him.
Yes, we can.
We are going
to swallow our pride,
and we're going to wait
until we can make a move
from a position of strength.
That's your tactic?
Holding your head down
and waiting?
That's what he did.
It took him five years.
Do you really think it's gonna
take him five years
to screw up again?
I bet it'll be more
like five minutes.
- Jessica...
- That's enough.
This happened today. Today.
We just took the hit.
We suffered a loss,
and you don't make
major life decisions
when you're reeling
from a loss.
I wanna buy some weed.
[Chuckles]
Sorry, man, you got
it wrong, but, uh,
hey, if you want a paper,
I'll be...
I'm not a cop, okay?
I know for a fact
that you're a dealer.
I've seen you here
every single day.
I know the drill.
A guy comes up,
he hands you a $100 bill,
he walks away with a folded
newspaper full of weed.
Well, I have money.
If you don't want it,
I'll be happy to take it
to the coffee cart
down at 50th and Lex
who we both know
is your competition.
Have a great day.
Yeah.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus so busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ All right
♪ all that time imagine this ♪
♪ The greenback boogie
Don't you dare touch his balls.
What the hell?
These bozos walked in here
right after the vote.
We're moving to the 46th floor.
You and Paul Porter
are switching.
Hardman.
Bowties have no place here!
All that bullshit
about working together?
You forgot to mention
that it was down
on the 46th floor.
It's just four walls, Harvey.
Yeah, so is a prison cell,
which is where you send people
to be punished.
Paul Porter was loyal to me
long before
we were Pearson Hardman.
I reward people
who are loyal to me.
Show me you are
one of those people.
It's one thing
to become king of the hill.
It's another to stay there.
Accept this with grace, Harvey.
You want grace?
I'll give you the courtesy
you never gave me.
I'll say it to your face.
I'm coming for you.
What were you doing in there?
Kissing the ring?
Don't try to weasel your way in
with another managing partner.
That job's already taken.
Daniel. You wanted to see me.
Don't mind if I do.
Louis, this firm has been
through a divisive fight.
Of which you were victorious.
We were victorious.
Unfortunately,
it's not a victory unless
we're united moving forward.
- That is so true.
- Jessica's a class act.
She'll take the defeat
in stride.
She's not the problem.
What do you need?
You made me senior partner.
I always pay my debts.
I'm a Lannister.
The problem is her pitbull.
Well, Harvey can be polarizing.
But I can't just fire him.
He's a senior partner.
Uh, I'm sorry, fire him?
Do you have
a problem with that?
Louis, he just came in here
and announced he's putting
a target on my back.
You voted for me.
That means there's
a target on your back too.
Tell me what to do.
Oh!
[Grunts] You have
to stop doing that.
Well, you weren't at your desk,
so I figured you and your small
bladder would be here.
These cases,
they're a priority.
- Fine.
- Do you know what that means?
Yes, I know what
the word priority means.
Well, you're gonna
get them done
before you even consider
doing anything for Harvey.
You don't get him a file,
you don't bring him a coffee,
you don't buy him his hair gel...
That's not what I do for him.
Right, like he buys
his own hair gel.
Doesn't matter.
You don't do anything
for him now.
You're just like everyone else.
You belong to me.
- I don't belong to anyone.
- Well, then quit.
Your days are numbered
here anyway.
You don't get this shit done,
I'm gonna fire you myself.
[Clicks tongue] Tch.
It's either me or the movers,
and at least I know
where my hands have been.
[Tape dispensing]
I need more packing tape.
Oh, it's right over there.
I know.
Wow, there's
a first for everything.
The mighty Donna,
nothing to say.
Trouble in paradise?
- Louis, get out.
- I'm not afraid of you.
Okay, listen...
I've, uh, been asked
to redistribute the workload.
Jessica focused too much
on the flash.
These cases won't make
The New York Times,
but they'll definitely bankroll
our bonuses.
It's an employee retirement
income security act case.
You know what that means?
I know what ERISA is, Louis.
Oh, good, so you won't mind
the detail-oriented nature
of the assignment.
I won't mind it at all.
[Claps] Great.
By the way, Harvey,
if you're planning
on pawning this off to Mike,
well, you can't.
Mike's focus has been too, um...
Harvey-centric.
So I assigned
our resident wunderkind
some cases of his own.
Auf wiedersehen.
You look overwhelmed.
Let me help.
Forget that.
You're gonna do this instead.
Louis said I'm not allowed
to prioritize your work anymore.
You think I'm taking orders
from Louis now?
Consider things status quo.
Yeah, well, they aren't.
They are as far as
you and I are concerned.
I give you work,
and you're gonna do it.
Oh, right, I forgot.
That's how it works with us.
Don't pout.
You're gonna love this case.
It's very detail-oriented.
And what are you doing?
Operation "Right the ship."
[Scoffs] Maybe it's time
that you just accept
that it's over.
You lost. Deal with it.
Excuse me?
[Scoffs]
You seem to live
in this deluded world
where you think
that you can always win.
But sometimes you can't.
Bad things happen.
You have to face
the fact that life is gonna be
this case or this case
or this case!
Jessica lost! You lost!
And there isn't anything
that any of us,
including the great and powerful
Harvey Specter, can do about it.
Go home.
Now.
[Rock music]
♪
Oh. [Knocking at door]
[Coughs]
Ugh.
[Bottle rolls]
[Grunts] Uh.
Yeah?
Okay, you're clearly
not ready to go.
What? Come on, the funeral
doesn't start for another...
- oh, shit!
- It's okay.
It's okay. Uh, can I wear this?
- Here, drink this.
- Okay.
You're gonna get in the
shower, and I'm gonna find you
something to wear, okay?
Mmhmm. Okay.
Oh.
- Mike?
- Yeah?
Is this a great idea?
Rachel, it's one night, okay?
Please, take it easy on me.
It looks like
more than one night.
[Sighs]
You're right.
[Toilet flushing]
Thanks, Rachel.
I'll be out in five, okay?
Okay.
Donna.
[Buzz]
[Office chatter]
Donna. [Buzz, buzz]
[Office chatter] Donna!
I'm sorry,
but apparently Paul Porter
doesn't believe in technology.
Look, I need
the employment survey.
Yeah, I'm working on it.
It's not done?
It's a survey of all 50 states.
You gotta get on this.
Mike could have done it
in his sleep.
I'm sorry I don't have
a photographic memory,
but my brain is already
too busy being awesome.
Well, what about one
of the other associates?
Which one?
- You know.
- Do I?
- The blonde one.
- Oh, of course.
- Then the brunette.
- Male? Female?
Yes.
You don't know a single
one of their names, do you?
- Mike Ross.
- Ha-ha. [Snaps]
Do I need to remind you
that you're the one
who sent him home yesterday?
I thought he would come back.
You know,
you could call him, Harvey.
Just get me anyone.
What?
No one's available.
- Why not?
- No one's available... to you.
Louis.
He's trying to bait me.
What are you gonna do about it?
Nothing.
Today is not the day
he's gonna see me sweat.
Mike, I'm sorry, but...
It's time.
I can't. I just...
Look, I know it's hard,
but if you don't go up there
and say something, there...
There's just no one else.
There's no...
none of these people
even know her.
You're not speaking for them.
You're speaking for you.
Everyone is gone.
Not everyone.
Tess?
Mike.
- How did you...
- My mom.
I'm so sorry.
What's going on?
- He doesn't want to speak.
- I can't.
You can.
What's your name?
- Rachel.
- Mike,
Rachel and I
are gonna be right here.
You can do this.
I promise, you're gonna feel
so much better after.
Or you'll feel
a hundred times worse.
[Chuckles]
Either way, you gotta do it.
Okay.
I, uh... remember things.
I remember the night that my
parents were taken away from me.
I remember my grandmother
taking me in.
She came to check on me.
It was, uh...
It was the middle
of the night, and...
I had wet the bed.
And she cleaned the sheets, !
And she... she cleaned me all up,
and she put me
in her bed, and, uh...
you know, I... started to cry.
Really hard, and, uh...
and she said,
"It's okay, Michael.
"It's okay.
"I've been crying too.
"But don't you wet this bed,
because I have
to sleep here too."
And, uh...
You know, we laughed,
you know? [Sniffles]
In spite of everything,
we laughed, and...
and we kept laughing.
We kept laughing
until I fell asleep.
When I woke up the next morning,
she wasn't just
my grandmother anymore.
She was...
she was my whole family.
[Sniffles] Well,
I'm not 11 years old anymore.
I'm not gonna wet
the bed tonight.
But I will remember...
that night
and everything
she has ever done for me.
For the rest of my life.
- You were great.
- Thank you.
She's right.
I'm Tess, by the way.
Oh, it's good to meet you,
Tess. Good to meet you, Rachel.
Are you two...
- Uh...
- Oh.
[Both laughing]
No, no. We work together.
I assume you knew Edith?
Grammy was the best part
about being friends
with this guy.
Oh, you called her grammy too?
- Oh, everybody did.
- So you guys must go way back.
Short story is, we've known
each other since we were seven.
Long story is,
you dated each other.
Mm, I don't think we need
to get into the long story.
We shared
a few milestones together.
First beer,
prom, sex...
And there's the long story.
Well, I don't
know about you two,
but I think we should get drunk.
I wish, but I have
to go pack up her room.
I have to get
back to the office,
and I do not want to see
you there later today, okay?
- Thanks, Rachel.
- Yeah, of course.
Let me know if you need
anything, just call me.
- Mm-hmm.
- Really good to meet you.
You too.
Doth my eyes deceive me?
It appears that you're actually
doing the task
that you've been assigned.
Doth you want to kiss my ass?
I sense frustration.
Case too much?
Can't handle all those numbers?
Louis, just because
financial cases bore me
doesn't mean
I can't do them in my sleep.
Well, did you remember
to do this?
I didn't have to,
because I did that.
Well, that means
that you have to...
Replace the custodian,
have an alternate,
show precedence,
generate cash flow projections,
and have everything audited
by an experienced fiduciary?
Impressive.
Well, I'll review these
for court, 4:00 p.m. today,
where you will be
my second chair.
Did I forget to mention that?
My bad.
Oh, and if you want
to pick up some coffee,
I take mine with cream
and stevia.
[Tch]
Would you like me
to put that in your calendar?
[Crash]
I will take that as a "no."
She loved you, you know?
Pretty sure she never
got over our breakup.
Well, that's because she knew
you would never do better.
[Chuckles]
What's going on?
I cancelled on her
the night before she died.
[Sighs] You must feel awful.
I was working.
I don't even remember what for.
And we're talking about me here.
I just know it seemed
so important at the time,
and now...
I didn't even get
to say good-bye to her.
But...
never really get to say good-bye
to anyone, do I?
The, uh...
the night before
I went to college,
I was supposed to see you,
and I couldn't.
Yeah. Yeah, you were having
dinner with your family.
Yeah.
"Dinner with my family"
was me sobbing in my bed.
[Chuckles]
We had said we'd break up
at the end of the summer, but...
I knew if I showed up,
I never would have been able
to do it.
- [Sighs]
- I'm sorry. I just...
I didn't have the guts
to say good-bye.
It's okay.
Mike...
I'm married.
You
are you kidding me?
Wait...
- Mike...
- Get out.
Right.
- Go.
- All right.
[Knocking at door]
When I sent you home,
I didn't mean for you
to never come back.
My grandmother died.
I know.
Look, you obviously weren't
ready to deal with it,
so I respected that
by keeping you busy.
Was I wrong?
No.
- Are you stoned?
- Yep.
And I'm not interested
in a lecture, so...
Good, 'cause I'm not
interested in giving one.
Yeah, help yourself.
Don't mind if I do.
[Inhales]
Is this the coffee cart guy?
[Distant traffic sounds]
Look, Donna, for the record,
I am sorry that you got caught
in this crossfire.
And no matter
what happens with...
there will always
be a place here for you.
With you?
Yeah. Yes.
It would be my honor.
You really don't get it,
do you?
Harvey and I are like this.
You think I would leave
him for anybody,
let alone somebody
who did what you did?
You betrayed your team.
Harvey and Jessica
were not my team.
Yes, they were.
And I was.
But no one is anymore.
And I might not like moving,
but the one thing
that I love about it
is that it is further away
from your smug face.
[Hiphop music] The whole bag?
How do you even do that, man?
It's like... I've got, like,
crazy cotton mouth right now.
Harvey Specter doesn't
get cotton "mouff."
- Cotton "mouff"?
- Mouff.
[Laughs] I guess Harvey
Specter does get cotton "mouff."
I can't help it,
these pretzels...
Both: Are making me thirsty!
[Laughter]
- Here, drink this, rookie.
- Oh, my God, I...
[chuckles]
[Sighs]
Did you ever hear of a hanger?
Oh, God, wow!
[Chuckling]
I just got an image
of you as a dad.
[Laughs] With, like, a little
Harvey Specter, you know,
all hair-gelled, and, like,
pinstripe Oshkosh B'gosh.
"Dad, don't play the odds,
play the man.
It's... it's a win-win."
You being like,
"go to your goddamn room."
Oh, look at this.
You bought an apartment
in Manhattan.
I got it for her.
Oh.
I always hated
the word "orphan."
I mean, I just...
I never felt like one.
Until now.
I ever tell you about my dad?
I think you know
the answer to that question.
He was a saxophone player.
He sat in with everybody
because everybody loved him.
He believed in love
at first sight,
and unfortunately...
his first sight was a groupie.
Your mother.
I was 16
when I caught her cheating.
I knew if I told my dad he'd...
next two years went by,
I didn't say a thing,
and she went right on just...
making him a fool.
Look, this is all to say that,
I lived in a house
surrounded by family,
but I know what it's like
to be totally alone.
Wow.
Your stoned is depressing.
You should never share
your feelings ever again.
I mean, not with me.
I gotta say, it's been
a tough week for both of us.
- Hardman.
- Oh, what I wouldn't give
to piss in that
bastard's office.
[Snickers]
That was pretty quick
off the tongue.
Well, I've done it before.
To Louis. No way.
- Way.
- [Laughs]
[Both laughing]
Wait a minute.
If you've done that before...
Why not do it again?
[Chuckling] [Ding]
Okay. Let's go.
No, no, no, no, no. [Claps]
It's not right.
It's not right?
I drank three Gatorades
on the way here.
I'm gonna pee orange.
It's right.
[Ding]
No.
If we're gonna do something,
it needs to be original.
[Whispers] Orange.
No
you know what?
I know what we're gonna do.
I'm gonna get the can opener.
Are you serious right now?
You're not messing with me?
You're finally gonna tell me
what you do with
that can opener?
- Do I look serious?
- You look stoned.
I am, but I never joke
about the can opener.
Come on. Mmm.
Let's go, let's go.
- All right, go.
- All right...
What we do is...
Okay, if you were
a narcissist with great hair,
what would your password be?
Pssh, Harvey.
Specter. [Types]
No, that's just way too easy.
One of his favorite
basketball players.
Shaquille O'Bryant?
[Ding]
I still don't understand
the thumbtack thing.
- Surprising, isn't it?
- Yeah.
Hey, say what you will
about this floor,
I'm pretty sure the cubicles
are bigger.
[Clears throat]
Hey, what's going on?
How you guys doing?
I was just, uh, helping
box a little bit,
'cause, uh, Donna was feeling
a little blue about moving.
What the hell are you doing?
Harvey. Harvey!
You looking for another way
to make my life miserable?
Harvey! Harvey, no!
Come on. You hit him, they win.
[Sighs]
You should of let me hit him.
Oh, I don't know about that,
but maybe we shouldn't have
let him leave.
Why?
Eh, uh, maybe
he wasn't snooping.
Maybe he was, I don't know,
trying to plant something,
like... like drugs.
In my record collection?
[Jamaican accent]
What better place to stash
the weed than with
the Bob Marley, man?
Louis doesn't even know where
to buy drugs,
let alone plant them.
- I know where to buy drugs.
- Congratulations.
No, I'm serious.
What if instead of peeing,
we planted something
in Hardman's office.
Unh, genius!
- It's a crime.
- Mm, maybe.
But he wouldn't hesitate
for one second
to do the same thing
to get rid of you.
What?
He wouldn't hesitate to plant
something to get rid of me.
- What, Louis?
- No, Hardman.
- [Sighs] I just said that.
- No.
What if Hardman planted
the CM memo in the first place?
Well.
Donna never saw the memo.
Donna never makes mistakes.
What if she never saw
it four years ago
because it wasn't there?
And then it was.
You really think
he had the balls
to walk into that file room,
open a box,
and plant a document?
There's no security cameras
and no locks on the doors.
Fine, but how did he get
the document in the first place?
Hardman brought Coastal Motors
into the firm.
Yeah, but he wasn't here
when the case went to trial.
No, not the trial, the defect.
What's the date
Sarah Layton left CM?
There.
- Hardman was still here.
- Makes sense.
Sarah Layton confronts Kemp.
He panics.
Who's the first person he calls?
- His lawyer.
- Hardman tells him to bury it.
That's a crime.
You said yourself he wouldn't
hesitate to commit a crime.
He knew the cars were bad
from the beginning.
[Laughs] What?
When Hardman came back,
the first thing he did
was ask Louis for a report
on every case at the firm.
Yeah, he was looking
for weaknesses.
He knew the CM win
was based on a lie,
made it look like it was my lie.
Which brings us to?
Tanner.
Hardman couldn't bring
the suit himself.
He needed an executioner.
And he picked Tanner.
So when I suspected
something was fishy,
I'd focus on Tanner, not him.
They were in on it together.
I went through every box
that Hardman looked at,
to find dirt on Tanner.
There was no dirt.
You need to call
a partner meeting.
I'll call for it...
five minutes after
you get me some proof.
[Grunting]
[Door slams closed] [Grunts]
Sorry, Harvey.
Pilates is on Wednesdays.
You and I are gonna go.
And when we're done,
you're gonna admit
to me what you did.
Oh, I've done
a lot of things, Harvey.
Well, I want to know
why you settled.
You know damn well
why I settled.
No, I don't.
I want to know about
you and Hardman,
and you're gonna answer
my questions,
or I'm gonna kick your ass.
I'm not doing the one,
and you can't do the other.
I can, and you will.
All right, let's go.
As long as it takes.
I win, you talk?
You lose, I don't.
[Smack] [Grunts] Unh.
Uh!
[Grunts, smack] Oh!
Why'd you settle?
Unh! I decline to answer.
Ohh! Why'd you settle?
I decline to answer.
Unh!
[Smack] Unh!
Yah!
[Both panting]
You get one question.
Well, let's see.
How about, why'd you settle?
Because that memo was a fraud.
What? You need
to come forward...
No, no, no, no, no.
I said one question, Harvey.
One question.
Oh, my God.
We were right.
- Right about what?
- [Sighs] I found it. [Laughs]
- You found what?
- I found it!
Mm.
No, no.
It can't be...
it can't be like this.
Why?
Because your grandmother
just died.
You think not kissing is going
to make that any better?
No, no, I think that's exactly
what it's gonna do,
and that's why it's a problem.
Rachel, in the middle
of the worst week ever,
I have found a moment
of something good.
Now, ple... I know.
But when something
like that happens,
people don't make smart choices.
Yeah.
No, you're right.
But being smart...
hasn't made either
one of us very happy.
[Sighs]
- Daniel.
- Louis.
I have something
that may be of interest.
Already?
I'm notoriously fast.
I have certain suspicions.
All I need you to do
is authorize action.
You really think he does?
I really think he did.
I am impressed.
You'd be surprised
what can do now
that I have
the proper motivation.
[Ding]
You're banned on this floor.
That's funny.
It's pee in a cup time.
Drug tests are for associates,
not the partners.
Yeah, well Hardman believes
in running a real clean ship.
You know, like "just say no.
Crack is whack."
Which is why a new policy went
into effect as of this morning.
You know, I don't smell
it on you now,
but I sure as hell
did last night
when you manhandled me
in your office.
I'm sure you had a lot
of fun laughing at that one.
You want to take it, you're
gonna have to take it forcibly.
Refusal to take this test
gives me grounds
to fire you for cause.
- I refuse.
- You're fired.
Per our bylaws, I'm entitled
to a hearing in front of
a quorum of our senior partners,
and I'm on record.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
Just take the test.
- I can't.
- Why not?
It's just a drug...
you've got to be kidding me.
You were the one who told me
to take it easy.
And you and I both know
what we did that night
in this very office.
That was a celebration.
This is different, th...
when did this happen?
Does it matter when?
I don't believe it.
You were high
when you came up
with that theory.
Doesn't matter how
we got there, we got there.
I bought us some time.
We can use the review
to present our case.
Do you have any evidence?
Not only did
he plant the document,
he wrote the damn thing.
How do you know that?
Tanner... indicated that to me.
Turns out, they weren't
in on it together.
Huh. And he's willing
to testify to that.
Oh, let me guess. No, he won't.
I've got Mike chasing
down another avenue.
Jessica, I don't do this now,
I'm gone anyway.
What is it?
Daniel and Louis
got their quorum.
Your review convenes in an hour.
Pursuant to New York
civil code,
a settlement based
on fraudulent representation
can be voided by the court.
Who are you?
My name's Mike Ross.
I work for Harvey Specter.
[Alarm beeps]
Get off my car.
As far as we can tell,
there were only two people
who knew about the problems
with the CM hood.
Sarah Layton, and you.
But I think there was a third.
[Chuckles]
You know, last time I was
ambushed in this garage,
I gave in. Not this time.
You met with Daniel Hardman
the night before
Sarah Layton's last day.
We have his calendar.
What do you want?
I want you to sign
this affidavit stating
you told Daniel Hardman about
the problems with the hood,
and that he advised you
to bury those problems
and cut a deal
with Sarah Layton.
[Chuckles]
Harvey came to me,
told me to settle,
and then we'd be done.
Now you're threatening me,
telling me to put it in writing,
and then we'll be done.
Sorry, junior.
We are done.
[Car door closes]
[Car starts]
That kid better get here fast.
He'll come through.
Harvey Specter has refused
to take a mandatory
drug test, leaving me no choice
but to terminate his employment.
As is his right,
he has requested a hearing
to dispute this.
Thank you, Daniel,
but I'm not here
to dispute anything.
After all, I was high.
I was high because I was being
forced to work for you.
A man who, it turns out,
knew CM was negligent
before I ever even
took the case.
- Uh, this is not the time...
- Shut up, Louis.
Don't do this.
If you go, I go.
Do you deny knowing
about the defects?
Unequivocally.
And you deny writing this memo?
Sending it to Tanner,
knowing that he would come
after this entire firm?
That's why he settled.
Because you told him
it wouldn't hold up.
That's wild conjecture,
and it's bullshit.
Why'd he settle?
He settled
because I did what I do.
That is not an answer.
Yes. It is.
This ends here.
The two of you
have now slandered me,
which violates
the morality clause
of the partners' agreement.
It's not slander
if it's the truth.
Unfortunately, you don't have
a shred of evidence,
because the evidence
doesn't exist.
Well, actually, it does.
This is a partners-only
meeting.
So have Tanner sue me.
But in the meantime,
I think the rest of the partners
are gonna want to see this.
It's a signed affidavit
from Lawrence Kemp,
stating that he told
Daniel Hardman about the defects
in the CM hood six years ago.
May 7th was the date
of that meeting,
per your calendar, to be exact.
You just denied knowing
anything about that,
unequivocally.
I guess you were just lying
to cover up the fact
that you were behind this entire
suit in the first place.
Is that the basis of this?
A coerced lie
from a man trying to say,
"my lawyer made me do it."
No way that holds up in court.
It doesn't have to.
It just has to make these
Harvard-educated
lawyers understand
that you made each and every one
of them spend $100,000
of their own money
to buy you control of my firm.
I think we've heard
all we needed to hear.
Harvey has admitted
to violating the drug policy.
All those in favor
of his dismissal?
Looks like you lost.
I'm glad you brought
up the bylaws.
Fraudulently suing your own firm
is grounds for firing.
You have no proof of that.
All those in favor
of Daniel Hardman's dismissal?
Hey, Harvey, I know I'm not
a partner, but do you mind?
- Go ahead.
- Nice.
Daniel, that $3 million
of our money
you spent on yourself.
Consider your partnership
bought out.
What was really
on that affidavit, anyway?
What I said was on it.
You realize it's a felony
to sign someone else's name
to a sworn document.
I didn't sign someone
else's name.
I signed my own name. [Exhales]
I mean, seriously,
how often do you really look
at a man's shoes?
To the firm of Pearson
and kiss my ass.
[Laughing] I told you we'd
be peeling him off the wall.
You go, I go.
He goes.
- I already went and came back.
- [Laughs]
[Knocking at door]
You're married.
I am.
You called me anyway.
I did.
So we're clear...
I don't consider anything
bought out.
Too bad.
'Cause the only way
you're getting another penny
is through litigation.
We may not have proof now,
but we will.
If this comes out at trial,
you'll never practice again.
Sign this confidentiality
agreement.
I'll waive my claim.
One time offer.
Take it or leave it.
For the record, I wasn't
the one who made the first move.
Harvey was.
Yeah, you made your first
move five years ago.
Maybe. But someday...
He'll make the first move
on you.
Goodbye, Daniel.
Are you gonna throw something
at me?
I'll go.
But don't kid yourself that this
is the last page of the story.
- Give me your toes.
- [Giggles] No.
[Both laughing]
Oh, just like riding a bike.
Oh, okay.
I should be more upset that you
just compared me to a bike,
but I love bikes. [Giggles]
[Knocking at door] Mmm, mwah.
- Pizza.
- Okay.
Unh. Oh!
Pepperoni. [Laughter]
[Sighs] Is this a bad time
to tell you that I'm a vegan?
Um, no.
More pizza for me.
- [Chuckles]
- Mwah.
[Sighs]
You were right.
I don't care about being smart.
Rachel...