Harvey, I don't need a perp-walk
or a front-page headline.
I just want the
person responsible.
Then hand me the deal we just negotiated
and justice will be served.
You know, if this were
anyone else but you,
I wouldn't even be
giving the courtesy of this meeting.
Becky, we're both
benefiting from this.
You've got nothing
on my clients
and I'm going
to help you get the person responsible.
So let me just
go do that.
You better make sure
Ms. Stone signs this.
Otherwise,
we don't have a deal.
How long have we
known each other?
Since you were
in the DA's office.
Then you know
we'll have a deal.
Talk soon.
Uh, how did it go
at the Department of Justice?
Follow me,
you'll find out.
I get to sit in?
With your head down and your mouth shut.
This isn't the usual...
- Uh...
- What are you doing?
Quick. Act like you're
telling me something important.
I am telling you
something important.
Oh, and then, uh,
after the injunction, you know,
both parties decided
to reassess...
My God. That woman with Rachel.
I took the LSAT's
for her a couple of years ago.
If she saw me,
she could blow my cover.
Oh, really?
And how would that go?
"Uh, excuse me.
When I was cheating for my LSAT's,
"that was the guy who
took the test for me"? Come on.
It could go down like that.
You don't know. People say things.
Ms. Stone, correct me
if any of this is wrong.
But you and I
both know it's not.
Please address me
and not my client, Mr. Specter.
You mean your client
who purchased $10 million
of Lunardi Pharmaceuticals?
And then, a day later,
word of their FDA approval got out
and the stock shot up
to $30 million?
She purchased that stock
for your clients,
Bert Kimble
and Dean Morello,
based on a tip sheet
handed out by your clients.
An allegation that tainted
their reputation,
yet the DOJ looked into it
and found nothing.
That doesn't mean
it didn't happen.
I'll turn your client
over in person. No handcuffs.
It will be
a country club prison.
And I'll make sure that she's processed
as gently as possible.
As long as she admits that she made
this trade of her own accord.
It's a crappy deal
wrapped in pretty paper.
Why aren't we dealing
with the Department of Justice?
Because the DOJ wanted
to put you behind bars for seven years,
and I got them down
to 11 months.
Look, it's a great
deal. You're going to sign it.
You're going to serve
your year in prison.
And every night,
when you climb into your bunk,
you're going to thank
your lucky stars
that Harvey Specter
negotiated on your behalf.
Nobody is ever going
to believe me,
and I don't have the resources
to fight this thing forever.
So I'll sign the
goddamn deal.
But I'm not
thanking anybody.
Harvey?
You came through.
My company's reputation means
everything to me.
Thank you.
So I trust we
won't be hearing
from the Department
of Justice again?
Unless you plan
on inviting them
to the company's
Christmas party, Bert, no.
I told Morello you could fix
this for us. Thank you, Harvey.
Reality's
starting to sink in,
and Gabby's a little
wound-up right now.
Let's, uh...
Let's give her a minute.
I've got the pretty papers in my office
for you to look over.
Keep an eye on her.
You're here to make sure
I don't change my mind about the deal?
No, I...
Would you?
You know, my father
was a teacher.
He worked hard,
followed the rules.
Last year, the district cut his pension
to save their budget.
I went to Wall Street
so I could make some money
before getting into
teaching, myself.
I never thought
I'd have to worry
if they let convicted
felons teach.
Could I get you
some water or something?
Oh...
I'm just going to
get you some water.
- Hey.
- I got it.
- Thanks.
So, uh, that girl
you were with earlier.
She a friend of yours?
Teresa? Yeah, she used to
be a paralegal here.
We were
pretty close.
She worked at
Pearson Hardman?
Mmm-hmm. And I just had
the unique pleasure
of giving her the summer intern tour
for prospective employees.
- Really?
- Yeah.
She's in her second year
of Harvard Law.
Meeting with
the partners as we speak.
- Huh!
- I know.
We used to do
everything together.
And now,
if she gets this job,
she will technically
be my boss.
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry, Rachel.
If you need to
talk about it, or...
No. Not now, thanks.
No. No, no, no.
What?
She's gone.
See the money, wanna stay
for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
You left her alone
to get her a water?
What, she didn't
want a latte?
I was trying
to be helpful.
You were very
helpful. To her.
You didn't see her,
Harvey.
She was scared.
She was a wreck.
Maybe that had to
do with the fact
that she was about to go to prison
for 11 months.
I think she was having
the reaction of an innocent woman.
And what was
telling you that?
Your years of
investigative experience?
No, I just...
I listened to her. That's all.
Let me tell you
something, okay?
Just because a pretty girl
tells you a story,
doesn't mean it's true.
If she'd gone to trial,
the burden of proof
would be on the prosecution.
Yet her own lawyer
told her to take the deal.
Not to mention that innocent
people don't run.
I think this fell out of her purse.
I found it here.
Why are you
telling me this now?
Because you were
mad at me before.
So your answer to that is to delay
giving me important information?
Well, when you
put it like that...
Okay. I've got to
smooth things over with the DOJ.
That phone is
our only lead.
Try not to lose it
before I get back.
- Ah.
- Okay?
Becky, there's been a slight hiccup
on the Gabby Stone business.
I don't want to hear about any hiccups.
She sign the deal or not?
Well, she was about to. My associate
left her alone for a second.
She took off.
Gabby Stone's in the wind?
"In the wind"? Really?
The woman isn't
a world-class felon. She'll turn up.
Well, it better be soon,
or the deal's off the table
and I'm going after
your clients.
That's funny.
I don't think so.
The SEC decided
they had no case
and their burden
of proof is lower.
If you had something on my clients,
you would have charged them already.
Harvey, I went out
on a limb for you.
You make me look bad on this, I promise
you, you'll regret it.
Donna,
where the hell is Mike?
Hey, anyone know
a guy named Bradley?
Yeah. Guy who's about
to miss the jumper.
All right. Does he have
a last name?
Yeah, Brickstein.
Do I look like
I have time for jokes?
Reger.
Bradley.
Come on, I'm open!
Mr. Reger.
Bradley Reger!
I'm sorry.
Can I help you?
I'm sure you've heard about the
investigation regarding Gabby Stone?
Are you with the
Department of Justice?
I have
several questions for you.
Did you help Gabby when she was charged
with insider trading?
Of course I did.
She wasn't just a trader.
She was my friend.
I recommended a lawyer
and let her borrow some cash
after you guys
froze her account.
That was Henderson.
He's a stickler for procedure.
Tell me, when was the last
time you saw her?
Bradley. Let me inform you
that withholding knowledge
of the whereabouts of a known fugitive
is a federal offense.
Do you understand me?
Gabby came in here
20 minutes ago.
She asked to borrow my keycard
to Morello Assets' offices,
and I gave it to her.
Well, the Department
appreciates your honesty.
Oh, and, uh,
Mr. Reger.
Put a little arc
in your jump shot. All right?
If poor shooting
were a crime,
I'd be forced to arrest you right here.
It's embarrassing.
Go get them.
Harvey.
I know where she is.
What are you doing here?
I told you I'd get her.
And I would
let you.
I just wanted to make
sure she didn't get away again.
The water was right outside
the room, okay?
And you said innocent
people don't run.
Do guilty people run
back to the scene of the crime?
We don't know
what she's doing.
She could be planning on taking a
baseball bat to all these computers,
for all we know.
Gabby,
what are you doing?
That stock was
on my tip sheet. It was on mine.
If I could find that tip sheet,
I could prove my innocence.
Is this what
guilty people do?
I know they're your clients,
but can you help me? Please.
I'm sorry. You can
either come with us,
or we'll have the
Department of Justice bring you in.
So, I meant
to ask you,
how did your friend's
interview go yesterday?
Teresa? She didn't get
the internship.
So how do you
feel about that?
To be honest,
I'm relieved.
I mean, she would have been a daily
reminder of what I couldn't do.
That I'll never score high enough on
the LSAT's or get into law school.
You know, that doesn't
have to be true.
It is. I need to accept
that I will always be a paralegal
because of
this stupid test.
I had a hard time sleeping last night.
You want to know why?
- No.
- Because Gabby Stone is innocent.
Well, I slept
like a baby.
I don't think
you believe that.
You think she's innocent, too.
You just don't want to pursue it.
She's not our client.
No, Morello
is our client.
And if someone else
in that office is responsible
and they do it again, then won't that
put our client in jeopardy?
Ooh, yep.
I'm right,
and you know it.
And now you have
the responsibility to investigate.
Did you tell that guy
at the basketball court
that you were an attorney for the
Department of Justice?
Not explicitly.
I mean, people hear
what they want to hear.
I won't impersonate
a federal agent again.
Probably a good idea.
Yeah.
Oh, hey, Mike.
Um, can I give you my roommate's cat
for the weekend?
Let's get it over with.
I have some actual work to do.
No, no, no.
It's not what you think.
It's just very annoying, and I figured
if you were looking after it,
the cat is as good
as gone. Right?
Gentlemen.
What's going on?
Some sort of
shenanigans?
Uh, no. It's nothing. It's just stuff
between the associates.
I said,
what's going on?
It's... Seth's just
giving me a hard time
for losing Gabby Stone
yesterday.
Although, we know, at this firm,
that we don't dwell
on our colleagues'
mistakes. Right?
I mean, just because one of your fellow
associates is incompetent
doesn't mean you have to constantly
remind this moron
what a careless idiot
he really is. Right?
You.
Harold, I called you
two nights ago
and you didn't
answer your phone.
Which is really funny, because you're
a first-year associate
who's lucky enough to be working here
at Pearson Hardman.
So when I need to
get a hold of you,
you will be reachable
at all times.
I don't care if
you're in a coma,
a hospital that's
burning down,
your mother's about to jump off
the Brooklyn Bridge.
You will pick up
your phone.
Absolutely.
- Got it?
- Yes.
Okay, thanks. Can you get out
of my office, please?
Harvey, once this whole
Morello thing gets fixed,
remind me to be
irritated with you
for not billing more
on the Swindon merger.
The fact is, mergers are boring,
okay? Plus, I'm busy.
Also, mergers? Boring.
How did you get these?
You mean tickets to the
Royal Shakespeare Company's
production of King Lear?
This show was sold out
the minute these tickets went on sale.
I live for King Lear.
How did you know that?
It's my job
to know that.
But why?
Louis, your billables
are outstanding.
You've landed three high-profile
clients in a month,
and I want to show
you my appreciation.
And I'm very happy
that you're excited.
So should we get dinner before
or after the play?
Uh, I don't know.
Jessica, do you remember
when we went to that Yankee game
and you caught that foul ball
and you ate all my nachos?
Did we go to the steak house that night?
Oh, that was a good meal.
Have a good time.
You know what, Louis?
Dinner after.
I'll have Norma
make a reservation.
Fantastic.
Dean, Gabby Stone is still making noises
about these tip sheets.
She insists that she
had a different sheet
on the day she
bought Lunardi.
She's lying.
I understand. But after she broke
into your offices last night,
the DOJ might be inclined to start
rattling cages again.
So, for the record,
you're telling me
the truth, right?
Harvey. You work
for me, remember?
Well, as your lawyer,
I need to be able to tell the DOJ
that we're all above board.
Of course.
So you won't mind
if I look around for myself?
We've had a clean
record for 50 years.
Please, Harvey,
look around.
Why is that on my desk?
Because the LSAT's are
a week from Saturday.
Great. Go away.
I'm busy.
There are only four tests a year.
Which means if you miss this one,
you're going to have to wait
another three months.
I can do math, too,
Good Will Hunting.
When did I say I was ready
to re-take the LSAT's?
I thought that after
our talk, you...
Nothing about our talk said I'm
interested in bombing the test again.
- You're not going to bomb it again.
- How do you know?
Because the first
time you took it,
you were missing one
essential ingredient.
- Me.
- Not interested.
If I let you help me,
will you leave me alone?
Mmm-hmm.
Okay.
I'll see you later.
Get excited.
Woo-hoo.
Hey, I forget. Why are we looking
into Gabby Stone again?
Oh, right. Because I said
she's innocent,
and now you agree with me.
No, I don't agree with
you that she's innocent.
But if there's even the slightest chance
that someone else is involved,
they're putting the whole company at
risk. And I can't have that.
Okay, so you disagree with
what we agree about?
I'll agree with that.
I don't feel sorry
for Gabby Stone at all.
Because?
I found her.
I was her immediate supervisor.
I nurtured her.
And then she tries
to cheat and give us a bad name.
How commonplace would you say
cheating is here?
It's not. That's not
the kind of shop we run.
So when Ms. Stone
made the trade
and the investment tripled in value,
you weren't suspicious?
My job's not to worry about the traders
that are making money.
My job is to worry
about the traders who aren't.
So how exactly does
the tip sheet system work?
Our technical analysts
predict stocks that are likely to have
larger than expected
volatility.
These predictions are handed out to our
traders on a daily basis
in the form
of a tip sheet.
All these traders get
the same tip sheet?
Exactly. They're printed
on red paper so they can't be copied.
Every trader is responsible
for returning their sheet
at the end of the day
so they can be shredded.
So no records exist.
We keep
electronic copies.
I'll need to see those copies
for the last year.
I thought you might.
I'm assuming you own a computer?
One more thing. I'll need to see
a list of all the trades
Morello Assets made
in the last year.
Well,
I can't give you that.
Why not?
The tip sheets
have expired,
but our current positions,
that's proprietary
information.
I can't release that
on just your say-so.
That's not a request.
We need to protect the company.
And we're covered
under attorney-client privilege.
And I'm telling you
I'm not giving you shit.
You think I don't know
what attorney-client privilege is?
You know, you corporate
lawyers look down your noses at us
because we didn't go
to Ivy League schools.
Just because I don't
have a fancy degree
doesn't mean you get to come into
my house and order me around.
And you go whine
to Morello,
and I'll knock you
on your ass like the puss you are.
Well, Sam, I'm sorry
that you feel that way.
But I've been working for your boss,
Dean Morello, for a very long time.
And let me tell
you something.
If you try to
stonewall me,
you'll be out on the street
in less than a week.
As for the other stuff, do I think that
I'm smarter than you?
You're damn right I do.
But if you think that means that I
can't kick your ass
up and down this floor,
take a swing and see what happens.
I didn't think so.
- Here you go.
- That was amazing.
It was like he was Mr. T
and you were Rocky.
But, like, not Rocky
at the beginning,
when he's all
scared of Mr. T.
But at the end,
when he was all, like,
"Uh, give it
your best shot." You know?
Adrian! Yes!
That's funny. But you might want to wipe
that grin off your face.
What? Why?
Because without those trades,
we don't have shit.
And your little girlfriend
is going to rot in jail.
And by the way, you've got to work
on your Stallone.
- You need a lower register.
- Uh!
That was an incredible
Stallone.
I've been doing that since I was a kid.
You can't touch it.
Uh!
- Not with food in your mouth.
- No, I swallowed it.
- Uh!
- There's food in your mouth.
- Adrian!
- That's disgusting.
Come on.
You got this one.
It's "A."
You know what?
It's "C."
Actually, it's "D."
It's definitely "D."
Final answer?
Yes. "D."
It's "A."
Rachel, you've
got to remember.
They're asking why the argument
is most vulnerable.
I could make the case that they're all
vulnerable arguments.
You could. But your first
instinct was "A."
You've got to
go with your gut.
Right. So what if my gut can find the
exception where "A" is wrong?
What am I supposed
to do then?
You ignore it.
I can't. That's easier
said than done.
Look, the test isn't trying
to trick you, Rachel.
But sometimes,
it is, Mike.
Well, you've got
to let that go.
- I can't.
- Why not?
Because I don't want
to get any questions wrong.
Okay. I think we
found your problem.
You're so afraid of getting fooled
by a few trick questions
that you're letting it mess you up with
all the other ones.
Look, Rachel, you want
to get into Harvard, you need a 170.
Okay? If you let a few of these
trick questions go,
you're going
to be fine.
But if you keep trying
to be perfect,
you're going to over-think
this whole thing
and you're going
to end up with a 130.
Rachel.
Nobody gets all
the trick questions.
What about you?
First grade, they gave
me an achievement test.
I scored in the
99th percentile.
So, they kept giving me
achievement tests
all the way up to the
eighth grade level.
And I kept getting in the 99th
percentile on every one of them.
What, you couldn't
get the 100th?
There is no 100th.
Next question.
Come on.
King Lear.
I happen to like
And unlike some
people I know,
Louis' references don't
begin and end with Top Gun.
Hey, I love Louis.
And I don't care what you say,
I am not leaving
my wingman.
You see, that's funny,
because that's from Top Gun.
"He's a wildcard,
flies by the seat of his pants."
You think I can't quote
Top Gun? Get the hell out of here.
Oh, that was good.
Hey, Mike.
Bert Kimble's coming to see me.
I need you in the meeting.
Whoa. The number
two at Morello?
I bet he's coming to yell at you after
your big showdown there yesterday.
If you need me,
I've got your back.
You thinking about
finally going to law school?
Oh. No, I'm helping
Rachel study.
The pretty paralegal.
Got it.
Okay.
It's not like that.
It's exactly like that.
Oh, that reminds me.
How did you manage
to take the LSAT's for a woman?
What do you mean?
We took the test the same day.
She signed my name on hers, and I
signed hers on mine.
Why? What's so funny?
I just pictured
you in drag.
I could pull that off.
I've got soft features.
I want to apologize
for Samuel's behavior.
He's had a chip
on his shoulder
ever since the Department of Justice
investigated Ms. Stone's malfeasance.
He's very protective
of the firm.
He's a good man to
have in your corner.
Well, so are you.
In these folders,
you will find every trade
made by Morello Assets in the last year.
Personally delivered
by Bert Kimble? I'm flattered.
Well, we just want to make sure you've
got everything you need, Harvey.
We really appreciate
your diligence.
Now, I better get
back to the office.
The Australian markets
are just opening up. Good to see you.
Always a pleasure, Bert.
Harvey, this is great.
We can take these
tip sheets and put the...
What are you doing?
This guy's not that friendly
to his own mother.
He's hiding something,
and I'm pissed.
What are you
talking about?
Those aren't
the real trades.
Okay. So how do
we get them?
Right.
How do I get them?
Hmm.
Hello?
You figure out how to get the
most profitable trades yet, Mike?
The Morello brokers hang out at
a bar called the Closing Bell.
I'm on my way now.
Just remember, you're working.
I'll talk to you later.
Can I get a beer?
Thank you.
Hey, hey, hey!
What's up, toolbox?
Oh, man. If you drink that
beer any slower,
I'm going to have
to get you a nipple.
Do I know you, or...
Vince Landis.
Morello Assets.
- Yeah. That's me.
- Yeah.
Russell Ginther. The "Gin."
The "Ginthesizer."
- What are you talking about?
- Come on.
Gervich Investments, man. We got
shit-housed here a couple of weeks ago.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
You, me, Pepiol,
Causwell, Williamson.
That guy, Dick. You still owe
me 20 bucks!
Yeah, right. Russell.
Right. Right.
You still begging for
scraps over there at Gervich, or what?
You wish.
Hey, I need a shot.
What is this?
Oh, drink mine.
Please.
Mmm.
- Baker?
- Uh-huh.
You're better
than that, man.
Money!
God, you guys are
a bunch of pussies.
I guarantee you
my biggest trades
kick the ass out of
your biggest trades.
I don't think so,
brother.
Last month, I made $2 million
on Cahill Metals in one hour!
Two million?
I made four million
off of Montroluxx back in February.
That stock tripled
overnight. What's up?
Four million?
Oh, that's adorable.
How about the six million
I just cleared on Rypien Micro Devices?
Oh, yeah? What do you think my boy here
made on Piper Web Systems?
- What, this guy?
- Uh-huh.
Uh, I don't know. A pack of chewing gum
and your sister's panties?
Oh, it's on.
Oh!
Vince Landis!
Seven million off
of Drogin Limited.
Eight million
off of Epling RTX.
$9 million off of RMA
Integrated Products.
Well, gentlemen,
greed is good.
So's his sister, right?
Come on, man. That's his sister.
That's not cool.
Dude, you just made,
like, the same joke.
Ah!
Hey,
Bradley's finally here.
Uh, all right, ladies. Listen, I've got
to split. It's been real.
- I'll get drinks next time, all right?
- Right.
Make money, money,
make money!
Whoo!
Ah.
Harvey.
I got the trades.
Good. We'll talk tomorrow.
What? No.
I'm coming over now.
You're drunk.
Do not come over.
All right, cool.
I'll see you in a minute.
Hey! Harvey, come on!
We've got to save Gabby!
"Gabbolini."
Oh. Oh, you've got
a sweet place, dude.
Don't ever call me "dude."
You think that maybe
I could take it off your hands?
Like, when you're
going out of town?
Like a...
Like a house-sitting type situation?
Remind me to have
Donna get you a spare key.
You have the trades?
Ta-da!
- Good.
- Hey, when can we, uh...
I'm still upset
that I didn't get the internship.
It would have been so much fun to work
together, don't you think?
Mmm, absolutely.
Let me ask
you something.
How did you turn it around
with the LSAT's?
What do you mean?
Come on. You took them,
didn't do so well.
And now,
you're at Harvard Law?
That's exactly what
I want to be doing. You can tell me.
What did you do, sleep with the grader?
What?
I paid someone to
take them for me.
- What?
- Uh...
There was this guy.
I heard about him from
a friend of a friend.
I paid him a 1,000 bucks
and he took the LSAT's for me.
He got me a 172.
You cheated on the LSAT's?
When we were paralegals, we were smarter
than half the associates.
Why... Why should I
be denied my chance
because I can't pass
some stupid test?
I'm living my dream,
Rach.
I'm not going to
apologize for it to anyone.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Hello?
Mikey. Yo, it's Scott.
Scott.
How are you, man?
I haven't talked
to you in forever.
You still taking LSAT's for other
people? I have a customer for you.
No, man. I'm... I'm not in that business
anymore. I'm sorry.
Trust me. You want to take this meeting,
dude. This chick is smoking hot.
What's her name?
Rachel Zane.
You didn't give her
my name, did you?
No. Of course not.
I'm not taking
that meeting, man.
What do you want me
to sign now?
A confession that
I killed Kennedy?
I'm not going to pretend
to be your best friend, Ms. Stone.
But my interests happen to be aligned
with yours right now.
So, please, sit down.
Your colleagues'
most profitable trades.
Why are you showing
them to me?
Every single one of them
comes from stocks
that Morello Assets
didn't officially recommend.
This is either a hell
of a coincidence,
or these traders were
all given different tip sheets.
So you believe me.
When I said my tip sheet had Lunardi
Pharmaceuticals on it.
Well, I'm getting there.
But you got flagged by the DOJ,
and no one else at Morello did.
So I want to know why.
What's different here?
Uh...
None of these trades
are for more than nine million.
That's Morello's
recommended amount.
And your Lunardi purchase
was for $10 million.
Maybe someone figured out that any
trade under $10 million
wouldn't draw
DOJ attention.
Why did you make a trade for $1 million
more than the recommended amount?
Look at me.
I'm not exactly
fraternity material.
It's a cutthroat world
and I wasn't performing well.
So I took a chance and
I tried to hit it big.
I picked the wrong trade.
Gabby, if you knew
you were innocent,
then why didn't you
fight this harder?
After I saw how much money the trade
made, I suspected something.
I went to Bert Kimble.
He reassured me that I made a profitable
trade and did nothing wrong.
He even told me I...
I had a $300,000 bonus coming at the end
of the quarter.
I should have
gone to someone.
Said something.
I made one mistake, and I'm going to
regret it for the rest of my life.
Scott. Yeah,
it's Mike Ross.
This Rachel Zane. Tell her
I'll take the meeting.
Just don't tell
her my name.
Who was that
on the phone?
It was nothing.
Are you thinking
about Gabby?
I'm thinking
about her lawyer.
What?
Knowing what she said, why would that
Zegan guy agree to a deal
that puts his client behind bars
without even putting up a fight?
I can't stand that
kind of shoddy work.
He's like the bad
version of both of us.
He doesn't care about his client
and he's not about winning.
He's got even less
style than you.
I don't really see
how that's relevant. At all.
Hold on. How did she
get this lawyer?
Her friend, Bradley.
The one who also
works at Morello.
Yeah.
I don't think Bradley's
as good a friend as she thinks he is.
Here's what
you're going to do.
I looked into it.
You were right.
You put this
together fast.
I care about Gabby.
You were right, too.
You want me
to go with you?
I'm sorry, but I've got to take
care of this one myself.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Rachel?
What are you doing
all the way over here?
Uh, this guy has
the best soft pretzels in town.
- Do you want to try it?
- No, I'm good.
Hey, how are you
feeling about the LSAT's?
I was really happy with
all the prep we did yesterday.
I'm really excited
for you.
You're excited for me?
Why do you even care?
I was just asking.
Well, just stop
asking. Look...
I came down here because I just wanted
to be by myself, and I bump into you.
And the first thing
you want to talk about is the LSAT's?
Okay. I'm sorry. I...
The truth is, I came down here
to clear my head, too.
About what?
It's Gabby Stone.
The girl who did
the insider trading?
She actually suspected that something
was wrong after the trade,
but she didn't do
anything about it.
She didn't want to
jeopardize her career.
Now she's going to be paying for that
mistake the rest of her life.
Anyway, I'm sorry
I ruined your alone time.
I'll see you
back at the office.
Let me ask you
something, Nick.
Does Bert Kimble
drag his feet paying you, too?
Excuse me?
Because in my experience,
getting money from that asshole
is like getting blood
from a stone.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Yes, you do.
You see, after I saw your client sitting
in jail, I got to wondering.
How did she find you?
I'm going to
call security.
Absolutely.
See, it turns out that
her friend, Bradley, recommended you.
Bradley, who's been at Morello Assets
for the past seven years.
So, I checked.
You know what I found?
You represented Bert Kimble
in a civil suit 12 years ago.
It just so happens
that you also represented
Lunardi Pharmaceuticals
in their FDA approval proceedings.
That doesn't
mean anything.
You've seen my
relationship with the DOJ.
Do you want me to
point them in your direction?
Or do you want to admit to me that Bert
Kimble is paying you off?
Harvey.
I don't understand.
I thought all this business
was done with.
It's almost
sorted out, Dean.
I'm just here to let you know
that Bert's a crook.
- What did you say?
- Harvey...
He used a lawyer
to periodically
provide him with inside information.
Once he got
this information,
he handed out one tip sheet different
from all the others.
So, the trader, in this instance,
Gabriele Stone,
would make a trade not knowing that she
was acting on an illegal tip.
It was actually
ingenious.
If the trade was
ever under suspicion,
even the trader
couldn't point to Bert.
Okay. We've heard
more than enough. Thank you.
I don't think so.
Ms. Stone made two mistakes.
One, she made a trade for more
than $9 million.
The other was not
going to the DOJ
the second the stock
shot up through the roof.
You son of a bitch.
I...
Harvey, this is
a lot to digest.
Well, I'll make it
easy for you, Dean. He's a cancer.
You don't cut him loose,
he's going to kill your whole company.
How dare you walk in here and accuse
me with these things?
I mean,
you are my lawyer!
No, Bert. I'm the lawyer
for Morello Asset Management.
As far as the law is concerned, Dean
Morello is my client, not you.
Dumb son of a bitch.
Bert...
- You're fired.
- What?
Effective immediately.
You're going to fire me?
Because of this?
I hope you're happy.
Because without me,
this hedge fund is nothing.
I'll be happy when the Department of
Justice puts your ass in handcuffs.
Enjoy your freedom, Bert,
because they're coming for you.
And since you're a bigger trophy
than Gabriele Stone,
you're going to get
a whole lot more than 11 months.
Harvey,
I want you to know
that I knew nothing
about any of this.
Dean, when I was
13 years old,
my little brother was getting bullied
by a kid in the neighborhood.
One day, I confronted
the kid's father.
He told me he didn't
know anything about it.
You know what his
problem was?
It was his goddamn
job to know.
Thanks for
getting me out.
I'm just sorry we couldn't get
you your bonus.
It wasn't mine
to begin with.
But without it, I don't know how
I'm going to pay you.
Don't worry about it.
Dean Morello is footing this bill.
You believed in me.
I can't tell you how grateful I am
to both of you.
Never doubted you
for a second.
Oh, Gabby. I, uh, wanted
to give you something.
You left it
on your desk.
Thank you.
All right, well,
I'm going to find some water.
You don't come back soon,
we're sending out a search party.
You never doubted
her for a second?
I didn't doubt her for a second.
I doubted her for days.
Yeah, that's not what just you led
her to believe.
People hear what
they want to hear.
Oh, I meant to ask you.
That big guy that
you got in a fight with, Mr. T,
was he in on
this whole thing?
No. He was
just a dick.
I mean,
that was the most
brilliant portrayal
of King Lear I have ever seen.
"Come not between
the dragon and his wrath."
It was...
Thank you for tonight, Jessica. Really.
This was nice.
This was really, really nice.
You're welcome, Louis.
And yes, this was really nice.
Listen, I...
I just want you to know
how much I appreciate
everything that you do for this firm.
I take a lot of
pride in my work.
I know. And you're very
good at what you do.
Okay. Can you just please say that once
in front of Harvey?
Louis, I know you and Harvey
have a rivalry.
And the truth is that, right now, Harvey
is more valuable to the firm.
But that doesn't always
mean that he's going to be on top.
Because
another truth is,
is that I can't always
count on Harvey to listen to me.
But I can count on you.
Yeah. Yes, you can.
So you keep doing
what you're doing, Louis,
and you're going
to be just fine.
And if he doesn't
know it already, I promise,
Harvey is going to understand just how
valuable you are to me.
You know, next week,
there's a revival of Cats.
No.
Nice touch. Tickets
to the Yankee game.
Found them on my desk.
Can't wait.
You're welcome.
Nachos are on
you this time.
Oh, those tickets aren't for you and me.
They're for you and Louis.
Oh, Sunday, the 20th. Did I mention
that I'm busy that night?
I know you are. You're busy going
to the Yankee game with Louis.
"Son, your ego's writing
checks that your body can't cash."
Oh, see, that's funny because now,
I'm quoting Top Gun.
And get out
of my office.
- Very funny. Very funny.
- Uh-huh.
Very funny.
Mike. Hey, you got
a second? I just...
I just want
to thank you.
Thank me? For what?
For going out of your way to help
me with the LSAT's.
Oh, it's nothing.
You would have done the same for me.
I put a lot of
pressure on myself. I always have.
You're right.
I'm a perfectionist.
- It's okay.
- No, it's not okay.
My dad,
he always wanted a son.
It was never something that he brought
up. It was just sort of there.
And I never felt like I was good
enough for him.
Which is why I don't
like to put myself
in positions
where I might fail.
So I decided to just
push the LSAT's.
Give myself a little
more time to study.
That's good.
That's great.
I think you made
the right choice.
Really? Why?
You were the one that's been pushing me
to take them next week.
I just meant that I support the decision
you made. That's all.
Why are you suddenly
changing your tune?
Because if you're not ready,
you're not ready.
Listen, I've got to go.
I'll see you tomorrow.
No, that's not why.
All that interest
in Teresa.
And then, the other
guy didn't show up. But you did.
You were going to
take the test for me.
What guy? What are
you talking about?
You know exactly
what I'm talking about.
- You're the test genius, right?
- Um...
Mike, I could pick up
the phone and find out right now.
Yes. I took the test
for your friend, Teresa.
That's the whole reason
you were trying to help me.
Because you thought if you didn't,
you were going to get caught.
- That's not true.
- How am I supposed to believe that?
Honestly, how am I
supposed to believe anything you say,
when the whole time you were at Harvard,
studying to be a lawyer,
you were actually
cheating for other people?
Yes. I was helping
people cheat. Okay? But...
But what?
But it's not
the whole story.