Harvard Trivia.
The lightning round.
Go. Pulitzer Prizes.
- Forty six.
- Nobel Peace Prizes.
- Five.
- What is the oldest book
in the Harvard
library collection?
- The Bible.
- Wrong.
The Gutenberg Bible.
Everyone knows
it's the Gutenberg Bible.
Yes, but you didn't say it.
The rules dictate
you must be precise,
as the law
is a very precise endeavor.
- How many U.S. Pres...
- Eight.
That's not fair.
You didn't even finish the question.
And yet, it's right.
The question was going to be, how many
U.S. Presidents have attended Harvard?
- You want names?
- No. We get it.
Final round. Ross is ahead by one.
One question each.
Points are double.
Double because he wants
to keep you in the game, Seth.
Bring it on, Ross.
I bleed crimson.
Oh, venomous banter. This is adorable.
I love it. Ross.
Square pizza.
Where do you get it?
Are you kidding?
Any self respecting Harvard alumnus
would know
the answer to that.
Late night studying,
you want square pizza, where do you go?
You know, I'm more of a burger guy.
I study better on protein.
That's pathetic.
- It's Pinocchio's.
- Mmm.
I answer mine, I win.
Yeah, I know.
How many current U.S. Supreme Court
justices are from our alma mater?
Five.
Got anything to say, Ross?
No.
Just that the answer is wrong.
Scalia, Roberts, Kennedy,
Breyer, Kagan.
- Ginsburg.
- Ruth Bader Ginsburg went to Columbia.
She graduated from Columbia after
she attended Harvard for two years.
The question was phrased,
"How many justices were from Harvard?"
Well, she was on
the Harvard Law Review.
When she arrived at Columbia
as a transfer, she was from Harvard.
The rules dictate
that you must be precise,
as the law
is a precise endeavor.
Congratulations.
That's what you get for second place.
To the victor
belongs the spoils.
A case. Pro bono.
One of your very own.
Congratulations. Enjoy.
Louis knows.
- Louis knows what?
- My dirty little secret.
You're Canadian?
No.
He knows that I didn't go to Harvard.
No, he doesn't.
How can you be
so sure about that?
Because you're walking with me
right now.
He did this whole
Harvard Trivia thing.
And then,
he brought up this pizza.
- And I...
- Ah, doesn't mean he knows.
Look. I think we need to hack
into Harvard's system or something.
You know?
And put my records in.
I can't. I'm booked this weekend.
I'm breaking into Fort Knox.
I gotta return
some stolen "dubloons".
Okay. Hilarious.
I'm serious.
Listen. Nobody is going
to check into your past
unless you give them reason to.
Louis is devious,
but he's not bold.
He won't think we did this. Because
he'd never think to do it himself.
- "Dubloons"?
- The ridiculousness of your suggestion
warranted the use of a silly word.
Got it.
Was that Quentin Sainz
I just saw leaving?
Mmm-hmm. You know him?
I know of him.
Why was he holding your hands?
Kissing them?
What are you implying,
Harvey?
I don't know.
Maybe you two are going steady.
I was implying that it looked
like he was grateful to you,
for taking his case.
Good.
Because that's exactly what it was.
That's a bad move. We may make money
billing out on their defense,
but when we lose,
which we will,
it's going to hurt us
in the long run.
How do you know we'll lose?
Because it's my job
to know.
His company's ALS wonder drug
is killing people.
ALS is incurable.
And everyone who is taking that drug
is going to die, anyway.
Hmm. That's your defense.
If he kills them a little faster,
it's a public service?
Our defense
is those allegations are untrue.
He has taken
this story all over town,
and not a single firm
thinks he has a case.
Which is why he came to me. Because
he wants someone who believes in him.
And what is it exactly
that makes you believe in him?
Well, I got to know
his character pretty well
during the time
that we were married.
Quentin is expecting you tomorrow.
See the money, wanna stay
for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
You forgot this last night.
I didn't forget that.
I have no intention
of taking this case.
Though I did get you this.
What is it?
Wedding gift.
I'm sorry it's so late,
but it's hard to be on time
when I never knew
you were married.
Are you seeing anyone,
Harvey?
Hmm?
You don't want to tell me,
and I don't really care.
Because, you and I share the same trait
of keeping our personal lives personal.
- You were married.
- It happened when you were at Harvard.
It didn't work out.
We were too dedicated to our careers,
and that's all
I'm going to say about it.
Okay. You're right.
It's none of my business.
- I'm still not taking this case.
- Why is that?
Because sometimes,
I do things that my clients don't like.
And if their ex-wives
are looking over my shoulders,
that's not really a problem.
But when their ex-wives
are also my Managing Partner,
that hamstrings me.
If I'm going to turn this loser
into a winner, I can't be hamstrung.
I can't have that.
Do what you've got to do.
- You won't interfere?
- What did I just say?
Do you have any idea
how hard it is
to develop a new drug
if you're not Pfizer
or Amgen, or Merck?
This is important, Harvey.
If Quentin came to you
looking for someone who trusts him,
why aren't you handling
this case yourself?
That's none of your concern.
Well, I'm not asking you
as your colleague.
I'm asking
you as Quentin's attorney.
After Quentin and I separated,
he started seeing
one of his research consultants. Lisa.
They're still together.
But he never
married her.
She doesn't want me
on the case.
Oh, terrific.
You're sticking me with a losing case
and a girlfriend who isn't going
to like me any more than she likes you.
Well, I'm sure
it's not the first time
someone hasn't liked you,
Harvey.
Who doesn't like me?
Picture the devil
without the charm.
Okay. So, Karinski
owned this building for two years?
Yeah. Then, things got bad.
Three below,
the heat went out.
I nearly froze to death.
Then, a gas leak in my stove.
You could smell the damn thing,
but he said it was fine.
I called for a month,
then I had to replace it myself.
Okay.
Why didn't you just move?
This is the apartment
I grew up in.
It's the only place
I've ever known.
I don't have
any brothers or sisters.
My parents
are not with me anymore.
I'm not leaving
the one connection
I have to them.
You said
you weren't sleeping.
Are you stressed out,
or...
Bedbugs.
- No.
- My place
is literally crawling with them.
Could you sleep, knowing the minute
you turn out the light,
- they're coming for you?
- No. I couldn't.
Well, Karinski won't do anything
about it without proof.
And I can't get someone from the city
down to verify they're there.
Don't worry. I can.
Two weeks,
next Thursday.
I... I... I don't think
that you heard me.
I need someone
down there today.
Two weeks,
next Thursday.
Okay. Uh, I'd like to speak
to your supervisor, please.
You can do that
next Wednesday.
Okay. Glenda?
Let me tell you what I'm going to do
between now and next Wednesday.
I know exactly
what you're going to do.
You're going to do
what every other lawyer threatens to do.
You're going to file
a 409/3 grievance
claiming that I did
not fulfill my obligation
to promptly direct you
to my supervisor.
A grievance that will be passed
on to my supervisor next Wednesday.
No. What I'm going to do
is hire a private investigator
to look into every aspect
of your life,
from the day you were born
until next Tuesday.
And then, I'm going to use
whatever it is they find
to make you wish
that your biggest problem
was keeping this job
that you seem to hate so much.
Yeah, I'm not like
every other lawyer, Glenda.
What did you say
your name was?
Specter. Harvey Specter.
You a baseball fan?
I am.
Then, I assume you know
Lou Gehrig was a bad man.
They didn't call him
"The Iron Horse" for nothing.
Then, he got ALS.
Do you know what it did to him?
His hands locked up,
then his legs.
His speech, eventually his breathing.
Couldn't control them.
His mind knew what it wanted,
but his body...
He was trapped inside,
unable to do anything.
Even today, you get ALS,
within three to five years, you die.
Or sooner, if someone takes your drug
and their liver fails.
Our drug makes people's
remaining years better,
and it doubles
their life expectancy.
Except for the people
whose livers are failing.
- You don't know...
- Lisa.
It's okay.
I can see why Jessica likes you.
You cut through the bullshit.
That's something
I always loved about her.
She just does it
with a little less charm than I do.
- Isn't she a little taller than you?
- It's the heels.
Let me tell you what it takes
to get a drug approved today.
We were 139 million into development
before we ever hit the shelves.
We jumped through every hoop
they threw at us
and we proved
our drug was safe for eight years.
So, you're saying
these claims are baseless?
We're talking about
six terminal patients
with a wide array
of medical issues,
and they're saying
my company's drug caused this?
They were drinking coffee
on the Titanic.
I don't think that put
Leonardo DiCaprio in the water.
Since Jessica
vouched for you,
I'm going to go ahead
and believe what you're telling me.
But since these other firms
determined you have exposure,
here's what we're going to do.
We're going to pay them.
We're going to pay them a little bit
of money so you can keep saving lives.
Because if we drag this out,
people won't think of your drug
as a way to save lives.
They'll think of it as a death sentence.
The guy from the housing department's
going to be here in about five minutes.
How did you manage that?
You know,
they're actually pretty receptive
when you explain the situation to them.
That's what
you have to do.
Prevent the spread.
I had to get rid of most of my things.
Clothes.
A record collection. Books.
I had a first edition
Catcher in the Rye.
- You know what that was worth?
- No.
The bugs can live dormant
for 18 months.
You just have to
throw everything out.
- Frank.
- Karinski.
- You're here.
- Yes.
- I live here.
- It's funny you should mention that.
Because you haven't paid rent
in four months, so I wasn't sure.
I haven't paid rent
because you haven't done...
My client has withheld rent
because the apartment is not habitable.
New York Housing Code,
subchapter two,
article four, section 27-20...
Hey. No rent, no apartment.
That's my code.
But if you want
something legal,
there's a court order.
You've got three days
to get out.
Or the Sheriff's department
will empty the place for you.
Have a nice day.
You're late.
- Look. It was Louis' pro bono. I, uh...
- Hey, that's my suit.
My extra suit,
from my office.
Yeah.
It's, uh, Louis' fault.
I went to the client's place.
It was overrun with bedbugs.
So, I went back
to the office.
Oh, you tracked bedbugs into my office?
- No.
- Oh, you walked in there naked?
No, Donna met me
in the downstairs Men's Room, and...
Okay. Donna's fired,
and you're buying me
an extra suit.
By the way, that's a three-piece suit.
Where's the vest?
Yeah, I've been meaning to talk to you
about that. Vests? Really?
Says the guy
with the bike helmet.
Uh, safety first.
Come on.
Ah.
The House that Amylinx built.
Nice. Very nice.
Collin Church, Mr. Sainz.
And Mr. Specter.
Lately arrived
to our little legal dispute.
You say legal dispute,
I say shakedown.
Always a fine line between the two,
n'est-ce pas?
Look, we could
sit here and posture
about the strengths and weaknesses
of our cases,
but frankly,
that's going to bore the hell out of me.
Seriously?
It could be much lower.
It could be much higher.
Then, let's pretend
it's just right.
My clients' lives
are being cut short.
And according
to accepted calculations,
the current value
of a life
is 7.9 million dollars.
You're not even
offering pennies on that.
Those happen to be
EPA calculations
based on
a full life expectancy.
Adjusted for plaintiffs whose expectancy
is just a fragment of this
yields a value
of $143,427.
Approximately.
What your child
fails to understand
is that
for someone with only
three to five years to live,
each day is worth infinitely more.
But the real crux
is the punitive damages.
Because if your client
wants to sell me the idea
that he didn't know about these side
effects years ago, I'm not buying it.
Which is why
we want $250 million.
- What?
- Quentin.
No.
This is outrageous.
Do you know
what you're doing?
You're bankrupting this company
and taking away years of life
from real people who are walking,
talking, and breathing easier
because of
the drug we make.
I don't represent those people.
My clients...
Have tenuous claims at best.
And unless one of your six is
Rupert Murdoch, you're out of your mind.
Okay.
You printed that?
Well, not yet.
But I will.
You realize
that's libelous.
Maybe it is,
maybe it isn't.
But after it runs, you and I
both know it won't much matter.
We're done here.
I don't take
to extortion.
I'm not going to be bullied
by an ambulance chaser,
no matter
how nice the suit.
It is nice, isn't it?
Italian. And it fits.
$250 million,
Mr. Sainz.
I'll give you
four days.
Church wants to play,
we play.
I have housing court
in the morning.
It's housing court.
Your grandmother could win.
Let's see just how real
his clients' liver problems are.
And if they are real, we suggest
they're from the disease itself.
Or they took
the wrong dose.
Or they took a cocktail
of combined drugs.
Also, I want to see
Quentin's company financials.
I already asked
for them once.
I want you to call them and follow up.
I want to know everything
Church could go after.
So, we've gone
from settlement to scorched earth.
I didn't feel like
writing a quarter billion dollar check.
- It's a negotiation.
- Exactly.
That's why I'm arming myself
for the next round.
By digging into Quentin?
I'm a boy scout.
I like to be prepared.
So, you think you'll look
like a boy scout
by putting dying people on the stand
and tearing them apart.
You're going to look
like an asshole.
For every one they claim has
a side effect, we have 600 who don't.
And if I need to look
like an asshole
to convince the jury
that hundreds
are more important
than the one,
I'm not going to lose
a minute's sleep over it.
Uh, I have court in...
In the morning.
Oh, I'm...
I'm not clear.
Was this a conversation
with my Managing Partner
or my client's ex-wife?
You need to settle this case,
Harvey.
Which I will do
if you stay out of it.
As you promised.
Make it go away.
- Rachel. I need to talk to you.
- Go away.
Uh-oh.
Who's picking on you now, Mikey?
Mom and dad
are fighting.
- Harvey and Jessica.
- What do you care?
Uh, I'm just rattled.
I have my first trial tomorrow.
Housing court.
Housing court?
I could win
at housing court.
You'll be fine.
But not
if you wear that suit.
Carvello v. Karinski Properties.
So, how does
this usually work?
Uh, well, usually,
the trial starts,
and, uh,
there's a judge.
And then, you know,
people say... Things.
You've never done this before,
have you?
Well, I never drove a car before
the first time I drove one,
and I'm still here,
aren't I?
Oh.
This is your first time?
I'm your first?
Don't worry.
I promise not to be gentle.
Frank,
it's nice to see you...
One last time.
Uh,
if it pleases the court...
It pleases the Court to decide
who speaks and when.
I'll sit down.
We're talking about
$4000 in withheld rent payments?
Uh, yes, Your Honor,
but we have receipts
for repairs,
lost clothing,
as well as...
$4000. Yes, Your Honor.
She was talking to me.
Why hasn't he paid,
Counselor?
Uh,
that one was for you.
Uh, bedbugs,
Your Honor.
I have receipts
that show
my client's
financial outlay
to rectify the problem
far exceeds the amount.
Housing Department
certified the presence of bedbugs?
- Uh, yes, Your Honor.
- Abatement?
- Uh...
- Excuse...
- Ex...
- I'll do it.
- There you go.
- That's...
Your Honor,
this is an eviction hearing.
The pertinent question
is not habitability,
but whether or not
rent has been paid.
Actually, city code states
that rent may be withheld
if the warranty of habitability
is breached.
In that case,
we request to see the checks
Mr. Ross' client
has placed in escrow.
- The... The...
- Checks.
In escrow.
Pending the outcome
of a rent abatement hearing?
That's not in the code.
It is the accepted practice.
And therefore,
binding in this courtroom.
Your client did put money in escrow,
I assume.
- I didn't have any money left. I had...
- Your Honor.
Eviction upheld.
- But Your Honor, he...
- Did you see me bang the gavel?
That means step aside.
Next case.
You never forget
your first.
You know what happens to pitchers when
they get shelled in Rookie League, Mike?
You think they
make it to the bigs?
Or do they just end up on some
sad American Legion team of has-beens?
I get it. I lost.
I'm sorry.
Well. You're sorry.
- In that case...
- No, I am sorry.
But right now,
I have some research to do for Harvey.
So, if you'll excuse me.
Remember when you stole that client
I had you bring in?
That was a good time for you,
wasn't it?
See, I gave you a nothing case
so that when you did win,
it would still do nothing
for your career.
But I still expected
you to win.
So, yeah.
I guess go back to your research.
Maybe that is your niche.
Maybe it is.
Most mornings,
I can make it out of the chair.
Get across the floor.
And I can hold my daughter.
How many were in the study?
Four hundred and twelve,
over two years.
And we have videos
of all of them.
Twenty-five percent
were given placebos.
The rest,
varying doses of Amylinx.
And more than half
are like that one,
showing significant
signs of improvement.
And you're telling me
there was nothing affecting the liver.
Yes.
And if you're just coming
to question that, we'll move on.
You don't like it that Quentin
went to his ex-wife, do you?
No, I don't.
I don't want any garbage from the past
getting in the way.
I mean, what Quentin's done here
is nothing short of miraculous.
I think I may have found a way
to keep that miracle going.
I was going through
the plaintiffs' medical files.
And then,
I found this.
This is good.
This is really good.
Jones v. Norco.
Washburn v. Hawthorne,
Incorporated.
Actually,
seven cases that Mr. Church
solicited lawsuits against
pharmaceutical companies.
In each case,
he was able
to exact a settlement
because the company knew
that even if they won,
a protracted battle
would do more damage than settling.
You have evidence of that?
Plaintiff number two in our case.
Eleanor Baker.
She also happens to be plaintiff
number seven in Jones v. Norco.
He's recycling plaintiffs.
That's very green of you.
Mr. Church?
Mr. Specter has his documents,
I have mine.
Showing that prior to FDA approval
of his drug,
Quentin Sainz company
was on the verge of bankruptcy.
Three months after that drug
hit the market,
sales rocketed
to $38 million a quarter.
Which is clear
financial motive
for falsifying
clinical trials.
Now, Your Honor, does that sound
like a groundless claim to you?
I told you
to go over those financials.
I asked them five times.
They never gave them to me.
- Your Honor.
- Mr. Specter.
You can question his tactics
all you'd like at trial. But he's right.
That right there
is financial motive for fraud.
This case
is moving forward.
Thank you, Your Honor.
- Jessica, what are you doing here?
- Get in.
I was just about to get some coffee.
Uh...
I heard about
your little setback in court.
Getting blind-sided by my own client
holding back isn't a setback.
- It's an embarrassment.
- What are you talking about?
Did you ever think
it's time to consider
that he isn't the upstanding man
that you think he is?
When we were married...
When I took a client
Quentin knew was guilty,
he never shut up about it.
He went on and on
about right and wrong.
Sounds annoyingly
self-righteous.
It was.
But it's also how I know
he didn't do this.
For all his faults,
Quentin has never lied to me before.
And he's not lying
about this.
So, stop questioning his ethics
and start winning this case.
We had a deal
that you were going to stay out of it.
You don't know
everything I know.
All right.
That's not
staying out of it.
No, you're right.
I'm not staying out of it anymore.
I'm sorry.
You looked into his background
this deeply?
The investigation
reveals what it reveals.
If he lied about this,
he could have lied about anything.
You think I didn't know he started
with Lisa before we were separated?
This is old news, Harvey.
I moved on a long time ago.
Jessica,
it's a pattern of behavior.
Quentin came to me because he knew
I thought he was a good man.
And I still do.
You obviously don't.
I'm taking the case.
What about Lisa?
If Lisa
has a problem with it,
then Lisa
can take it up with me.
It's kind of ironic isn't it?
You and I both lost in court yesterday?
You lost?
In Housing Court?
How does one lose
in Housing Court?
People win there
without lawyers.
Well, he had a lawyer.
Tanaka. And she...
Vivien Tanaka?
Yeah. What, you know her?
If your landlord is using Vivien Tanaka,
this isn't about bedbugs.
Vivien Tanaka represents
half the high-rises in Manhattan.
This isn't a petty rent dispute.
Your guy's going condo.
Well, that's great.
Forcing Frank out for a conversion
is harassment.
I can go after him
for that.
No.
You want to take down Vivien?
You better go in there
with more than just one client.
You show the pattern,
the settlement goes up.
If they did this to him,
I guarantee they've done this to others.
So, I should find other people
in Frank's building?
Think bigger.
Bigger how?
Karinski owns five buildings.
And they all used to be
rent-controlled.
But now,
they go for a million and a half a unit.
Nice profit margin.
I went to look
for Housing Department complaints
in the year prior
to his remodel.
In each one of them, tenants
who couldn't buy into the conversion
ended up
with some complaint.
You know, garbage, heat, air.
All of them.
One by one,
Karinski drove them out.
You couldn't get their names
from Housing Complaints?
No. He gave me some names, but I need to
make this bigger than just his building.
Look, I only get one hour off a day
for lunch, and I never take it.
You really need me
for this?
You see these people
who are leaving the building?
Mmm-hmm.
The entire building
looks like them.
I know I clean up okay,
but...
Mmm. You need me
to class you up a bit.
- Not class. But...
- Class.
Whatever
gets you through the door.
- Alright. You ready?
- Yeah.
Hi, there. Uh, my wife and I
are here to see some of the new units.
Isn't that right, honey?
So, what do you think,
sweetheart?
Hmm, it's fine.
But I liked the place on 52nd better.
Fifty-second? That's awful close
to your mother.
No, no.
We're not talking about my mother.
Oh, I... Okay.
That doesn't matter to me.
I mean, I love being near your mother.
I love your mother.
Crazy.
So, why don't you tell us something
about your little building?
Well, I think you'll find that not only
are the amenities top quality,
- so are the tenants.
- That's good to hear.
You know, because we're not just looking
at buying square footage,
but really put down
some roots.
That is such the right way
to look at it.
- Is it?
- Yes. And I think you'll also find
that the people who've bought here,
they're like you.
They're young, ambitious.
We're acting.
It's just,
you keep touching me.
Is there a problem?
Any other questions I can answer?
I'm sorry. My wife, here...
My beautiful wife
just gets a little paranoid sometimes.
You know, you wouldn't believe
how long it took her
to just go out with me
in the first place.
Forever.
Are there any other tenants
who have been here for a while?
You know, who might be able to show us
the ins and outs of the place?
The neighborhood?
Well, the building
was totally renovated two years ago.
So, most of our tenants are newer.
We only reopened in January.
Mmm.
But I think there are
some of the old tenants who bought in.
Do you think that we might be able
to speak to them?
Just to be sure.
It would really make us
feel more comfortable.
Ow.
She's feisty.
- So in love.
- Yes.
- Yes, we are.
You came to me
because you wanted someone
who knows you always tell the truth.
- Well, you don't.
- What are you talking about?
Lisa.
I asked you back then
if anything had started
before we were separated.
You said it hadn't,
and I believed you.
Because I didn't
want to hurt you.
You want to know
what hurts me?
I thought it was my ambition
that caused our divorce.
- I never said that.
- No.
But you let me believe it.
I shouldn't have started with Lisa
when I did.
But it happened long after you and I
both know we weren't working.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I didn't have the courage
to tell you then.
What about now?
Now?
They're manipulating
the facts.
And I'm not going to apologize
just because we happened to hit it big
when I was about to lose everything.
I'm going to defend you
either way.
Because I took this case,
and that's what I do.
But if I'm going
to stake my reputation on this,
then I need to know
if there are any other lies
that are going to come up
and sandbag me.
And I need to know
right now.
Thanks.
I see I have
some catching up to do.
People are stupid
when they're young.
Do you want to know why?
I want to know why they're stupid
all the other years of their lives.
Glenfiddich. Smooth.
That's nice.
You never got married.
Now we're sharing
our personal lives?
Till death do us part.
I actually believed it.
Did he falsify
the clinical trials?
He says
he wouldn't do that.
So, why are we drinking?
He says
he wouldn't do that
because he needs
the drug to work.
He's dying.
Quentin has ALS.
Ms. Parker,
how long have you worked for Mr. Sainz?
Well, technically,
I'm an independent consultant.
But I've been a part of Amylinx
from the beginning.
Yes.
I imagine you have been.
We're just trying to establish
your credentials for testifying for him.
How long have you known
Quentin had ALS?
- From the beginning.
- And how long have you known
Quentin falsified trial results
to get the drug on the market?
To save his own life.
What?
No. He wouldn't do that.
Come on, Lisa.
We're all
on the same team here.
We're trying to figure out
how to protect the man you love.
Well,
I thought you believed in him.
You slept with Quentin
while he was married to me.
He said it never happened,
and I believed him.
But I have learned
that he can lie.
So, do I believe in him now?
No.
This is damage control.
We're just trying to protect him.
Because they will find out
and he will get caught.
And if you don't tell us
the real facts,
we can't mitigate
the damage from his lie.
But he didn't lie.
I swear he didn't.
But you did,
didn't you?
He was sick.
He needed the drug,
and you would have done anything
for FDA approval.
Come on, Lisa.
Help us help him.
You didn't see
what he was like.
He was barely Quentin then.
And then, he got better.
And I've never seen
anything like it.
I was the one to see it.
See what, exactly?
Six months in,
one person out of the hundreds
started showing signs of liver damage.
And that would
jeopardize approval.
Yeah, and I couldn't take that chance.
So, I took the person out of the study.
You never told Quentin?
No. He would have waited.
And we didn't have the time.
He didn't have the time.
And I love him.
So, what else could I do?
Look,
there is an upside to all of this.
Upside?
To the fact that I
unknowingly defrauded the FDA?
Well, the key word
is "Unknowingly."
Lisa is an outside contractor.
The company may be liable
for actual damages,
but we can shift the blame
for the fraud to Lisa.
There would be
a small payment,
but you might be able
to keep the drug on the market.
And throw Lisa
under the bus?
She was throwing you
under the bus.
She was trying
to save my life.
Would there be
criminal charges?
Possibly.
She should get her own lawyer.
It's a conflict for us.
Look,
our goal is to protect you.
I don't know.
There is an alternative.
You can join
Church's lawsuit.
Jessica,
we're lawyers for the company.
We can't advise him
to do that.
- Harvey, this is his life.
- That's not the point.
This is my case,
my call.
Wait, wait, wait.
What would that mean?
Sainz Pharmaceuticals
would go down,
but you'd share
in the settlement.
You could open
a new company.
Keep the drug alive
under a different corporate umbrella.
I'm not pretending
I'm one of them.
You are one of them.
I can't do that.
It's not who I am.
Now,
isn't there another way?
You are one of them.
And they're one of you.
Mike, we've got work to do.
Where are you?
Oh, I'm looking at you right now
in conference room C.
I'm sorry.
Can you please excuse me?
AA meeting?
Here in the office?
Funny.
No, it's my law suit.
- Which suit is that?
- Against Johnny Karinski.
Between Frank's building and the one
Rachel and I are about to buy into.
Oh, yeah.
Uh, we're married.
It's a long story.
Look, you said think bigger. Right?
I tracked down 15 former tenants
who are willing to testify
to all manner of harassment that forced
them out of their apartments.
You did this overnight?
Yeah.
I couldn't sleep, anyway.
I kept thinking
I felt bedbugs.
But I get these people
in front of a judge to tell their story,
and there is no way that Vivien Tanaka
can spin this to save Karinski's ass.
You should
hear their stories.
It would
break your heart.
Yeah,
if you had a heart.
Emotion is fine, but you better have
some cold, hard facts to back it up.
Because Vivien Tanaka
is no pushover.
But... It's good work.
Keep at it.
I'm going to go do
what I've got to go do.
We need more.
How are we
going to get more?
Mike?
Is this the building
we were in yesterday?
No rent, no apartment.
That's my code.
Yeah. Before and after.
We need to go
carpet shopping.
I see you found my ad.
Trying to steal my thunder,
Harvey?
Business School 101. You have a crisis,
you acknowledge the problem.
You want to be Tylenol,
not Toyota.
A little late for you to acknowledge
this is a crisis.
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you
very much for coming here today.
Quentin Sainz
placed this ad
because your lawsuit made it clear
that his drug
had side effects
that he didn't know about.
We wanted to know
how widespread this problem was.
We had an outpouring
of response.
Not from people
struggling like yourselves,
but from people desperate
to keep the drug available.
You think we're lying.
You're here because you think this
company has been hiding things from you.
And you're right.
They have.
But Quentin
wants to come clean.
He wants to show you exactly
what it is that he's been hiding.
I can't really open it.
I can't hold anything.
And, uh, I don't know how much longer
I can keep working.
It will get better.
It will.
You know it will.
I guess.
I bet my life on it.
It's not fair you got ALS
in the first place.
And it's definitely not fair you had
side effects from the drug I created
and I didn't.
But now
that I know they exist,
I want to fix them.
So that people like you...
And maybe even you
can have
what I have right now.
But he can't.
He can't if he gives you
what you're asking.
We're not saying
that you don't deserve compensation.
Our commitment to you
is this.
We are offering you
partial ownership
in his company.
A company
that is trying to save lives.
Money isn't going
to help you live longer.
Taking the deal
and letting Quentin
try and fix the problem could.
Like it or not,
you're all in the same boat.
Give Quentin the opportunity
to keep that boat from sinking.
They really
took the offer.
Uh-huh.
Church didn't like it.
- Hmm.
- But they didn't like Church.
- They liked you.
- Hmm.
And me.
Who wouldn't?
Oh, your mother
was never a fan.
Want to know the truth?
My father wasn't much of a fan, either.
Now, that is a lie and I know it.
Real truth is, they'd both
take you over Lisa in a minute.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
From now on,
back to no more lies.
Well,
if we're going to do that...
You remember that time
that your Jag got side-swiped
when it was parked
outside the house?
Yeah.
Yeah, it didn't exactly
go down that way.
I was mad.
You were mad.
Oh, you brought a sack lunch.
We would have shared.
Amusing.
As was this.
Your little lawsuit.
Take your sack of presents and run, kid.
You're in way over your head.
Oh, I think
he'll be just fine.
Hello, Vivien.
Hello.
So, the rookie
called in the veteran.
No, no. I'm just here to watch.
I love spectator sports.
You enjoy watching the Yankees
destroy a little league team?
David and Goliath happens to be
one of my favorite stories.
Okay. I'll bite.
What's in the bag?
Hey, hey.
What are you doing?
Oh.
Do you recognize this carpet?
Make him
get that out of here.
This is your own carpet, Mr. Karinski.
It's from Frank Carvello's apartment.
Come on.
You feel the fibers, the texture.
It's almost alive.
You brought bedbugs in here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
That's vandalism! Assault!
You know,
I'm happy that you put it that way,
because that's exactly what we're
going to be charging your client with.
What are you talking about?
He didn't just fail
to eradicate a bedbug infestation.
He actually created one.
Yeah, he pulled the carpet
from one of his old buildings,
carpet that was already infested,
and then, he re-installed it in
my client's apartment to drive him out.
That's crazy.
You might want to warn your client
about perjury.
We've got sworn testimony
from the installer.
And a picture
of the same carpet
from one of his old buildings
before it was renovated.
By the way, my wife and I really love
what you've done with the place.
So, it looks like
we're talking about, what,
assault, violations of rental codes,
health codes,
and you know,
just basic codes of human decency.
And if a jury in New York
heard all that?
Wow. Imagine the damages.
Harvey, spectate. Please.
Just get that carpet
out of here.
So, Vivien,
how am I doing
for my first time?
This still counts
as my first time, doesn't it?
Now, let's talk about
how much this is going to cost you.
Yes?
Just thought
you'd like to know.
Your case,
the pro bono?
I won.
How exciting for you.
But like I said,
it's just a pro bono case.
It's not going
to help your career.
I did also manage
to sign 15 new clients
who are all suing
for the same harassment.
And they will be paying.
So, you can multiply this number
times 15.
That's not bad
for Rookie League.
Come on. Tell me that wasn't worth
missing your lunch hour for.
Mmm.
Makes me proud to be your wife.
Oh. Yeah, wait.
What is this coming up?
Is that our third
or our fourth anniversary?
- It's our fifth.
- Ah.
Doesn't it mean
anything to you?
Yeah. In fact, I think that we should
have a date night and celebrate.
- You're funny.
- Hey.
I'm serious.
I can't date anyone
from the office.