You're Chloe's mother.
You... you said she wasn't eating.
I thought I could help.
- I'm really sorry.
- Oh. Oh, my gosh.
I gotta go. I have to go.
Listen, wait. I... I should tell you
that I called Social Services.
What does that mean?
They're coming tomorrow
to take custody of Chloe.
Oh... Sorry...
Hello, Lilly...
Now what'd you do?
Lilly is Chloe's mother.
Wh... And what proof do you have?
I just found her breastfeeding the baby.
Oh, you have no idea
what you're talking about.
Uh... Are you being serious?
Unlike you city people, folks around here,
we don't just leap to conclusions.
Oh, really? Okay.
Because you made up your mind about me
before we even started working together.
Oh, no, no, no.
That was professional intuition.
Hm. Okay. Well, Lilly just admitted
to being Chloe's mother,
which leads me to believe that your
intuition is as outdated as your office.
Come back to bed.
I, uh... gotta get to work.
I'll make it worth your while.
I'm late as it is.
Can't Preacher open the bar?
Hm?
Oh, I just gotta check in.
Hmm.
My first client at the salon
isn't until nine.
I can make you breakfast in bed.
I gotta go.
Okay.
- Oh, next Friday...
- Yeah.
...I was thinking, after dinner,
I could spend the night at your place.
Hm?
It's our two-year anniversary.
- Oh.
- Mm.
See, um...
I didn't think we were
doing anniversaries.
Well...
maybe it's time we started.
I just thought it might be nice.
Well, things are nice...
the way they are.
- She is a loose cannon.
- You can't fire Mel.
Yeah, she broke protocol.
This isn't the army.
No, it is my business,
and I get to run it the w...
Well, you have made quite a mess.
We are mandated by law
to report child abandonment.
I made the right decision.
Don't you lecture me.
I'm not lecturing you.
I'm reminding you of your oath and duty
as a physician.
Okay, okay. Both of you,
back to your corners.
- She started this.
- Hah...
First things first.
No one else can know
that Lilly is Chloe's mother.
She doesn't need anyone else
running her business
through the town gossip mill.
Agreed.
Second, we need to talk some sense
into Lilly before Social Services arrives.
- I went out there to see her this morning.
- And?
I couldn't even get inside.
This is not the Lilly I know.
At her age, a... a secret pregnancy,
then abandoning her baby?
Something's wrong with her.
She might have postpartum depression.
No, Lilly's never been depressed
a day in her life.
This is more than just being depressed.
It's a serious condition
that can happen after giving birth,
and it can appear without warning.
So, what are we gonna do about Chloe?
Well, I spoke to Social Services.
The way things stand,
Chloe will probably be placed
into temporary foster care,
which means she will have foster parents.
Parents who could bond with her,
parents who would seek
to terminate Lilly's parental rights.
And once Chloe's in the system,
it's gonna be tough
gettin' her back to Lilly.
- How much time do we have?
- Not much.
You know, the Social Services person
is gonna show up here this afternoon,
and with Lilly not cooperatin',
I mean, we have got ourselves a situation.
She has grown children.
Maybe one of them could take Chloe.
I think that's called kinship placement.
That could work.
Well, before she slammed the door
in my face,
she said she did not want
to get her family involved.
Does she have a husband?
- He died about... six months ago.
- Yeah.
So, she's isolated,
with limited social support.
That's not an ideal situation
for someone battling depression.
I can talk to her.
Oh, please. I think you've done enough.
Well, I don't see you
coming up with any solutions.
- Well, I'm...
- What if I volunteer to foster Chloe?
- Until Lilly gets better.
- Anyone not directly related to Chloe
has got to be vetted,
and that could take weeks or months.
There's gotta be someone.
Well, the only people cleared to... to step
in are licensed healthcare providers,
and... and I don't know the first thing
about babies.
But I know a wonderful
healthcare provider.
I'm gonna check on Chloe.
What did you do that for?
You need to rehire Mel, ASAP.
- Absolutely not.
- Why?
Because she defied you?
You need her help with Lilly,
and she's the only one fit to take Chloe.
She was the one who quit first.
I mean, I... I suggest you find yourself
another solution.
If you turn down Mel's help,
and Lilly loses her baby,
I'm going to blame you.
Now, Hope, ju...
Hope, don't...
What... what'd that wall ever do to you?
Nothin' that I know of.
You all right?
I'm good. I'm good.
We just gotta move this along.
- What's the rush?
- We need Mel to stay.
We?
Virgin River needs her.
Doc isn't getting any younger.
Yeah, she's the hottest doctor
I think I have ever seen.
Hey, hey. She's a nurse practitioner,
and you just be respectful.
And that windowsill is still crooked.
So, I, uh... I heard you found a baby
on Doc's doorstep.
Oh, you did, did you?
And where did you hear that?
My grandma.
She got a call from some lady on the PTA.
- Yeah, word travels fast around here.
- Yeah.
I... I had to sit through a lecture
about being a gentleman with the ladies.
Your grandmother has a point.
I hope you're smart enough
to stay out of trouble.
Can we go on talkin' about the hot doctor?
Hey. What'd I say about being respectful?
Okay. I'm sorry, but respectfully,
you know, she's extremely...
Okay.
- I'm gonna head back to the bar.
- Okay.
- I, uh... I got this.
- All right.
Hey.
You look serious.
And you look sweaty.
I was helping out a friend.
- So, where's Chloe?
- Uh, Paige volunteered to watch her.
She eating any better?
No. She hates the bottle,
and she's barely eating enough
to keep up her weight,
which means she's hungry and cranky.
Well, how are you holdin' up?
I mean, between Chloe and work,
you must be exhausted.
Yeah. Well, no work today,
'cause I got fired yesterday.
- Why?
- Well, he refused to call Social Services,
so I did.
Well, for the record,
I think you were right to do what you did.
Thank you.
You want me to talk to Doc for you?
No. No, no, no. This is my problem.
Thank you for offering, though.
Sure.
Have you eaten?
- No, I'm not hungry.
- No, come on. You gotta eat.
Well, I have to go pick up Chloe
from Paige, so...
Okay. Then why don't I fix some food,
and we'll take it to go?
A little fresh air will be good
for both your appetites, I think.
- Fresh air?
- Yeah.
- Ah. Where is this fresh air, exactly?
- Well, you'll see when we get there.
Ah... Jack, I'm not really up
for surprises today.
I'm gonna pick you and Chloe up
from your place in an hour.
Uh...
Come on, this is good stuff.
Yeah, it is.
Just a little more. Just a little more.
Come on.
Just a little more.
A little more, baby.
oh!
Oh, my...
Wait a minute. Where's my epidural?
You said you didn't want one.
- I... I changed my mind. I need it.
- Shh...
- You, of all people, know it's too late.
- What?
What?
Have you ever been in labor?
Somebody needs to get me some painkillers.
No, sweetheart,
you wanted a natural birth.
- Oh, screw natural. Come on.
- Uh...
We're beyond the point of no return.
- The baby's head is crowning.
- What?
- We have to do this old-school, okay?
- No.
- We?
- You. You are amazing.
- Okay? You are.
- I'm not amazing.
I'm trying to squeeze a watermelon
out of me without any drugs.
- Okay. Listen to me.
- This is your fault.
And I'm very sorry, okay?
Mom, one last good push.
- You got this.
- Ready?
You got it, Mel.
You didn't call me back.
- I was worried.
- I'm fine.
Well, you sound stressed.
Why don't you come home?
Uh... There was, um...
a complication with the baby,
and I'm... I'm thinking of becoming
her temporary caregiver.
As in fostering?
- Yeah.
- That's a horrible idea.
Wow! Okay, don't...
don't beat around the bush.
No, I am serious.
Taking on someone else's baby would be
a huge mistake at this point in your life.
And what point am I at, exactly?
You're obviously
not thinking rationally.
You don't know what I'm thinking.
You're right, I don't.
But I know that a baby is not the answer.
It's...
I'm the only one
that can keep her in Virgin River.
No, it is not your responsibility, okay?
You need to take care of yourself.
Joey, you don't understand.
Mel, I was there with you.
Start to finish.
I helped you pick up the pieces.
Don't you remember?
Yeah. Yeah.
How could I possibly forget when you're
constantly reminding me how broken I am?
No, that is not what I'm saying.
- Yeah, it is. You just don't realize it.
- ♪ Turn out the light ♪
♪ Goin' into the dark ♪
♪ And into the night ♪
♪ Singin' our songs ♪
♪ All in reverse ♪
♪ Givin' more time ♪
- You're on my side, aren't you?
- ♪ And I won't give up ♪
Yeah.
Sweet thing.
Hi.
Oh, I thought Preacher
didn't allow you back here
since the Great Grease Fire of 2012.
It's peanut butter and jelly.
Oh, I always took you
for a roast beef kind of guy.
I'm taking Mel out to lunch by the river.
Pray that it works, because I need you
to counteract the calamity
Doc's created between the two of them.
Firing her didn't help things.
I'm working on mending that fence.
You focus on showing her
what Virgin River has to offer.
Gourmet peanut butter and jelly?
- Heaven help us.
- No, I've got chips and sodas.
Out of the kitchen.
Leave the food to me.
Leave the lunch to me.
You can't make important decisions
while eating peanut butter.
Lemon wedges go behind the bar.
If we put 'em here,
customers can help themselves
without havin' to ask us every time.
You really think it's a good idea
for people to be puttin' their dirty hands
in the same bowl over and over?
Come on, man. What's your problem?
They're just lemons.
We got systems here, Brady.
And we're not about to change 'em
just because you're too lazy
to do things right.
Hey.
When are we gonna flip pancakes?
Oh, it's a little late
in the day for that, sweetheart.
- Preacher promised.
- Hey, listen.
Buddy, as soon as
we finish this dessert order,
you and I, we will whip up
some pancakes, hm?
If it's okay with you.
It's fine,
if it's really okay with you.
- He just said it was.
- It is.
- Yes!
Oh, uh... by the way, I'm going to start
paying all the vendors by check.
So, I just need to know if you want me
to write the checks in your name
or the bakery's.
Uh... I prefer cash.
Well, yeah,
it's just that the, uh, accountant
has requested a more legitimate
paper trail.
Okay. Well, what if you write
my weekly check out to yourself,
then cash it, then pay me that?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure our accountant
wouldn't consider that legitimate.
The thing is,
I don't have a checking account.
Well, that's okay. I can, um...
I can write the checks out to the bakery.
- The bakery doesn't either.
- Oh.
I've never worked with a business
that didn't... didn't have a bank account.
Well, I guess I just do things
a little different than everyone else.
Okay.
- Well, I'm sure we can work something out.
- Yeah. Can we talk about this later?
Yeah. Yeah, sure, if that's what you want.
- Okay.
Preacher? Honey, can you whip me up
a tuna melt real quick?
Yeah, sure, um... just as soon as I finish
up some business with Paige, yeah.
Oh, yeah, speaking of business.
Have either of you heard anything more
about that abandoned baby?
- Someone left their baby?
- No, honey, they didn't.
They sure did. I'm thinkin' it's gotta
be someone from out of town.
You know, I just can't see anyone
from Virgin River doing this.
You never know. People do crazy things
when they're desperate.
Well, I don't care.
It's unforgivable.
You know,
I actually have to get back to work.
- Come on, Chris, let's pack up.
- What about the pancakes?
- We'll do it another time, sweetheart.
- Aww.
Thank you.
- Thanks, Preacher.
- Yeah.
See ya, Connie.
I will be right back with that tuna melt.
Oh, thank you, honey.
Oh, and will you add a little extra cheese
for me while you're at it?
Okay.
Thanks.
- Hope.
- Ah.
- How'd it go?
- This ought to do the trick.
Ooh. Thank you.
Keep Mel in town, we'll be square.
I'll do my best.
Oh... Ohh.
Ahem.
Hope, what's the 411 on that baby?
Did you find the mother?
Still no word.
- No clues? Really?
- Mm.
I'm thinkin' it's gotta be someone
from one of those pot farms.
What makes you say that?
Well, you can't hide a pregnancy.
I mean, if it was someone in our orbit,
we'd have heard about it.
- Mm.
- I'll give Mary Ellen another call.
She's got her sewin' circle
spreadin' the word.
Mm.
We need to get this Lilly thing resolved.
Connie's got everyone in Humboldt County
looking for Chloe's mother.
Well, she does have a knack of spreadin'
gossip, particularly when gossip
- is shrouded in altruism.
- Yeah.
- Did you try speaking with Lilly again?
And I know I don't have
a lot of experience treatin' postpartum,
but I gotta tell you,
- she is in bad, bad shape.
- Mm.
Well, you know who does have experience?
A midwife. If only we had one here.
Like it or not,
this is no longer a solo mission.
You need help.
And you need to ask Mel for it.
She doesn't respect my authority.
She thinks for herself.
That used to be a quality you admired.
She looks so peaceful.
Man, what I wouldn't give
to feel half that relaxed.
Oh, what,
so this calm exterior is just an act?
No, I'd say it's more
of a well-rehearsed habit.
Yeah.
I know it well.
In the ER,
you can't exhibit signs of stress,
'cause it freaks out the patients.
Finally, we get a peek
behind the curtain, huh?
What does that mean?
Well, you seem so cool and collected.
Oh, I wouldn't say that.
Well, then you're confident.
I definitely wouldn't say that.
Oh, come on.
What, you moved to a... a new town, alone,
in the middle of nowhere.
You immediately go head-to-head
with the world's crustiest boss.
That's impressive.
Is that what you think of me?
Hm?
Impressive?
Yeah.
Hm.
Anyway, while we're being honest,
I can't take credit for lunch.
This is all Hope.
- Aah! God, she is everywhere, isn't she?
- Yep.
You know, she told me about Lilly.
She shouldn't have done that.
Ah, she's... worried.
No, Doc should not have told Hope.
Hope should not have told you.
It's a violation
of patient confidentiality.
Well, she wasn't gossiping.
She's just trying to help.
No, I know, but it doesn't matter why.
She's still crossing a line doing that.
Mm.
You know, I'm thinking of becoming
Chloe's temporary guardian.
- Whoa.
- Yeah.
It's just the only chance I think she has
of staying in town.
That's a big responsibility.
I know.
I really had no idea
what this job was gonna be like.
Well, sometimes those turn out
to be the best jobs.
You think?
Yeah.
When I signed up for the Marines at 18,
whew!
I had no clue.
Now, it's...
...part of my DNA.
Yeah, well...
I don't think that, uh, Virgin River
is ever gonna be a part of my DNA.
Well, never say never.
I think never is the most likely choice.
So, just come back in ten minutes.
I'll be right back.
Give you guys some time.
Thank you.
♪ Don't tell me the truth ♪
♪ Tell me that didn't happen ♪
- Do you wanna hold her?
- ♪ There's been a mistake ♪
- ♪ There's been a misunderstanding ♪
- What did I do wrong?
It was a placental abruption.
There was nothing that anyone
could have done.
♪ Dirty your hands ♪
♪ Tearing my heart into pieces ♪
- I can't breathe.
- Hey, just relax.
Relax. Sh, sh, sh. sh.
- It's okay.
- ♪ if this is the end ♪
- I got you. In and out, okay?
- ♪ Then we whisper the wind ♪
- Yeah.
- ♪ And release it ♪
♪ We don't have to know ♪
We almost lost you in there.
- You know that?
- ♪ We don't have it all worked out ♪
- The doctor saved your life.
- ♪ We can just ♪
- ♪ Keep walking ♪
- He saved the wrong life.
- ♪ Blind ♪
- Don't say that, because I need you. Okay?
I need you. And we are going
to get through this together.
I want my baby.
- Please.
- I want my baby.
I know, sweetheart. I want her too.
I can't do this.
I can't do this! I can't do this!
- ♪ Keep walking ♪
- You can if you want to.
- ♪ Blind ♪
- What?
You said you can't do this.
I think you can.
You don't know me very well.
I know you fight for what you believe in.
And if Chloe gets sent to Social Services,
I know you'll find another way
to help her and Lilly.
And you know how I know that?
- Shh, shh, shh.
- You are relentless
- when it comes to helping people.
- It's okay. It's okay.
Okay.
It's okay.
Wow, would you look at that?
Incredible.
Mmm... Like I said...
never say never.
...what I'm asking...
I didn't ask you to do this
just to be, you know, asking.
Ahem. What's going on?
Doc has something
he wants to... to say to you.
Right?
Yes?
- Vernon Edwin Mullins, speak.
- Ahem.
It... it's just unusual, uh,
that I get, uh... served up a situation
where I can't solve the problem.
And this thing with Lilly's depression,
just... it's... it's a tough nut to crack.
I'm happy to go talk to her,
if that's what you're asking.
Well, I don't see how you
could make it any worse.
You know, I don't need your approval.
If you'd just listened to me,
Social Services wouldn't be
on the way here to pick up Lilly's baby.
I'm never going to apologize
for doing my job.
No, of course you won't,
'cause you don't understand
that in Virgin River,
we believe our job
is to take care of each other.
Not just ourselves.
Whoa! Hey... Let's just remember
why we're all here.
We all want what's best for Lilly.
Jack, can you drive us to Lilly's so...
Doc can stay behind
to meet Social Services?
Sure. Come on.
You can ride shotgun.
Do... Well, shouldn't Mel stay behind?
She's the one who called.
Vernon, so help me,
you are jangling my last nerve.
For once, just do as you're asked.
Oh...
I can't talk right now.
Listen, I get it. Okay?
You're feeling alone and ashamed.
I left my baby.
Lilly, you're experiencing
a hormonal imbalance.
It has nothing to do with whether or not
you're a good mother.
I think you have postpartum depression.
It can alter your perception of reality.
But the good news is that it's treatable.
No. J...
She's better off with someone else.
A good person.
- You are a good person, Lilly.
- I can't take care of her.
Okay?
I'm not a young woman anymore. And...
...with Buck gone...
the farm alone is too much for me.
If that's the way you really feel,
then I understand.
But can you do something for me
before I go?
Oh...
- Oh, God.
- No, no...
- The whole town know?
- It's just Hope and Jack.
I can't look them in the eye.
They must think I'm...
No. They think that you're not feeling
well, and they're worried about you.
What is it you want me to do?
If you're gonna give up your daughter,
just... spend a little time with her.
You're trying to trick me.
No. Honestly, I'm not trying to trick you.
It's just that this is gonna be
your last opportunity to say goodbye.
Come on.
Hey, is something wrong with the pies?
No.
No, not at all.
In fact, the strawberry is a big hit.
- Oh.
- I just, um...
I just feel, you know,
badly about earlier,
you know, with the whole, uh...
you know, the whole check thing.
Oh, don't worry about it.
I mean, I'll figure something out.
If I have to, I'll find a third-party
vendor to run the checks through.
Listen, Paige, if, um... if you're willing
to go through that much trouble,
then it obviously, you know,
means a lot to you.
So, we can keep things the way they are.
You know, money-wise.
Really? I'd appreciate that.
Hell, I don't trust banks either.
My mom always told me to keep some bills
under my mattress in case of emergency.
Well, thank you for understanding.
- So, we're good?
- Of course.
Preacher!
Hey, little dude, hm?
Mm, mm!
Can I help in the kitchen
tomorrow morning?
Well, that is up to your mom.
Sure, as long as he's no trouble for you.
I'm no trouble, right, Preach?
Trouble?
An extra set of hands at the griddle?
You would be doing me a favor.
In fact, I think I could use some help
prepping right now.
Can I, Mom? Please?
Okay, but just for a little bit.
- Yes!
- All right.
Thanks.
Okay. I got your door!
Go.
On three. Ho, three. Mm! Oh.
All right, let's do this, Master Chef.
Mm!
That's all...
hers.
At one point, the boundary ran way back...
Lilly wants me to sit with her
and the baby.
Why don't you two... take a walk,
give me some time?
- Well, I don't really wanna go too far.
- Jack knows the place.
- He'll... he'll keep you close.
- Yeah, we can just walk the farm.
Standing around worrying isn't gonna
do anyone any good, including Lilly.
Go.
It's no use fighting.
This is a pretty big farm for Lilly
to handle all by herself.
Yeah.
It was a shame when Buck died.
Most of the workers left, and I mean,
everyone from town came out
and tried to help where they could,
but she put a stop to that.
Said she wasn't interested in charity.
So...
I mean,
losing Buck just about destroyed her.
Farm life is hard.
I mean, none of the kids wanted to stay,
and she was too proud to ask 'em to.
Yeah.
I can understand not wanting
to burden your family and friends.
Well, I don't see helping someone
you love as...
an obligation.
I mean, to me it's an opportunity
to show gratitude, right?
Well, yeah, but you know,
if you're the one that needs the help,
sometimes it can make you feel weak.
True, but...
well, that's why family and friends
should be there
to help you get strong again.
Yeah. I guess I never looked at it
like that before.
I'd just hate to see her have any regrets,
you know?
You know, my sister and I used to
have one of these when we were kids.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
You guys close growing up?
Yeah. We were best friends.
We're still really close now,
but, you know...
sometimes I feel like
she doesn't know who I am.
So, who are you?
You know what?
Most days I don't even know who I am.
It was my dream when I was younger
to be a vet.
Have a big farmhouse
and fill it with kids.
Well, dreams are funny things.
They can come true
when you least expect it.
We should go.
Yeah?
Are you coming?
Yeah.
I tried to get Lilly
to call one of her daughters,
but she wouldn't budge.
And Doc called. He's on his way
with the lady from Social Services.
Well, you want me to try talking to Lilly?
No. I'm gonna try one more time.
- Here.
- Oh, gosh, thanks, Jack.
Baby.
You gotta get up and out of this room.
Okay.
You promised me...
when I left this morning.
You promised.
I wish I was dead.
Mel.
It's how I feel.
You won't always feel this way.
I ca...
I can't live without her.
Hey, we're gonna get through this.
- I won't get through this.
- Yeah. Yes.
- I won't.
- You...
You're strong.
- I'm not strong anymore.
- Yes, you are. You're strong.
Hey.
- It's my baby.
- You can do this.
There's nothing more to say.
- Lilly...
- Please. Please. I'm... I'm so tired.
I... I just want to be left alone.
I lost my baby.
It was a few years ago.
And I was so excited.
I'd always wanted to be a mother.
But there was, um...
there was a complication during delivery,
and she was stillborn.
There was nothing they could do.
I'm really sorry.
But... why are you telling me this?
After her death,
I couldn't get out of bed.
Like, it was days before
I could even sit upright.
I was just sad all the time.
Something as simple
as brushing my teeth...
would send me into hysterics.
I even thought about taking my own life.
But eventually, my husband
dragged me to the doctor,
and she told me
that what I had wasn't just grief.
It was postpartum depression.
So, you understand.
I do understand.
But... with therapy and medication,
I started feeling like myself again.
I was still...
heartbroken...
over losing my baby,
but that sadness
was no longer controlling me.
It's too late. They're taking her away.
It's not too late.
I'm a certified caregiver.
So, if you want, Social Services
will allow me to look after Chloe
until you can get back up on your feet.
And that way,
- she doesn't have to leave Virgin River.
- No. I don't know. It's too much.
You barely know me.
You know, someone just reminded me
the value in accepting help
when it's offered.
What if when I'm better, um...
I still can't take care of her?
I'm sure the town would love
nothing more than to help you and Chloe.
Oh...
Just think about it, okay?
They've been in there a long time.
Sure would be nice if I could read lips.
Hope. Get away.
What do you think they're saying?
Look, I don't like eavesdropping
on other people's private affairs.
Oh, you're about as helpful
as tits on a bull.
What did you and Lilly discuss?
Though it pains me to say it,
I'm gonna have to side with Doc
on this one.
I think Lilly deserves her privacy.
Hah!
- Well, don't look at me.
- The suspense is killing me.
Oh, I'm not that lucky.
You know, whatever decision Lilly makes,
she's gonna need our support.
She's gonna need medical help
either way.
Yeah, leaving her depression untreated
can be dangerous.
I'll personally make sure
she's looked after.
I'll second that.
Oh. Um... Could you come sit
with Terry and me?
Have a seat, you guys.
Hi, just have a seat, Doc.
Hey.
Okay.
Um...
Uh...
Lilly and I have talked at length.
We have determined
what the next step should be.
Uh... But first, I... I just wanna
thank all of you for everything.
Lilly, I've known you for over 20 years.
We're family, and family helps family.
And I'm... I'm really,
truly grateful for that, Hope.
And you've just been so kind to me.
But I... I can't ask you
to be Chloe's guardian.
We're here to support you,
whatever decision you make.
Good. Good. Because you've inspired me
to be strong
when I didn't think I had it in me.
So, I called my daughter, Tara.
And... um...
I spoke to Tara on the phone.
And as she is a direct relation,
I have agreed to a kinship placement.
She can assume the role of caregiver
until Lilly is ready to be assessed
for reunification.
And Tara's gonna be here by nightfall
to take guardianship of Chloe.
We will make sure
that Lilly gets all the help she needs.
And... and Mel is extremely qualified
in this area.
Okay. Well, if you'll excuse me,
I need to call the office.
Oh!
Um... Do you mind if I have a moment
- alone with Mel, just...
- No.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Oh, Lilly.
Oh!
Thanks. All of you.
Um...
Wow.
You were willing to take on
a stranger's child.
If you could be that strong,
I decided I could pick up the phone.
And Tara, she didn't sound disappointed
in me at all.
She sounded surprised...
and really excited
to meet her baby sister.
It took a lot of courage
to make that phone call.
And don't worry,
I'll stay until Tara gets here.
And I'll leave my number
so you can call me anytime you want.
I honestly don't know how to thank you.
- You know what? Go see Doc tomorrow.
- Okay.
And I'll take good care of you.
Get you set up with a therapist
and some meds.
A therapist?
There's a woman in Clear River,
and she specializes
in this kind of depression.
Uh... someone wants
to join in the celebration.
Hey, there.
Um... I... I would love
to keep the name Chloe for her,
if that's all right with you.
- I love it. Yeah.
- Good.
'Cause when she grows up,
I can tell her that she got her name
from the nice nurse
who helped her when I couldn't.
Yes.
Hey, there.
Sh, sh, sh, sh.
Oh, that's it.
Unbelievable.
- What?
- Don't "what" me.
You know very well what.
Uh, I assure you, I have no idea.
Not even a thank you for me sweet-talking
Mel into helping you with Lilly.
You know, when credit is due,
you are the first one in line.
- Mel helped Lilly of her own accord.
- Exactly.
That is exactly the reason
you should hire her back.
Where else are you gonna find a qualified,
kind-hearted nurse who's
willing to put up with you?
We don't see eye-to-eye.
Maybe that's a good thing.
We all have blind spots.
It might be good to have someone around
who... who can see yours.
Boy, you are just...
You're not gonna give up, are you?
I don't have anywhere to be.
Okay. Fine. Fine. But the...
the trial period remains in effect.
My name is still on the door.
And, Hope...
I do owe you a thank you.
For what?
For knowin' me.
Damned hard to admit I...
I am slowin' down.
Don't play the "old" card with me.
You've been a stubborn old goat
since the day we met.
The only thing slowing down around here
is this truck.
It's time to retire her and get yourself
something from this century.
- Oh...
- Hope?
Oh...
Hope!
- Are you all right?
- I...
- I don't feel right.
- No?
- No...
- Breathe. Breathe.
- That's it, just breathe.
- What's happening to me?
Oh, you're gonna be fine.
You are gonna be fine.
I'm gonna take care of you. Okay? Yeah.
It's so quiet.
Well, lots of farmers
and ranchers around here.
They tend to turn in early.
Animals don't take days off.
Yeah.
Whew.
Was a crazy couple of days, huh?
Yeah, it wasn't what I was expecting.
So, what's gonna happen when the town
finds out that Lilly is Chloe's mother?
Well, uh... Hope will handle the town.
Oh.
Yeah, so I guess it's not so bad
that she's in everybody's business
after all, huh?
Well, when you're on Hope's good side,
she has a heart of gold.
Yeah.
So, how are you feeling...
after leaving Chloe?
Mm...
Yeah, I'm just...
glad that she's where
she's supposed to be.
Yeah.
And thank you, by the way,
for all your help with Chloe and with me.
Oh, of course.
You know, if, uh...
if you really wanna thank me,
there is something
that you could do for me.
Oh, yeah? What's that?
Stay.
Right.
And now you're gonna tell me
the town needs me... blah-la-la-la...
No. Actually, I was not gonna say that.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
What were you gonna say?
That I've gotten used
to havin' you around.
Used to having me around.
- Mm.
- Gosh, that is quite the compliment.
- Are you sure you wanna go that far?
- Well, you didn't let me finish.
Oh, sorry.
What I was going to say...
- if you were to leave...
- ♪ Life is a mystery ♪
...you'd be missed.
♪ And joy it is to be ♪
I don't know what to say.
Just say you'll think about it.
- Jack...
- Look, just consider it.
Okay. I will think about it.
Thanks.
But there is one other thing
that I've been... dying to ask you.
Oh, okay.
What's the story there?
Uh...
It's, uh... not something
that I'm ready to talk about.
Not right now.
Okay.
I understand.
Jack.
- Hey.
- Uh, hey.
- Hm!
Sorry. Hi. Uh, we haven't met.
I'm Charmaine.
I'm Jack's girlfriend.
I'm sorry. I'm Mel.
Hi.