Oh, I come from a land
From a faraway place
Where the caravan camels roam
Where it's flat and immense
And the heat is intense
It's barbaric, but hey, it's home
When the wind's from the east
And the sun's from the west
And the sand in the glass is right
Come on down, stop on by
Hop a carpet and fly
To another Arabian night
Arabian nights
Like Arabian days
More often than not
Are hotter than hot
In a lot of good ways
Arabian nights
'Neath Arabian moons
A fool off his guard
Could fall and fall hard
Out there on the dunes
Ah, salaam and good evening
to you, worthy friend.
Please, please, come closer.
Too close. A little too close.
There.
Welcome to Agrabah,
city of mystery, of enchantment,
and the finest merchandise
this side of the River Jordan,
on sale today. Come on down.
Look at this. Yes.
Combination hookah and coffeemaker.
Also makes julienne fries.
Will not break. Will not...
It broke.
Ohh! Look at this.
I have never seen one
of these intact before.
This is the famous
Dead Sea Tupperware.
Listen. Ah, still good.
Wait. Don't go.
I can see that you're only interested
in the exceptionally rare.
I think, then, you would be
most rewarded to consider this.
Do not be fooled by its
commonplace appearance.
Like so many things, it
is not what is outside,
but what is inside that counts.
This is no ordinary lamp.
It once changed the course
of a young man's life.
A young man who, like this lamp,
was more than what he seemed.
A diamond in the rough.
Perhaps you would like
to hear the tale?
It begins on a dark night,
where a dark man waits
with a dark purpose.
(HORSE NICKERS)
You are late.
A thousand apologies,
O patient one.
You have it, then?
I had to slit a few
throats, but I got it.
Ah-ah-ahhh.
The treasure.
Ow!
Trust me, my pungent friend.
- You'll get what's coming to you.
- What's coming to you. Awk!
Quickly! Follow the trail.
Faster.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
(WIND HOWLING)
JAFAR: At last, after all
my years of searching,
the Cave of Wonders.
Awk. Cave of Wonders.
By Allah.
Now, remember. Bring me the lamp.
The rest of the treasure is
yours, but the lamp is mine.
(CHUCKLES)
Awk, the lamp. Awk, the lamp.
Jeez, where'd you dig this bozo up?
Shh.
(ECHOING RUMBLE)
- Who disturbs my slumber?
- (THIEF GASPS)
It is I, Gazeem, a humble thief.
Know this.
Only one may enter here,
one whose worth lies far within.
A diamond in the rough.
What are you waiting for? Go on.
(BEAST SIGHING)
- (ROARING)
- (SCREAMING)
No!
Seek thee out the
diamond in the rough.
(COUGHING)
I can't believe it.
I just don't believe it.
We're never gonna get a
hold of that stupid lamp.
Just forget it. Look at this. I'm
so ticked off that I'm moulting.
Patience, Iago. Patience.
Gazeem was obviously
less than worthy.
Oh, there's a big surprise.
I think I'm gonna have a heart
attack and die from that surprise.
What are we gonna do? We got
a big problem here, a big...
Yes.
Only one may enter.
I must find this one, this...
Diamond in the rough.
MAN: Stop! Thief!
I'll have your hands for
a trophy, street rat.
All this for a loaf of bread?
Whoa!
(SCREAMING)
- GUARD: There he is!
- You won't get away so easy!
You think that was easy?
(GIGGLING)
You two, over that way,
and you, follow me.
- We'll find him.
- Morning, ladies.
Getting into trouble a little
early today, aren't we, Aladdin?
Trouble? No way. You're only
in trouble if you get caught.
- Gotcha.
- I'm in trouble.
And this time...
(MONKEY SQUEAKING)
Perfect timing, Abu, as usual.
- Abu.
- Come on. Let's get outta here.
(SINGING) Gotta keep one jump
Ahead of the bread line
One swing ahead of the sword
I steal only what I can't afford
That's everything
One jump ahead of the lawmen
That's all, and that's no joke
These guys don't
appreciate I'm broke
- Riffraff
- BOTH: Street rat
- GUARD: Scoundrel
- MAN: Take that
Just a little snack, guys
Rip him open
Take it back, guys
I can take a hint
Gotta face the facts
- You're my only friend, Abu
- WOMEN: Who?
Oh, it's sad Aladdin's
hit the bottom
He's become a one-man rise in crime
I'd blame parents
Except he hasn't got 'em
Gotta eat to live
Gotta steal to eat
Tell you all about it
When I got the time
One jump ahead of the slowpokes
One skip ahead of my doom
Next time gonna use a nom de plume
There he is
One jump ahead of the hit men
One hit ahead of the flock
I think I'll take a stroll
Around the block
- MAN: Stop, thief
- Vandal
- Abu
- Scandal
Let's not be too hasty
Still I think he's rather tasty
Gotta eat to live
Gotta steal to eat
Otherwise we'd get along
GUARDS: Wrong
MAIN GUARD: Get him!
He's got a sword!
You idiots. We've all got swords.
(GROANING)
- One jump ahead of the hoof beats
- Vandal!
- One hop ahead of the hump
- Street rat!
- One trick ahead of disaster
- Scoundrel!
They're quick, but I'm much faster
Here goes, better throw my hand in
Wish me happy landin'
All I gotta do is jump
(SCREAMING)
GUARDS: Yuck! Oy!
And now, esteemed effendi,
we feast. All right.
ABU: Yum, yum!
Uh-oh.
(SIGHS)
Here. Go on. Take it.
(GIGGLING)
(GROANS)
Ah, don't. Huh?
On his way to the
palace, I suppose.
Another suitor for the princess.
- (GIGGLING)
- (WOMAN SCREAMS)
- (WHINNYING)
- Out of my way, you filthy brats.
Hey!
If I were as rich as you,
I could afford some manners.
Oh. I'll teach you some manners.
(MEN LAUGH)
(GRIMACING)
Look at that, Abu.
It's not every day you see a
horse with two rear ends.
CROWD: Ooh!
You are a worthless street rat.
You were born a street rat,
you'll die a street rat,
and only your fleas will mourn you.
I'm not worthless.
And I don't have fleas.
(SIGHS)
Come on, Abu. Let's go home.
(SINGING)
Riffraff, street rat
I don't buy that
If only they'd look closer
Would they see a poor boy?
No, siree
They'd find out
There's so much more
To me
(SIGHS) Someday, Abu,
things are gonna change.
We'll be rich, live in a palace,
and never have any problems at all.
(ROOSTERS CROWING)
I've never been so insulted.
Oh, Prince Achmed. You're not
leaving so soon, are you?
Good luck marrying her off.
Oh! Jasmine.
Jasmine!
- Jasmine!
- (SNARLING)
Confound it, Rajah.
So, this is why Prince
Achmed stormed out.
Oh, Father.
Rajah was just playing with
him. Weren't you, Rajah?
You were just playing
with that overdressed,
self-absorbed Prince
Achmed, weren't you?
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Dearest, you've got to stop rejecting
every suitor who comes to call.
The law says you must
be married to a prince
by your next birthday.
The law is wrong.
You've only got three more days.
Father, I hate being
forced into this.
If I do marry, I want
it to be for love.
Jasmine,
it's not only this law.
I'm not going to be around
forever, and, well, I...
I just want to make sure
you're taken care of.
Provided for.
Please try to understand.
I've never done a thing on my own.
I've never had any real friends.
(GRUMBLES)
Except you, Rajah.
I've never even been
outside the palace walls.
But, Jasmine, you're a princess.
Then maybe I don't want to
be a princess any more.
Oooh! I... I...
Allah forbid you should
have any daughters.
Hmm?
I don't know where
she gets it from.
Her mother wasn't nearly so picky.
Oh! Ah, Jafar.
My most trusted advisor.
I am in desperate
need of your wisdom.
My life is but to
serve you, my lord.
It's this suitor business. Jasmine
refuses to choose a husband.
- I'm at my wit's end.
- Awk! Wit's end!
(LAUGHING)
Oh!
- Have a cracker, pretty Polly.
- (JAFAR LAUGHS)
Your Majesty certainly has
a way with dumb animals.
(GRUMBLES)
Now, then, perhaps I
can divine a solution
to this thorny problem.
If anyone can help, it's you.
But it would require the use
of the mystic blue diamond.
Oh. Uh, my ring?
But it's been in the
family for years.
It is necessary to find
the princess a suitor.
Don't worry.
Everything will be fine.
The diamond.
Here, Jafar.
Whatever you need will be fine.
You are most gracious, my liege.
Now, run along and play
with your little toys, hmm?
Yes. That will be pretty good.
(SPITS, COUGHS)
I can't take it any more!
If I gotta choke down on one more of
those mouldy, disgusting crackers...
Bam! Whack!
Calm yourself, Iago.
Then I'd grab him around
the head. Whack!
Soon I will be sultan, not
that addlepated twit.
And then I stuff the crackers
down his throat. Ha, ha!
(WHINING)
Oh, I'm sorry, Rajah.
But I can't stay here and
have my life lived for me.
I'll miss you.
(WHIMPERS)
Good bye.
(VENDORS CALLING OUT)
Okay, Abu. Go.
Try this. Your taste buds
will dance and sing.
(SQUEAKING)
- Get your paws off that.
- (TAUNTING)
Why, you...
Get away from here,
you cursed, filthy ape!
Good bye.
- Nice going, Abu.
- (COOING)
Breakfast is served.
Pretty lady, buy a pot. No
finer pot in brass or silver.
Sugar dates. Sugar dates and figs.
Sugar dates and pistachios.
Would the lady like a necklace?
A pretty necklace
for a pretty lady.
Fresh fish!
We catch 'em, you buy 'em!
Oh, no. I don't think so.
- Oh!
- (GULPING)
- Excuse me.
- (GULPS)
(BELCHES)
I'm really very sorry.
Wow.
Uh-oh.
Hello? Hello?
Oh, you must be hungry.
Here you go.
You'd better be able
to pay for that.
- Pay?
- No one steals from my cart.
Oh, I'm sorry, sir.
I don't have any money.
- Thief!
- Please...
If you let me go to the palace,
I can get some from the sultan.
Do you know what the
penalty is for stealing?
No! No, please!
Thank you, kind sir. I'm
so glad you found her.
I've been looking all over for you.
- What are you doing?
- Just play along.
You, uh, know this girl?
Sadly, yes. She is my sister.
She's a little crazy.
She said she knew the sultan.
She thinks the monkey
is the sultan.
O wise Sultan, how may I serve you?
(GIBBERISH)
Tragic, isn't it?
But no harm done.
Now, come along, sis.
Time to go see the doctor.
Oh, hello, Doctor. How are you?
No, no, no. Not that one.
Come on, Sultan.
(GIBBERING)
(GASPING)
Huh? What?
Come back here, you little thieves!
(EXPLOSION)
With all due respect,
Your Rottenness,
couldn't we just wait
for a real storm?
Save your breath, Iago. Faster.
Yes, O mighty evil one.
(PANTING)
Part, sands of time.
Reveal to me the one who
can enter the cave.
Yes! Yes!
There he is.
My diamond in the rough.
That's him? That's the clown
we've been waitin' for?
Let's have the guards extend him an
invitation to the palace, shall we?
Swell.
(COUGHS)
(SINISTER LAUGHTER)
Almost there.
I want to thank you for
stopping that man.
Uh, forget it.
So, this is your first time
in the marketplace, huh?
Is it that obvious?
Well, you do kind of stand out.
I mean, uh, you don't seem to know
how dangerous Agrabah can be.
Hmm. I'm a fast learner.
Wow.
(CHUCKLING)
Hey.
Come on. This way.
Whoa. Watch your head there.
Be careful.
Is this where you live?
Yep. Just me and Abu.
Come and go as we please.
That sounds fabulous.
Well, it's not much, but
it's got a great view.
Wow. The palace looks
pretty amazing, huh?
Oh, it's wonderful.
I wonder what it would
be like to live there,
and have servants and valets.
Oh, sure. People who tell you
where to go and how to dress.
It's better than here.
You're always scraping for
food and ducking the guards.
You're not free to
make your own choices.
- Sometimes you feel so...
- You're just...
- Trapped.
(CLEARS THROAT)
So, where are you from?
What does it matter?
I ran away and I am not going back.
- Really? How come?
- Why, you...
My father's forcing
me to get married.
That's... That's awful.
- ALADDIN: Abu!
- (ANGRY SQUEAKING)
What?
Abu says, uh, that's not fair.
- Oh, did he?
- Yeah, of course.
And does Abu have
anything else to say?
Well, uh, he wishes there was
something he could do to help.
Oh, boy.
Hmm.
Tell him that's very sweet.
Here you are.
- They're after me!
- They're after you?
My father must have sent them...
- Do you trust me?
- What?
- Yes...
Then jump!
We just keep running into each
other, don't we, street rat?
Run! Go! Get out of here!
Get this thing off of me!
- It's the dungeon for you, boy.
- Get off of me.
Let him go.
- Looky here, men. A street mouse.
- (GUARDS LAUGH)
Unhand him, by order
of the princess.
Princess Jasmine.
- The princess?
- ABU: Princess?
What are you doing outside the
palace? And with this street rat.
That's not your concern. Do as
I command. Release him.
I would, Princess, except
my orders come from Jafar.
- You'll have to take it up with him.
- Believe me, I will.
Jafar?
Oh, Princess.
Awk! Jafar, I'm stuck.
How may I be of service to you?
The guards just took a boy from
the market, on your orders.
Your father has charged me
with keeping peace in Agrabah.
- The boy was a criminal.
- What was his crime?
I can't breathe, Jafar.
Why, kidnapping the
princess, of course.
If you could just...
Aah! That hurt!
He didn't kidnap me. I ran away.
Oh, dear.
Oh, how frightfully upsetting.
Had I but known...
What do you mean?
Sadly, the boy's sentence has
already been carried out.
What sentence?
- Death.
- (GASPING)
- By beheading.
- No.
I am exceedingly sorry, Princess.
How could you?
(WEEPING)
(COUGHING)
(GASPING)
So, how did it go?
I think she took it rather well.
(JASMINE CRYING)
It's all my fault, Rajah.
- I didn't even know his name.
- (RAJAH MURMURING)
She was the princess.
I can't believe it.
I must have sounded
so stupid to her.
ABU: Yoo-hoo! Aladdin! Hello!
Abu. Down here.
(SQUEAKING)
Come on, help me out of these.
(SCOLDING)
Hey, she was in trouble.
Ah, she was worth it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't worry, Abu.
I'll never see her again.
I'm a street rat, remember?
And there's a law.
She's gotta marry a prince.
- She deserves a prince.
- Ta-da!
I'm a fool.
MAN: You're only a fool
if you give up, boy.
Who are you?
A lowly prisoner, like yourself.
But together, perhaps
we can be more.
I'm listening.
There is a cave, boy,
a Cave of Wonders,
filled with treasures
beyond your wildest dreams.
Ooh!
Treasure enough to impress
even your princess, I'd wager.
Jafar, can you hurry up?
I'm dyin' in here.
- (SQUAWKING)
- But the law says only a prince can...
You've heard of the
golden rule, haven't you?
Whoever has the gold
makes the rules.
(WHEEZING LAUGH)
Why would you share all of this
wonderful treasure with me?
I need a young pair of legs and a
strong back to go in after it.
Uh, one problem.
It's out there. We're in here.
Uh-uh. Things aren't
always what they seem.
So, do we have a deal?
Oh, I don't know.
(THUNDER CRASHING)
Who disturbs my slumber?
Uh, it is I, Aladdin.
Proceed.
Touch nothing but the lamp.
Remember, boy, first
fetch me the lamp,
and then you shall
have your reward.
Come on, Abu.
(SQUEAKING)
- Would you look at that!
- (WHIMPERING)
Just a handful of this stuff would
make me richer than the sultan.
Abu!
(WHINES)
Don't touch anything.
We gotta find that lamp.
(GRUMBLES)
Huh?
- Aladdin!
- Abu, will you knock it off?
(SCREECHES)
Abu, what are you, crazy?
A magic carpet.
Come on. Come on out.
We're not gonna hurt you.
(SCREECHES)
Hey, take it easy, Abu.
He's not gonna bite.
Thanks.
(SQUEAKING)
Wait a minute. Don't go.
Maybe you can help us.
Hey! Whoa!
You see, we're trying
to find this lamp.
- I think he knows where it is.
- (SQUEAKS EXCITEDLY)
(ECHOES)
(WHISPERS) Wait here.
(MOANING)
Oh!
This is it?
This is what we came all
the way down here to...
Abu! No!
- CAVE: Infidels!
- Uh-oh.
CAVE: You have touched
the forbidden treasure!
Now you will never again
see the light of day!
Whoa!
Help! Help! Help!
Gotcha!
Carpet, let's move.
Abu!
Abu, this is no time to panic.
Start panicking.
BOTH: Whoa!
(ABU PANTING)
(THUNDER CRACKS)
(ROARING)
- Help me out.
- Throw me the lamp.
I can't hold on. Give me your hand.
First give me the lamp.
(MANIACAL LAUGHTER)
Yes!
At last!
- (WICKED LAUGHTER)
- (ALADDIN STRUGGLES)
What are you doing?
Giving you your reward.
Your eternal reward.
(SCREAMING)
(YELLING)
(ROARING)
(CHUCKLING)
It's mine.
It's all mine.
I... Where is it?
No.
No!
Jasmine?
SULTAN: Oh, dearest.
What's wrong?
(SNIFFLING)
Jafar has
done something terrible.
There, there, my dear.
We'll set it right.
Now, tell me everything.
Oh.
Aladdin. Wake up.
Aladdin.
Oh! My head.
We're trapped.
That two-faced son of a jackal!
(SNARLING)
Whoever he was, he's long
gone with that lamp.
Aha!
(CHUCKLING)
Why, you hairy little thief.
Looks like such a beat-up,
worthless piece of junk.
Hey, I think there's
something written here,
but it's hard to make out.
Aah!
Oy!
10,000 years will give you
such a crick in the neck.
Hang on a second.
Whoa! Whoa!
Does it feel good
to be outta there.
I'm telling you, nice to be
back, ladies and gentlemen.
Hi. Where you from?
What's your name?
Uh... Uh, Aladdin.
Aladdin. Hello, Aladdin.
Nice to have you on the show.
Can we call you Al?
Or maybe just Din?
How about Laddie? Sounds like,
"Here, boy. C'mon, laddie."
I must have hit my head
harder than I thought.
Do you smoke? Mind if I do?
(GIGGLING)
Oh, sorry, Cheeta. Hope
I didn't singe the fur.
Yo, Rugman. Haven't seen
you in a few millennia.
Give me some tassel. Yeah. Yo, yo.
Say, you're a lot smaller
than my last master.
Either that or I'm gettin' bigger.
Look at me from the side.
Do I look different to you?
Wait a minute. I'm your master?
That's right. He can be taught.
What would you wish of me?
The ever impressive,
the long contained,
the often imitated,
but never duplicated...
(ECHOING)
Duplicated, duplicated...
Genie of the Lamp!
Right here direct from the lamp,
right here for your very
much wish fulfillment.
Thank you.
- Whoa. Wish fulfillment?
- Three wishes, to be exact.
And ixnay on the wishing
for more wishes.
That's it. Three. Uno, dos, tres.
No substitutions,
exchanges or refunds.
Now I know I'm dreaming.
Master, I don't think you quite
realise what you've got here.
So why don't you just ruminate whilst
I illuminate the possibilities.
(SINGING)
Well, Ali Baba had them 40 thieves
Scheherazade had a thousand tales
But, master, you're in luck
'Cause up your sleeves
You got a brand of
magic never fails
You got some power
In your corner now
Some heavy ammunition in your camp
You got some punch, pizzazz
Yahoo and how
See, all you gotta do
Is rub that lamp and I'll say
"Mr Aladdin, sir
What will your pleasure be?"
Let me take your order
Jot it down
You ain't never had
a friend like me
Life is your restaurant
And I'm your maitre d'
Come on, whisper
what it is you want
You ain't never had
a friend like me
Yes, sir
We pride ourselves on service
You're the boss, the king, the shah
Say what you wish
It's yours, true dish
How 'bout a little more baklava?
Have some of column A
Try all of column B
I'm in the mood to help you, dude
You ain't never had
a friend like me
Oh, my
No, no
My, my
(SCATTING)
Can your friends do this?
Can your friends do that?
Can your friends pull this
Out their little hat?
Can your friends go poof
Hey, looky here
Ha-ha!
Can your friends go
"Abracadabra, let her rip"
And then make the sucker disappear?
So don't you sit there
Slack-jawed, buggy-eyed
I'm here to answer
All your midnight prayers
You got me bona fide certified
You got a genie
For your charge d'affaires
I got a powerful
urge to help you out
So what's your wish?
I really wanna know
You got a list
That's three miles long, no doubt
All you gotta do is rub like so
Mr Aladdin, sir
Have a wish or two or three
I'm on the job, you big nabob
You ain't never had a friend
Never had a friend
Like me
Ah-ha-ha!
- Wah-ha-ha!
- (GREEDY LAUGH)
You ain't never had
a friend like me
- (BUZZING)
- (WEAK APPLAUSE)
(CHATTERING)
Huh?
- (GROANS)
- So, what'll it be, master?
You're gonna grant me any
three wishes I want, right?
Ah, almost.
There are a few provisos,
a couple of quid pro quos.
Like?
Ah, rule number one,
I can't kill anybody.
So don't ask.
Rule number two.
I can't make anybody fall
in love with anybody else.
You little ponem there.
Rule number three. I can't bring
people back from the dead.
It's not a pretty picture.
I don't like doing it.
Other than that, you got it.
- Hmm.
- Oh!
Provisos? You mean limitations?
On wishes? Some all-powerful genie.
Can't even bring people
back from the dead.
I don't know, Abu. He probably
can't even get us out of this cave.
Looks like we're gonna have
to find a way out of here.
Excuse me?
Are you lookin' at me?
Did you rub my lamp?
Did you wake me up?
Did you bring me here?
And all of sudden you're
walking out on me?
I don't think so, not right now.
You're gettin' your
wishes, so sit down!
- (ABU SCREECHES)
- In case of emergency,
the exits are here, here,
here, here, anywhere.
Keep your hands and
arms inside the carpet.
We're...
Outta here!
SULTAN: Jafar, this is an outrage.
If it weren't for all your
years of loyal service...
From now on, you are to discuss
sentencing of prisoners with me,
before they are beheaded.
I assure you, Your Highness,
it won't happen again.
Jasmine...
Jafar. Let's put this whole
messy business behind us.
Please.
My most abject and humblest
apologies to you as well, Princess.
At least some good will come
of my being forced to marry.
When I am queen, I will have
the power to get rid of you.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
There, now. That's nice.
All settled, then.
Now, Jasmine, getting back to
this suitor business... Jasmine?
Jasmine!
(GROWLS)
If only I had gotten that lamp.
"I will have the power
to get rid of you."
(GROWLING)
To think we gotta keep kissing up
to that chump and
his chump daughter
- for the rest of our lives...
- No, Iago.
Only until she finds
a chump husband.
Then she'll have us banished.
Or beheaded.
BOTH: Eww!
Oh. Wait a minute. Jafar.
What if you were the chump husband?
What?
Okay, you marry the
princess, all right?
And, uh, then you become the sultan.
Oh.
Marry the shrew.
I become the sultan.
- The idea has merit.
- Yes, merit. Yes.
And then we drop papa-in-law and
the little woman off a cliff.
Yaaah!
Kersplat!
(WICKED LAUGHTER)
I love the way your
foul little mind works.
(BOTH LAUGH SINISTERLY)
Thank you for choosing Magic
Carpet for all your travel needs.
Don't stand until the rug
has come to a complete stop.
Thank you. Goodbye now.
Good-bye. Thank you.
Well, how about that,
Mr Doubting Mustafa?
Oh, you sure showed me.
Now, about my three wishes.
Dost mine ears deceive me?
Three? You are down by one, boy.
Ah, no. I never actually
wished to get out of the cave.
You did that on your own.
Well, I feel sheepish.
All right, you bad boy,
but no more freebies.
Fair deal. So, three wishes.
I want them to be good.
What would you wish for?
Me?
No one's ever asked me that before.
Well, in my case... Ah, forget it.
- What?
- No, I can't. I...
Come on. Tell me.
Freedom.
You're a prisoner?
It's all part and parcel
of the whole genie gig.
Phenomenal cosmic powers...
Itty bitty living space.
Genie, that's terrible.
But, oh, to be free...
Not have to go, "Poof.
What do you need?
"Poof. What do you need?
Poof. What do you need?"
To be my own master.
Such a thing would be
greater than all the magic
and all the treasures
in all the world.
But what am I talking about?
Let's get real here.
It's not gonna happen.
Genie, wake up and
smell the hummus.
Why not?
The only way I get outta this
is if my master wishes me out.
So you can guess how
often that's happened.
I'll do it. I'll set you free.
- Uh-huh, yeah, right.
- No, really, I promise.
After I make my first two wishes,
I'll use my third
wish to set you free.
Well, here's hopin'. All right.
Let's make some magic.
So how 'bout it? What
is it you want most?
Well, there's this girl.
Wrong.
I can't make anybody
fall in love, remember?
Oh, but, Genie, she's
smart and fun and...
- Pretty?
- Beautiful.
She's got these eyes that
just... And this hair. Wow.
And her smile... (SIGHS)
Ami.
C'est l'amour.
But she's the princess.
To even have a chance,
I'd have to be...
Hey, can you make me a prince?
Let's see here.
Chicken  la king? Nope.
Alaskan king crab. Ow.
I hate it when they do that.
Caesar salad. Ah! Et tu, Brute? No.
Aha. "To make a prince."
Is that an official wish?
Say the magic words.
Genie, I wish for you
to make me a prince.
All right!
Yo, yo! Woof! Woof!
First, that fez-and-vest combo
is much too third century.
These patches. What are
we trying to say, beggar?
No. Let's work with me here.
Ooh. I like it. Muy macho.
Now, it still needs something.
What does it say to me?
It says mode of transportation.
Excuse me, monkey boy.
Aqu. Over here.
- Uh-oh.
- GENIE: Here he comes.
What better way to make your
entrance on the streets of Agrabah
than riding your very
own, brand-new camel?
Watch out. They spit.
Mmm. Not enough.
Still not enough. Let's see.
What do you need?
Yes!
Esalalumbo shimin Dumbo.
- Whoa!
- (TRUMPETS)
Talk about your trunk space.
Check this action out.
(TRUMPETS)
(FRIGHTENED MONKEY NOISES)
Abu, you look good.
GENIE: He's got the outfit.
He's got the elephant.
But we're not through yet.
Hang on to your turban, kid.
We're gonna make you a star.
(DOOR OPENS)
Sire, I've found a solution to
the problem with your daughter.
Awk. The problem
with your daughter.
Oh, really?
Right here.
"If the princess has not chosen a
husband by the appointed time,
"then the sultan shall
choose for her."
But Jasmine hated
all those suitors.
How could I choose
someone she hates?
Not to worry, my liege.
There is more.
"If in the event a suitable
prince cannot be found..."
Jerk.
"A princess must then be wed to..."
Hmm. Interesting.
What? Who?
The royal vizier.
Why, that would be me.
But I thought the law says that
only a prince can marry a princess.
I'm quite sure that...
Desperate times call for
desperate measures, my lord.
Yes. Desperate measures.
You will order the
princess to marry me.
I will order the princess to...
But you're so old.
The princess will marry me.
The princess will marry...
- (TRUMPET FANFARE)
- What? What is that?
That music.
(CHUCKLING)
Jafar, you must come and see this.
(SINGING)
Make way for Prince Ali
Say, "Hey, it's Prince Ali"
Hey, clear the way
in the old bazaar
Hey you, let us through
It's a bright new star
Oh come, be the first on your block
To meet his eye
Make way, here he comes
Ring bells, bang the drums
You're gonna love this guy
Prince Ali, fabulous he
Ali Ababwa
Genuflect, show some respect
Down on one knee
Now, try your best to stay calm
Brush up your Sunday salaam
Then come and meet
His spectacular coterie
Prince Ali, mighty is he
Ali Ababwa
Strong as 10 regular men definitely
He faced the galloping hordes
A hundred bad guys with swords
Who sent those goons to
their lords? Why, Prince Ali
He's got 75 golden camels
Don't they look lovely, June?
Purple peacocks, he's got 53
Fabulous, Harry.
I love the feathers.
When it comes to
exotic-type mammals
Has he got a zoo
I'm telling you
It's a world-class menagerie
Prince Ali, handsome is he
Ali Ababwa
That physique, how can I speak
Weak at the knee
Well, get on out in that square
Adjust your veil and prepare
To gawk and grovel and stare
At Prince Ali
- He's got 95 white Persian monkeys
- He's got the monkeys
- Let's see the monkeys
- And to view them he charges no fee
He's generous
So generous
He's got slaves
He's got servants and flunkies
Proud to work for him
They bow to his whim, love serving him
They're just lousy
with loyalty to Ali
Prince Ali
Prince Ali, Amorous he
Ali Ababwa
Heard your princess
Was a sight lovely to see
And that, good people, is why
He got dolled up and dropped by
With 60 elephants, llamas galore
With bears and lions
A brass band and more
With his 40 fakirs
His cooks, his bakers
His birds that warble on key
Make way
For Prince Ali
Splendid. Absolutely marvellous.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Your Majesty,
I have journeyed from afar to
seek your daughter's hand.
Prince Ali Ababwa.
Of course. I'm
delighted to meet you.
This is my royal vizier,
Jafar. He's delighted, too.
Ecstatic.
- I'm afraid, Prince Abubu...
- Ababwa.
Whatever.
You cannot just parade in here
uninvited and expect to...
By Allah, this is quite
a remarkable device.
Ooh.
I don't suppose I might...
Why, certainly,
Your Majesty. Allow me.
Sire, I must advise against this.
Oh, button up, Jafar.
Learn to have a little fun.
Ow, ow, ow.
Ahh! Whoa!
Look out, here I come.
Just where did you
say you were from?
Oh, much farther than
you've travelled, I'm sure.
- Try me.
- SULTAN: Look out, Polly.
Hey, watch it.
Watch it with the dumb rug.
Aah!
Whew!
Out of the way. I'm
coming in to land.
Jafar, watch this.
- Spectacular, Your Highness.
- That was lovely.
Yes, I do seem to
have a knack for it.
This is a very impressive youth.
And a prince besides.
(WHISPERS) If we're lucky, you won't
have to marry Jasmine after all.
- I don't trust him, Sire.
- Nonsense.
One thing I pride myself on, Jafar,
I'm an excellent judge of character.
Oh, excellent judge.
Yeah, sure. Not!
SULTAN: Jasmine will like this one.
And I'm pretty sure I'll
like Princess Jasmine.
Your Highness, no. I must
intercede on Jasmine's behalf.
This boy is no different
from the others.
What makes him think he is
worthy of the princess?
Your Majesty, I am
Prince Ali Ababwa.
Just let her meet me.
I will win your daughter.
How dare you.
All of you. Standing
around deciding my future?
I am not a prize to be won.
Oh, dear.
Don't worry, Prince Ali. Just
give Jasmine time to cool down.
I think it's time to say
good-bye to Prince Abubu.
ALADDIN: (SIGHS)
What am I gonna do?
Jasmine won't even
let me talk to her.
I should've known I couldn't pull
off this stupid prince wish.
(GROWLING)
So move.
Hey.
That's a good move.
I can't believe it.
I'm losing to a rug.
Genie, I need help.
All right, Sparky, here's the deal.
If you wanna court the little lady,
you gotta be a straight shooter.
- Do you got it?
- What?
(READING)
No way.
If Jasmine found out I was
really some crummy street rat,
she'd laugh at me.
A woman appreciates a man
who can make her laugh.
Al, all joking aside, you
really ought to be yourself.
Hey, that's the last
thing I wanna be.
Okay, I'm gonna go see her.
I just... I gotta be
smooth, cool, confident.
How do I look?
Like a prince.
(SIGHS)
- ALADDIN: Princess Jasmine?
- (GROWLING)
- Who's there?
- It's me, Prince Ali.
Ahem. Uh, Prince Ali Ababwa.
I do not want to see you.
No, no, please, Princess.
Give me a chance.
- JASMINE: Just leave me alone.
- Down, kitty.
So, how's our little beau doing?
- Good kitty, take off.
- (RAJAH GROWLING)
Down, kitty.
Wait. Wait.
Do I know you?
Uh, no. No.
You remind me of someone
I met in the marketplace.
The marketplace?
I have servants who go to
the marketplace for me.
Why, I even have servants who go
to the marketplace for my servants,
so it couldn't have
been me you met.
No. I guess not.
GENIE: Enough about you,
Casanova. Talk about her.
She's smart, fun,
the hair, the eyes.
Anything. Pick a feature.
Ahem. Uh, Princess
Jasmine? You're very...
Wonderful, magnificent, glorious,
- punctual.
- Punctual.
- Punctual?
- Sorry.
- Uh, beautiful.
- Nice recovery.
Hmm.
I'm rich, too, you know.
- Yeah.
- The daughter of a sultan.
I know.
A fine prize for any
prince to marry.
Uh, right. Right. A prince like me.
Warning! Warning!
Right. A prince like you.
And every other stuffed shirt,
swaggering peacock I've met.
Mayday! Mayday!
JASMINE: Just go jump off a balcony!
- What?
- Stop her. Stop her!
- Want me to sting her?
- Buzz off.
Okay, fine. But remember,
"bee" yourself.
- Yeah, right.
- What?
Uh... Uh, you're right.
(SIGHS) You aren't just
some prize to be won.
You should be free to
make your own choice.
I'll go now.
- No!
- What? What?
How...
How are you doing that?
- It's a magic carpet.
- It's lovely.
- (KISSES)
- You, uh...
You don't want to go
for a ride, do you?
We could get out of the
palace, see the world.
- Is it safe?
- Sure. Do you trust me?
- What?
- Do you trust me?
Yes.
(SINGING)
I can show you the world
Shining, shimmering, splendid
Tell me, Princess
Now, when did you last
Let your heart decide
I can open your eyes
Take you wonder by wonder
Over, sideways and under
On a magic carpet ride
A whole new world
A new fantastic point of view
No one to tell us no
Or where to go
Or say we're only dreaming
A whole new world
A dazzling place
I never knew
But when I'm way up here
It's crystal clear
That now I'm in
A whole new world with you
ALADDIN: Now I'm in
JASMINE: Unbelievable sights
Indescribable feeling
Soaring, tumbling, freewheeling
Through an endless diamond sky
- A whole new world
- Don't you dare close your eyes
- A hundred thousand things to see
- Hold your breath, it gets better
I'm like a shooting star
I've come so far
I can't go back to
where I used to be
- A whole new world
- Every turn a surprise
- With new horizons to pursue
- Every moment red-letter
BOTH: I'll chase them anywhere
There's time to spare
Let me share
This whole new world with you
- A whole new world
- That's where we'll be
- A thrilling chase
- A wondrous place
For you and me
- It's all so magical.
- Yeah.
It's a shame Abu had to miss this.
Nah. He hates fireworks.
He doesn't like flying, either.
Uh, that is, um... Oh, no.
You are the boy from
the market. I knew it.
- Why did you lie to me?
- Jasmine, I'm sorry.
- Did you think I was stupid?
- No.
- That I wouldn't figure it out?
I mean, I hoped you wouldn't.
No, that's not what I meant.
Who are you? Tell me the truth.
The truth?
The truth. Um...
The truth is...
I sometimes dress
as a commoner, um,
to escape the pressures
of palace life.
But I really am a prince.
Why didn't you just tell me?
Well, you know,
royalty going out into
the city in disguise,
it sounds a little
strange, don't you think?
Hmm.
Not that strange.
Good night, my handsome prince.
Sleep well, Princess.
(SIGHS)
Yes!
For the first time in my life,
things are starting to go right.
- (YELLING)
- (STRUGGLING)
(MUFFLED)
Abu. Abu.
Hold him.
I'm afraid you've worn out
your welcome, Prince Abubu.
(MUFFLED)
Why, you...
Make sure he's never found.
(LAUGHING)
Never fails. You get in the bath
and there's a rub at the lamp.
Hello? AI?
(GASPING)
Al! Kid, snap out of it.
You can't cheat on this one.
I can't help unless you make a wish.
You have to say, "Genie, I want
you to save my life." Got it?
Come on, Aladdin!
I'll take that as a yes.
(IMITATING ALARM)
Up scope.
(BABBLING IN GERMAN)
(COUGHING)
Don't you scare me like that.
Genie, I, uh...
I...
- Thanks, Genie.
- Oh, Al.
I'm gettin' kind of
fond of you, kid.
Not that I wanna pick out
curtains or anything.
(HUMMING)
SULTAN: Jasmine.
Oh, Father, I just had
the most wonderful time.
- I'm so happy.
- You should be, Jasmine.
I have chosen a husband for you.
- What?
- You will wed Jafar.
(GASPING)
You're speechless, I see.
A fine quality in a wife.
I will never marry you.
- Father, I choose Prince Ali.
- Prince Ali left.
Better check your crystal
ball again, Jafar.
- Prince Ali!
- (GASPING)
How in the... Uh. Awk!
Tell them the truth, Jafar.
You tried to have me killed.
What? Ridiculous
nonsense, Your Highness.
He is obviously lying.
Obviously lying.
Father, what's wrong with you?
I know what's wrong.
Oh, my!
Your Highness, Jafar's been
controlling you with this.
(STAMMERING)
What? Jafar?
You, you traitor!
Your Majesty, all this
can be explained.
Guards! Guards!
Well, that's it.
We're dead. Forget it.
Just dig a grave for both
of us. We're dead.
- SULTAN: Arrest Jafar at once.
- (STRUGGLING)
This is not done yet, boy.
- (LAUGHING)
- (COUGHING)
SULTAN: Find him! Search
everywhere!
- Jasmine, are you all right?
- Yes.
Jafar, my most trusted counsellor,
plotting against me all this time.
This is horrible, just horrible.
How will I ever...
Huh?
Can this be true?
My daughter has finally
chosen a suitor?
Ha, ha! Praise Allah!
You brilliant boy,
I could kiss you.
I won't. I'll leave that to my...
But you two will be wed at once.
Yes, yes. And you'll be
happy and prosperous,
and then you, my boy,
will become sultan.
- Sultan?
- SULTAN: Yes.
A fine upstanding youth
such as yourself,
a person of your unimpeachable
moral character
is exactly what this kingdom needs.
IAGO: We gotta get outta here.
I gotta start packing. Only essentials.
We gotta travel light.
Bring the guns, the weapons, the
knives, and how about this picture?
I think I'm making
a weird face in it.
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
Oh, boy. He's cracked.
He's gone nuts.
Jafar! Jafar! Get a grip!
Good grip.
Prince Ali is nothing more than
that ragged urchin, Aladdin.
- He has the lamp, Iago.
- Why, that miserable...
But you are going to
relieve him of it.
Me?
Sultan?
They want me to be Sultan?
Huzzah!
(SINGING)
Hail the conquering hero
(PATRIOTIC TUNE PLAYS)
Aladdin, you've just won
the heart of the princess.
What are you gonna do next?
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
(WHISPERING) Psst. Your line is,
"I'm going to free the genie."
Any time.
- Genie. I can't.
- Sure you can.
You just go, "Genie,
I wish you free."
I'm serious.
Look, I'm sorry. I really am.
But they wanna make me sultan.
No. They wanna make
Prince Ali sultan.
Without you, I'm just Aladdin.
- Al, you won.
- Because of you.
The only reason anyone thinks I'm
worth anything is because of you.
What if they find out I'm
not really a prince?
What if Jasmine finds out?
I'd lose her.
Genie, I can't keep
this up on my own.
I can't wish you free.
Fine. I understand. After all,
you've lied to everyone else.
Hey, I was beginning
to feel left out.
Now, if you'll excuse me, master.
(SIGHING)
Genie, I'm really sorry.
(RASPBERRY)
Well, fine. Then
just stay in there.
What are you guys looking at?
- (WHIMPERING)
- (SNIFFLING)
ALADDIN: Look, I... I'm sorry.
Abu, I'm sorry. I didn't...
Wait. Come on.
(SIGHING)
What am I doing?
(SIGHS)
Genie's right.
I gotta tell Jasmine the truth.
JASMINE: Ali. Oh, Ali. Will you
come here?
(SIGHING)
Well, here goes.
Jasmine? Where are you?
(IMITATES JASMINE)
Out in the menagerie. Hurry.
- I'm coming.
- (PANTING)
(WICKED LAUGHTER)
- (GOOFY CHUCKLE)
- You got a problem, Pinky?
Jerk.
(GLEEFUL CACKLING)
Boy, Jafar's gonna
be happy to see you.
(IMITATES JAFAR)
"Excellent work, Iago."
Ah, go on.
"No, really. On a scale of
one to 10, you are an 11."
Oh, Jafar, you're too kind.
I'm embarrassed. I'm blushing.
People of Agrabah,
my daughter has finally
chosen a suitor.
- (CROWD CHEERING)
- ALADDIN: Jasmine.
Ali, where have you been?
Jasmine, there's something
I got to tell you.
The whole kingdom's turned out
for Father's announcement.
No. But, Jasmine,
listen to me, please.
- You don't understand...
- Good luck.
- SULTAN: Ali Ababwa!
- (CHEERING)
Oh, boy.
(CHEERING)
Look at them, cheering
that little pipsqueak.
Let them cheer.
You know, Al, I'm getting really...
I don't think you're him.
Tonight, the part of Al
will be played by a tall,
dark and sinister ugly man.
- I am your master now.
- I was afraid of that.
Genie, grant me my first wish.
I wish to rule on high as sultan.
- Whoa!
- Bless my soul.
What is this? What's going on?
Oh, my goodness, what's happening?
Father.
(CACKLING)
Jafar, you vile betrayer.
That's Sultan Vile Betrayer to you.
Oh, yeah? We'll just
see about that.
- (GASPS) The lamp.
- (JAFAR LAUGHS)
Finders keepers, Abubu.
(WHISTLES)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Genie, no!
Sorry, kid. I got a new master now.
Jafar, I order you to stop.
Ah, but there's a new order now.
My order.
Finally, you will bow to me.
We will never bow to you.
Why am I not surprised?
If you won't bow before a sultan,
then you will cower
before a sorcerer!
Genie, my second wish...
I wish to be the most powerful
sorcerer in the world!
- (JAFAR LAUGHS MANIACALLY)
- Genie, stop!
Ladies and gentlemen,
a warm Agrabah welcome
for Sorcerer Jafar!
Now, where were we?
Ah, yes. Abject humiliation.
- Down, boy.
- (MEOWS)
Oh, Princess.
There's someone I'm dying
to introduce you to.
Jafar. Get your hands off her.
(SINGING)
Prince Ali yes, it is he
But not as you know him
Read my lips
And come to grips with reality
Yes, meet a blast from your past
Whose lies were too good to last
Say hello
To your precious Prince Ali
Or should we say Aladdin?
Ali?
Jasmine, I tried to
tell you. I'm just...
So Ali turns out to be
Merely Aladdin
Just a con, need I go on
Take it from me
His personality flaws
Give me adequate cause
To send him packing
On a one-way trip
Genie!
So his prospects
Take a terminal dip
His assets frozen, the venue chosen
Is the ends of the Earth, whoopee!
- So long!
- Good-bye, see ya.
Ex-Prince Ali
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
(WIND HOWLING)
(SHIVERING)
Abu.
Abu!
(ABU WHIMPERING)
Oh, this is all my fault.
I should have freed the genie
when I had the chance.
- Abu. Are you okay?
- (TEETH CHATTERING) Mmm-hmm.
I'm sorry, Abu.
I made a mess of everything.
Somehow, I gotta go back
and set things right.
Carpet.
- (ABU CHITTERS)
- (ALADDIN STRAINS)
Abu, start digging.
(FRANTIC PANTING)
That's it.
Yeah! All right!
(WHINES)
Now, back to Agrabah. Let's go.
- IAGO: Puppet ruler want a cracker?
- (SULTAN MOANING)
Here's your cracker. Shove them
all the way down your throat.
Here. Have lots.
Stop it. Jafar, leave him alone.
(GROWLING)
It pains me to see you
reduced to this, Jasmine.
A beautiful desert
bloom such as yourself
should be on the arm of the most
powerful man in the world.
What do you say, my dear?
Why, with you as my queen...
- Never.
- (ENRAGED GROWL)
I'll teach you some respect.
(GASPING)
No. Genie.
I have decided to
make my final wish.
I wish for Princess Jasmine
to fall desperately
in love with me.
Ah, Master, there are a few
addendas, some quid pro quos...
Don't talk back to me,
you big blue lout.
You will do what I order
you to do, slave.
JASMINE: Jafar.
I never realised how
incredibly handsome you are.
Mmm. That's better.
Now, pussycat,
tell me more about myself.
You're tall, dark,
well dressed...
AI. AI, little buddy.
Shh.
Al, I can't help you.
I work for Seor Psychopath
now. What are you gonna do?
Hey, I'm a street rat,
remember? I'll improvise.
JASMINE: Cute little
gaps between your teeth.
Go on.
And your beard is so twisted.
- You've stolen my heart.
- (GASPING) Jafar...
- (IAGO MUMBLING)
- And the street rat?
What street rat?
- (CLATTERING)
- (GASPING)
(GASPING)
BOTH: Yech!
That was...
You!
How many times do I
have to kill you, boy?
Get the lamp.
No!
Ah, ah, ah, Princess.
Your time is up.
(GROWLING)
Jasmine.
Oh, nice shot, Jaf...
Don't toy with me.
Abu!
JAFAR: Things are
unravelling fast now, boy.
(JAFAR LAUGHING)
Get the point?
(LAUGHING)
(STRAINING)
I'm just getting warmed up.
Are you afraid to fight me
yourself, you cowardly snake?
A snake, am I?
Perhaps you'd like to see
how snakelike I can be.
(SCREAMING)
(SINGING) Rick 'em, rack 'em, rock 'em, rake
Stick that sword into that snake
You stay out of this.
Jafar, Jafar, he's our man.
If he can't do it... Great!
JASMINE: Aladdin.
(SCREAMS)
Jasmine, hang on.
(LAUGHING)
You little fool.
You thought you could defeat the
most powerful being on Earth.
Squeeze him, Jafar.
Squeeze him like a... Awk!
Without the genie,
boy, you're nothing.
The genie. The genie.
The genie has more power
than you'll ever have.
What?
He gave you your power.
He can take it away.
Al, what are you doing? Why are
you bringing me into this?
Face it, Jafar. You're
still just second best.
You're right.
His power does exceed my own.
But not for long.
The boy is crazy. He's
a little punch-drunk.
One too many hits with the snake.
Slave, I make my third wish.
I wish to be an all-powerful genie!
All right, your wish is my
command. Way to go, Al.
Yes.
Yes!
The power.
- (JAFAR LAUGHS)
- (JASMINE COUGHS)
The absolute power!
- What have you done?
- Trust me.
The universe is mine to
command, to control!
Not so fast, Jafar. Aren't
you forgetting something?
- Huh?
- You wanted to be a genie, you got it.
What?
And everything that goes with it.
- No! No!
- I'm gettin' out of here.
ALADDIN: Phenomenal cosmic powers...
You're the genie. I don't want...
Itty bitty living space.
Al, you little genius, you.
- Ahh!
- (MEOWS)
JAFAR: Get your blasted
beak out of my face.
- IAGO: Oh, shut up, you moron.
- Don't tell me to shut up.
Allow me.
Ten thousand years in a Cave of
Wonders ought to chill him out.
(IAGO YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
JAFAR: Shut up!
Jasmine...
I'm sorry I lied to you
about being a prince.
I know why you did.
Well, I guess this is good-bye?
Oh, that stupid law.
This isn't fair.
I love you.
(SNIFFLES) Al, no problem.
You've still got one wish left.
Just say the word and
you're a prince again.
But, Genie, what
about your freedom?
Hey, it's only an
eternity of servitude.
This is love.
Al, you're not gonna find another
girl like her in a million years.
Believe me, I know. I've looked.
Jasmine, I do love you,
but I got to stop pretending
to be something I'm not.
I understand.
Genie, I wish for your freedom.
One bona fide prince
pedigree coming up.
- What?
- Genie, you're free.
I'm free. I'm free.
Quick. Quick. Wish for
something outrageous.
Say, "I want the Nile."
Wish for the Nile. Try that.
- Uh, I wish for the Nile.
- No way!
(LAUGHING GLEEFULLY)
Oh, does that feel good! Oh!
I'm free! I'm free at last!
I'm hittin' the road. I'm off
to see the world. I'm...
Genie, I'm...
I'm gonna miss you.
Me, too, Al.
(SNIFFLES)
No matter what anybody says,
you'll always be a prince to me.
That's right.
You've certainly proven your
worth as far as I'm concerned.
It's that law that's the problem.
- Father?
- Well, am I sultan or am I sultan?
From this day forth,
the princess shall marry
whomever she deems worthy.
Him. I choose...
I choose you, Aladdin.
Call me Al.
Oh, all of you, come over
here. Big group hug.
Group hug.
Mind if I kiss the monkey?
Ooh, hairball.
Well, I can't do any more damage
around this Popsicle stand.
I'm outta here!
Bye-bye, you two crazy lovebirds!
Hey, Rugman, ciao. I'm history.
No, I'm mythology.
I don't care what I am. I'm free!
(SINGING)
A whole new world
A whole new life
For you and me
A whole new world
(LAUGHING)
Made you look.
You have been a fabulous audience.
Tell you what, you're the best
audience in the whole world.
Take care of yourselves.
Good night, Alice!
Good night, Agrabah!
Adis, amigos!
Improved By: Lhadyjana