(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
(ALL LAUGHING)
MAMA: Tanya, Fievel?
Will you stop that
twirling, twirling?
Uh, no. No more.
MAMA: That's it. Time for bed. Come.
(PAPA LAUGHING)
PAPA: But, Mama, it's Hanukkah!
MAMA:
For you, every night is Hanukkah.
Papa, enough already.
They'll never get to sleep.
(PANTS) All right. All right.
FIEVEL: Presents.
What about presents?
Presents? What presents?
MAMA: Oh, Papa.
(CHUCKLES)
Just a joke.
For Tanya, a new babushka.
Happy Hanukkah.
(GASPING)
Oh, Papa. Thank you.
You have only one parent?
Thank you, Mama.
Hmm.
And for you, Fievel,
a new hat.
And not just any hat.
A new hat that has
been in the family
for three generations.
It belonged to me, my father,
and my father's father,
and now, it belongs to you.
Happy Hanukkah.
It's too big!
You'll grow.
(CHUCKLES)
Ah, did I ever tell you
about the Giant Mouse of Minsk?
TANYA: No.
No.
Was it anything like
the mouse with the long hair
that the prince climbed up?
No. This mouse, the Mouse of Minsk,
was tall as a tree.
His tail was a mile long.
Really?
Really.
He was so big,
he frightened all the cats.
Shh!
Don't say that word.
Talk about something else.
TANYA: America.
MAMA: Another fairy tale.
America.
What a place!
In America, there are mouse
holes in every wall.
MAMA: Who says?
ALL: Everyone!
In America, there are bread
crumbs on every floor!
You're talking nonsense.
In America, you can
say anything you want.
But most important...
(WHISPERS)
And this I know for fact,
in America, there are no cats.
Shh. They'll hear you.
How could they hear us?
(RUMBLING)
(BABY CRYING)
MAMA: There, you see?
(NEIGHING)
(ALL SHOUTING)
MAN: The Cossacks! The Cossacks!
(ALL SCREAMING)
(ALL GROWLING)
(ALL GASP)
(ROARING)
Don't cry, Yasha.
I'll scare them away.
(SHUSHING)
PAPA: Fievel, you'll get hurt!
(ALL SCREAM)
Go away!
(CLANGING)
Go away, cats! Go away!
(CAT ROARING)
(SCREAMS)
(CAT GROWLS)
(GASPING)
Whoa!
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS)
(ALL GROWLING)
(PANTS)
Fievel, angel, are you all right?
(GIGGLING) Yes, Mama.
Then never do that again!
Mama, look.
In America,
there are no cats.
(BELL TOLLING)
(FOGHORN BLOWING)
(JOVIAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(ALL GASP)
(MUSIC STOPS)
Look, Papa, water.
Is it the ocean?
Yes. Keep walking.
(JOVIAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(ALL GASP)
FIEVEL: Look, Papa, smoke!
Is the boat on fire?
No. No. Keep walking!
(JOVIAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(ALL GASP)
Look, Papa, birds!
Are they seagulls?
BOTH: Keep walking!
Keep walking!
ALL: Keep walking!
(JOVIAL MUSIC PLAYING)
I just wanted to see.
Fievel, this is the last
time I take you to America.
Bye-bye!
(BLOWS)
(BELL TOLLING)
(ALL CHEERING)
ALL: Auf Wiedersehen.
Auf Wiedersehen.
Ooh, auf Wiedersehen!
You know I got a cousin in America.
Ah! (SPITS)
You and everybody else.
Huh?
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(VIOLIN PLAYING)
(HUMMING)
Are we there yet?
Not yet. Soon.
How soon?
Soon.
Maybe we should
have stayed in Russia.
We'll be all right.
As long as we're together,
we'll be all right.
Ah, so, Mr. Curious,
you've discovered the herring.
Herring?
I thought they were fish.
(LAUGHING)
But, Fievel, herring are fish.
Really?
Certainly.
In the ocean,
there are all kinds of fish,
and herring is one of them.
All kinds?
Yes. Tiny fishes,
not so tiny fishes,
fishes as big as this boat.
(GASPING) Wow!
Let's go up and see the fish!
Not now.
Your mama's worried.
Come back, Fievel.
(LAUGHS)
Wait!
Oh, what am I going to do with you?
You stay closer to home!
Don't you go running off again!
Mama!
Ah, so we return, hmm?
We saw some fish!
Fish?
Lucky you didn't see some cats.
(ALL GASP)
Cats!
(SPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGES)
ALL: Cats!
Oh!
I didn't see any cats.
ALL: Whew.
Won't it be nice to get to America
where we don't have to worry
about cats anymore?
There are no cats in America,
but back home in mother Russia...
ALL: Oh!
♪ Our family was traveling
♪ Through the snow to Minsk
♪ Suddenly Papa
♪ Saw those huge paw prints
♪ When I heard him screaming
♪ I fainted dead away
♪ And I woke up an orphan
(ALL GASP)
Oy vey.
But!
ALL: But...
♪ But there are no cats in America
♪ And the streets
are paved with cheese
♪ Oh, there are no cats
in America
♪ So set your mind at ease ♪
(ALL LAUGHING)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
If you think things
were bad in Russia,
you should see things
in my country! (LAUGHS)
♪ The times were hard in Sicily
♪ We had no provolone
♪ The don, he was a tabby
♪ With a taste
for my brother, Tony
♪ When Mama went
to plead for him
♪ The don said
he would see her
♪ We found her
rosary on the ground ♪
(ALL GASP)
Poor mamma mia!
But!
♪ But there are
no cats in America
♪ And the streets
are paved with cheese
♪ Oh, there are no cats
in America
♪ So set your mind at ease ♪
(ALL LAUGHING)
Surely, that's sad,
but sadder still...
♪ When I was but a lad
♪ I lost my true love fair
♪ A calico
♪ He caught us by surprise
♪ In a flash of teeth and fur
♪ Her tail was
all he left of her
♪ 'Neath the heather
♪ Is where it too-ra-loo-ra
♪ Lies ♪
ALL: Oh.
But!
♪ But there are
no cats in America
♪ And the streets
are paved with cheese
♪ But there are
no cats in America
♪ There are no cats in America
♪ That's why
♪ We sail
♪ These seas ♪
(GRUNTS)
Hey, fellas, want a bite?
(ALL GAGGING)
Oh, it's the end of the world.
No, it's worse.
(YELPS)
Hmm.
(SCREAMS)
Fievel.
Fievel, come, sit here.
Yes, Papa.
Fievel.
(GASPING)
(THUNDER CRACKING)
Fish!
PAPA: Fievel! Fievel!
Fievel!
I'm getting my hat, Papa!
PAPA: Fievel!
Fievel, come back!
My hat!
Wait!
Fievel, stop!
Stop!
Pa... (COUGHS) Papa!
Fievel!
Don't move!
Papa!
Grab my hand!
Help!
PAPA: Grab my hand!
Fievel!
(SCREAMS)
(ROARING)
(GASPING)
(FIEVEL SCREAMS)
Fievel, come back!
(COUGHS)
Papa, help!
(ROARING)
(GASPING)
(SCREAMS)
Fievel!
(GASPING)
(COUGHING)
Papa!
WOMAN: America.
MAN: No, no. New York.
Name?
Smovolodny-Dhromovichsky.
Okay, Mr. Smith.
Family, "Mousekewitz".
How many?
Five.
(SIGHS) I mean four.
Okay. Next?
TANYA: Papa, why did they
change my name to Tilly?
CHOIR: ♪ Give me your tired
♪ Your poor
♪ Your huddled masses
♪ Yearning to breathe free
♪ The wretched refuse
♪ Of your teeming shore
♪ Send these
♪ The homeless
♪ Tempest-tossed, to me
♪ I lift my lamp
beside the golden door ♪
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
(SNEEZES)
Ah! A little immigrant.
(LAUGHS)
Now they are coming by bottle.
Uh, where is your papa?
Your maman, eh?
I don't know. They were
on the boat to America.
Ah! Then you are in luck,
my little immigrant.
This is America!
(GASPING) America.
I thought it was bigger.
Oh, it is bigger.
All of that is also America.
Wow!
This is just
an island at the doorway
where I, Henri le pigeon,
am putting up my
Statue of Liberty! (LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
I know, my little immigrant,
you want to find your family,
and you will.
But how?
It's so far away, and it's so big!
(SNIFFLES)
I'll never find them anyway.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
But did you say,
"Never"?
So young, and you have lost hope.
Ah, this is America,
the place to find hope!
If you give up, you will
never find your family.
So, never say never!
Say...
♪ Never say never
♪ Whatever you do
♪ Never say never, my friend
Henri...
Ah, tais-toi!
♪ If you believe that
your dreams will come true
♪ They'll come
true in the end
But I...
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah!
♪ Keep up your courage
♪ Don't ever despair
♪ Take heart and
then count to 10
♪ Hope for the best
♪ Work for the rest
♪ And never say never again
Oh, but it's impossible!
I'll never find my family.
Ah, ah, ah!
Never say never!
Now, say that. Go on.
♪ Never say never
♪ Whatever you do
Again!
♪ Never say never
♪ To me
See how easy?
♪ If you believe you
can come shining through
That's... That's how
it's going to be.
Perfect! (LAUGHS)
♪ Now don't you go and give up
♪ Give out or give in
♪ When the going's rough,
just get tough
♪ And just tell
yourself you're gonna win
♪ Remember to look on
the bright side till then
♪ And never
♪ Say never
♪ Again
Now are you ready to
go and find your family?
Yes!
Chantal!
Take my little
friend to immigration.
You will find your family there.
Everyone goes through immigration.
I would take you there myself,
but then I'd never
finish my statue.
Henri, you said, "Never"!
Oh, so I did!
♪ Never
♪ Say never
♪ Again ♪
Au revoir! Bonne chance!
Good luck!
FIEVEL: Good-bye!
MAN 1: Come on, keep it
moving, keep it moving.
All right.
MAN 2: Hurry, hurry!
Yes, sir! Step off the
boat and into prosperity!
Welcome, greenhorns!
This is America!
Today's special, the Brooklyn
Bridge, just a dollar!
CHILD: Golly, the Brooklyn Bridge!
Ticket to Chicago!
Used only once!
(ALL GASP)
CHILD 1: Gee whiz!
CHILD 2: Only once, Ma.
Apple, apple?
Get my apple while it lasts.
Hurry, it's going fast!
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
CHILD 3: I'll take one!
Eighteen, 19, 20, 21.
(CREATURE COUGHING)
Would you please put
out that filthy thing?
I'm suffocating down here.
You don't like it?
Hey, you know you're not the
only cockroach in New York City.
There are millions
of roaches who'd give
their left feet to
work for Warren T. Rat.
Good. Fire me!
I'm fed up with that filthy smoke...
Hey!
And this pocket!
I've seen kitchen stoves
cleaner than this place.
Hey, come on.
Look at my suit.
All right, all right, Digit.
All right. (CLEARS THROAT)
Hey, how much money
did we make today?
Oh.
Oh, well. Well, let's see.
Uh, seven, nine, four, six,
carry one, drop two. (CLICKING)
Uh, take five,
five down, seven up, 98.6...
(COUNTING INAUDIBLY)
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And two plus two is 22.
What did we make?
What's the boodle?
(STUTTERS) Oh, so far,
we have collected $89 and...
And 13 cents. Uh-oh.
(LAUGHS)
And we'll get another 17 from Moe.
Uh, that's 50 cents
less than yesterday.
What?
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Fifty cents!
I hate to lose money.
Mmm. Where can I pick up
an extra 50 cents?
(CHUCKLES)
Bye!
Au revoir, my little immigrant!
Huh?
(GRUNTS)
Hmm. Hey, boss, a kid.
(SIGHS)
Hmm. You know, Moe can
always use an extra kid
at 50 cents a day.
Yeah.
Very interesting.
Ahem! Well, well, well!
Rat's the name, Warren T. Rat.
What can I do you for, kid?
I'm looking for my family.
Hey, you come to
the right fellow, kid.
I know exactly where they are.
Come with me.
But Henri said I'd find them here!
Have it your way, kid.
But remember what Shakespeare said.
And I quote.
(CLEARS THROAT)
"Opportunity knocks but..."
Uh... But, uh...
Psst! Once!
"But... But once!
"Taken at the tide,
t'will lead to fortune.
"If denied, t'will never return."
Do you really know
where my family is?
(LAUGHS)
Trust me. Hey, trust me.
TANYA: Mama, I keep having this
feeling that Fievel's alive.
Tanya, it will go away.
After a while, it will go away.
WARREN: Come with me.
Hey, hey, hey.
Don't break a gut there.
"O! Pardon me,
"thou bleeding piece of earth,
"That I am meek and gentle
with these butchers."
(CLEARS THROAT)
This is where they are.
Papa!
(SCREAMS)
(CACKLING)
Not bad, huh, Moe?
A new worker.
What about my family?
You don't need a family, kid.
You got a job here!
Just send me his salary, will you?
(SLAMS)
And where do you
think you're going?
You're mine! Now get to work!
(ALL SCREAM)
You! What are you looking at?
Back to work!
I want to get out of here.
(LAUGHS) You and me both.
I have to find my family.
Oh, shut up! Go to sleep.
CHILD 1: Pipe down.
CHILD 2: Oh, be quiet!
I wish we had that
mouse with the long hair.
She could drop her hair out the
window, and we can all climb down.
Sure. Out the window.
CHILD: Oh, fairy tales!
Wait a minute!
This kid may have something.
Tony Toponi's the name.
Put it there. Well, uh...
Fievel.
Fievel Mousekewitz.
Fievel!
Ooh, that name's got to go!
Hey, I'll tell you what...
Fillie!
Fillie?
Yeah!
Fits you perfect!
Hey, Fillie.
You got any idea
where your family is?
Fillie!
Fillie Mousekewitz!
TONY: Hey, Fillie!
(CHILD SHUSHING)
WOMAN: ♪ Poor wandering one
♪ Though thou
hast surely strayed
♪ Take heart of grace
♪ Thy steps retrace ♪
(BELL TOLLING)
ALL:
I pledge allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America
and to the republic
for which it stands,
one nation...
WOMAN: Fievel!
Fievel!
What am I going to do with you?
Come on, come little ones, eat.
Don't gobble so.
Back! Back! Mine!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(SCREAMS)
(PANTS)
(COUGHING)
(VIOLIN PLAYS)
Papa.
Papa!
CONDUCTOR:
Grand and Hester streets!
(BELL RINGING)
(WOMEN GIGGLING)
Here, Papa. Here I am.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
Papa? (ECHOING)
Are you there?
(SNIFFLES)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(LOUD MUSIC PLAYS)
(DISTORTED MUSIC PLAYING)
WOMAN: Oh, my word! A mouse!
(ALL SCREAM)
MAN: What's going on up there?
Hey! Shut up out there!
WOMAN: What's going on up there?
(LAUGHS)
(WHISTLES)
Hey, Fillie!
I've been looking all over for you.
Pardon the expression,
but you look like something
the cat dragged in, you know?
Hey, you all right?
Yeah, I guess so.
Listen, you go
running off like that
and you're gonna get
yourself seriously lost.
Stick with me, okay?
(SIGHS)
Hey, hey, hey. Hey!
What, we engaged or something?
(SCOFFS)
(WHISTLES)
Why can't we try to
find Fievel, Papa?
Oh. (SIGHS)
Just try!
I know, Papa.
Play your violin.
Play Fievel's song.
Oy, Tanya.
Maybe he'll hear it.
You can't find what's not there.
Okay, okay.
I got it all figured out.
We'll start looking for
your family over in...
(BABBLING)
This is America.
Don't be afraid.
Are you going to let
those cats push you around?
Tony? Hey, Tony, where you going?
(GIGGLES)
I ask you this.
Are we going to stand by
and let cats wreck our homes,
our businesses and our lives?
If we all got together, we could
do something about the cats!
Yeah. We should all get together.
This is America.
We have free speech.
You can say "cat" here.
(ALL GASP)
Cat, cat, cat!
And double cat!
MOUSE: Shh! Not so loud.
Shh.
Please, not that word.
Wait a minute. Come back!
Where are you going?
(GASPING)
Oh.
(GIGGLING)
(STUTTERS) So,
if we all got together,
we could do something about the...
(WHISPERS) Cats.
Yeah.
Cat...
Ca...
Cat.
(BLABBERING)
Tony?
Tony, what's wrong with you?
(SIGHS)
(ALL CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
FIEVEL:
But there are no cats in America.
MOUSE: That does it.
I'm getting out of here!
Mmm-hmm, me too.
What are you all afraid of?
Cats, cats, cats, cats.
Papa told me.
Everyone knows it.
There are no cats.
(ROARING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(ALL GASP)
(PANTS)
Hey, you all right?
I mean, you ain't
hurt or nothing, are you?
No. No, I'm okay.
(GRUNTS) Thank you.
No, really, I'm all right.
Really, I am.
(GASPING)
How about you?
TONY: Nah!
Who do those cats think they are?
I'll show them
a thing or two next time.
Hey, where's Fillie?
Fillie? Who's Fillie?
Oh, I gotta find him.
He's just a kid.
Fillie!
Tony!
Whoa!
Phew! Hmm. Some scrap, huh?
There are cats here.
Wait till I tell Papa!
If I find him.
You see,
he's looking for his family.
Aw, the poor darling.
(GASPING) Wait a minute!
Honest John, at Tammany Hall.
He'll know where your family is.
He will?
Tony, he knows
every mouse in the city!
Ha! Told you to
stick with me, yeah?
Come on.
(PANTING)
Oh!
Well, Mr. There Are
No Whats in America?
Mmm?
Cats.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
(MAN LAUGHING)
It's me third wake today,
and I'm not finished.
We've got to do
something about them cats.
(SIGHS)
Besides paying Warren T. Rat
for no protection.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Oh, oh, poor lad.
So young.
He never had a chance to vote.
Well, he'll vote from now on.
I'll see to that.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
(ALL GASPING)
Honest John.
It's Gussie Mausheimer!
Oh.
Ooh-whee, the richest and most
powerful mouse in New York.
What's she doing
slumming in this part of town?
(GASPING)
There's a dead mouse on that table.
It's an Irish custom, Gussie.
The cats got him today.
Precisely why I am here to see you.
(HICCUPS) Would you care for
a wee drop of the creature?
Today was the worst ever.
Those cats are killing everyone!
They don't even know the
difference between rich and poor.
The wretches!
Oh, shameful!
As you know,
I have dedicated my life
to helping those less
fortunate than myself.
Uh, that's everyone.
And now I want you to help me.
We must have a wawwy.
A wawwy? What's a wawwy?
You know, a wawwy.
A large gathering
of mice for a reason.
Oh, a rally!
That's what I said, a wawwy.
(SIGHS)
Tomorrow at Mausheimer Park,
we will all decide what to do.
I'll bring the uptown mice
and you bring
the mice from downtown.
Madam,
you can count on Honest John.
(GRUNTS)
(SLAMS)
At last, we're all getting
together about the cats.
Bridget.
Oh, Fillie.
Honest John, he's lost his family.
By any chance, do you
know the Mousekewitzes?
Oh, hmm.
Are they registered to vote?
(HICCUPS)
They just got off the boat.
Oh. (CLEARS THROAT)
Sorry, don't know them yet.
(HICCUPS)
(CHUCKLES)
BRIDGET:
That's my mother and father.
(SIGHS) The cats got them
two years ago November.
Now, don't you worry.
Yours are all right.
And they're out there somewhere.
Now. (KISSING)
Get some sleep.
♪ Somewhere
♪ Out there
♪ Beneath the
♪ Pale moonlight
♪ Someone's
♪ Thinking of me
♪ And loving me tonight
♪ Somewhere
♪ Out there
♪ Someone's saying a prayer
♪ That we'll find
♪ One another
♪ In that big somewhere
♪ Out there
♪ And even though I know
♪ How very far apart we are
♪ It helps to think
we might be wishing
♪ On the same bright star
♪ And when the night wind
starts to sing
♪ A lonesome lullaby
♪ It helps to
think we're sleeping
♪ Underneath the same big sky
♪ Somewhere
♪ Out there
♪ If love can
♪ See us through
♪ Then we'll be
♪ Together
♪ Somewhere out there
♪ Out where dreams
♪ Come true ♪
GUSSIE: Attention, please!
Attention, please!
You all know why we are here.
We have got to do something
about these cats.
(CROWD CLAMORING)
Not so loud! They'll hear you!
GUSSIE: So?
Let them hear me.
FEMALE: You can talk!
You're rich!
(CROWD IN UPROAR)
Money is not everything.
I know, because I have money
and I have everything,
but what are they
worth without freedom?
Hear, hear!
ALL: Yeah! Right!
Why did we come to America?
For freedom!
(ALL CHEERING)
Why are they building that statue?
What does it stand for?
Freedom!
So what do we want?
ALL: Freedom!
Right!
Freedom from cats.
And because this is America, we
can do something about them!
What do we do?
(CROWD CLAMORING)
Papa, I can't see.
MOUSE: They're bigger than we are!
Not if we all work together.
What are you afraid of?
Are we men, or are we mice?
ALL: Mice!
MOUSE:
Mice, indeed, and proud of it!
So, what are we going to do
about those cats?
Well?
Any ideas?
HONEST JOHN: Ahem.
Oh, yes, well, I...
(COUGHS)
Oh, dear.
I have an idea.
Yes?
(WHISPERING)
Hmm.
(CHUCKLES)
What did he say?
(WHISPERS)
Uh, he, he said, uh...
(WHISPERS) Uh-huh.
Hmm...
Ohh.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Yes. Cute little fellow.
Wait a minute.
I think this little fellow
has got something here.
(CLEARS THROAT)
We have a plan!
(CROWD CHEERING)
Oh, Papa.
She's in the way again!
(SHUSHING)
(EERIE LAUGHTER)
Look out below!
Shh!
We have a plan!
E pluribus unum!
(WHISTLES)
(EXPLOSION)
Ladies and gentlemen,
I want to thank you so much
for your participation.
And I want to close by saying,
that a vote for Honest John
is a vote for freedom!
Freedom is what it is!
And thank you again, one and all!
(ALARM RINGS)
Holy spumoni!
We should have been at
the pier an hour ago!
The pier?
That's a scary place!
I promised Bridget we'd be on time.
Wait for me! Wait!
Geez Louise, am I in the doghouse!
Pick 'em up!
(PANTING)
Tell me what time it was, huh?
But, Tony, I can't tell time!
Tony, slow down! Wait!
Wait!
(VIOLIN PLAYING)
Papa?
Tony!
Papa!
(ECHOING) I'm coming, Papa!
(GASPING)
(ALLIGATOR CHOMPING)
(VIOLIN PLAYING)
Papa?
All right, ante up, boys.
Hey, no cheating.
(GROWLING)
Hmm.
(GASPING)
Ooh! I got it! I got it!
(SQUEALS) I got it!
Rummy!
(CHUCKLES)
Tiger, for the hundredth time,
we're playing poker.
I knew that. I knew that.
But who can concentrate with
all that, you know, noise?
(GROWLS)
Hey, Tiger.
When the boss plays, it's culture.
Sure, culture.
I think it sounds, uh, melodious.
"If music be the food of love,
"play on, McDuff, play on."
(SIGHS) Oh, I don't know which is
worse, the music or the Shakespeare.
Rats! This nose, this nose
here keeps getting in the way!
You... You could stop playing.
(CHUCKLES)
(SCOFFS)
That's funny.
I've never known a
cockroach with good taste.
(GULPS)
But, I've known plenty that taste...
(LAUGHING EVILLY)
Good.
Play, play, play!
Ahem. Hmm.
(YAWNS)
Warren T!
(LAUGHS)
(GASPING)
You!
You're not a rat!
You're a cat!
How did you get in here?
Come here, you little...
(SCREAMS)
(SHRIEKS IN PAIN)
Gentlemen, cat's out of the bag!
(CRASHING)
Get me that mouse!
Let me at him.
I mean, let me at him.
I'll kill him! Get out of my way!
Get out of my way!
(GROANS)
You just stepped on my tail!
(GRUNTS)
Come here, you little runt!
CAT: Get him!
(GROANS)
(ALL SHOUTING)
(CAT GUFFAWING)
GUSSIE: Once more.
There is the boat.
The boat whistle blows
at 6:00 in the morning,
and that is when we must release
the secret weapon!
(ALL CHEERING)
So, the cats must be here
at 6:00 on the dot,
not a moment before or after.
Now, when you go to get the cats,
what do you do to
make them come here?
(CLEARING THROATS)
(TAUNTINGLY)
Nyah nyah nyah-nyah nyah.
Right!
Now get some sleep.
We have a long day ahead.
CAT: No, no, no.
Boss, it was not me.
I promise, that wasn't me.
(SNORING)
TIGER: Wake up.
Uh, wake up.
Jake! Wake up.
You're up.
Uh, go get some sleep, Jake.
(SOBBING)
JAKE: Oh, yeah, you're right.
Rest, sleep.
(GROWLS)
On your guard, Tiger!
(GROWLING)
Don't make any funny moves.
'Cause I'm crafty, and I'm quick.
I have the instinct of a cat.
(WHISPERS) What am I saying?
I am a cat!
(SOBBING)
Oh, hey, now don't start that.
I didn't mean to scare
you that much, really.
It's okay, little buddy.
Hey, I'm your friend.
Aw, come on.
Be happy. (CHUCKLES)
Aw.
Oh, come on.
What are you crying for?
I can't get out of
here and I have to,
so I can find my family.
You lost your family?
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, no.
(SNIFFLES)
That's terrible.
You know, I lost my family, too.
(SOBS)
Years ago, I mean.
(SOBBING) Eight brothers...
Ten sisters...
Three fathers...
Don't cry.
You'll find them.
(SNIFFLES)
Do you really think so?
Gee, you're nice.
Um, my name is Tiger.
What's yours?
Fievel, Fievel Mousekewitz.
TIGER: (WHIMPERING) Oh, dear.
Listen. I like mice.
(WEEPS)
Oh, no, not like that.
I mean, I don't eat
red meat at all.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm a vegetarian.
That's right.
Oh, a little fish now and then.
But what I really
like is some nice... Shh...
Broccoli. (SNICKERS)
You know, I thought all cats
were supposed to be mean.
Mean? Ha!
I am mean! (GROWLING)
TIGER: Then... And...
Aw, what's the use?
I like butterflies
with big golden wings
and blue and green tips.
Me, too!
Yeah? Ha.
I like Swiss cheese ice cream.
Me, too! Me, too!
You too, too? Hmm.
Wait a minute.
What's your favorite book?
Um, The Brothers Karamazov.
The Brothers...
(CHUCKLES) I can't believe it.
I can't believe it!
(PURRS)
♪ I can tell we got
an awful lot in common
♪ Even though we look
as different as can be
♪ We don't even have to try
♪ To see things eye to eye
♪ It just comes
to us naturally
♪ Come to think of it
♪ I think we fit together
♪ Playing cat and mouse
won't get us very far
♪ There's no
need to feud and fuss
♪ When it isn't really us
♪ Let's you and me
♪ Be who we are
♪ We're a duo
♪ A duo
♪ A pair of lonely ones
♪ Who were meant to be a two-o
♪ A duo
♪ It's true-o
♪ Wherever we go
♪ We're going me and you
♪ Oh, no matter what
♪ Now we've got one another
♪ We'll be there to pick
each other off the floor
♪ Any time you're feeling glum
♪ Count on me to be your chum
♪ If you get an itch attack
♪ I'll be there
to scratch your back
♪ Now who could
ever ask for more
♪ Oh oh oh
♪ Oh ♪
(LAUGHS)
(LAUGHING WILDLY)
Oh, stop! Oh, stop!
No! Don't! Don't stop!
More! More!
♪ We're friends and that's
what friends are for
♪ We're a duo
♪ A duo
♪ A pair of lonely ones
♪ Who were meant to be a two-o
♪ A duo
♪ It's true-o
♪ If we're ever in a stew
♪ We know we
can make it through
♪ Cause you've got me
♪ And I got
♪ Your
Yes, sir!
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(ALARM RINGS)
(GASPING)
Where did that come from? Don't.
(GRUNTING)
Oh, stop it! Uh! Oh!
WARREN:
Tiger, how did he get away?
TIGER: He overpowered me.
You're fired.
TIGER: Good. I'm glad.
I never liked you,
and besides, your music stinks.
Tony! Help!
Help! Cats!
FIEVEL: Tony, Bridget, help!
Cats!
It's the cats!
(GASPING)
FIEVEL: Help!
Oh, they're early!
Wake up! Everybody, wake up!
(FIEVEL SCREAMING)
Cats!
Help!
Wake up! The cats are here!
(CATS GROWLING)
Wake up!
(ALL SHUSHING)
Cats!
(KAZOO BLOWING)
The cats!
Release the secret weapon!
What? Release the... Oh, no!
(KAZOO BLOWING)
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh, no! No, no!
Wait for the boat whistle!
(GROWLING)
(GROANS)
Hold your fire.
It's that rat, Warren T.
He's not a rat.
He's a cat.
He's their boss.
Pay no attention to
that little mouse.
Just throw down all your
money and that kid.
And I will personally convince
these cats to leave you alone.
You're wrecking the plan!
It's not supposed
to happen this way!
Just throw down that kid!
Oh. yeah?
FIEVEL: Bull's eye!
(ALL GASP)
Disregard the nose.
What's in a nose?
A nose by any other name
would smell as sweet...
(ALL GASPING)
MOUSE: Great whiskers, it's a cat!
He's a cat!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, wait a minute.
Who are you going to believe,
me or your own eyes?
(CROWD CLAMORING)
(PANTS) Release the secret...
No, no!
(SHOUTING) Hey, easy, easy!
All right. Then, I take
it we can't do business.
Warren, you're through.
Washed up, ruined!
(SCOFFS)
You'll never get another cent
from any mouse, anywhere.
Eh? We'll see about that.
Just wait, you little rat.
(CHUCKLES)
Just wait.
Adiós!
ALL: Fire!
Oh! Tie it Off! Hurry!
(SHRIEKS)
(GRUNTS)
Oh, saints be praised.
It stopped.
(PANTS)
(HORN BLOWS)
Release the secret weapon!
(ALARM SOUNDS)
(GASPING)
Release? Oh, no!
Release the secret weapon!
Make up your mind!
Ooh, ooh! My goodness!
Release the secret weapon!
Release the weapon!
Release the blasted weapon!
Faster, papa.
(KAZOO BLOWING)
WARREN: We can't do business here, huh?
(CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLING CONTINUES)
(BELL RINGS)
(GASPING)
GUSSIE: Release the secret weapon!
Faster!
(CRASHING)
(EXPLOSION)
(GROWLING)
Get a load of that.
(ALL SCREAM)
(GROWLING)
CAT 1:
It's the Giant Mouse of Minsk!
CAT 2: Oh, you're right.
(GROWLING THUNDEROUSLY)
(ALL SHRIEK)
BOTH: Yay!
(GASPING WILDLY)
Head for the pier!
(SCREAMS)
We did it!
Whoa!
(SCREAMS)
(GASPING)
(MACHINE GRUNTING)
(CHEERING)
MOUSE: They can't swim!
Ladies and gentlemen,
credit where it's due.
We owe it all to Fillie
and his Mouse of Minsk!
♪ Now there are no
cats in America... ♪
Fillie! Who's Fillie?
(MICE SINGING)
(COUGHING)
Someday,
Gussie Mausheimer, someday!
And you, too, Mousekewitz.
All of you! I hate mice!
I'm having a heart attack here.
(CLEARS THROAT) Oh, don't worry,
gentlemen. Don't worry.
There are plenty of
mice in Hong Kong.
Oh, my! I'll have to learn
to calculate in Chinese.
Hmm. Let me see, uh.
(TALKING GIBBERISH)
(HORN BLOWS)
WARREN: Hey, I wonder how you
say "trust me" in Chinese.
(LIQUID FLOWING)
The pier's on fire!
(ALL SCREAMING)
(CROWD CLAMORING)
MAN: Move it! Move it! Move it!
Bring that hose over here.
You there, come on!
TONY: (CALLING) Fillie!
Fillie Mousekewitz!
Where are you?
Tony, look.
Fievel!
BRIDGET: Fillie!
Papa, listen.
BRIDGET: Fillie Mousekewitz!
Ah, so what? Someone is
calling a Fillie Mousekewitz.
They changed my name to Tilly.
Maybe they changed Fievel's
name to Fillie.
(SIGHS)
Come on, Papa. Just got to see.
Wait!
Stop! Stop!
TANYA: Hurry. Hurry!
Fillie Mousekewitz!
Fillie!
(PAPA PANTING)
Wait!
Stop! om
You are calling for
a Fillie Mousekewitz, right?
Here, tell my daughter his
name is Fillie and not Fievel.
His name is Fillie.
You see?
And Fievel.
And Fievel?
TANYA: Papa.
No, no, no, there are many Fievel
Mousekewitzes in New York.
Maybe thousands.
It could still be
another Fievel Mousekewitz.
No, Papa.
Look.
(EXPLOSION)
(CHUCKLES)
Get a load of this, huh.
Hey, kid,
you're sleeping in my place.
Huh?
Hey, give me that!
Got any food on you?
Hey, what's your story?
(STAMMERING)
I've been looking for my family.
(SNICKERS) Hey, fellows, he's
looking for his family.
(IN SING SONG VOICE)
He's looking for his family!
(ALL LAUGHING)
I stopped that a long time ago.
At least you know who they are.
Yeah!
Why are you looking for them?
They should be looking for you.
They don't care.
Forget them.
(WHIMPERING)
You're right, they don't care!
And if they did,
they would have found me.
Well, if they don't care,
I don't care!
I don't care if I
never see them again.
Yeah, you're nothing.
You're junk, you're trash.
(ALL GIGGLING)
Here. (SCOFFS)
Make yourself a bed.
I'll never find them again anyway.
Never
This is my home now.
(THUNDER CRACKING)
TANYA: Fievel!
Fievel!
Fillie!
Hey, Fillie Mousekewitz!
I never dreamt this morning
I would be riding a feline.
(CHUCKLES) A feline?
A cat!
I knew that. I knew that.
Keep playing. Keep playing.
We will find him.
(VIOLIN PLAYING)
TANYA: Fievel!
Fievel!
Fievel, where are you?
PAPA: Fievel?
Fievel?
Papa?
Papa.
PAPA: Fievel?
Papa!
Where are you?
Fiev... Wait, stop!
Fievel!
I'm coming, Papa!
Papa!
(CHUCKLES) Fievel.
MAMA: Fievel!
Mama, look!
Mama!
(PAPA CHEERING)
What's come over me?
I am hugging a cat.
I've never been so
happy in my life.
I have friends,
lots of little tiny friends.
BRIDGET: Oh, Tony, isn't it grand?
Say, I don't hear no
one thanking me here.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh!
Fievel, I knew
you were alive. I knew it!
Oh, my little boy
back from the dead.
America. Hmm.
What a place.
(SNIFFLES)
My Fievel.
I thought I would
never see you again.
Never say never, Papa.
Oh!
Oh! I nearly forgot.
Here, Fievel, your hat.
MAMA: Your hat... It fits.
PAPA: My son.
Now, you are a mouse.
My statue is finished.
(SCATTING)
Wait till you see her.
She is beautiful.
Magnifique.
Mama, look, don't be afraid
to open your eyes. (SHRIEKS)
(CHUCKLES)
Look what you're missing.
You're missing everything.
MAMA:
Papa, when we land, I'll look.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
No, whoa!
This is... Oh, whoa, whoa!
Oh, oh, this is nice.
Oh, thanks, fellas.
I appreciate you
coming back for me.
You in the front, higher, higher!
TIGER: Whoa!
TANYA:
Oh, Henri, she's so beautiful.
(GASPING) Wow.
(GIGGLING)
Henri, what's that over there?
Oh, that is more America.
FIEVEL: Can we go see it?
(HENRI CHUCKLES)
You will, my little American.
(CHUCKLES)
Someday, you will.
BOTH: Bye, bye.
♪ Somewhere out there
♪ Beneath the pale moonlight
♪ Someone's
♪ Thinking of me
♪ And loving me
♪ Tonight
♪ Somewhere out there
♪ Someone's saying a prayer
♪ That we'll find one another
♪ In that big somewhere
♪ Out there
♪ And even though I know
♪ How very far apart we are
♪ It helps to think
we might be wishing
♪ On the same bright star
♪ And when the night wind
♪ Starts to sing
a lonesome lullaby
♪ It helps to think
we're sleeping underneath
♪ the same big sky
♪ Somewhere out there
♪ If love can see us through
♪ Can see us through
♪ Then we'll be
♪ Together
♪ Somewhere out there
♪ Out where dreams
♪ Come true ♪