This is a tale aboutan unprejudiced heart...
and how it changed our valley forever.
There was a time not so long ago...
when pigs were afforded norespect except by other pigs.
They lived their whole livesin a cruel and sunless world.
In those days, pigs believed thatthe sooner they grew large and fat,
the sooner they'd betaken into pig paradise.
- Haa! Haa! Get up!- A place so wonderful...
- that no pig had ever thought to come back.- Yo! Yeah!
Good-bye, Mom.
So when the day came for their parents togo to that other world of endless pleasures,
it was not a time foryoung pigs to be sad.
Just another step towards the daywhen they, too, would make the journey.
Perhaps it was because he was alone.
Perhaps his sadnessmade him easier to catch.
Whatever the reason, of the thousandsof animals in the piggery that day...
only one was chosen.
- How's this one, Harry?- Just right for the purpose.
- How much do I owe you?- It's a runt, Harry. A worthless, little runt.
You're too modest, Esme Hoggett.
Nine out of ten first prizesfor jams and jellies...
is more than a matter of luck.
Luck still plays its part. Ourberries were wickedly good this year.
And our water is very tasty too.
Of course, we don't use the town water.
Arthur Hoggett! How's it going, Arthur?
How are those sheep ofyours? Come on, try your luck.
How about taking a guess,Arthur? All for a good cause.
- Don't keep pigs.- Christmas day. Think of it. What a feast!
That'll do, Pig.
The pig and the farmerregarded each other.
And for a fleeting moment,something passed between them.
- A faint sense of some common destiny.- Hah. Strange.
First time the little thinghasn't screamed its head off.
Now you'll have to have a guess.
Sixteen pounds, five-
Eew.
Two ounces.
Hooey! Hoggett!
Thanks, Arthur. We'll beweighing the little pig tomorrow.
We'll phone you if you win.
When you win, Arthur. When you win!
Care to guess the pig's weight, sir?
Support the Lion's Club.
Ooh!
What could we do witha pig, eh, Duchess?
Just think. Two nicehams. Two sides of bacon.
Oh, and pork chops, kidney,liver, chitlins, pickle his feet.
- Save his blood for blackpuddin'. There's the telephone.
Hoggett!
Good news, Arthur. You've won the pig.
Oh.
Pigs are definitely stupid.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
- What is it, Mom?- That's a pig.
- They'll eat him when he's big.- Will they eat us?
Good heavens, no! The bossesonly eat stupid animals...
like sheep and ducks and chickens.
Yea!
It does look stupid, Mom.
Not as stupid as sheep, mind you.But pigs are definitely stupid.
Excuse me. No, we're not.
- Good heavens! Who are you?- I'm a Large White.
- Yes, that's your breed, dear. What's your name?- I don't know.
What did your mother call you to tellyou apart from your brothers and sisters?
Our mom called us all the same.
And what was that, dear?
She called us all Babe.
Perhaps we shouldn't talktoo much about, uh, family.
I want my mom.
There, there. You've gotto be a brave boy now.
I left my mother when I was your age,and my pups will have to leave me soon.
But I'll keep an eye on you, if youlike, just 'til you find your feet.
The little pig's a bit low.He's going to sleep with us...
just 'til he finds his feet.
Until he finds his feet.
But, Mom, he'll wet the bed!
Nonsense!
If you do want to do anything,you'll go outside, won't you?
Good boy.
Yea!
Yeah! Yeah! Stomp on him!
What's your name, Pig?
- What does he taste like?- Where did he come from?
Comin' through! Hey, get lost!
We've got to dosomething about that duck.
Ooh! Ooh!
Doodle-loo-dee-doo.
- What's that noise?- It's only Ferdinand.
- What's Ferdinand?- He's a duck.
- He wants to be a rooster.- He hates being a duck.
- We'll catch him one day and eat him. Won't we, Mom?- Yes, dear.
Yech! Who'd want to eat a duck?
Babe, you wait here.
- Aren't pigs allowed?- Not live ones.
- Sorry, dear. Only dogs and cats inside the house.- Why?
That's just the way things are.
Whoa!
- Ow! -Pig-pig-piggy!
Ooh, what a spectacularfeast I've got for you.
Oh, yes! What a luckylittle pork chop you are.
Delicious! Oh, yes! Yum, yum, yum.
Who's gonna grow upto be a big, fat pig?
You are! You are! Yum, yum, yum.
- Where are we going?- To work with the sheep.
- What's sheep?- Sheep is animals with thick, woolly coats.
And thick woolly heads. And mencan't look after them without us.
- Why do they need us?'Cause we're sheepdogs! Yea!
- Not you, dear.- Why not?
We have to do dogs' work. You're a pig.Your job is to stay here and eat your food.
We'll be back at the end of the day.
They don't think I'llremember. Well, I don't forget.
Seems like a sheep'sjust born to suffer.
Hello? Excuse me.
Darn wolf!
- I'm not a wolf. I'm a pig. What are you?- Ewe.
Pig. What are you?
I'm a ewe. A ewe!
- You're a sheep!- I'll not be called a common sheep, thank you kindly.
I'm a Border Leicesterewe. The name's Maa.
Oh.
- What's wrong with you, Maa?- Foot rot. And I got me a nasty cough.
And I'm not as young as I used to be.
Hmph.
- Seem like a nice young pig. What be your name?- Babe.
Not like them wolves. Treatyou like dirt, they do!
- Bite you as soon as look at you, those savages!- Bite you?
And worse. Some wolves be so bad,
they run a sheep downand tear it to pieces.
Fly would never do that!
Fly, is it? A right viciouscreature she be, I'll tell you.
- Not Fly.- All them wolves is cruel to sheep. Always have been.
Brutal savages! That's what they be.
I wouldn't want to see a gentle soullike you mixin' with the likes of them.
That afternoon when he saw Fly,
the pig's mind was atangle of questions.
Cruel, vicious, brutal?
What was it that dogsdid in the fields all day?
- Hello, Babe? Had a good day?- Yes, thank you.
The old sheep had to be wrong about Fly.
And the pig promised himself that he wouldnever think badly of any creature ever again.
Crime and Punishment!
The morning of the terrible crime...
started like any other on Hoggett Farm.
Comin' through! Comin' through!
Take off!
- Now!- Up, up, up.
Nee-nee-nee-nee.
Hmm?
I was worried it might have a harsh tone,but that's quite a nice musical ring.
I walked into O'Halloran's Hardware,and there it was waiting for me.
What a splendid way towake up each morning!
Hoggett, dear. Church.
When embarking on an audacious crime,
a duck needs a willing accomplice.
A creature who isreliable, beyond suspicion,
and above all, extremely gullible.
Hey! Psst!
Wha- What?
You look like an intelligent,sophisticated, discerning young fella.
- Who, me?- Yeah. Follow me. Oh, boy! Are you in for some fun!
What are we doin'? Where are we goin'?
Now the duck knewexactly what he had to do.
- The alarm clock had to go. His very life depended on it.- Do you see it?
- Yes.- Good.
So I go through the kitchen,across the living room...
- Good, good.- into the bedroom.
Get the mechanical roosterand bring it out to you.
- What about that cat?- But quietly bring it out to you.
- Excellent.- I don't think I can do it.
It's against the rules. Only dogsand cats allowed in the house.
It's a good rule, but this is biggerthan rules. This is life and death.
- It is? -Mm-hmm. Follow me.
Hello! Look, there'ssomething you should know.
- Humans eat ducks!- I beg your pardon?
Most ducks prefer to forget it, but thefact is that humans like to eat plump ducks.
I don't think so. Not theboss. Not the boss's wife.
Come on. Humans don't eat cats. Why?
- Well, they're- - They'reindispensable. They catch mice.
Humans don't eat roosters. Why? They make eggswith the hens and wake up everyone in the morning.
I tried it with thehens. It didn't work.
So I turned to crowing,and lo! I discover my gift.
But no sooner do I become indispensablethan they bring in a machine to do the job!
Ah, the treachery of it!
- A mechanical rooster!- Oh, dear me.
Oh, dear you?
I suppose the lifeof an anorexic duck...
doesn't amount to much inthe broad scheme of things.
But, Pig,
I'm all I've got.
Why do you need me to do it?
- I'm allergic to cats.- Oh.
They make me sneeze.
Ahh.
Don't worry. I won't wake the cat.
My life is in your hands.
Oh, dear.
Oh, no!
Ah, boy.
No, no, no!
Your foot, your foot! Takethe string off your foot.
Wait, wait. Let me put itthis way. Stop. Turn around-
Shh.
No, no! The other way! Turn-
No, stop! Oh!
Stop! Stop, stop, stop!
Don't, don't, stupid. Go outside... now.
- But you said you can't do without me.- I can. Trust me, I can.
- Are you sure? You're positive?- Yes!
- Go outside and stand guard.- Okay. Good idea.
Oh, boy. Want something done,you gotta do it yourself.
- Hmm.- Guard against what?
Ahh! Ahh! Don't worry.
Stick with me and please, Ibeg you, not one more word.
All right.
Aah-
Don't sneeze, Ferdie.
- Just hold yourbreath. - Ahhh-
Ah-choo!
It was my mistake. I was tryingto loosen things up a little.
But, no. Today provesthat it doesn't work.
From now on, we'llall respect the rules.
To each creature its own destiny.
Every animal in its proper place.
And a pig's proper place is underthe old cart, not in the barn.
And absolutely never in the house.
- Is that understood?- Yes, sir.
Now, Pig, regarding thecompany you keep. Being young,
it's hard to discriminate,so I'll make it easy for you.
I forbid you to talkto or consort with...
that duck... ever.
- Have I made myself clear?- Uh... what's "consort"?
It means, young man,
that you must not goanywhere near that duck.
As for the fugitive duck, when heshows himself, let him know this:
Being a duck he must behave like a duck.No more of this crowing and nonsense.
He should accept what heis and be thankful for it.
- That goes for all of us.- Here, here!
Rex continued long into the night.
Elsewhere, there was more talk.
The subject was Christmas dinner...
and whether that year the maincourse would be roast pork...
or Duck a l'Orange.
And pork is a nice, sweet meat.
Then there's the crackling. Thatalways adds interest and texture.
Get him!
Get the pig! Get the pig! Get the pig!
Get him! Get him!
- Psst!- Ferdinand!
- Everyone's been looking for you.- Shh. Shh.
- What is this place?- What's happenin' out there?
Rex isn't very happy.Boy, all these new rules!
I'm not allowed to- Oops.
Not allowed to what?
Huh?
- Piggy!- What? You didn't see me, all right?
And I didn't see you. All right? Oops.
The time comes for all creatures...
when childhood ends...
and the doorway opensto life as an adult.
And so it was with Fly's pups.
Though that time wasall too soon for Fly.
Puppy, puppy, puppy. Come on.
In my pocket.
Fly?
May I call you Mom?
And so it was that the pig...
found his place inthe world of the farm.
And he was happy, even in his dreams.
- Hello!- Folks, how are you? Merry Christmas!
How's my favorite girl?
Nanny's got a jellybean.
Give us a kiss.
Guess what we're havingfor Christmas dinner.
- Roast pork.- I hate pork.
Darn silly carry-on, if you ask me.
The cat says they call it Christmas.
Christmas! Christmas dinner, yeah.
Dinner means death.
Death means carnage!Christmas means carnage!
Christmas means carnage!
Oooh.
Yes!
Wait.
Eatin' pigs! Blaah! Barbarians!
You're goin' back to the fields, Maa.
Oh, young'un, tragic thereain't more of your kind.
- I'll be thinkin' of ya always.- I could come visit you.
I'd like that, but-
Well, we shouldn'thope for too much. Ooh!
And so, it was Christmas Eve.
And time had run out for the pig.
- Are you doing him tonight then?- Mmm.
Good. The blood'll drain by morning.
- Pity.- What's that?
Nothin'.
What on earth are you babbling on about?
Shame to miss out on the best hamprize at next year's fair, is all.
Nice plump haunches he's gettin'.
Beautiful. Still...
silly to wait, I suppose.
Here it is!
- The bird.- Yuck. Chicken?
No, it's Duck a l'Orange.
And, Mother, it looks absolutely superb.
- I'm not going to eat any of it!- This is fabulous.
Ferdinand!
If you're out here, who's that in there?
Her name's Rosanna.
Why Rosanna?
- She had such a beautiful nature.- Oh, Ferdinand.
- I can't take it anymore.- Really!
The fear's too much for aduck. It eats away at the soul.
There must be kinder dispositionsin far-off gentler lands.
The only way you'll findhappiness is to accept...
that the way things areis the way things are.
The way things are stinks! I'mnot gonna be a goner. I'm gone.
I wish all of you the best of luck.
- Where will you go?- No idea.
But I'm a clever duck. Icould do with an adventure.
- I'll miss you, Ferdie.- Ferdie? No one's ever called me that before.
Hey, good luck, Pig. Huh?
- I am outta here.- Bye, bye.
Ow! Would you do me a favor, old thing?
- Anything.- Open the gate, huh?
Ah! Ah! Ahh!Ha-ha-ha! Whoa!
The pig knew it was againstthe rules to leave the farm.
But something was definitely wrong.
How lovely, darling. What is it?
It's a fax machine. You cansend us letters by phone.
- Hmm.- Oh.
At any other time, the pigwould've been tickled pink...
by his first visit to the sheep fields.
But now there was fear in the air.
Maa and her kind were under threat.
Hey, Frank, feel likepork for dinner tonight?
- Young'un, you're alive!- Maa!
What's happening? Who are these men?
I'll get him out. Come around, Sniff!
Where's our boss? It doesn't seem right.
- What's wrong, dear?- It's the wrong one!
I want the house Isaw on the television!
Oh, there, there.
Get! Quick! Get the dog in.
Out of the sheep! Come on!
Let's go!
Good dog.
Good pig.
Oooh.
Oooh!
- Hey, hey. Dad says his little porker's a watch pig.- Dearie me!
If it's not a duck thatthinks it's a rooster,
it's a pig that thinks it's a dog!
A pig that thinks it's a dog!
A washing machine, aradio, a new alarm clock.
I think it's a lovely fax machine,darling, but can't you use it?
We already have one, Mom.That's the whole idea.
We can send faxes to each other.
Don't be afraid of itjust because it's new.
These accounts are a real worry, Arthur.
Every month your expenditureis greater than your income.
It's eating up your reserves.
You need to modernize, getsome sort of cash flow going.
You're still using a horseand cart, for God's sakes.
- Dad?- Funny, that.
- What?- Those chickens, that pig.
What's the pig got to do with anything?
Nothing.
Just look at them. Thebrowns and the whites.
Come, Rex. Come, Fly.
Come, Pig.
Come, Pig!
Perhaps he's pleased with youfor what you did yesterday.
- I didn't do much.- If it wasn't for you, dear,
they could've stolen the whole flock.
- Is Rex unhappy with me?- Oh, he'll be all right.
Just stay out of his way today.
Way to be, Fly. Rex, come by.
That'll do.
You're so quick. I'd neverbe able to fly like you can.
Pigs aren't built to fly, dear.
But speed isn't thething. It's attitude.
They just have to know who's boss.
Out you go.
Mmm!
Get 'em up, Pig.
- He wants you to drive them out of the yard.- Away to me, Pig.
Remember, you have to dominate them.
Do that and they'll doanything you want. Go.
Woof!
Woof, woof, woof!
Woof! Woof! Woof, woof, woof, woof!
This is ridiculous, Mom.
Nonsense. It's only your first try.
But you're treating them like equals.They're sheep. They're inferior.
- Ah, no they're not.- Of course they are!
We are their masters. Let them doubt itfor a second and they'll walk all over you.
- Fly, get that pig out of there.- Make them feel inferior. Abuse them. Insult them.
- But they'll laugh at me.- Then bite them.
Be ruthless. Whatever ittakes. Bend them to your will.
- Enough!- Go on! Go!
Move along there, you-
You, uh, big butt heads!
- Ow!- Young'un, stop this nonsense.
What's got into you? I just finishedtellin' what a nice young pig you be.
Maa, I was just trying to be a sheepdog.
Hah! Enough wolves inthe world already...
without a nice ladlike you turnin' nasty.
You haven't got it in ya, young'un.
You and I are descendedfrom the great sheepdogs.
We carry the bloodlineof the Ancient Bahou.
We stand for something.
And today I watched in shameas all that was betrayed.
- Rex, he's just a little pig.- All the greater the insult.
I'm sorry I bit you. Are you all right?
I wouldn't call that a bite, myself. Yougot teeth in that floppy mouth or just gums?
You see, ladies, a heart of gold.
Ahh. Heart of gold.
No need for all thiswolf nonsense, young'un.
All a nice little piglike you need do is ask.
Thanks very much. Itwas very kind of you.
- A pleasure.- What a nice little pig!
All right, how did you do it?
I asked them, and they didit. I asked them nicely.
We don't ask sheep, dear.We tell them what to do.
I did, Mom. They were really friendly.
Maybe Rex might be a little morefriendly if I had a talk with him.
No, no, no. You better leave that to me.
Rex?
I know it was hard for you today...
watching all that happening.
But surely it's notworth all this misery.
Please, dear, not onsuch a beautiful night.
You put these ideas into his head!
Two-facedtraitorous wret-
Get down!
Down, Rex. Fly!
A dark cloud haddescended on the valley.
And the pig felt that thetroubles were all his fault.
But he was certain that he knewhow to put things right again.
Oh, uh, e- excuse me, sir.
But I-I-I thinkall this trouble-
Well, it's not distemper.Can't be rabies.
Must be the hormones.
- What about Hoggett's notion, the dog jealous of the wee pig?- I don't see that myself.
No. So what should we do?
You can keep him locked up or...snip, snip. I can do it Tuesday.
No.
Or Wednesday.
Hoggett doesn't want the dogoperated on. He's a breeding dog.
I can sedate him, of course,
but he'll be useless as a working dog.
- I'll give you pillsto put in his food.
Good dog.
The Sheep Pig.
A pig doing the work of a sheepdog?
With Rex out of action and Fly injured fromthe fight, Farmer Hoggett had no choice.
Maa! Maa! The boss hasto give you some medicine.
Oh, dear, I thought so!It's horrible stuff, that.
- I know, but it's for the best.- Young'un, if you say so.
Shoo! Shoo!
When the thought first came to him,
Farmer Hoggett dismissedit as mere whimsy.
But, like most of his harebrainedideas, it wouldn't go away.
- What are they doing?- It's a sheepdog trial.
So it's like acompetition for sheepdogs?
And their bosses. It'slike an obstacle course.
How do they decide who wins?
It's time and mistakes. You getpoints for how quick you are.
And they take pointsoff for every mistake.
Every time a sheep goes the wrong way,that's a mistake and you lose points.
- Looks like fun!- For a sheepdog, there's no prouder moment.
- Rex and Iused to- - Hmm?
Never mind.
Oh.
Was Rex a champion?
He had the makings of the greatest championthere ever was, but it wasn't to be.
- What happened?- A while back when Rex was in his prime,
the winter rains brought agreat flood to the valley.
Rex and the boss got most ofthe flock onto the high ground.
Then Rex went back tolook for the strays.
He found them. They'd beenstranded by the rising water.
He tried to herd them across tosafety, but they wouldn't budge.
Too afraid and too stupidto save their own skins.
It was freezing cold andthe water kept rising.
Rex stayed with themright through the night.
By morning, the sheep were drowned.
- And when they found Rex, he was barely alive.- Oh, Mom!
Two weeks rest in front of thefire saw him back on his feet.
But his hearing wasnever the same again.
He'd never want anyone to know,but he's almost totally deaf.
- Is that why he's so, you know, angry?- That's not the half of it.
All this was barely a month beforethe Grand National Challenge.
He tried his best, but he couldn't hearthe boss's calls, and it slowed him up.
The cold truth is that, butfor the stupidity of sheep,
Rex would've been thechampion of champions.
Good dog.
That's it, all right. Good.
Here we go. All right.
Now, through here like this.
And then, big hookto the left. Big hook.
Big hook. Through this gate here.
It was at that time that Mrs. Hoggettbegan to worry about her husband.
But Farmer Hoggett knewthat little ideas...
that tickled and naggedand refused to go away...
should never be ignored...
for in them lie the seeds of destiny.
Close the gate likethat, and you're done.
A Tragic Day.
Mom. Mom! Can we start work early today?
Oh, dear, it's not even dawn yet.
You can go to work when therooster crows. Oh, go back to sleep.
Ahem.
Um, excuse me.
Hello, sir. Excuse me,but it's nearly dawn, and-
- What?- Sorry to disturb you.
It's nearly dawn, and I wondered if you'd mindcrowing just a few minutes early this morning.
- Get out of here!- But, well, see I-
- Get lost!- Oh, okay.
Whoa!
Now the pig understood why thesheep called all dogs wolves.
And he was filled witha deep and terrible rage.
Maa! Maa!
- Are you all right?- Hello, young'un.
Oh, Maa, can you get up?
I don't reckon.
It's over, Maa. Thewolves have gone far away.
I'll get the boss uphere to look after you.
- You'll be all right.You'll be all right!
Oh, Maa! Maa!
Maa! Maa!
Maa!
Home, Pig.
Fly knew that there was onlyone fate for any creature...
that took the life ofa sheep on Hoggett Farm.
But Fly could never believethat Babe was a sheep killer,
so she remained in the field to dosomething she'd never talk to the sheep.
Tell me. Who killed the old one?
- Wolf! - Wolf. Is that theonly words you half-wits know?
- Wolf!- Are you saying it was a dog?
- Where's Babe?- Was it wolf or Babe?
Wolf! Babe!
Farmer Hoggett was carryingsomething in the crook of one arm.
A kind of black, shiny tube.
Come, Pig.
The pig had a vague memorythat shiny tubes produced food,
and guessed that somequite unexpected surprise...
would come out of twosmall round mouths.
Babe! Wolf!
Quiet!
Fly decided to speak very slowly,
for it was a cold fact ofnature that sheep were stupid...
and no one would everpersuade her otherwise.
Please, please would you be...
so kind as to tell me what happened?
Quiet!
Please, tell me whathappened this morning.
The sheep spoke very slowly...
for it was a cold fact of naturethat wolves were ignorant...
and nothing wouldconvince them otherwise.
Babe came! He saved us!
- The wolves killed Maa.- But Babe drove the wolves away!
Thank you! Thank you!Thank you all very much!
Pleasure talkin' to ya.
Hooey! Hoggett! Hooey! Arthur!
Oh, there you are!Well, what do you think?
That was the police on the telephone.Said there are wild dogs about.
Apparently the Mitchellslost six lambs this morning.
What are you doing with that gun?
Oh, I- Nothing.
Pig of Destiny!
It's all very simple. Halfan hour at 350 degrees.
I've given you rabbitcasserole for Friday.
Now, for Duchess, it's liver inthe morning, heart for the evening.
Except Fridays, when it's steak inthe morning, and cooked liver at night.
Warm it up a bit but test it, because shebites into it before she knows what's what.
That'll be the bus.
- Oh, bye, bye.- Have a good time. Bye.
Hello, everyone!
Oh, dearie me, Valda.
I know I have to be atthe National Conference.
I am the Assistant General Secretaryof the Northeast Region after all,
but I do worry aboutleaving that man alone.
- Still acting a bit strange?- Just silly things.
Odd little things onlya wife would notice.
- Still, he can't get up to too much mischief in three days.- Of course not.
Go on.
Go on!
- Oh! Good evening.Shame about the weather.
Nasty cough!
It had been a long timesince Arthur Hoggett...
had had an animal in whoseabilities he had so much faith.
And with the National Grand ChallengeSheepdog Trials only two days away,
he wasn't going to let the factthat his animal was a pig deter him.
He had been worried, forhe was a truthful man,
that the heading mightsay "Name of dog. "
And then whatever he put would be a lie.
But as it happened, luck, forthe moment, was running with him.
It's all right, really!
I'm just, well- Bless you.
Whoa, whoa! Uh, easy, whoa! Ah.
Oh, no.
- So, ah... what's happening?- Oh, no.
Shh. Easy, easy.
- Good pig. Good pig.- Huh? Huh?
Hold still. Hold still.
Huh?
There are many perfectlynice cats in the world.
But every barrel has its bad apples.
And it is well to heed the old adage,
"Beware the bad cat bearing a grudge. "
- How are you feeling?- A bit tired.
You'll need a good sleep to putyou in top condition tomorrow.
Don't stay up too late. Good night.
Good night, Mom.
Oh, do forgive me forscratching you, dear.
I got a bit carriedaway. It's a cat thing.
Oh. Well-But oh-
Feeling good about tomorrow, are you?
Mm-hmm. It should beall right, I think.
I probably shouldn't say this,but I'm not sure if you realize...
how much the other animals are laughingat you for this sheepdog business.
Why would they do that?
Well, they say that you've forgottenthat you're a pig. Isn't that silly?
They even say that youdon't know what pigs are for.
What do you mean?
- You know... why pigs are here.- Why are any of us here?
Well, the cow's here to be milked.
The dogs are here to help theboss's husband with the sheep.
And I'm here to be beautifuland affectionate to the boss.
Yes?
The fact is that pigsdon't have a purpose.
Just like ducks don't have a purpose.
- I don't- - All right, foryou own sake, I'll be blunt.
Why do the bosses keepducks? To eat them.
So why do the bosses keep a pig?
The fact is that animals that don't seemto have a purpose really do have a purpose.
The bosses have to eat. It's probablythe most noble purpose of all...
when you come to think about it.
They eat pigs?
Pork, they call it. Or bacon.
They only call thempigs when they're alive.
But, uh, I'm a sheep pig!
The boss's husband's justplaying a little game with you.
Believe me, sooner orlater, every pig gets eaten.
That's the way the world works.
Oh! I haven't upset you, have I?
- Mom?- Mm-hmm.
- Mom!- Good heavens!
What on earth are youdoing out in the rain?
You should be looking after yourselfwith such a big day ahead of you.
- Are pigs for eatin'?- Who told you that?
The cat told me. Pigs don't havea purpose except to be eaten.
Is it true?
It's true. For many pigs, it's true.
So my mother, my father,my brothers and my sisters,
- all- -Probably, dear.
- Do you want to talk about it?- No, it's all right.
I understand. I'll be all right.
Even... the boss?
Yes, dear.
Ooh! Ooo!
Babe?
Babe!
Babe's run away.
Rex?
Please?
Call the boss.
He's over here.
Hold on, Pig. You'll be home soon.
He's got a cold, but thatdoesn't explain a pig not eating.
He's got me stonkered, Arthur.But I can tell you this.
If you don't get fluids intohim soon, you're gonna lose him.
C'mon, son. Pull yourself together.
The boss needs you.
Here we go.
Come on, Pig. Ah, come on.
There's my boy.
Come on, then. Come on.
Listen, Arthur, I'lltell you what we can do.
You're listed third, but wecan put you last in the program.
However, you must be here by 3:30;otherwise you'll be disqualified.
All right.
And welcome back to the NationalGrand Challenge Sheepdog Trials...
coming today from the Kingsmith ShowGround in the heart of sheep country.
The weather's been patchy,
but we've already seen somewonderful work by these talented dogs.
Stay there.
Excuse me, sheep.
Hello! Hello! Good morning to you all!
I've never met a sheep withsuch a strong, dark face.
Are they feeding you well?
Babe, I'll try.
All right, blockheads!Pay attention over here!
Now, you pay attention towhat this pig has to say...
or I'll come in thereand rip you to shreds!
Hadn't thought of this. Keep talkingto them. I'll see what I can do.
- Doesn't it look a picture? Our show ground on the telly!- Apart from the weather.
- Look! There's your Bert!- Bert Ford and Sweep doing very well.
- Sweep's having a little trouble with this gate, Clive.- A lot of trouble actually.
- That's going to set Bert back.- Don't worry, Valda. Just a little slipup.
Look, he's doing much better now.
Too many loose sheep. And Sweep'susually such a reliable dog.
Hey, whoa. Stop!
If those sheep won't talk to Babe, theboss is going to look like an idiot.
- I don't know what to do.- There is one thing.
I gotta go! I'll try to be back in time.
Ahem. It must've beenterrible weather for you,
- out in the field with allthis rain we've been having.
Hey, that dog's in a hurry.
Come on, Nick, I got abeer and a TV waiting.
The last entry isPig. Owner, A. Hoggett.
- Was that "Hoggett"?- I think it was!
- Huh?- He said Hoggett. It was clear as a bell.
Must be another Hoggett. We only havethe two dogs, and they certainly...
aren't-
Wolf! Wolf!
Shut up, you morons!
The little pig's in trouble.
What trouble has come to our Babe, wolf?
The sheep at the trials won'ttalk to the little fellow.
They won't listen. Hedoesn't know what to do.
Don't know what we could do to help.
- It's not right to give help to a wolf.- You wait here, wolf.
You'll have to speak up. I'ma... little hard of hearing.
I asked you to wait here, wolf.
Do what you're told byan old sheep for a change.
We'll see what we can do for you.
Work completed. Restore power.
Very frustrating tobe sitting up here...
wondering what's causing the delay.
We have someone on theirway to the judges' rooms now.
We'll tell you what's causing theproblem as soon as we find out.
- Perhaps it's a drug test?- Yeah, it could be.
- I've never heard of a drugtest at a sheepdog contest before.
We've got somethin' here thatmight be of use to our pig.
Password! Password!
Before we gives you anythin',
- you'll be makin' us a solemn promise.- Yes?
- Treat us civil! - Yes!You gotta treat us nice-like.
I'll try.
- No bitin'!- That's right. Wolf must avoid bitin' us sheep...
- at all costs!- All right! I'll try that too.
It's preposterous! We'd be the laughingstockof every sheepdog organization...
- in every civilized countryin the world! - There's no rule-
We'll see about that when the adjudicationcommittee have finished their meeting.
What will we have next year, alaughing hyena doing show jumping?
But the most important ofall, you must promise...
never ever to let thispassword we be about to give...
to be used against any sheep anywhere.
I promise you that. I'll makesure the pig knows it too.
- We have the promise!- 'Tis for Babe.
Maa would have wanted it.
Baa, ram, ewe.
To your breed, yourfleece, your clan be true.
Sheep be true. Baa, ram, ewe.
Is that it? Is that the password?
Mr. Hoggett, the judges wouldlike me to convey to you...
their disappointment thata man such as yourself,
with a long and honorable association withthe work of National Sheepdog Association,
should see fit to flout...
the historic conventions whichhave long ruled our sport.
However we find thereis no rule, as such,
which would prevent your...animal... being entered.
The committee has ruledthat if you wish to proceed,
there is nothing we can do to stop you.
What do you wish to do?
There appears to be somemovement down there now.
I expect if there areno further problems,
we shall see Hoggett and his dog Pig.
- Unusual name. Strange name, isn't it?- Pig.
Anyone for a game of cards?
Oh, good grief! Look!
He's a fool!
Entry number 23, Mr.A. Hoggett with Pig.
This is just too crazy to believe.
And if that isn't enough. Wehave a stray dog on the field.
They trying to round him up?
The dog's gonna give a fewtips on how to be a sheep pig.
Well, it's up to him now.
Away to me, Pig.
Get off!
Baa, ram, ewe. Baa, ram, ewe!
To your breed, yourfleece, your clan be true.
Sheep be true. Baa, ram, ewe.
What... what did you say?
Get yourself a dog, Hoggett.
There, there, Esme. It'snot the end of the world.
Is he just going to standthere until his time runs out?
Or could this be some sort of protest?
Maybe we should line up aninterview with the sheep pig?
Or the sheep pig's trainer.
He's a lively sort of fellowby the looks of things.
Good heavens!
- Hey!- Shh.
It's Babe!
I-I-
- It,uh- - Hmm.
Oh, beautifully done! I can't tellyou how grateful I am to y'all.
Now, for one last favor.
If the three ladies with collarswould kindly walk out of the ring,
I'd be very much obliged.
And so it was that inall the celebration,
in all the hubbub ofnoise and excitement,
there were two figures whostood silent and still...
side by side.
The pig did it! The perfect score!
Yippee! Yippee!
And though every single human in thestands or in the commentary boxes...
was at a complete loss for words,
the man, who in his life had utteredfewer words than any of them...
knew exactly what to say.
That'll do, Pig.
That'll do.
And a-one and a-twoand a-three. Hit it.