October is inventory time,
so right now, Statler Toyota
is making the best deals of the year
on all 1985-model Toyotas.
You won't find a better car
at a better price with betterservice anywhere in Hill Valley.
That's Statler Toyotain downtown Hill Valley.
The Senate isexpected to vote on this today.
In other news, officials at thePacific Nuclear research facility
have denied the rumor thata case of missing plutonium
was in fact stolen fromtheir vault two weeks ago.
A Libyan terrorist grouphad claimed responsibility
for the alleged theft.
However, officials now attribute
the discrepancy to asimple clerical error.
The FBI, which is investigatingthe matter, had no comment.
Hey, Doc?
Doc?
Hello! Anybody home?
Einstein, come here, boy.
What's going on? Oh, God.
Oh, Jesus!
That is disgusting.Where the hell is he?
Whoa!
Rock 'n' roll.
Yo. DOC: Marty, is that you?
Hey. Hey, Doc. Where are you?
Thank God I've found you.
Listen, can you meet me atTwin Pines Mall tonight at 1:15?
I made a major breakthrough,and I'll need your assistance.
Wait a minute. 1:15 in the morning?
Yeah.
Doc, what's going on?
Where you been all week? Working.
Where's Einstein? Is he with you?
Yeah, he's right here.
You know, Doc, you leftyour equipment on all week.
My equipment. That reminds me, Marty.
You better not hook up to the amplifier.
There's a slightpossibility of overload.
Yeah. I'll keep that in mind.
Good. I'll see youtonight. Don't forget now.
1:15 a.m., Twin Pines Mall.
Right.
Are those my clocks I hear?
Yeah, it's 8:00.
Perfect! My experiment worked!
They're all exactly 25 minutes slow!
Wait a minute. Wait a minute, Doc.
Are you telling me that it's 8:25?
Precisely.
Damn! I'm late for school.
Jennifer. Marty, don't go this way.
Strickland's looking for you.
If you get caught, it'llbe four tardies in a row.
All right, come on. I think we're safe.
You know, this time it wasn't my fault.
The doc set all hisclocks 25 minutes slow.
Doc?
Am I to understand you're still hangingaround with Dr. Emmett Brown, McFly?
Tardy slip for you, Miss Parker.
And one for you, McFly. Ibelieve that makes four in a row.
Let me give you a nickel'sworth of free advice, young man.
This so-called Dr. Brown isdangerous. He's a real nutcase.
You hang around with him, you'regonna end up in big trouble.
Ooh. Yes, sir.
You got a real attitudeproblem, McFly. You're a slacker.
You remind me of yourfather when he went here.
He was a slacker, too.
Can I go now, Mr. Strickland?
I noticed your band is on the roster
for the dance auditionsafter school today.
Why even bother, McFly?You don't have a chance.
You're too much like your old man.
No McFly ever amounted to anything
in the history of Hill Valley.
Yeah, well, history is gonna change.
Next, please.
Okay, guys, let's rock 'n roll.
All right.
We're the... We're the Pinheads.
One, two, three.
Okay, that's enough. Thank you, fellas.
Hold it, fellas.
I'm afraid you're just too darn loud.
Next, please.
Bring up the next group, please.
Re-electMayor "Goldie" Wilson.
Progress is his middle name.
"Too loud." I can't believe it.
I'm never gonna get a chanceto play in front of anybody.
Marty, one rejectionisn't the end of the world.
I just don't thinkI'm cut out for music.
But you're good, Marty.You're really good,
and this auditiontape of yours is great.
You've gotta send it into the record company.
It's like Doc's alwayssaying. Yeah, I know. I know.
"If you put your mind to it,
"you can accomplish anything."
That's good advice, Marty.
All right, okay, Jennifer.
What if I send in the tapeand they don't like it?
What if they say I'm no good?
What if they say, "Get out ofhere, kid. You got no future"?
I mean, I just don't think Ican take that kind of rejection.
Jesus, I'm starting tosound like my old man.
Come on. He's not thatbad. Save the clock tower.
At least he's letting youborrow the car tomorrow night.
Check out that 4x4.
That is hot.
Okay. Back her up.
Someday, Jennifer. Someday.
Wouldn't it be great to takethat truck up to the lake?
Throw a couple ofsleeping bags in the back.
Lie out underneath the stars.
Stop it. What?
Does your mom know?About tomorrow night?
No, get out of town.
My mom thinks I'm goingcamping with the guys.
Jennifer, my mother would freak out
if she knew I wasgoing up there with you,
and I'd get the standard lecture about
how she never did that kindof stuff when she was a kid.
I mean, look, I thinkthe woman was born a nun.
She's just trying tokeep you respectable.
Well, she's not doing a very good job.
Terrible.
Save the clock tower.Save the clock tower.
Mayor Wilson is sponsoring aninitiative to replace that clock.
Thirty years ago, lightningstruck that clock tower
and the clock hasn't run since.
We at the Hill ValleyPreservation Society
think it should be preservedexactly the way it is
as part of our history and heritage.
There you go, lady. There's a quarter.
Thank you.
Don't forget to take a flyer.
Right.
Save the clock tower!
Where were we?
Right about here.
Jennifer!
It's my dad. I've got to go. Right.
I'll call you tonight.
I'll be at my grandma's.
Here, let me give you the number.
Bye.
Bravo,Tango, Delta 6-2-9.
Tow for impoundment.Any unit, please respond.
Perfect. Just perfect.
I can't believe you'd loan me your car
without telling me it had a blind spot.
Blind spot? I could've been killed.
Now, Biff, now, I never noticed
that the car had any blind spotbefore when I would drive it.
Hi, Son.
What, are youblind, McFly? It's there.
How else do you explainthat wreck out there?
Biff, can I assume
that your insurance isgoing to pay for the damage?
My insurance? It's your car.
Your insurance should pay for it.
I wanna know who'sgoing to pay for this?
I spilled beer all over itwhen the car smashed into me.
Who's gonna pay my cleaning bill?
Ah...
And where's my reports?
Well, I haven't finished those up yet,
but I figured sincethey weren't due till...
Hello? Hello? Anybody home? Huh?
Think, McFly. Think! All right.
I got to have time to get them retyped.
Do you realize what would happen
if I hand in my reportsin your handwriting?
I'll get fired.
You wouldn't want thatto happen, would you?
Would you? Of course not, Biff.
Now, I wouldn't want that to happen.
Now, look. I'll finishthose reports on up tonight,
and I'll run them on overfirst thing tomorrow, all right?
Not too early. I sleep in Saturday.
McFly, your shoe's untied.
Oh.
Don't be so gullible, McFly.
Got the place fixedup nice, though, McFly.
I have your car towedall the way to your house
and all you got for me is lite beer?
What are you looking at, butthead?
Say hi to your mom for me.
I know what you're going to say, Son,
and you're right. You're right.
But Biff just happensto be my supervisor,
And I'm afraid I'm just notvery good at confrontations.
But the car, Dad.
I mean, he wrecked it. He totaled it.
I needed that car tomorrow night, Dad.
Do you have any idea howimportant this was to me?
Do you have any clue?
I know, and all I can say is, I'm...
I'm sorry.
Believe me, Marty, you're better off
without having to worryabout all the aggravation
and headaches of playing at that dance.
He's absolutely right, Marty.
The last thing you need is headaches.
Kids, we're going to have toeat this cake by ourselves.
Your Uncle Joey didn'tmake parole again.
I think it would be nice ifyou all dropped him a line.
Uncle "Jailbird" Joey?
He's your brother, Mom.
Yeah. I think it's a majorembarrassment, having an uncle in prison.
We all make mistakes in life, children.
God damn it. I'm late.
David, watch your mouth!
You come here and kiss yourmother before you go. Come here.
Come on, Mom. Make itfast. I'll miss my bus.
See you later, Pop.
Time to change that oil.
Hey, Marty. I'm notyour answering service.
While you were outsidepouting over the car,
Jennifer Parker called you twice.
I don't like her, Marty.
Any girl who calls up a boyis just asking for trouble.
Oh, Mother, there's nothingwrong with calling a boy.
I think it's terrible.Girls chasing boys.
When I was your age, I neverchased a boy or called a boy
or sat in a parked car with a boy.
Then how am I supposedto ever meet anybody?
Well, it'll just happen.
Like the way I met your father.
That was so stupid. Grandpahit him with the car.
It was meant to be.
Anyway, if Grandpa hadn't hit him,
then none of you would have been born.
Yeah, well.
I still don't understandwhat Dad was doing
in the middle of the street.
What was it, George? Bird-watching?
What, Lorraine? What?
Anyway, your Grandpahit him with the car
and brought him into the house.
He seemed so helpless,
like a little lost puppy, andmy heart just went out to him.
Yeah, Mom, we know. You'vetold us this story a million times.
You felt sorry for him,
so you decided to go with him
to the Fish Under the Sea dance.
No. It was the EnchantmentUnder the Sea dance.
Our first date. I'll never forget it.
It was the night of that terriblethunderstorm, remember, George?
Your father kissed me for the veryfirst time on that dance floor.
It was then that I realized
that I was going to spendthe rest of my life with him.
Hello.
Marty, you didn'tfall asleep, did you?
Doc.
No. No, don't be silly.
Listen, this is very important.I forgot my video camera.
Can you stop by my place and pickit up on your way to the mall?
Yeah. I'm on my way.
Einstein! Hey, Einstein,where's the doc, boy? Huh?
Doc!
Marty! You made it!
Yeah.
Welcome to my latestexperiment. This is the big one,
the one I've beenwaiting for all my life.
Well, it's a DeLorean...
Bear with me, Marty. All yourquestions will be answered.
Roll tape and we'll proceed.
Doc,
is that a DEVO suit?
Never mind that now.
Not now.
All right. I'm ready.
Good evening. I'm Dr. Emmett Brown.
I'm standing on the parkinglot at Twin Pines Mall.
It's Saturday morning,October 26, 1985, 1:18 a.m.,
and this is temporalexperiment number one.
Come on, Einie. Hey,hey, boy, get in there.
That a boy! In you go. Sit down.
Put your seat belt on. That's it.
Whoa, whoa. Whoa.
Okay.
Please note that Einstein's clock
is in precise synchronizationwith my control watch.
Got it? Right. Check, Doc.
Good.
Have a good trip,Einstein. Watch your head.
You got that thing hooked up to the car?
Watch this.
Yeah. Okay. Got it.
Jesus!
Not me! The car! The car!
If my calculations are correct,
when this baby hits 88 miles per hour
you're going to see some serious shit.
Watch this. Watch this.
What did I tell you?
88 miles per hour!
The temporal displacement occurred
exactly 1:20 a.m. And zero seconds!
Jesus Christ!
Jesus Christ, Doc! Youdisintegrated Einstein!
Calm down, Marty. I didn'tdisintegrate anything.
The molecular structure of both Einsteinand the car are completely intact.
Then where the hell are they?
The appropriate question is,
"When the hell are they?"
You see, Einstein has just becomethe world's first time traveler.
I sent him into the future.
One minute into the future, to be exact.
At precisely 1:21 a.m. And zero seconds,
we shall catch up withhim and the time machine.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute, Doc.
Are you telling me thatyou built a time machine
out of a DeLorean?
The way I see it,
if you're going to builda time machine into a car,
why not do it with some style?
Besides, the stainless-steelconstruction made the flux dispersal...
Look out!
What? Is it hot?
It's cold. Damn cold.
Einstein, you little devil!
Einstein's clock is exactly one minute
behind mine and still ticking!
He's all right. He's fine.
And he's completely unawarethat anything happened.
As far as he's concerned,the trip was instantaneous.
That's why his watch isexactly one minute behind mine.
He skipped over that minute
to instantly arriveat this moment in time.
Come here. I'll show you how it works.
All right.
First, you turn the time circuits on.
This readout tellsyou where you're going.
This one tells you where you are.
This one tells you where you were.
You input your destinationtime on this keypad.
Say you want to see the signing
of the Declaration of Independence.
Or witness the birth of Christ.
Here's a red-letter datein the history of science.
November 5th, 1955.
Yes, of course. November 5th, 1955.
What? I don't get it. What happened?
That was the day I invented timetravel. I remember it vividly.
I was standing on the edgeof my toilet, hanging a clock.
The porcelain was wet. I slipped,
hit my head on the edge of the sink,
and when I came to, I had a revelation,
a vision, a picture in myhead, a picture of this.
This is what makes time travelpossible. The flux capacitor.
Flux capacitor?
It's taken me almost 30 yearsand my entire family fortune
to realize the vision of that day.
My God, has it been that long?
Things have certainlychanged around here.
I remember when this was all farmland
as far as the eye could see.
Old man Peabody owned all of this.
He had this crazy ideaabout breeding pine trees.
This is heavy-duty, Doc. This is great.
Does it run on regularunleaded gasoline?
Unfortunately, no. It requires something
with a little more kick. Plutonium.
Plutonium. Wait a minute.
Are you telling me thatthis sucker is nuclear?
Hey, hey, hey! Keeprolling. Keep rolling there.
No, no, no, this sucker's electrical,
but I need a nuclear reaction
to generate the 1.21 gigawattsof electricity I need.
Doc, you don't just walk intoa store and buy plutonium.
Did you rip that off?
Of course. From a groupof Libyan nationalists.
They wanted me to build them a bomb,
so I took their plutonium and, inturn, gave them a shoddy bomb casing
full of used pinball machine parts.
Come on. Let's get youa radiation suit. Jesus!
We must prepare to reload.
It's safe now. Everything's lead-lined.
Don't you lose those tapes now.
I need that as a record.
Let's put this back here. There we go.
I almost forgot my luggage.
Who knows if they've gotcotton underwear in the future?
I'm allergic to all synthetics.
The future?
That's where you're going?
That's right, 25 years into the future.
I've always dreamed of seeing thefuture, looking beyond my years,
seeing the progress of mankind.
Why not?
I'll also be able to see whowins the next 25 World Series.
Doc.
Huh?
Look me up when you get there.
Indeed, I will. Roll 'em.
I, Dr. Emmett Brown,
am about to embark onan historic journey.
What am I thinking of?
I almost forgot tobring extra plutonium.
How did I ever expect to getback? One pellet, one trip.
I must be out of my mind.
What is it, Einie?
Oh, my God.
They found me. I don'tknow how, but they found me.
Run for it, Marty!
Who? Who?
Who do you think? The Libyans!
Holy shit!
I'll draw their fire!
Doc, wait!
No!
You bastard!
Go! Damn Soviet gun.
Go!
Come on! Move, damn it!
Jesus!
Holy shit!
Let's see if you bastards can do 90.
What is it? What is it, Pa?
Looks like an airplane without wings.
That ain't no airplane. Look.
Children!
Listen... Whoa.
Hello?
Excuse me.
Sorry about your barn.
It's already mutatedinto human form! Shoot it!
Take that, you mutated son of a bitch!
Get away!
Hold it.
Shoot it, Pa!
My pine! Why you...
You space bastard! You killed our pine!
All right. All right. Okay, McFly.
Get a grip on yourself.It's all a dream.
It's just a very intense dream.
Listen, you got to help me.
Don't stop, Wilbur! Don't!
It can't be.
This is nuts.
Come on.
Perfect.
Remember, fellowcitizens, the future is in your hands.
If you believe in progress,re-elect Mayor Red Thomas.
Progress is his middle name.
Mayor Red Thomas' progress platform
means more jobs, better education,
bigger civic improvementsand lower taxes.
On election day, cast yourvote for a proven leader.
Re-elect Mayor Red Thomas.
This has got to be a dream.
Hey, kid. What'd you do? Jump ship?
What?
What's with the life preserver?
I just want to use the phone.
Yeah, it's in the back.
Brown.
Great. You're alive.
Come on.
Do you know where 1640 Riverside...
Are you going to order something, kid?
Yeah. Give me a Tab.
Tab? I can't give you a tabunless you order something.
Right. Give me a Pepsi Free.
You want a Pepsi, pal,you're going to pay for it.
Just give me somethingwithout any sugar in it, okay?
Something without sugar.
Hey, McFly.
What do you think you're doing?
Biff.
I'm talking to you,McFly, you Irish bug!
Hey, Biff. Hey, guys. How are you doing?
You got my homework finished, McFly?
Well, actually, I figured sinceit wasn't due till Monday...
Hello? Hello? Anybody home?
Think, McFly. Think! Okay.
I got to have time to recopy it.
You realize what would happen
if I hand in my homeworkin your handwriting?
I'll get kicked out of school.
You wouldn't want thatto happen, would you?
Would you?
Now, of course not, Biff.
No. I wouldn't want that to happen.
What are you looking at, butthead?
Biff, get a load of thisguy's life preserver.
Dork thinks he's going to drown.
How about my homework, McFly?
Okay, Biff. Well, I'llfinish that on up tonight
and then I'll bring it overfirst thing tomorrow morning.
Not too early. I sleep in Sundays.
Oh, McFly, your shoe's untied!
Don't be so gullible, McFly. Okay.
I don't want to see you in here again.
Okay. All right. Bye-bye.
What?
You're George McFly.
Yeah. Who are you?
Say! Why do you let those boys
push you around like that for?
Well, they're bigger than me.
Stand tall, boy. Havesome respect for yourself.
Don't you know, if you letpeople walk over you now,
they'll be walking over youfor the rest of your life.
Look at me. You think I'm gonna
spend the rest of mylife in this slop house?
Watch it, Goldie. No, sir!
I'm gonna make something of myself.
I'm going to night school,
and one day, I'm going to be somebody.
That's right. He's going to be mayor.
Yeah, I'm...
Mayor!
Now that's a good idea!I could run for mayor.
A colored mayor. That'll be the day.
You wait and see, Mr.Caruthers. I will be mayor.
I'll be the most powerfulman in Hill Valley,
and I'm going to clean up this town.
Good. You can startby sweeping the floor.
Mayor Goldie Wilson. Ilike the sound of that.
Hey, Dad! George! Hey, you on the bike!
He's a peeping Tom.
Dad!
Hey, wait a minute. Waita minute. Who are you?
Stella! Another one of these damn kids
jumped in front of my car!
Come on out here! Helpme take him in the house!
Mom? That you?
There, there, now. Just relax.
You've been asleep foralmost nine hours now.
I had a horrible nightmare.
I dreamed that I went backin time. It was terrible.
Well,
you're safe and soundnow, back in good old 1955.
1955?
You're my... You're my...
My name is Lorraine.
Lorraine Baines.
Yeah.
But you're... You're so...
You're so thin!
Just relax, Calvin. You gota big bruise on your head.
Where are my pants?
Over there, on my hope chest.
I've never seen purpleunderwear before, Calvin.
Calvin? Why do youkeep calling me Calvin?
Well, that is your name,isn't it? Calvin Klein?
It's written all over your underwear.
Oh, I guess they call you Cal, huh?
No, actually, people call me Marty.
Oh.
Pleased to meet you, Calvin.
Marty.
Klein.
Do you mind if I sit here?
No. Fine.
No. Good. Fine. Good.
That's a big bruise you have there.
Lorraine, are you up there?
Oh, my God! It's my mother!
Quick! Put your pants back on!
So, tell me, Marty,how long have you been in port?
Excuse me?
I guessed you're a sailor.
That's why you wear that life preserver.
Coast Guard.
Sam, here's the young man
you hit with your car out there.
He's all right. Thank God.
What were you doing in the middleof the street, a kid your age?
Don't pay attention to him.He's in one of his moods.
Sam, you quit fiddling with that thing.
Come in here to dinner.
Now, let's see. Youalready know Lorraine.
This is Milton, thisis Sally, that's Toby,
and over there in theplaypen is little baby Joey.
So, you're my uncle Joey.
Better get used to these bars, kid.
Yes. Joey just lovesbeing in his playpen.
He cries whenever we take him out,
so we just leave himin there all the time.
Well, Marty, I hope you like meatloaf.
Listen, I really ought to...
Sit here, Marty.
Sam, stop fiddling with that thing
and come in here and eat your dinner.
Look at it roll.
Now we can watch JackieGleason while we eat.
It's our first television set.
Dad just picked it up today.
Do you have a television?
Well, yeah. You knowwe have two of them.
Wow! You must be rich.
Oh, honey, he's teasing you.
Nobody has two television sets.
Hey. Hey, I've seen this one.
I've seen this one! This is a classic.
This is where Ralph dressesup as a man from space.
What do you mean, you'veseen this? It's brand-new.
Yeah, well, I saw it on a rerun.
What's a rerun?
You'll find out.
You know, Marty, you look sofamiliar to me. Do I know your mother?
Yeah, I think maybe you do.
Oh, then Iwant to give her a call.
I don't want her to worry about you.
You can't.
That is, nobody's home.
Oh.
Yet.
Listen, do you knowwhere Riverside Drive is?
It's on the other end of town.
A block past Maple. East end of town.
Wait a minute, a block past Maple.
That's John F. Kennedy Drive.
Who the hell is John F. Kennedy?
Mother?
With Marty's parents out of town,
don't you think heought to spend the night?
I mean, after all, Dad almostkilled him with the car.
That's true, Marty.
I think maybe youshould spend the night.
I think you're our responsibility.
Gee, I don't know.
And he can sleep in my room.
I gotta go! I gotta go!
Thanks very much. It was wonderful.
You were all great. Seeyou all later. Much later.
He's a very strange young man.
He's an idiot.
Comes from upbringing. Hisparents are probably idiots, too.
Lorraine, you ever have a kid
who acts that way, I'll disown you.
Doc?
Don't say a word.
I don't wanna know your name.
I don't want to know anything about you.
Listen, Doc... Quiet!
Doc, it's me, Marty.Don't tell me anything.
Doc, you got to help... Quiet. Quiet.
I'm going to read your thoughts.
Let's see now. You've comehere from a great distance?
Yeah. Exactly.
Don't tell me!
You want me to buy a subscription
to the Saturday Evening Post.
No.
Not a word. Not a word now!
Quiet.
Donations. You wantme to make a donation
to the Coast Guard Youth Auxiliary.
Doc.
I'm from the future.
I came here in a timemachine that you invented.
Now, I need your help toget back to the year 1985.
My God.
Do you know what this means?
It means that this damnthing doesn't work at all!
Doc, you got to helpme. You are the only one
who knows how your time machine works.
Time machine? I haven'tinvented any time machine.
Okay. All right, I'll prove it to you.
Look at my driver'slicense. Expires 1987.
Look at my birthday,for crying out loud!
I haven't even been born yet.
And look at this picture.
It's my brother, my sister and me.
Look at her sweatshirt,Doc. "Class of 1984"?
Pretty mediocre photographic fakery.
They cut off your brother's hair.
I'm telling the truth,Doc. You got to believe me.
Then tell me, future boy,
Who's President of theUnited States in 1985?
Ronald Reagan.
Ronald Reagan? The actor?
Then who's vice president? Jerry Lewis?
I suppose Jane Wyman is the First Lady.
Whoa. Wait, Doc!
And Jack Benny issecretary of the treasury.
Doc, you gotta listen to me.
I've had enough practicaljokes for one evening.
Good night, future boy!
No, wait, Doc. Doc.
The bruise on your head,I know how that happened.
You told me the whole story.
You were standing on your toilet
and you were hanging a clock,
and you fell and you hityour head on the sink.
That's when you came up withthe idea for the flux capacitor,
which is what makestime travel possible.
There's something wrong withthe starter, so I hid it here.
After I fell off my toilet, I drew this.
The flux capacitor.
It works!
I finally invent something that works!
You bet your ass it works.
Somehow we've got to sneakthis back to my laboratory.
We've got to get you home!
Okay, Doc, this is it.
Never mind that. Never mind that now.
Why, that's me! Lookat me! I'm an old man.
Good evening. I'm Dr. Emmett Brown.
I'm standing on the parkinglot at Twin Pines Mall.
Thank God, I've still got my hair.
What's on Earth isthis thing I'm wearing?
This is a radiation suit.
Radiation suit?
Of course. 'Cause of all thefallout from the atomic wars.
This is truly amazing.
A portable television studio.
No wonder your presidenthas to be an actor.
He's gotta look good on television.
Whoa. This is it. This isthe part coming up, Doc.
No, no, no, this sucker's electrical,
but I need a nuclear reaction
to generate the 1.21 gigawatts...
What did I just say?
This sucker's electrical,
but I need a nuclear reaction
to generate the 1.21 gigawatts...
1.21 gigawatts!
1.21 gigawatts.
Great Scott!
What the hell is a gigawatt?
How could I have been socareless? 1.21 gigawatts!
Tom, how am I going togenerate that kind of power?
It can't be done, can it?
Doc, look. All we needis a little plutonium.
I'm sure that in 1985,
plutonium is availablein every corner drugstore,
but in 1955, it's alittle hard to come by.
Marty, I'm sorry, but I'mafraid you're stuck here.
Whoa, whoa.
Doc, stuck here? I can't bestuck here. I got a life in 1985.
I got a girl.
Is she pretty?
Doc, she's beautiful.She's crazy about me.
Look at this. Look what she wrotehere, Doc. I mean, that says it all.
Doc, you're my only hope.
Marty, I'm sorry, but the onlypower source capable of generating
1.21 gigawatts of electricityis a bolt of lightning.
What did you say?
A bolt of lightning.
Unfortunately, you never know
when or where it's ever going to strike.
We do now.
This is it! This is the answer.
It says here that a bolt of lightning
is going to strike the clock tower
at precisely 10:04 p.m.Next Saturday night!
If we could somehowharness this lightning,
channel it into the flux capacitor,
it just might work.
Next Saturday night, we'resending you back to the future!
Okay, all right. Saturday'sgood. Saturday's good.
I can spend a week in 1955.
I can hang out. You can show me around.
Marty, that is completelyout of the question.
You must not leave this house.
You must not see anybodyor talk to anybody.
Anything you do can have seriousrepercussions on future events.
Do you understand?
Yeah. Sure. Okay.
Marty,
have you interacted withanybody else today, besides me?
Yeah, well, I might've sortof bumped into my parents.
Great Scott!
Let me see that photographagain of your brother.
Just as I thought. This provesmy theory. Look at your brother.
His head's gone.It's like it's been erased.
Erased from existence.
Whoa.
They really cleaned thisplace up. Looks brand-new.
Now remember.
According to my theory, you interfered
with your parents' first meeting.
If they don't meet,they won't fall in love,
they won't get marriedand they won't have kids.
That's why your older brother's
disappearing from that photograph.
Your sister will follow, andunless you repair the damage,
you'll be next.
Sounds pretty heavy.Weight has nothing to do with it.
Which one's your pop?
That's him.
Okay. Okay, you guys.
Very funny. You guysare being real mature.
Maybe you were adopted.
Okay, real mature, guys.
Okay, pick up my books.
McFly.
That's Strickland.
Jesus, didn't that guy ever have hair?
Shape up, man. You're a slacker.
Do you want to be a slackerfor the rest of your life?
No.
What did your motherever see in that kid?
I don't know, Doc.
I guess she felt sorry for him
'cause her dad hit him with the car.
Hit me with the car.
That's the Florence Nightingale effect.
It happens in hospitals when nursesfall in love with their patients.
Go to it, kid.
Hey, George, buddy.
I have been looking all over for you.
You remember me, the guy whosaved your life the other day?
Oh.
Yeah. Good.
There's somebody I'd like you to meet.
Lorraine?
Calvin!
I'd like you to meet mygood friend George McFly.
Hi. It's really a pleasure to meet you.
How's your head?
Good. Fine.
Oh. I've been so worried about you
ever since you ran off the other night.
Are you okay? Yeah.
I'm sorry. I have to go.
Come on!
Isn't he a dreamboat?
Doc, she didn't even look at him.
This is more serious than I thought.
Apparently, your mother isamorously infatuated with you,
instead of your father.
Whoa. Wait a minute, Doc.
Are you trying to tell me thatmy mother has got the hots for me?
Precisely.
Whoa. This is heavy.
There's that word again. "Heavy."
Why are things so heavy in the future?
Is there a problem with theEarth's gravitational pull?
What? The only way
we're going to get thosetwo to successfully mate
is if they're alone together,
so you've got to get yourfather and mother to interact
in some sort of social...
What? You mean like a date? Right!
What kind of date? I don't know.
What do kids do in the '50s?
They're your parents.You must know them.
What are their common interests?
What do they like to do together?
Nothing.
Look! There's a rhythmicceremonial ritual coming up.
Of course! The EnchantmentUnder the Sea dance!
They're supposed to go to this.
That's where they kissfor the first time.
All right, kid.
You stick to your father like glue
and make sure he takesher to that dance.
George, buddy.
Remember that girl Iintroduced you to, Lorraine?
What are you writing?
Uh... Stories.
Science fiction stories about visitors
coming down to Earth from other planets.
Get out of town! I didn'tknow you did anything creative.
Let me read some.
Oh. No, no, no, no.
I never let anybody read my stories.
Why not?
Well, what if they didn't like them?
What if they told me I was no good?
I guess that would be prettyhard for somebody to understand.
No. No, not hard at all.
So, anyway, George. About Lorraine.
She really likes you.
She told me to tell youthat she wants you to ask her
to the Enchantment Under the Sea dance.
Really? Oh, yeah.
All you got to do is goover there and ask her.
What? Right here, rightnow, in the cafeteria?
What if she said no?
I don't know if I could takethat kind of a rejection.
Besides, I think she'drather go with somebody else.
Who?
Biff.
Don't kid around. Come on.
I'm gonna leave.
You want it. You know you want it.
You know you want me to give it to you.
Shut your filthy mouth.I'm not that kind of girl.
Maybe you are and youjust don't know it yet.
Get your meat hooks off of me.
You heard her.
She said, get your meat hooks off.
Please.
So what's it to you, butthead?
You know, you been looking for a fight.
Since you're new here, I'mgoing to cut you a break, today.
So, why don't you make likea tree and get out of here.
George!
Why do you keep following me around?
Look, George... I'm telling you, George,
if you do not askLorraine to that dance,
I'm gonna regret itfor the rest of my life.
But I can't go to the dance.
I'll miss my favorite televisionprogram, Science Fiction Theatre.
Yeah, but, George, Lorrainewants to go with you.
Give her a break.
Look, I'm just not ready toask Lorraine out to the dance,
and not you or anybodyelse on this planet
is going to make me change my mind.
Science Fiction Theatre.
Who are you?
Silence, Earthling.
My name is Darth Vader.
I am an extraterrestrialfrom the planet Vulcan.
Marty!
Marty! Marty!
Hey, George, buddy.
You weren't at school. Whathave you been doing all day?
I overslept. Look, I need your help.
I have to ask Lorraine out,
but I don't know how to do it.
All right. Okay, listen, keep yourpants on. She's over in the cafe.
God! How do you...
What made you change your mind, George?
Last night, Darth Vadercame down from Planet Vulcan
and told me that if I didn't takeLorraine out, that he'd melt my brain.
Let's just keep this brain-meltingstuff to ourselves, okay?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
All right, okay. There she is, George.
Now just go in there and invite her.
Okay. But I don't know what to say.
Just say anything, George.
Say whatever's natural, the firstthing that comes into your mind.
Nothing's coming to my mind.
Jesus, George, it's awonder I was even born.
What? What?
Nothing. Nothing. Nothing.
Look, tell her destinybrought you together.
Tell her that she isthe most beautiful girl
you have ever seen in the world.
Girls like that stuff.
What are you doing, George?
I'm writing this down.This is good stuff.
Yeah. Okay, let's go.
Can you take care of that? Right.
Lou, give me a milk.
Chocolate.
Lorraine. My densityhas popped me to you.
What?
Oh.
What I meant to say was...
Wait a minute. Don't Iknow you from somewhere?
Yes.
Yes. I'm George. George McFly.
I'm your density.
I mean,
your destiny.
Oh.
Hey, McFly.
I thought I told younever to come in here.
Well, it's going to cost you.
How much money you got on you?
How much do you want, Biff?
All right, punk.
Now I'm going to...
Whoa, whoa, Biff. What's that?
That's Calvin Klein.Oh, my God, he's a dream.
Whoa, whoa.
Kid! Kid, stop! Stop!
Hey!
I'll get itback to you, all right?
You broke it!
Come back here!
Wow. Look at him go!
Get him!
To the car! Go! Go!
What's that thing he's on?
It's a board with wheels.
He's an absolute dream.
Come on, come on!
Look out for the car!
Whoa!
I'm going to ram him.
Shit!
Ooh!
Thanks a lot, kid.
I'm going to get that son of a bitch.
Where does he come from?
Yeah, where does he live?
I don't know, but I'm going to find out.
Oh, my God.
They found me. I don'tknow how, but they found me.
Run for it, Marty!
Oh, my God.
They found me. I don'tknow how, but they found me.
Run for it, Marty!
Doc?
Hi, Marty. I didn't hear you come in.
Fascinating device, this video unit.
Listen, Doc.
You know, there's something
I haven't told you about the night
we made that tape. Please,Marty, don't tell me.
No man should know toomuch about his own destiny.
You don't understand. I do understand.
If I know too much about my own future,
I can endanger my own existence.
Just as you've endangered yours.
You're right. Now...
Let me show you my planfor sending you home.
Please excuse the crudity of this model.
I didn't have time to buildit to scale or paint it.
It's good. Thank you. Thank you.
Okay, now.
We run some industrial-strengthelectrical cable
from the top of the clock tower
down, suspending it over the street
between these two lamp posts.
Meanwhile, we'veoutfitted the time vehicle
with this big pole and hook,
which runs directlyinto the flux capacitor.
At the calculated moment, youstart off from down the street,
driving directly toward the cable,
accelerating to 88 miles per hour.
According to the flyer, at precisely10:04 p.m. This Saturday night,
lightning will strike the clocktower, electrifying the cable
just as the connectinghook makes contact
thereby sending 1.21 gigawattsinto the flux capacitor
and sending you back to 1985.
All right, now. Watch this.
You wind up the car and release it.
I'll simulate the lightning.
Ready.
Set.
Release.
You're instilling me witha lot of confidence, Doc.
Don't worry. I'll takecare of the lightning.
You take care of your pop.
By the way, what happenedtoday? Did he ask her out?
I think so.
What did she say?
It's your mom! She's tracked you down!
Quick! Let's cover the time machine.
Hi, Cal... Marty.
Mom. Lorraine.
How did you know I was here?
I followed you.
Oh. This is my doc...
My uncle, Doc Brown.
Hi. Hi.
Marty, this may seem a little forward,
but I was kind ofwondering if you'd ask me
to the Enchantment Underthe Sea dance on Saturday.
Wow, you mean... Youmean nobody's asked you?
No. Not yet.
What about George?
George McFly?
He's kind of cute and all, but not...
Well, I think a man should be strong,
so he can stand up for himself
and protect the woman he loves.
Don't you?
Yeah.
I still don't understand.
How am I supposed togo to the dance with her
if she's already goingto the dance with you?
Well, because, George,she wants to go with you.
She just doesn't know it yet.
That's why we got to show her
that you, George McFly, are a fighter.
You're somebody who'sgonna stand up for yourself,
somebody who's gonna protect her.
Yeah, but I've never pickeda fight in my entire life.
Look, you're not going tobe picking a fight, Dad.
Daddy-o.
You're coming to her rescue, right?
Okay, let's go over the plan again.
8:55, where are you going to be?
I'm going to be at the dance.
Right. And where am I going to be?
You're gonna be in the car with her.
Right, okay. So, right around 9:00,
she's going to get very angry with me.
Why is she going to get angry with you?
Well, because, George,nice girls get angry
when guys take advantage of them.
You mean you're goingto go touch her on her...
No. No, George, look.
It's just an act, right?
Okay. So, 9:00, you're strollingthrough the parking lot.
You see us struggling in the car.
You walk up, you openthe door, and you say...
Your line, George.
Oh!
Hey, you, get your damn hands off her!
You really think I ought to swear?
Yes, definitely.
God damn it, George, swear.
Okay. So, now you come up.
You punch me in the stomach.
I'm out for the count, right?
And you and Lorrainelive happily ever after.
You make it sound so easy.
I just... I wish I wasn't so scared.
George, there's nothing to be scared of.
All it takes is alittle self-confidence.
You know, if you put your mind to it,
you can accomplish anything.
...Hill Valley areaweather this Saturday night.
Mostly clear, withsome scattered clouds.
Lows tonight in the upper 40s.
Are you sure about this storm?
Since when can weathermen predictthe weather, let alone the future?
You know, Marty, I'm goingto be very sad to see you go.
You've really made adifference in my life.
You've given me something to shoot for.
Just knowing that I'm goingto be around to see 1985.
That I'm going to succeed in this!
That I'm going to have achance to travel through time!
It's going to be really hard waiting30 years before I can talk to you
about everything that'shappened in the past few days.
I'm really going to miss you, Marty.
I'm really going to miss you.
Doc, about the future...
No!
Marty! We've already agreed
that having information about the future
can be extremely dangerous.
Even if your intentions are good,
it can backfire drastically.
Whatever you've got to tell me,
I'll find out through thenatural course of time.
"Dear Dr. Brown.
"On the night that I go back in time,
"you will be
"shot by terrorists.
"Please take whateverprecautions are necessary
"to prevent this terrible disaster.
"Your friend,
"Marty."
'Evening, Dr. Brown.What's with the wire?
Oh, just a little weather experiment.
What you got under here?
No! Don't touch that!
Some new, specializedweather-sensing equipment.
You got a permit for that?
Of course I do.
Just a second. Let mesee if I can find it here.
Do you mind if we park for a while?
That's a great idea. I'd love to park.
Huh?
Marty, I'm almost 18 years old.
It's not like I've never parked before.
What?
Marty, you seem sonervous. Is something wrong?
No.
Lorraine! Lorraine, what are you doing?
I swiped it from the oldlady's liquor cabinet.
Yeah, well, you shouldn't drink.
Why not?
Because you...
You might regret it later in life.
Marty, don't be such a square.
Everybody who's anybody drinks.
Jeez, you smoke, too?
Marty, you're beginning tosound just like my mother.
We're going to take a little break,
but we'll be back in a while,
so don't nobody go nowhere.
Marty? Why are you so nervous?
Lorraine.
Have you ever been in a situation
where you knew you hadto act a certain way,
but when you got there, you didn't know
if you could go through with it?
You mean like how you'resupposed to act on a first date?
Sort of.
I think I know exactly what you mean.
You do?
You know what I do in those situations?
What?
I don't worry.
This is all wrong. Idon't know what it is.
But when I kiss you,it's like I'm kissing
my brother.
I guess that doesn'tmake any sense, does it?
Believe me, it makes perfect sense.
Somebody's coming.
You caused 300 bucks damageto my car, you son of a bitch.
And I'm going to take itout of your ass. Hold him.
Let him go, Biff. You're drunk.
Well, look-ey what we have here.
No, no! You're staying righthere with me. Come on, Lorraine.
Let me go!
Leave her alone, you bastard!
Take him in back, allright? I'll be right there.
Just admit thatyou want it. Come on.
Well, go on. This ain't no peep show.
Hey, let's put him in there.
Yeah!
That's for messing up my hair.
What the hell are you doing to my car?
Hey, beat it, spook.This don't concern you.
Who you calling "spook," peckerwood?
Hey, hey, listen, guys...
Look, I don't want to messwith no reefer addicts, okay?
Get home to your mama, boy.
Biff!
Hurry, Biff!
Let me out of here!
Reginald, where are your keys?
The keys are in the trunk.
Say that again?
I said, the keys are in here.
Come on!
Hey, you, get your damn hands off...
Oh.
I think you got the wrong car, McFly.
George, help me! Please!
Just turn around, McFly, and walk away.
Please, George.
Are you deaf, McFly?
Close the door and beat it.
No, Biff. You leave her alone.
All right, McFly.
You're asking for it, andnow you're going to get it.
Biff, stop it!
Biff, you'll break his arm!
Biff, no!
Give me a hand here, Reginald.
Damn it, man! I sliced my hand!
Whose are these? Mine.
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
You're going to break his arm!
Biff! Biff, leave him alone!
Let him go! Let him go!
Are you okay?
Who is that guy?
That's George McFly.
That's George McFly?
Excuse me.
The storm.
Hey, guys, you gotta get backin there and finish the dance.
Hey, man. Look at Marvin's hand.
He can't play with his hand like that,
and we can't play without him.
Yeah, well. Look,Marvin, you got to play.
See, that's where they kiss forthe first time on the dance floor.
And if there's nomusic, they can't dance.
If they can't dance, they can't kiss.
If they can't kiss, they can'tfall in love and I'm history.
Hey, man, the dance is over
unless you know somebodyelse that can play the guitar.
This is for all you lovers out there.
Earth angel, Earth angel
Will you be mine?
My darling dear
George, aren't you going to kiss me?
I don't know.
Scram, McFly. I'm cutting in.
Earth angel, Earth angel
The one I adore
Hey, boy, you all right?
I can't play.
George!
George.
Excuse me.
The vision of your happiness
Earth angel, Earth angel
Please be mine
My darling dear
Love you for all time
I'm just a fool
A fool in love
with you
Yeah, man, that was good.Let's do another one.
No. I got to go.
Come on, man. Let's dosomething that really cooks.
Something that cooks.
All right.
All right!
All right, this is an oldie, but...
Well, it's an oldie where I come from.
All right, guys, listen,this is a blues riff in B.
Watch me for the changes,and try and keep up, okay?
Way down inLouisiana Down in New Orleans
Way back up in the woodsamong the evergreens
There stood a log cabinmade of earth and wood
Where lived a country boyname of Johnny B. Goode
He never ever learnedto read or write so well
He could play the guitarjust like he's ringing a bell
Go, go Go, Johnny, go, go
Go, Johnny, go, go, go
Go, Johnny, go, go
Hey, George, I heard youlaid out Biff. Nice going.
George, you ever think ofrunning for class president?
Johnny B. Goode
Go, Johnny, go, go
Go, Johnny, go, go, go
Johnny B. Goode
Chuck! Chuck, it's Marvin.
Your cousin, Marvin Berry.
You know that new soundyou're looking for?
Well, listen to this.
I guess you guys aren'tready for that yet.
But your kids are going to love it.
Lorraine.
Marty, that was very interesting music.
Yeah.
I hope you don't mind,
but George asked ifhe could take me home.
Great! Good. Good, Lorraine.
I had a feeling about you two.
I have a feeling, too.
Listen, I got to go,
but I wanted to tell youthat it's been educational.
Marty, will we ever see you again?
I guarantee it.
Well, Marty, I want to thankyou for all your good advice.
I'll never forget it.
Right, George.
Well, good luck, you guys.
Oh!
One other thing. Ifyou guys ever have kids,
and one of them, whenhe's eight years old,
accidentally sets fireto the living room rug,
go easy on him.
Okay.
Marty. Such a nice name.
Damn! Where is that kid?
Damn!
Damn! Damn!
You're late! Do youhave no concept of time?
Hey, come on. I had to change.
Do you think I'm goingback in that zoot suit?
The old man reallycame through. It worked.
He laid out Biff in one punch.
I didn't know he had it in him.
He's never stood up to Biff in his life.
Never?
No. Why? What's the matter?
All right! Let's setyour destination time.
This is the exact time you left.
Let's send you back atexactly the same time.
It'll be like you never left.
Now, I painted a white lineon the street way over there.
That's where you'll start from.
I've calculated the precise distance,
taking into accountthe acceleration speed
and wind resistance retroactive
from the moment the lightning strikes,
which will be in exactly7 minutes and 22 seconds.
When this alarm goesoff, you hit the gas.
Right.
Well, I guess that's everything.
Thanks.
Thank you.
See you in about 30 years.
I hope so.
Don't worry!
As long as you hit that wire
with the connecting hook atprecisely 88 miles an hour,
the instant the lightningstrikes the tower
everything will be fine.
Right.
What's the meaning of this?
You'll find out in 30 years.
It's about the future, isn't it?
It's information about the future.
Wait a minute.
I warned you about this, kid.
The consequences could be disastrous!
Doc, that's a risk you'regoing to have to take.
Your life depends on it!
No!
I refuse to accept the responsibility.
In that case, I'lltell you straight out.
Great Scott!
You get the cable, I'llthrow the rope down to you.
Right! I got it!
Doc!
Come on, come on. Let's go!
All right! Take it up!
Go!
Doc!
What?
I have to tell you about the future.
I have to tell you about the future!
What?
On the night I go backin time, you get...
Doc!
Go!
No, Doc!
Look at the time!
You've got less than fourminutes. Please, hurry!
Yeah!
Damn it, Doc! Why did youhave to tear up that letter?
If I only had more time.
Wait a minute. I gotall the time I want.
I got a time machine. I canjust go back early and warn him.
Okay. Ten minutes ought to do it.
Okay. Time circuit's on.Flux capacitor, fluxing.
Engine running. All right.
No. No, no.
Come on. Not thistime. Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Here we go. Here wego. This time. Come on.
Please. Please. Come on!
Doc.
Crazy drunk driver.
Whoo!
All right. Fred.
You look great. Everything looks great.
1:24. I still got time. I'm coming, Doc!
No! No, not again! Come on! Come on!
Libyans.
No!
You bastard!
Go!
Doc! Doc!
No! No!
You're alive.
Bulletproof vest?
How did you know?
I never got a chance to tell you.
What about all that talk aboutscrewing up future events?
The space-time continuum?
Well, I figured, what the hell?
So, how far ahead are you going?
About 30 years. It'sa nice, round number.
Look me up when you get there,all right? Guess I'll be about 47.
I will.
Take care.
You, too.
Right. Bye-bye, Einie.
Oh. And watch that re-entry.It's a little bumpy.
You bet.
What a nightmare.
If Paul calls me, tell him I'mworking at the boutique late tonight.
Linda, first of all,I'm not your answering service,
second of all, somebody named Greg
or Craig called youjust a little while ago.
Well, which one was it, Greg or Craig?
I don't know! I can't keep upwith all of your boyfriends.
Hey.
What the hell is this?
Breakfast.
Did you sleep in yourclothes again last night?
Yeah. I...
Yeah. What are you wearing, Dave?
Marty, I always weara suit to the office.
You all right? Yeah.
I think weneed a rematch, George.
A rematch?
Why? Were you cheating?
No.
Hello. Good morning.
Mom! Dad!
Did you hit your head?Marty, are you all right?
You guys look great.Mom, you look so thin.
Why, thank you, Marty. George!
Good morning, sleepyhead.
Good morning, Dave. Linda.
Good morning, Mom.
Marty, I almostforgot. Jennifer Parker called.
I sure like her, Marty.She is such a sweet girl.
Isn't tonight the night of the big date?
What? What, Ma?
Aren't you going up to the lake tonight?
You've been planning it for two weeks.
Mom, we talked about this.How can I go to the lake?
The car's wrecked.
Wrecked? Wrecked?
When did this happen? Why wasn't I told?
Quiet down.
I'm sure the car is fine.
Why am I always the lastone to know about these things?
See? There's Biff outthere waxing it right now.
Now, Biff, I want to make sure that
we get two coats of waxthis time, not just one.
I'm just finishing upthe second coat now.
Now, Biff, don't con me.
I'm sorry, Mr. McFly.
I meant I was juststarting on the second coat.
Biff. What a character. Alwaystrying to get away with something.
I've had to stay on top ofBiff ever since high school.
Although, if it wasn't for him...
We never would have fallen in love.
That's right.
Mr. McFly! Mr. McFly, this just arrived.
Oh, hi, Marty. I thinkit's your new book.
Honey! Your first novel.
Like I've always told you,
you put your mind to it,you can accomplish anything.
Oh, Marty, here's your keys.
You're all waxed up, ready for tonight.
Keys?
How about a ride, mister?
Jennifer.
Oh, are you a sight for soreeyes! Let me look at you.
Marty, you're acting likeyou haven't seen me in a week.
I haven't.
You okay? Is everything all right?
Oh, yeah.
Everything is great.
Marty! You've got to come back with me!
Where?
Back to the future.
Wait a minute. What are you doing, Doc?
I need fuel.
Go ahead. Quick! Get in the car.
No, no. Doc, I just got here, okay?
Jennifer's here. We're gonnatake the new truck for a spin.
Well, bring her along.This concerns her, too.
Wait a minute, Doc. Whatare you talking about?
What happens to us in the future?
Do we become assholes or something?
No, no, no, no, Marty.
Both you and Jennifer turn out fine.
It's your kids, Marty.
Something has got tobe done about your kids.
Hey, Doc, we better back up. We don'thave enough road to get up to 88.
Roads? Where we're going,we don't need roads.