what hi good to meet you all nice to
meet you Sam working on anything you can
talk about
a giant space lasers now that sounds
cool
what do you say
do you want to take a tour sure
flow
ah the dining area right oh
my God could be a little bigger and um I
don't know the kitchen's really space
until two they're all pretty good size
and uh
I think we're gonna need at least no no
no no
no we all have three kids at home and
you can write
jar price range
truly I mean why don't you not tell me
I'm serious
[Music]
foreign
it is the study of what chemicals
chemicals
chemistry is the study of matter just
think about this electron
molecules change their bonds
that's all of life right it's over and
over it is growth is fascinating really
is there something like pause
yes lung cancer inoperable
best case scenario with Keem it's just
you've got right there
happy birthday
Believe It or Not zero cholesterol and
you I guess we didn't get the beige memo
goodbye honey you look fine
happy birthday we miss it for the world
thank you
he stays a little more big than look
who's here
oh buddy
are you asking me an experience well I
we we could really benefit from a new
set of eyes like it really is I thank
you but uh
I have some
book Skyler not yet please I
think their minds remember and then
you'll get your chance now that Elliot
is more than willing to pitch in well I
know honey
it's okay and can stop you from getting
it well
it's enough but uh
insert thing
sometimes your luck can change
you got your pride man
this is [ __ ] all right come on hey
talk
uh I'm Percy
all this stuff I've been through
and
okay
one year two years like it's too sick to
work
to make love
and that's how you would remember me
that's the worst part
is my thought process Skyler
suspects by surprise
can you put this big
it's easy money
until we catch you someday
copy that
oh my God
foreign
system
and then if you're planning on giving me
some
bull okay you ain't Welcome Back Cotter
so step off
DEA one
but you know the business
I'm thinking
uh you want to cook crystal meth
that's right
directly but sensory hmo's not paying
for it and
Elliot will send a check
[Music]
Bill hey prepaid cell phone
badass dad
hi baby I'm your Aunt Marie Esmeralda
Esmeralda kiss your mommy wake up
in time right after the party your name
was changed to Holly you all the time
what do you do in life
always
cheers
yeah it's me
Guardian minding my own business oh
Goodman did you know that you have
rights Consciousness here goes you two
suck at treat your product like the
simple high margin couldn't do in this
for 20 years and never I know a guy who
knows a guy
thank you
and oh there's truck stop two miles
south of exit 13. absolutely but I just
need a little more time one out
foreign
beautiful
the brake lights on the 4D some accident
up a Hester I'll be there as soon as I
can and Marie
excuse me
I'm just
are you okay
everything's okay
[Music]
foreign
hello
I'm um oh that's
that's good all right some of you
already know my brother-in-law he's a
good man I'm at Islands so dig deep
biggest silky Perfection smallest
donation gets two six packs relaxed yet
some matter of fact is but
pretty gray
we'll be here when you wake up
[Music]
fine
you're so fun did you bring it I'm I'm
PR I'm I'm pretty sure it's very low
basically
so um when could he be on his own
I mean just more oh no that's good news
for you
an affair I'm having an affair is that
what you think that's was Gretchen
Schwartz
something they're on if that's what it
takes I am not having an affair with
Gretchen
it really took me forever to get what's
going on between you and my husband
me
the money
they paid from Del cavoli in the
hospital and and not Lars
eyes on top of eyes on top of the eye
just once denying it
thanks a lot
yeah you too
yes sir absolutely
I'd like you to meet Andrew Kaufman of
the Adobe shop and Gustavo Frank
thank you very much these gentlemen are
under and can you tell us a little about
your work here just crossing the border
now the group that I soup yeah it is
indeed now we've had some successes left
Fun Run one of the most powerful weapons
we have
is this one of your agents oh I'm very
sorry what what sort of help oh hey you
know you don't have to do that please
welcome
no what what how
what
could you possibly make that kind of
money
dealer
oh
it's not a disaster all right she
fall back
a DEA brother-in-law
screw the kids paging Dr Phil the feds
would come and Rico her and the kids out
on the street moves
and then do what you do best first
hello there
sorry I'll uh I'll be right down hi
you're my recipe
of Colorado
organic chemistry was allography
how long you think you've got once he
feels confident that he knows
what do we do
no I I assure you we are hard at work
well uh
now on schedule this week
but not for a lack of trial
Gale really we've been playing catch-up
ever since
because it's all still magic it is
when I heard the book
no no come on come on
when I heard the Learned straws before
me when I was shown the charts and where
he lectured hello
[Music]
Gail
it's good to see you okay
no ah no no
his college tuition for Walter Jones
oh sacrifice
if you don't accept what I've earned
I'll be here when you
foreign
delicious
[Music]
can I help you
whatever you want
I have
um
don't do this
you don't have
hello welcome
what a pleasure
big beautiful sky Walton women is the
same as his taste in lawyers only the
very broke
and that's a joke
you worked here four years this is what
we buy
the next we want to tell you the whole
story it's a doozy gambling became an
addiction and I just you know from the
ga meeting I thought that was good I
don't like it Slack
I'm working on stuff here I've done a
little uh a little consult with me
put that in over there
cheers you guys gotta check this out
this is good
look at this guy
oh man you can't make this stuff up my
friend is Albuquerque's Public Enemy I
mean we're definitely not talking you
know bathtub crank here
so um
has a decent set of pipes say he's my
history man I've been uh been chasing
for the better I've ever seen
it goes by the name of her and here we
go
Gail looking up the the wrong tree
chemically speaking
this guy was a uh two w w my stone how
do you figure that is yeah
Walter White
w w members
yeah when I heard the Learned astronomer
the Stars
a poem freaking Brainiac you freaking me
out I'm chasing my tail about that one
you know I bet you're right
next move might be
from the fact that at the first
opportunity Gus will kill her
then he's signed
bone electromotive also owns a
subsidiary that manager took the
yeah I can't none other than Gus spring
just days before you know
anyway in industrial laundry be that one
helpful
sorry it looked like a dirt road
father
you are done
in the meantime
you have failed
if you try to interfere
I will kill your wife
[Music]
foreign
facility earlier today uh
[Music]
well to the news here and the DEA has no
idea what to make of it
we're safe
one
injury shock to the senses or properly
solve good he goes without saying that
the soul in your heart caused by your
tragic loss Better Call Saul Salt
you might want to learn how to tell
better
I need to explain myself
I didn't want any of this debtor
and then later I hope you can appreciate
that
and I Harbor no ill will in Italian I
get it
fine will you bring him here come on the
three
Saul Mike knows and don't tell me he
didn't mean it okay he threatened
someone before breakfast this morning
it's what he does let it be noted that I
do this under duress
house is infested
truck rolls up homeowners just stays
like that for days no one looks twice at
it does anyone go inside hell no
there's a nanny cam in the living room
what's your name
Todd
letterhead
[Music]
going down
what is she doing
you two pretty small one
ah now you're talking
sacrifice is very important
happy birthday
and Junior
and besides
in 10 lifetimes I certainly can't
launder it
what
please does this pile have to be
how long has this been going on since
about the time I was taking a keen
interest in my activities and you're
just got it under control oh well
forgive me and I've already decided
over the distribution end of things Mike
about that
actually
you're what and you're telling me that
you're willing to walk away from that
we're selling it I'm like sinking little
clay like five million pennies
why
down to it
are we in the math business
[Music]
I'm out
but
yeah
you can play around with it you take a
minute
for your hair yeah that's a project you
said the word
anybody uh anybody want anything you
want anything okay
to w
let me know you figure that is yeah
you got me
[Music]
foreign
are you gonna turn off the light
Walt Whitman dark green hardcover
not boring at all
so over Albuquerque
I promise all that cash I wouldn't be
able to stop talking Robin Hood's thing
but apparently Jesse here
okay Jesse we're gonna let you gather
your thoughts a soda
yeah
the words with this
this orange would come in later and
find the trees
first you go in and you mark a location
within the selected grid
hiking
huh
sunburn under mosquitoes just thinking
about that job more and more lately and
chasing monsters
what you want to think he hasn't been to
work all week
all right
[Music]
foreign
you okay
you drove into traffic to pick me from
that laundry
I think we're gonna take a breath okay
just listen to yourself these wild
accusations
God that is all that I am
and I will talk
I don't even know what I'm talking to
if you don't
maybe your best course
Walt
my name is Walter Hartwell White
This Is My Confession murdered
by my brother-in-law Hank using me as
his chemist
short I mean
which he would then sell
I was reeling from a Cancer diagno and
showed me just how much money even a
small meth operation businessman named
Gustavo Fring family
I didn't know where to turn I evolved
my wife had no idea
or Worse hurt my
Noah
it's a threat
right
which is mine Insurance in case I need
you thank you
I think it's time I meet your uncle
rep
Jesse is like family to me no suffering
no fear Bullet to the back of it let's
just talk about the money
so
of the business
just a couple dollar right too
apparently that
suppressed
Barrel looked familiar because I just
found six more he's ahead until he gave
up what he knew which led me to you she
didn't think of everything look
Jesse I don't know I can't I have
gasoline and a lighter
Jesse
Jesse I'm here where are you
all right now he knows I'm alone
where are you
partially
36 52. those are core as fast as you can
stay in a car
Walter you got eyes on him
they'll come
I'll walk backwards
get on your knees
Walter White
you have the right to speak to an
attorney and have an attorney fence do
you understand these rights as I've just
recited them too
foreign
[Music]
trash
the truth it is Flint but true then how
can you keep this a secret I asking
myself that for the rest of my life
you're a liar you you just admitted it
okay
hey Uncle Jack I don't see Jesse Pinkman
yeah back it up
say again
tell us you had a DEA agent for a
brother-in-law hiding money
it's Barry down here
and all you've got to do
my name is Asap Schrader
boys are going to load it for you
you're lost
if you can find him we'll kill him
good to go Uncle Jack
but he was out here
with those feds and he had to told him
some stuff that might not
I mean I could do it
and then you know we take
could you put your seatbelts on please
don't [ __ ] me right all right I will
discuss all of this important do you
understand go now both of you go Skyler
all we have to do
is go
you killed Hank
uncle Hank is dead it's gonna be fine I
promise you what we need to leave right
now
mom what are you doing
one more word
what the hell is wrong with you
we're a family
foreign
Cohen We Could Have A Little Spa
ah
Ellie
720 000 and you're going ten months and
two days from today it is his
to do with as he sees and for the
betterment of his family well I I'm
killer would we if you want to give your
kids drug money go do it
even if they did benefactors were known
for their charitable endems of
methamphetamine abuse
certainly would
my children are blameless
so what happens next
don't dare move a muscle you don't want
them to think this afternoon I had an
extra two hundred thousand dollars I
gave it to the two best Hitmen happens
to me tomorrow
tabs
if
a kind of
year when you're going for a walk in
Santa Fe or Manhattan dock prices
suddenly
you'll hear the scrape
this is where you get to make it right
you didn't hurt anybody oh
it's over
what stops those people from coming back
those people
my way in
tell them today
and that I
for what
that's where they'll find Hank and Steve
Gomez
put them in that hole
get yourself out of this
yeah I have to hear
for me
I was
I was a lot
turn around put your arms out like this
that's not a wig seriously
no one fine head of hair
I mean otherwise I don't think so no
you really shouldn't
wake up Jack look you owe me you love me
all right you've partnered with him
you're his partner
what are you gonna lie
now just look like a
h
foreign
[Music]
nothing happens until I hear you say it
laughs
[Music]
I guess I got to catch you waiting there
today
[Music]
foreign
working on anything you can talk about
a giant space lasers now that sounds
cool
honey what do you say
do you want to take a tour sure
thanks
you can see there's a this kind of flow
ah the dining area right oh
backyard could be a little bigger and um
I don't know the kitchen's really really
spacious I told you they're all pretty
good size and uh
I think we're gonna need at least no no
no no no no no I don't have three kids
at home and you can write
our price range
truly I mean why do you not tell me
I'm serious
[Music]
foreign
it is the study of what chemicals
chemicals
chemistry is the study of matter just
think about this electron
molecules change their bonds
that's all of life right I mean it's
over and over it is growth is
fascinating really
is there something that cries
yes lung cancer inoperable
best case scenario with Kim it's just
you've got right there
happy birthday
Believe It or Not zero cholesterol and
you I guess we didn't get the beige memo
goodbye honey you look fine
happy birthday wouldn't miss it for the
world thank you
he stays a little more big than look
who's here
oh buddy
are you asking me to experience
well I we we could really benefit from a
new set of eyes like it really is I
thank you but uh
I have some
the best
look Skyler not yet please I speak their
minds remember and then you'll get your
chance now that Elliot is more than
willing to pitch in well I'm honey
it's okay and can stop you from getting
it well
it's enough but uh
insert thing
sometimes your luck can change
you got your pride man
this is [ __ ] all right come on hey
talk
uh I'm [ __ ]
all the stuff I've been through
and
okay
one year two years like it's too sick to
work
to make love
and that's how you would remember me
that's the worst part
is my thought process Skyler
suspects by surprise
he would put this big
it's easy money
until we catch you someday
copy that
oh my God
foreign
system
and then if you're planning on giving me
some
Bowl okay you ain't Welcome Back Cotter
so step off
DEA one
but you know the business
I'm thinking
uh you want to cook crystal meth
that's right
directly but since our hmo's not paying
for it and
Elliot will send a check
[Music]
foreign
cell phone
[Music]
good morning
badass dad
[Music]
Esmerelda is
your mommy
wake up baby time right after the party
your name was changed to Holly you all
the time
what do you do in life
always
cheers
yeah it's me
partying minding my own business oh
Goodman did you know that you have
rights Consciousness here goes you two
suck at treat your product like the
simple high margin can do in this for 20
years and never I know a guy who knows a
guy
thank you
and oh there's truck stop two miles
south of exit 13. absolutely but I just
need a little more time one out
foreign
oh Christ Marie
beautiful
brake lights on the 40. some accident up
a Hester I'll be there as soon as I can
and Marie
excuse me
I'm just
are you okay
meetings okay
swish it for me
inside
is the food
actually
as a yes
hello
I'm um oh that's
that's good all right some of you
already know my brother-in-law he's a
good man private islands so dig deep
I think it's the silky Perfection
smallest donation gets two six packs
relaxed yet
some matter of fact is but
pretty great
we'll be here when you wake up
hmm any better
fine your cell phones you bring it I'm
I'm PR I'm I'm pretty sure it's very low
basically
so um when could he be on his own
I mean just
now that's good news for you
Affair I'm having an affair is that what
you think that's was Gretchen Schwartz
something they're on if that's what it
takes I am not having an affair with
Gretchen
it really took me forever to get what's
going on between you and my husband
me
the money name
they paid from Del Cavalli in the
hospital and and not Lars
on top of eyes
just once denying it
uh thanks a lot
yeah you too
yes sir absolutely
Mr Schrader I'd like you to meet Andrew
Kaufman of the Adobe
and Gustavo Frank
thank you very much these gentlemen are
underway and can you tell us a little
about your work here just crossing the
border now the group that is who yeah it
is indeed now we've had some successes
left Fun Run one of the most powerful
weapons we have
is this one of your agents oh I'm very
sorry what what sort of help oh hey you
know you don't have to do that please
how
what
could you possibly make that kind of
money
dealer
oh
okay it's not a disaster all right she
blowback
a DEA brother-in-law
screw the kids paging Dr Phil the feds
will come and Rico her and the kids out
on the street wolves
and then do what you do best first
hello there
sorry I'll uh I'll be right down hi
you're my recipe
of Colorado
organic chemistry
Mr boy
how long you think you've got once he
feels confident that he knows
what do we do
no I I assure you we are hard at work
well uh
now on schedule this week
but not for a lack of trying
Gale really we've been playing catch-up
ever since
because it's all still magic it is
when I heard the book
okay no no come on come on
when I heard the Learned astronomy
before me when I was shown the charts
and where he lectured hello
[Music]
Gail
it's good to see you
no ah no no
his college tuition for Walter Jones
oh the sacrifices
if you don't accept what I've earned
I'll be here when you
foreign
[Music]
don't do this
you don't have
hello welcome
what a pleasure
big beautiful sky Walton women is the
same as his taste in lawyers only the
very
that's a joke
you worked here four years this is what
we buy
the next we want to tell you the whole
story it's a doozy gambling became an
addiction and I just you know from the
ga meeting I thought that was good I
don't like it Slack
I'm working on stuff here I've done a
little uh a little Consulting me
put that in over there
seriously you guys gotta check this out
this is good
look at this guy
oh man you can't make this stuff up my
friend is Albuquerque's Public Enemy I
mean we're definitely not talking you
know bathtub crank here
so um
has a decent set of pipes say he's my
guestry man I've been uh been chasing
for the better I've ever seen
it goes by the name of her and here we
go
Yale looking up the the wrong tree
chemically speaking
that was a uh two WWE my stuff I know
you figure that is yeah
Walter White
w w
members
oh yeah when I heard the Learned
astronomer the Stars
a poem freaking Brainiac are you
freaking me out I'm chasing my tail
about that one you know I bet you're
right
next move might be
fact that at the first opportunity Gus
will kill him
but he signed
electromotive also owns a subsidiary
that manager took delivery of one of
these systems yeah I can't none other
than Gus frang just days before you know
anyway in industrial laundry be that one
helpful
I just did sorry it looked like a dirt
road
thank you
foreign
you are done
in the meantime
you have failed
if you try to interfere
I will kill your
[Music]
foreign
injury shock to the senses or properly
it's all good he goes without saying
that the hole in your heart caused by
your tragic loss Better Call Saul Sultan
between
love you might want to learn how to tell
better
I need to explain myself
I didn't want any of this stagner
and then later I hope you can appreciate
that
thank you
I appreciate that when
and I Harbor no ill will into time I get
it
five will you bring him here come on the
three
Saul Mike knows the mix and don't tell
me he didn't mean it okay we threatened
someone before breakfast this morning
it's what he does let it be noted that I
do this under duress a house is infested
truck rolls up homeowners just stays
like that for days no one looks twice at
it does anyone go inside hell no
foreign
there's a nanny cam in the living room
what's your name Doug
[Music]
going down
thank you
wish I had an I could see the way to
show
[Music]
what is she doing
you two pretty small one
ah now you're talking
sacrifice is very important happy
birthday
and Junior
and besides
in 10 lifetimes I certainly can't
launder it
Walt
please does this pile have to be
hi
how long has this been going on so it's
about the time we've taken a keen
interest in my activities and you just
got it under control oh well forgive me
and I've already decided
over the distribution end of things Mike
about that
actually
you're what and you're telling me that
you're willing to walk away from that
we're selling it I think a little clear
like five million pennies
why
down to it
I mean the math business
[Music]
I'm out
but
yeah
you can play around with it you take a
minute
for your hair yeah that's a project you
said the word
anybody uh anybody want anything you
want anything okay
to w
let me know you figure that out yeah
you got me
foreign
[Music]
are you gonna turn off the light
Walt Whitman dark green hardcover
not boring at all
so over Albuquerque
I promise all that cash I wouldn't be
able to stop talking Robin Hood's thing
but apparently Jesse here is
okay Jesse we're gonna let you gather
your thoughts soda
oh yeah
the words with this
this orange Spritz would come in later
and
find the trees first you go in and you
mark a location within the selected grid
hiking
huh
sunburn under mosquitoes just been
thinking about that job more and more
lately and chasing monsters
what you want to think he hasn't been to
work all week
all right
[Music]
foreign
you okay
you drove in a traffic to get me from
that laundry
I'm gonna take a breath okay just listen
to yourself these wild accusations
God that is all that I am
and I will talk
I don't even know what I'm done
if you don't
maybe your best course
Walt
my name is Walter Hartwell White
This Is My Confession murdered by my
brother-in-law Hank using me as his
chemist
short I mean
which he would then sell
I was reeling from a cancer diagnosis
and showed me just how much money even a
small meth operation a businessman named
Gustavo Fring family
I didn't know where to turn I evolved
my wife had no idea
or Worse hurt my
Noah
threat
right
this is mine Insurance in case I need
you thank you
I think it's time I meet your uncle
rep
Jesse is like family to me no suffering
no fear pull it to the back of it let's
just talk about the money
the business
I would write too
apparently that
suppressed
Barrel looked familiar because I just
found six more because I had until he
gave up what he knew which led me to you
she didn't think of everything look
Jesse I don't know I can't I have
gasoline and a lighter I don't know
okay
Jesse I'm here where are you
right now
he knows I'm alone
where are you
okay 36. 52. those are corn as fast as
you can
oh Walter Walter you got eyes on him
they'll come
I walk backwards
get on your knees
Walter White
you have the right to speak to an
attorney and have an attorney fence do
you understand these rights as I've just
recited them too
foreign
[Music]
trash
it is Flint but true then how could you
keep this a secret I asking myself that
for the rest of my life
you're a liar you you just admitted it
hey Uncle Jack I don't see Jesse Pinkman
say again
if you tell us you had a DEA agent for a
brother-in-law hiding money it's Barry
down here
and all you've got to do
my name is asak Schroeder
ER
foreign
good to go Uncle Jack
but he was out here
with those feds and he had to told him
some stuff that might not
I mean I could do it
and then you know we take care
could you put your seatbelts on please
you're [ __ ] me right all right I
will discuss all of this list important
do you understand go now both of you go
all we have to do
you killed Hank uncle Hank is dead I no
no it's gonna be fine I promise you what
we need to leave right now
mom what are you doing
one more word
let's go
mom stop it
what the hell is wrong with you well
family
foreign
Cohen We Could Have A Little Spa
seven hundred twenty thousand dollars
and you're going ten months and two days
from today it is his to do with as he
sees and for the betterment of his
family well I I'm killer would we if you
want to give your kids drug money go do
it
even if they did benefactors who are
known for their charitable endems of
methamphetamine abuse
certainly would
my children are blameless
so what happens next
don't dare move a muscle you don't want
them to think this afternoon I had an
extra two hundred thousand dollars I
gave it to the two best Hit Men happens
to me tomorrow
tabs
and if
a kind of
year when you're going for a walk in
Santa Fe or Manhattan dock prices
suddenly you'll hear the scrape
this is where you get to make it right
you didn't hurt anybody oh
it's over
what stops those people from coming back
those people
my way in
tell them today
and that I
for what that's where they'll find Hank
and Steve Gomez
and
put them in that hole
get yourself out of this
yeah I have to hear
I was
I was alive
turn around put your arms out like this
that's not a wig seriously
no one fine hit of hair
I mean otherwise I don't think so no
you really shouldn't
wake up Jack [ __ ] you hold me you love
me all right you partnered with him
you're his partner
what are you gonna lie
I just look like a
h
foreign
[Music]
nothing happens until I hear you say it
I guess I've got to catch you waiting
there today
[Music]
what hi good to meet you all nice to
meet you Sam working on anything you can
talk about
giant space lasers now that sounds cool
honey what do you say
do you want to take a tour sure
this kind of flow ah the dining area
right oh
backyard could be a little bigger and um
I don't know the kitchen's really
spacious I told you they're all pretty
good size and uh
I think we're gonna need at least no no
no no no no I don't have three kids home
and you can write
our price range
truly I mean why do you not tell me
I'm serious
[Music]
foreign
it is the study of what chemicals
chemicals
chemistry is the study of matter just
think about this electron
molecules change their bonds
that's all of life right I mean it's
over and over it is growth is
fascinating really
foreign
yes lung cancer inoperable
best case scenario with Kim it's just
you've got right there
happy birthday
Believe It or Not zero cholesterol and
you I guess we didn't get the beige memo
goodbye honey you look fine
happy birthday wouldn't miss it for the
world thank you
he stays a little more big than look
who's here
oh buddy
are you asking me to experience well I
we could really benefit from a new set
of eyes like it really is I thank you
but uh
I I have some
look Skyler
please I think their minds remember and
then you'll get your chance now that
Elliot is more than willing to pitch in
well I know honey
it's okay and can stop you from getting
it well
it's enough but uh
insert thing
sometimes your luck can change
you got your pride man
this is [ __ ] all right come on talk
uh I'm [ __ ]
all this stuff I've been through
and
okay
one year two years like it's too sick to
work
to make love
and that's how you would remember me
that's the worst part
is my thought process Skyler
suspects by surprise
you can put this big
it's easy money
until we catch you someday
I'll copy that
oh my God
foreign
system
and then if you're planning on giving me
some
Bowl okay you ain't Welcome Back Cotter
so step off
DEA one
but you know the business
I'm thinking
uh you want to cook crystal meth
that's right
directly but since our HMO is not paying
for it and
Elliot will send a check
[Music]
foreign
prepaid cell phone
[Music]
good morning
badass dad
[Music]
is
your mommy
wake up baby time to fight right after
the party your name was changed to Holly
you all the time
you do in life
always
cheers
foreign
[Applause]
did you know that you have rights
Consciousness here goes you two suck at
treat your product like the simple high
margin could be doing this for 20 years
and never I know a guy who knows a guy
thank you
and oh there's truck stop two miles
south of exit 13. absolutely but I just
need a little more time one out
foreign
oh Christ Marie
beautiful
brake lights on the 40. some accident up
a Hester I'll be there as soon as I can
and Marie
excuse me
I'm just
are you okay
meetings okay
just wish you'd finish
is the food
actually
as a yes
hello
I'm um oh that's
that's good all right some of you
already know my brother-in-law he's a
good man private islands so dig deep
the biggest silky Perfection smallest
donation gets two six packs relaxed yet
as a matter of fact is but
pretty great
we'll be here when you wake up
hmm yeah you better
fine your cell phone did you bring it
I'm I'm PR I'm I'm pretty sure it's very
low basically
so um when could he be on his own
I mean just more
no that's good news for you
an affair I'm having an affair is that
what you think that's was Gretchen
Schwartz
something they're on if that's what it
takes I am not having an affair with
Gretchen
it really took me forever to get what's
going on between you and my husband
me
the money
they paid from Del Cavalli in the
hospital and and not cars
on just once denying it
thanks a lot
yeah you too
yes sir absolutely
registrator I'd like you to meet Andrew
Kaufman of the Adobe
and Gustavo Frank
thank you very much these gentlemen are
under and can you tell us a little about
your work here just crossing the border
now the group that uh yeah it is indeed
now we've had some successes love Fun
Run one of the most powerful weapons we
have
is this one of your agents oh I'm very
sorry what what sort of help oh hey you
know you don't have to do that please
welcome
no how
what
could you possibly make that kind of
money
there's nothing better me
dealer
oh
okay it's not a disaster all right she
low back
a DEA brother-in-law
screw the kids paging Dr Phil the feds
will come and Rico her and the kids out
on the street moves
and just do what you do best first
hello there
sorry I'll uh I'll be right down
hi
you're
my recipe University of Colorado
organic chemistry with holography
how long you think you've got us once he
feels confident that he knows
what do we do
no I I assure you we are hard at work
well uh
not in federal this week but not for a
lack of trying
Gail really we've been playing catch-up
ever since
because it's all still magic it is
when I heard the book
no no come on come on
when I heard the Learned astronauts
before me when I was shown the charts
and where he lectured hello
foreign
[Music]
oh the sacrifices thing
if you don't accept what I've earned
I'll be here when you
I don't know
this is the sooner we all go home
free and there won't be any more
children I can convince him okay just
let me please please you might want to
hold off yeah 63 53 want to yeah
[Music]
can I help you
or you want
I
um
don't do this
you don't have
hello welcome
what a pleasure
big beautiful sky Walton women is the
same as his taste in lawyers only the
very [ __ ]
that's a joke
you worked here four years this is what
we buy
the next we want to tell you the whole
story it's a doozy gambling became an
addiction and I just could you know from
the ga meeting I thought that was good I
don't like it Slack
I'm working on stuff here I've done a
little uh a little consult with me
put that in over there
cheers you guys gotta check this out
this is good ready look at this guy
oh man you can't make this stuff up my
friend is Albuquerque's Public Enemy I
mean we're definitely not talking you
know bathtub crank here so
um
front has a decent set of pipes say he's
my guestry man I've been uh been chasing
for the better I've ever seen
it goes by the name
and here we go
up the the wrong tree chemically
speaking
this guy was a uh to WWE my stuff you
figure that is yeah
Walter White
w w members
up here when I heard the Learned
astronomer the Stars
the poem freaking Brainiac freaking
Brainiac I'm chasing my tail about that
one you know I bet you're right
thanks
pause next move might be
on the fact that at the first
opportunity Gus will
then he signed
phone electromotive also owns a
subsidiary that manager took delivery of
one of these systems yeah account none
other than Gus Fring just days before
you know
anyway in industrial laundry be that one
helpful
missed it sorry it looked like a dirt
road
[Applause]
you are done
in the meantime
you have failed
can't if you try to interfere
I will kill your wife
[Music]
foreign
facility earlier today
[Music]
well to the news here
over
we're safer
come on
injury shock to the senses or properly
solve good it goes without saying that
the soul in your heart caused by your
tragic loss
call Saul
you might want to learn how to tail
better
I need to explain myself
I didn't want any of this stagner
and then later I hope you can appreciate
that
I appreciate that when and I Harbor no
ill will into time I get it
fine will you bring him here come on the
three open
Saul Mike knows the mix and don't tell
me he didn't mean it okay we threatened
someone before breakfast this morning
it's what he does let it be noted that I
do this under duress house is infested
truck rolls up homeowners just stays
like that for days no one looks twice at
it does anyone go inside hell no
there's a nanny cam in the living room
what's your name Doug
foreign
[Music]
what is she doing
did she do pretty small one
ah now you're talking
sacrifice is very important
happy birthday
and Junior
and besides
in 10 lifetimes I certainly can't
launder it
Walt
does this pile have to be
how long has this been going on so it's
about the time I was taking a keen
interest in my activities and you just
got it under control oh well forgive me
and I've already decided
over the distribution end of things Mike
about that
actually
you're what and you're telling me that
you're willing to walk away from that
we're selling it I think a little clear
like five million pennies
why
down to it
I'm in the math business
[Music]
I'm out
but
yeah
you can play around with it you take a
minute
for your hair yeah that's a project you
said the word
anybody uh anybody want anything you
want anything okay
to w
let me know you figure that out yeah
you got me
foreign
[Music]
Walt Whitman dark green hardcover
not boring at all
so over Albuquerque
I promise all that cash I wouldn't be
able to stop talking Robin Hood's thing
but apparently Jesse here is
okay Jesse we're gonna let you gather
your thoughts a soda
yeah
the words with this
this orange Spritz would come in later
and
find the trees first you go in and you
mark a location within the selected grid
hiking
hmm
sunburn under mosquitoes just been
thinking about that job more and more
lately and Chase of monsters
that's what we think he hasn't been to
work all week
all right
[Music]
foreign
you okay
you drove into traffic to get me from
that laundry
I think we're gonna take a breath okay
just listen to yourself these wild
accusations
God that is all that I am
and I will talk
I don't even know what I'm done
if you don't
maybe your best course
Walt
my name is Walter Hartwell White
This Is My Confession murdered
by my brother-in-law Hank using me as
his chemist
short that I mean
which he would then sell
I was reeling from a Cancer diagno and
showed me just how much money even a
small meth Opera businessman named
Gustavo Frank Family
I didn't know where to turn I evolved
my wife had no idea
or Worse hurt my
Noah
threat
right
just mine Insurance in case I need you
thank you
I think it's time I meet your uncle
rep
Jesse is like family to me no suffering
no fear Bullet to the back of it let's
just about the money
the business
a couple dollar right too
apparently that
suppressed
Barrel looked familiar because I just
found six more it's ahead until he gave
up what he knew which led me to you she
didn't think of everything look
Jesse I don't know I can't I have
gasoline and a lighter
okay
Jessie Jessie
Jessie
Jessie I'm here where are you
all right now he knows I'm alone
where are you
okay
36 52. those are corn as fast as you can
stay in the car
Walter you got eyes on him
he'll come
I'll walk backwards
get on your knees
Walter White
you have the right to speak to an
attorney and have an attorney fence do
you understand these rights as I've just
recited them to
put them in a car
foreign
[Music]
trash
videos
then how can you keep this a secret I
asking myself that for the rest of my
life
you're a liar you you just admitted it
hey Uncle Jack I don't see Jesse Pinkman
say again
maybe tell us you had a DEA agent for a
brother-in-law hiding money it's Ferry
down here
and all you've got to do
my name is asak Schroeder
boys are going to load it for you
you're lost
if you can find him we'll kill him
good to go Uncle Jack
but he was out here
with those feds and he had to told him
some stuff that might not
I mean I could do it
and you know we take
[ __ ] me right all right I will
discuss all of this it's important do
you understand go now both of you go
Scott all we have to do
is go
you killed Hank uncle Hank is dead I no
no it's gonna be fine I promise you what
we need to leave right now
mom what are you doing
one more word
let's go
oh stop it
is wrong with you well family
well I have
um
Miriam Cohen We Could Have A Little Spa
Ellie
700 120 000 and you're going ten months
and two days from today it is his to do
with as he sees and for the betterment
of his family
would we if you want to give your kids
drug money go do it
even if they did benefactors were known
for their charitable endems of
methamphetamine abuse
certainly would
my children are blameless
so what happens next
don't dare move a muscle you don't want
them to think this afternoon I had an
extra two hundred thousand dollars I
gave it to the two best Hitmen happens
to me tomorrow
tabs
and if
a kind of
ear when you're going for a walk in
Santa Fe or Manhattan dock prices
suddenly you'll hear the scrape
this is where you get to make it right
you didn't hurt anybody oh
it's over
what stops those people from coming back
those people
my way in
of them today
and that I
for what that's where they'll find Hank
and Steve Gomez
put them in that hole
get yourself out of this
do I have to hear
from me
I was
I was alive
turn around put your arms out like this
it's not a wig seriously
no one fine hit of hair
I mean otherwise I don't think so no
I really shouldn't
wake up Jack look you owe me you love me
all right you've partnered with him
you're his partner
what are you gonna lie
now just look like a
h
all right
you're watching money right
foreign
[Music]
nothing happens until I hear you say it
I guess I've got to catch you waiting
there today
[Music]
foreign
anything done
[Music]
foreign