[Music]
okay one picture in my history this what
I'm afraid of
[Music]
you
everyone who told a thing for chicken I
[Music]
don't see anything you take the picture
now I didn't picture to a normally I
would take the picture you take a
picture you take it you guys don't fight
[Music]
and to save the Dolphins foundation 11
million dollars to the save the Pumas
foundation 1.2 million dollars to the
Patagonian wasp salvation fund 1.4
million dollars to the dyslexic
Dalmatians foundation now the livestock
where the old stiff leaves me I believe
that what the bereaved is trying to
express is that the sudden death of her
only father has left a great gaping void
in her bank in her life and Carrigan
wonders what he has left her to fill it
up with hmm let's see
Bobcats owls snakes daughter Carrigan
Whipstaff Manor in name and and I'm late
for lunch so if you'll excuse me are you
trying to tell me that I just spent the
last two days holding his clammy and
waiting for him to kick and all I get in
return is one lousy piece of property no
it was lousy 50 years ago now it's
condemned enjoy wait six it's not fair
all three times then I'm gonna drag you
every one of those damned Dolphins into
court knock yourself out if this is all
your fault as usual if you would have
just forged the damn will in our jargon
this is condemned seafront yes don't you
bend flipper got more money than me
Carrigan the be dinner
[Music]
Buccaneers and buried gold Whipstaff
doth a treasure hold treasure
if you ain't get I knew that please
support nothing finally gonna get what I
deserve
Kerrigan I think I need a doctor oh
there's plenty of name
[Music]
so what do you think I think you're
going to get what it's done wow this
verse is fabulous you could just do so
much with it
spooky hello who is it
wait you can't why not
and the party is free if you are you the
caretaker no is it
are you a transient no not exactly
the shop charcoal is the thing I do
don't scream hey I get that alive are
you a burglar I must warn you but I am
all
hello listen cut the crap okay if you
don't show yourself right now I'm gonna
have you arrested for trespassing tell
me no no you can do that
[Applause]
[Music]
so tell me you have experience
I was quite bit strange not you know
like exactly doing it but I started it
and I talked to who have done it I've
seen in the videos and I feel very
confident with my knowledge I could I
could do it no cloud and you can handle
it it's a no problem
it's like no problem whatsoever piece of
cake this crumb cake
[Music]
well how does it go
Oh what's a fine what there's no problem
piece of cake
who are you gonna call someone else what
do we do now
what do I usually do when something
stands in my way
[Music]
are you sure we're not going to have
over balls here it's I have huffed and
puffed now I want to rip this place down
I want my treasure they can't want a
pile of rubble for Christ's sake Oh
[Music]
people plate you're sweaty Baptists
bustin types are quite space it's do
something Ollie was a friend did you
ever feel the way Priscilla cowbell that
you'd like to be completely different
almost everybody feels like that once in
a while but most of the time I hope you
can be glad to be yourself that's really
something to celebrate more on the
Pentagon Playboy's is the story unfold
but now step aside Sigmund Freud just
back Joyce brothers it's dr. James
Harvey therapist to the dead are you
depressed are you anxious are you lonely
do you need someone to talk to
no problem if you're a ghost
you can call them ghosts if you like or
as I prefer the living impaired but the
bottom line is they need help sometimes
[Music]
after this sudden unexpected death of
his wife Amelia dr. Harvey gave up
conventional psychiatry and some say
conventional sanity now along with his
loner daughter Kat short for Kathy doc
Harvey travels from town to town
searching for paranoid poltergeists
scared specters the depressed and the
death
I can feel about what your father does
for a living do you believe in ghosts
have you ever seen one did your father
ever hurt you in any way please father
would you just talk to it rusty it's the
first day school and I'm sure Morgan
here
[Music]
[Applause]
would work don't like this now not I
hate this I hate this but if you have
talent here but I have had a long and
trying day you think screaming times
having rough times but rum-raisin I
happy if you can handle that my Harry
passed away five years ago but he was so
miserable if spirit wouldn't leave the
apartment so I called dr. Harvey he came
over and in a few weeks
Harry left smiling the living impaired
are known for haunting us my question is
what's haunting them it's a lack of
resolution
ghosts are simply spirits without
resolution unfinished business
and it's my job to find out what that is
and so dr. James Harvey continues work
riding his daughter along to the ride
this week they're in Santa Fe but next
week who knows now from the ghost
strengths are shrinking yes I'm soon
here prema get me Santa Fe
[Music]
That's Life that's liar they're all
peoples laid that down and uh honey I'm
sorry about your cactus Spooner's I
don't care what they said you are not
demented you're a picture of mental
health
we were talking about you I mean ty is
planning afterlife therapy what skin
you're hiking hey some people go through
life never questioning the norm a you
and I we're doing something
extraordinary with our lives
no we aren't doing anything you're the
one who's been packing up my stuff and
moving me around the country I mean in
two years I have been nine different
poles I skated in nine different
cafeterias but I can t remember anyone's
name for one I would just like to be one
place long enough weeks time honey you
will
I mean come on we're moving to
Friendship Maine even I might make one
yeah will you better dad single guy your
age more likely to become a bank hostage
and make new friends you sound like your
mother
and I can find us
mom's not a ghost Oh
when finished business this business
thing
I'll tell you what you go with me this
one last time if I don't find what I'm
looking for it's a no more moving no
more ghost mining
promise
here
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
it's not so bad Stephen King dr. Harvey
hello I'm Carrigan Crittenden and
distance hello I'm a close personal
friend
uh-huh and this is my daughter Kat his
close personal daughter so nice to meet
you can very nice to meet you you have a
beautiful daughter dr. Harvey very
beautiful ah I can't tell you how happy
we are that you could come all the way
to its death very happy the both of us
you're kind of hurting my face huh yeah
dr. hardy exactly what kind of time
frame are you looking please tell me you
just go in houses right um I said as
with the traditional psychological cure
it can take weeks or even years excuse
oh you didn't just say the word years
did you it's conceivable no it isn't
days in two weeks
thank you possibly a month no years
again forget it
ed check it okay that's I will be
watching you back
basically you have a lovely night
Wow hey there
Chisolm house I did what she liked me
what if she just hi I'm Jeffrey I'm a
ghost no toes after ah yep I'm Kathryn
sup good for oh god I kill for a pinkie
oh great that was easy yeah
penny shoulder now but we ought to get a
back to 20 amps in the morning right
yeah 22 should be fine all right I'm
gonna go find a room Jeff you're going
to be all right along hey if I'm not
back in ten days on the search party
[Music]
stretch
faster
stinky man they had cool parents wonder
where docking dopest with
[Music]
dad I found my room girl
Oh much yes hey space master here see me
mr. president
wait desperate yes this is a nice room
you're right place the Freak holiday Oh
mom over here
hey mind if I help you unpack my Bowser
we'll just do repacking to eat anyway
right I'm kidding I'm kidding
this place is fine good night bucket
we're going to be glad we came
[Music]
hi man perfect person
anyone - then I saw go it was a real Don
what are you saying
I saw a go and in a head and it was
rounding it was white and see-through
Anthony no dad please do you not think
I'm as crazy as I thought you were I'm
promised no no no good but remember
ghosts can't hurt you okay there's
simply spirits with unfinished business
all right
let's just see about this ghost tonight
check here Oh see no ghosts there check
over here
oh no listen they're singing check the
clear yeah see pleasure to meet you sir
[Music]
I can walk you now
right now I want you to stay in here no
matter what you hear okay sweet that I'm
sorry I'm not believing you you're
thinking you're a total loser
oh honey apologize man dem phonies run
faster when we go down to Selma you're
Flicka
[Laughter]
[Music]
and I want to scale one to ten ten being
fun and one being you yeah we had fun
thank ball bed why aren't you inside
doing your chores
yeah where's dinner I'm starving look at
me I've wasted away how would you guys
relax out here tonight we'll eat
alfresco hey sounds great
who's this hey shorty you wouldn't be
trying to keep us out of the house would
ya no no I can see right through that
bulbous little head of yours you just
had your lovely night I thought we'd
have fun just eating into the Harvest
Moon a fact so you smell something we're
now beside him
oh you afraid
then we freeze I'd like to make contact
with you but just one of them think we
said don't come when the Rose will know
spooky get beyond that I would like
approach you do that kill you
yo mama now our bridge place and friends
you think you got it tough I got a
facelift it was one just like an
underneath hey boys we got a closet
eight here
[Laughter]
smell gram before they walk on the
runway though we have dr. James or
everywhere especially not to what Maki
[Music]
stop it you are we scary or work oh and
it looks as if we're gonna go into
sudden death overtime anybody more
little stitch good dog
[Music]
to finally work domicile ah geez okay
Wendy's down for the count
Wow when I buy a green back what the
hell is dancing
[Music]
see you
oh my god you're hurt look at that point
yet mine that's not my hair I wasn't
watching the golden you say minute but
what I my family does you have to try
screams your ways are my uncles and I
got awfully cranky I'll let you go okay
you're so cold
yeah but it's easily heating up sex
come on okay I use you sure you kind of
happens for me you'll have me again what
are you made of well you don't like
tinkling feeling when your football
asleep I think I may to that
[Music]
Sunnyside up kinda makes me yeah no
problem
[Music]
so can you go invisible and I that was
easy
fresh
[Music]
go ahead I've never done this
me neither can you hurt me no can I hurt
you you know
coupe why not for our penis breakfast
yes honey you okay how about a paper New
York Times the journal tongue conference
sure come hungry
[Music]
you want
I smell of fleshies in the morning
[Music]
they're gone
they must a mr. crossed over
oh yes again bone bag fellows warning
dad I'm here you serve the finish suckin
intruders before run gimme my
I feel like Oprah on hiatus you know
what the problem is
okay there's got no respect for after
all we've done for the little blow work
hey hey what the hell do you think
you're doing ball bed before you should
be dirty enough to eat off but we have
company
oh yeah well company loves me you guys
are disgusting now she's creepy
thank you I mean what's your problem
used to clean the floor
shut up skin big ha ha hey get a great a
lot of fun I know you will all right
guys we've obviously gotten off on the
wrong foot here now you know and I know
that you really shouldn't be here so
I'll tell you what why don't you go
ahead and finish your meal and you can
meet my office and start the process of
crossing over what do you say well it's
your hour
what
[Music]
amber wait up
how's that like last year my name is BIC
coming
okay game down what I'm going on it okay
I've got a couple of announcements to
make
first the asbestos removal from the gym
is taking a little longer than planned
so we're going to have to push back the
Halloween dance just like a couple of
months well as most of you know my
parents are finished see a new boathouse
so I'm sure it'd be no poem having beer
party at my place great that's done
secondly we have a new student today I
like you all to meet Harvey Kathleen
would you like some up and say hi to
everyone for me
Harvey so why don't you settle something
special about yourself Kathleen um it's
cat Wow well I guess I just moved here
my dad from Santa Fe and friendship
seems like a pretty friendly place so
where are you guys living and outer
Spain know you've heard of it you
actually live there well yeah I mean I
know it looks kind of funky got some
outside and everything but I mean I
don't know it inside is kind of cool
putting a few drinks blood whiskers
checked it we did for the Halloween
dance right
this girl has a seriously seriously
creepy house with room to spare
oh wait a minute wait a minute I thought
we were having the party at my place oh
okay we'll take a vote whoever wants to
party at my house there's your hands
Whipstaff
[Music]
Johns Hopkins University very impressive
this one Thank You Jenna hey what a dish
that a little missus perhaps hahaha oh
you animal he available that she's my
wife Amelia she's deceased
every better but we're not here to talk
about me see now don't you feel just
awful I was just goofing
well don't be goofing on Amelia she's as
nice a person as they come
she's always treated you right lunch
thank you I got no complaints she's
always been an angel to me quit what are
you saying I'm saying she's a peach not
a better wine you've actually seen what
you think I'm blind of course I've seen
it
well hasn't what you're not looking for
are you doc well that's not really the
focus of our sessions here is it but as
long as you raise the issue you wouldn't
have a way of contacting others like
yourselves would you I didn't think so
now that's not generally a loud bad back
I mean you gotta go through channels
paperwhite clickers holiness you know
what I'm saying
but for you I don't know maybe we could
work something out you keep that ghoul
Crittenden off our backs and I'd say we
got a deal right boys
do you say so you know where Amelia
floats go that easy Anna we got a ghost
the ghost network we shall haunting
stories we throw parties the parties are
always pretty good
that was fast
I I think it's for you
[Music]
go
you
[Music]
[Applause]
hmm what are you doing hi can I come in
uh no no so much nicer out here in the
flesh serves fresh air so did you ask
about about the party yeah yeah yeah he
kind of hit the ceiling but um I think
it's gonna be okay cool so listen if
you're not hooked up with anybody else
you wanna wanna hang out for you party
I'd love to all right cool
all right see you
well did you ask her
yeah and she actually believed you it's
really bite no it's absolutely perfect
hey see I'm a dancer always life before
her listen I know you want to go come on
you have a great time together
however I have a date what's this big
guy got that I don't huh Hulk big fleshy
deal I can very bad okay how about a
reflection
okay okay but can't do this come with me
if you want to live oh my god mime is
very high
castle is beautiful I come here every
night alone mm-hmm what we like when you
realize I was I was
I don't remember you don't remember
anything for your life
no so
nothing Oh
but you don't remember what school you
went to how old you were you favorite
song so what about your dad
not even your mom is that bad no just
confess
[Music]
wonder why you don't remember anything
yes when you're a ghost
what's the matter that much anymore so
you forget sometimes I worry that I'm
trying to forget forget what my mom just
everything the sound of her making
breakfast downstairs the way she put on
her lipstick so carefully
I do remember she always do decide
yourself and when she hugged me I
breathe already Odie and I remember
before I go to sleep she'd was from my
hair started me eyes rosy cheeks a happy
girl morning
you
Kaspar
it was a ghost did she forget about me
no she'd never forget you cat mm-hmm
if I were alive would you go to the
Halloween dance with me cat
the window pole
how'd you scar was it um in your wallet
I was thinking maybe I could use it says
perfect costume I saw in the store
downtown you always made your costume ah
oh I think I could come up with
something pretty good why don't we just
roll you in luminous oil and you could
go as a leftover don't worry
you always look cute I don't want to
look cute cute like when you're 9 years
old and you've got paper mache around
your head I wouldn't look nice like like
date night
really honey you know I think maybe it's
time that we sat down a little late for
that day all right
oh don't worry
not the happening oh good you know that
I would love to buy you everything that
you wanted but until miss Crittenden
pays me that thing is pretty worthless
um well that's okay don't worry about it
I'm sure I can come up perfect
please whatever you do don't want those
guys crash it oh no I think they're
actually getting to be quite focused now
[Applause]
[Music]
scream
railroads the patient has finally
arrived late again I see could this be
an expression of hostility bastard
it's your our Freud what so silent no
pearls of wisdom today that come on Doc
hey top don't stop come on back hang
with a homeboy hey wait a second
what you ain't thinking about packing it
in now are you doc
we just are to have fun it ain't often
we need a bone bag as amusing as you oh
this is serious I think that that is
having one of them fleshy breakdowns
time for drastic measures
you think we should break into a song no
I think it's time we gave that bad guy
around but Scripture but what about the
party the potty you'll have to wait are
you thinking what I'm thinking
gentlemen happy hour happy hour happy
[Music]
the dark dark this is in half H this is
a pawn you pay a man to get the ghost
out of a house and what V do it gets the
gun and exactly
about time
look familiar
Oh
[Music]
your weight it was a mom Kenneth go
ahead Casper
it's perfect you think I can wear to the
party tonight
Casper
[Music]
I can bake my dad's get me the sled yeah
it's like a question would happen cuz I
know how to write it
and one morning I came down for
breakfast and there was just for me for
no reason at all it took it out on a
sledding all thing attached to that's
enough but I couldn't stop I was having
so much fun
got late got dart I got sick dad got sad
[Music]
what's it like to die like being born
lead backwards
to remember I didn't go we're all
supposed to go just be behind my dad
wouldn't be
is that your dad
McSpadden claimed that he was haunted by
the ghost of his dead son and that he
invented a machine to bring back to life
Lazarus
sorry I guess we'll have to take the
long way I got here
don't you know a shortcut
you guys Casper no wall human time flip
hold on why
[Music]
well what was that the up and Adam
machine
ident was a great adventure but that
looks all getting going in the morning
didn't he ever hear of caffeine my dad's
kind of a slob boys me down you need to
do everyone today no matter how busy
would drop everything to play pirates
with me today is very cold this step
onto your old so where's this Lazarus
friend you're looking at down there
that's useful know there's a way to get
it going
I just can't what about that dance dance
next of all wait Gazi this
[Music]
[Applause]
hmm
[Music]
what is it
careful it'll make the whole thing work
kind of insistence primordial soup mix
it's what brings goes back to life just
enough one
[Music]
pull the lever which one I don't know
try one
Kaspar none of you live
[Music]
oh man how am I going to do this
couldn't you get my easy-bake oven
towards
[Music]
[Applause]
it's just any ideas
yes no the riffin is scared of death
anymore
one minute should be a book next you're
back on your feet free to come and go as
you please
hell you could even fly through a thick
of steel let me get you ladies behind
like a treasure for example crack with
pop get back 11 on your way to the
Riviera if you were a ghost if you were
[Music]
won't hurt a bit
today you are entertainers way too
personally
[Music]
what a tragic waste so my favorite
sunglasses nah man the best back
[Music]
wardroom Harlan County Jail Christmases
the Ganges wick playoffs or game play
shooter hurts knock-knock perfect when
it's dr. hobby got a lot of spirit you
know and I'm saying yeah you got his
whole miserable life ahead so we could
do him a favor
put about a good misery hey good idea
we've been the ghostly trio long enough
time to make it huh what thing I just
say something here you get a little
personal I just have to tell you you
guys remind me of what it's like that
hang out with the boys
I mean you are absolutely there every
time I mean you look like right to face
you some ghost town you know what I'm
gonna tell it Miss critten good kind
good cut solutely you're not going
anywhere
it's your house you're haunting it
possession is nine-tenths of the law yes
yes
I didn't think so at first but you guys
are great I love you why I sweet i-i
can't-- broke him now all right the
night is young mm-hmm we are going to
clean out everybody Sally's got booze
until we lose it
[Music]
you mean my friend miss Crittenden in
the flesh
we're a couple of minutes dad what are
you doing just like to say helping you
remember now coming
[Music]
we're here oh okay hi come on in
this is the room three together you'll
be safe and I'll be ready
Hey
she wants a Halloween party she's gonna
get a hell party
[Music]
stay back
keep away from me yes sir don't come
near me you spiteful spook I'll knock
you into the next world come on hey
bobbin back it's my turn of the oven
dad yes this thing Duggan you blasted
little worm you aah
Kerrigan how kind of you to drop it
there's one thing I've learned from you
it's always kick them when they're down
and baby you're 6 feet under
oh what a shame sorry sweetheart we're
through I never forget this you
ungrateful lousy little worm you of all
you can horn me all you want but it's
going to be in a great big expensive
house with lovely purple wallpaper and
great big green carpets and a little dog
called Carrigan a [ __ ] just like you I
got the power I got the treasure and you
ever liked it
any other taking no but aren't you
forgetting something
what your unfinished business
my what you know unfinished business
I'll go have unfinished business that's
why they don't rustle unfinished it
I have no unfinished it I have my best
mine man I had every unjust perfect wait
wait I like I have a I am NOT ready to
cross over yet well yes
[Music]
my pleasure
a ball that's your treasure are you
kidding
it's our graph I Duke Snider the
Brooklyn Dodgers my favorite player
Casper no what have you got him men he's
just a little dead I'm free I've never
felt so good my life I can play okay
stinky work with him
yeah hey who's the girl daddy me Ted
check check check blue Jan atomic and
traffic per block 2
Oh where's flat alert don't you remember
yeah I remember
[Music]
Oh can't don't cry oh please come on dr.
Harvey you need this more than I do
castle this is the way it's gotta be
[Music]
Oh like the strangest dream I thought we
almost lost each other for a minute
there
your party starting without you
your gates probably waiting maybe we
should get going
where are we
go ahead what about you your party don't
do your thing
don't hang chill check it or whatever
you call I think you got a data
I hope
champagne
yeah wait any more passing at your head
oh my people are gonna freak
let me see cool thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
that's right
yes mom are you an angel that was a very
noble thing you did tonight Casper I
know cat will never forget it she needs
her father and I know yours will never
forget it either you fulfill his
greatest dream Casper and I know he is
very very proud of you and for what
you've done I'm giving you your dream in
return but just for tonight sort of a
Cinderella deal so I have until midnight
turn hey Cinderella got until midnight
and Arella wasn't 12 years old
every now and then we find special
friend who never lets us down who
understand it all reaches out each time
from you're the best friend that I've
done I know you can take the heart of
you will never it I'll make a wish for
ya and hope it will come true
the life will just become old man
if you lure your thanks back on
yesterday remember me this way remember
me
[Music]
until the I was a good dancer
Kaspar
[Music]
hello James
all right just me
Kadir 100 things to say let's just say
you know three crazy ghosts who kept
their word James I know you've been
searching for me but there's something
you have to understand you and cat loves
me so well when I was alive but I have
no unfinished business please don't let
me be yours
and paranthas cane cat is growing up
beautifully because of you no wonder I
miss you so much
a couple thing itself
don't think of the extension every time
she gets a phone call french fries are
not a breakfast food pencil and ask her
to wear a t-shirt under her bathing suit
my daughter is denatured
[Music]
wait
where I can watch over both of you until
we're together again
[Music]
[Applause]
huh
[Music]
you