Palmer figured out that we're
doing this with Seidel.
And unless
we drop the lawsuit,
he's going to come
after us for collusion.
If I pull out of that hearing,
Palmer can't touch us.
But I'm not doing anything until you
tell Nathan exactly what's going on.
There's nothing to tell.
You said you were doing this case
as a way to get into the Bar.
And I just
withdrew my application.
I knew Mike was a fraud
before he was arrested.
I leveraged it to get
my name on the wall.
I thought I knew
what kind of man you were.
How dare you say
that to me?
The first time we slept together,
you were with another man.
I don't want to spend
the rest of my life
with a man who gave up
on his dreams.
And I know that you don't
want to be that man either.
We have proof
of over a dozen instances
of you committing
corporate espionage.
What do you want?
You're going to
settle with those miners.
You're going to forget
you ever heard of us.
And you're going to honor your
original agreement with Craig Seidel.
I don't just want you
to set that hearing.
I want you to bulldoze
anyone who stands in my way.
What time is it?
Don't worry. You're
not late for work.
Here.
Thanks.
God, I could use this.
I got in pretty late
last night.
Does that have anything
to do with the flowers
I just found
in the kitchen?
Can't a guy just buy you
flowers because he loves you?
He can.
But he didn't.
You're right.
I bought them
to say thank you
for doing whatever it took
to make sure I got my shot
at getting into the Bar.
Wait, does that mean that...
Yeah.
We did it.
My hearing's tomorrow.
Seidel's on our side.
I can't believe it.
This could
really happen.
I know.
What is it?
I promised Oliver that I would
tell Nathan about the whole thing.
Mike, you can't do that.
I know I can't.
But I've got to get a couple
of days off for the hearing.
Which means I've got
to tell him something.
Louis. What are
you doing here?
I hope you don't mind
I stopped by.
I had to see you. I couldn't
sleep at all last night.
Neither could I.
Tara, please.
I know we had a fight.
But you told me you
wanted to get to know me.
And I swear, what I told you was
the worst thing I've ever done.
Louis, the thing I'm having
trouble dealing with
has nothing to do with
that person at your firm.
It has to do with how you
treated me last night.
Tara, please.
Let me finish.
You shared something
horrible with me,
gave me no time
to process it
and while
I was taking it in,
you not only attacked
my integrity,
you made me feel
ashamed of myself.
You are right. I lashed
out and I shouldn't have.
But I only did it because I was
afraid of you rejecting me.
And I will...
Tara, I will die
if you reject me.
That's the thing,
Louis.
You had a reason for
reacting the way you did.
But I'm not sure
I want to be with a man
who thinks there's ever a
reason to treat me that way.
Tara.
I'm sorry, Louis.
They're waiting for me
in the conference room.
I told you I'll call,
and I will call.
Nathan.
Mike, what's up?
Nothing. I just want
to give you this.
This is a check
for $50,000.
I know.
We settled.
I gave the miners
their checks last night.
Mike, this is the most
money we've ever made on a case.
For once, we're not going to
have to worry about making rent.
Yeah, right.
That's not a joke.
Wait, you're telling me
that $50,000
can really make that big a
difference to the clinic?
I'm telling you that I
know, in corporate law,
money doesn't matter
unless it's in the millions.
But here, $50,000 makes all
the difference in the world.
Well, in that case, Nathan,
I've been working here seven
days a week since I started
and I've got some personal stuff
that I need to take care of...
Stop right there.
Look. You just bought me
30 days' rent.
The least I can do
is give a few days back.
Right.
Thank you.
Okay,
let's hear it.
Hear what?
The joke you spent
all morning coming up with.
What joke?
I was just going to ask you
where the law library was,
but then I realized you've
never set foot in there.
Shouldn't you be at the
clinic saving whales?
First of all,
that's Greenpeace.
And second of all,
I took the day off
so I could prepare
for the character
and fitness committee.
Oh! That means
you're taking
whatever that hitch is
going to be seriously.
You know I am.
That's what
I like to hear,
because I don't want
somebody working here
who doesn't listen
to my advice.
Harvey, I still don't
think you understand.
When this thing is over,
I am not coming back here.
Mike.
I told you.
I want to do good.
Then do good here.
And I also told you
that the only reason
I agreed to this whole
thing in the first place
was because I couldn't stand to
watch someone like Oliver fail
and not be able
to help him.
And people like Oliver don't
work in places like this,
they work
in places like that.
And people like you shouldn't
be working anywhere.
What are you
doing here, Anita?
I'm here because
the US Attorney's office
requested that they be notified if
Mike Ross ever applied to the Bar.
What does the US Attorney's
office have to do with Mike?
Nothing.
Except I happen
to work there.
And as of one week ago,
I'm also the newest member of the
character and fitness committee.
Bullshit.
There's a whole process
to get on that committee.
There's no way you just
happened to be in the pipeline.
You're right.
I wasn't.
But when a member
takes leave,
he has the right
to appoint his replacement.
And Walter Samson
appointed me.
You think
I'm not going to find out
whatever bullshit you did
to get this guy to drop out?
Be my guest.
Because if Mike is going
before that hearing,
that means you did
something, too.
What do you want?
I want to tell you
you might as well
cancel this hearing
and save us all
a lot of time.
Because the vote
has to be unanimous.
And you are never
getting my vote.
See the money,
wanna stay for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
P® Krishna_Teja P®
Rachel,
whatever you're doing,
you need to put it down
and start looking
for every single instance
where a person
was admitted to the Bar
and the vote
wasn't unanimous.
Mike, what's going on?
Anita Gibbs got herself
onto the board.
Then what
we should be doing
is finding a way
to get her kicked off.
Harvey's working on it.
But in the meantime,
I need to know the ins
and outs of this committee.
Because while she's on it,
she's going to use every
dirty trick in the book
to end this thing
before it gets started.
Where are you going?
I'm going to go hole
myself up in the library
and start preparing answers to every
dirty question I can think of.
Louis,
are you okay?
I'm fine, Donna.
What can I do for you?
I know you know
Benjamin and I
have been working
on a business.
But I'm not sure
that you know
that we brought on Stu
as an investor.
I didn't, Donna. That's great.
It is.
But there's a problem and
I need your help with it.
Anything.
Benjamin applied
for a patent
and it turns out
that our technology overlaps
with someone else's.
How much overlap?
32.5%.
That's over the threshold.
Unless Benjamin can get you below 30...
He can't.
But Stu says
we can negotiate
with whoever holds
the patent,
get them to give us
an exclusion,
and we'll still be able to
move forward with The Donna.
Donna, this is exactly
what I need.
What do you mean?
Tara and I got
into a huge fight.
She's deciding right now
if we're going
to stay together.
This is exactly what I needed
to take my mind off it.
Louis, I don't mean
to sound insensitive,
but this is incredibly
important to me.
I know you.
And if this is
going to make you
go in there and blow
this thing up,
I can't have that.
Donna, listen to me.
I may be losing
the closest woman in my life.
But you are
the second closest.
I swear that I won't do
anything to harm your company.
Thank you.
Knock 'em dead.
When were you
going to tell me?
Tell you what?
That the prosecutor
that put Mike in prison
just got herself
put on that panel.
What?
That's right.
And I want to know why I heard
about it from her and not you.
I'll tell you why.
Because I didn't know.
But now that I do,
this thing is done.
The hell it is.
Are you crazy?
Anita Gibbs is a goddamn
assistant US attorney.
She gets one whiff of this
and we are both disbarred.
Which is why we're going to
make sure that doesn't happen
by getting her
kicked off that panel.
And how exactly are
we going to do that?
We're going to start
by you telling me
everything there is to
know about Walter Samson.
Well, then, we might as
well give up right now.
Because Walter Samson
is as clean as they come.
No one is that clean.
Well, this guy is.
And I didn't sign on...
Listen to me. You said
you were in on this.
And I'm telling you
right now, you still are.
Because we moved
heaven and earth
to get you out
of hot water,
and I got no problem
putting you right back in.
Fine.
But you better be careful.
Because if you're
looking at Gibbs,
she's going to be
looking at us.
And you coming to my lobby
in the middle of the day
is going to get us
all caught.
Gentlemen, thank you for meeting
with me on such short notice.
Our pleasure.
I assume you looked through
the documents I sent over
and found them
to your liking.
On the contrary, we found
them most disturbing.
In particular, the fact that you
used our fundamental principles
and worked up
from there.
What?
We'd never even seen
your fundamental principles
prior to applying
for that patent.
Can you prove that?
Of course
we can't prove that.
It's not possible
to prove a negative.
Words spoken by every hack who's ever
copied someone else's technology
and claimed it
as their own.
What's going on here?
I came to you to negotiate
an exclusion in good faith.
And we're prepared
to offer you...
We don't care what
you're prepared to offer.
And we didn't bring you here
to give you an exclusion.
We brought you here
to send a message.
This is a $90 million lawsuit against
your client if they go to market.
Gentlemen, please. I am not
saying we got here first.
But it's a 2.5% overlap,
and we are open to a 15%
revenue sharing arrangement.
And we're not open to shit.
Because we were here first.
Listen to me.
I am trying
to keep my cool.
We don't care if
you keep your cool or not,
because we've got you and there's
nothing you can do about it.
So you can take your offer
and shove it in a drawer
along with that sorry excuse
for a digital secretary,
because neither one of them is ever
going to see the light of day.
Oliver.
What are you doing...
Is it still on?
Is what still on?
Your deal.
To get into the Bar.
Oliver, listen to me.
Because when I asked
Nathan where you were,
he said you were taking a couple
days for personal reasons.
And all of
a sudden,
I got this pit in my stomach
that wouldn't go away.
So I decided
to ask you
if there's a reason
I got that pit
or if I'm just an asshole
for doubting you.
You're not
an asshole, Oliver.
God damn it, Mike.
You told me you didn't
have to tell Nathan
because there was
nothing to tell.
And when I told you that,
there wasn't.
But then my deal got
put back on the table...
Which means you could have
told him this morning.
But you didn't.
So now I have to.
Oliver. Hey, wait.
Please, hear me out.
I'm not going to
hear you out, Mike.
I was sitting here
for an hour,
hoping I was wrong
about you.
You weren't wrong
about me.
I care about people.
I want to help the clinic,
and the reason I didn't
tell Nathan what I did
is because I'm just waiting
until I can help him even more.
Help how?
BY being a shady lawyer?
By being someone who wouldn't
have lost Sofia Price her home.
I cannot believe
you just said that to me.
I said it
because it's true.
And you know it.
Look, I am going to tell
Nathan everything
as soon as
my hearing is over.
You have my word.
Why should I believe
the word of a liar?
Because of what I did for
those miners and the clinic.
And if that's not enough, how
about what I did for you?
You didn't do
shit for me.
But fine,
I won't tell Nathan.
Just so long as
when this thing's over,
you go back to your
corrupt corporate world.
Because I don't care
what you tell yourself,
you're never going
to belong in mine.
Harvey, what are you
still doing here?
The hearing's across town
in 10 minutes.
I'm not going to the hearing,
Donna, and neither are you.
Why not?
Because if you and I
can't do what we need to,
whatever Mike does at that
hearing isn't going to matter.
Give it to me.
We need to figure out what
Walter Samson's weak spot is.
Tell me how
and I'm all in.
Start by contacting
every person we know
and asking them what they
know about this asshole.
Because Gibbs has
something on him.
And if I can't find out what it is, then
I can't get her off that committee.
Where are you going?
To see someone who doesn't
know Samson at all.
Before we get started,
I'd like to point out these
interviews are normally for us
to quickly approve standard
applicants to the Bar.
However, Mr. Ross is
no standard applicant.
Therefore, we will convene
for as long as it takes
before ruling
on his application.
Now...
Mr. Chairman, if I may.
Last winter,
Mr. Ross pled guilty
to defrauding
the citizens of New York.
Therefore, I propose we reject
his application right now,
because Mr. Ross is a felon and the
New York Bar does not accept felons.
Mr. Chairman,
with all due respect
to the new board member,
you do.
Not only does
the Bar accept felons,
but years ago, this very
committee admitted Neal Wiesner,
a man who spent years in
prison for attempted murder.
Now, Ms. Gibbs may think my crime
is worse than attempted murder,
but I don't think it's worth
throwing away 140 years of precedent
by not even allowing me
to make my case.
Come on, let's go.
Come on.
Come on. Shit.
What the hell
are you doing?
What does it look
like I'm doing?
I'm watching my money
go down the toilet.
Well, it looks to me
like I paid you to do a job
and you're sitting here
doing this.
Okay, I'll let you in
on a little secret.
It only takes 15 minutes
to hack someone.
If you can't find something
in the next 45,
it means there's
nothing to find.
Bullshit. There's always
something to find.
I'm telling you
there isn't.
He doesn't drink, smoke,
gamble, cheat, nothing.
Listen to me.
I paid you good
money to do a job,
and if you don't put some
more effort into this,
I'm going to spread the word
that you aren't worth shit.
And this time, it won't be
coming from Louis Litt.
It will be coming
from me.
Then keep
your damn money.
When I tell you there's nothing
to find, there's nothing to find.
I guess
what I'm saying is,
not only do I admit
what I did,
but I regret it with
every fiber of my being,
and I'd like to apologize to my
clients, my former colleagues,
and finally, to the
fraternity of men and women
that I have wanted to be a
member of since I was a child.
Well, that was
a moving statement.
I just have one question.
If you regret
what you did so much,
why weren't you willing
to serve your full sentence?
I wasn't unwilling.
I was offered a deal
to help convict
a known criminal
and I took it.
You were offered a deal to get
out early and you took it.
I protected
an innocent man and...
What you did was insinuate yourself
into your roommate's life,
gain his trust, and
pretend to be his friend.
True or false?
You're taking it
out of context.
The context is
you portrayed yourself
as one thing, when really,
you were another,
which is what you did the entire time
you pretended to be an attorney,
and what I believe you are
doing to this body right now.
Mr. Chairman, if she's going to impugn
his character while he's speaking,
then he's entitled to let
someone else speak for him.
This
isn't a trial.
We don't allow
character witnesses here.
Actually, you do.
Article IV, 16A.
Applicants are
allowed a witness
as a rebuttal
for an accusation
leveled by
a committee member.
That article hasn't
been cited in 30 years.
Maybe that's because
no applicant
has ever had to stand
before the person
who put them away.
You make a point.
We'll pick this up first thing in
the morning with your witness.
Thank you.
Rachel, that was
exactly what I needed.
If you hadn't done that...
I know.
But right now, I'm more
concerned with the fact
that she's turning
them against you.
Which means even after
Harvey kicks her off,
Seidel's job is going
to be that much harder.
And we only have one shot at
having someone speak for me.
Mike, come on.
We've got to get back
to the office
and start going through
everyone it could be.
We'll make a list of pros
and cons and... Rachel.
I know who it is.
Julius.
Mike.
What are you doing here?
I was hoping
that we could talk.
Look, I'm sorry, man.
This is not a good time.
I just put the baby down
and the wife and I...
Please, it won't
take long.
I've got this
hearing tomorrow
for the character portion
of the Bar.
I wanted to ask
if you'd speak for me.
You mind if I ask, why me?
Because you're
the only one I know
who's qualified
to tell the board
that I was a different man when
I got out than when I went in.
No offense, Mike.
But the truth is
I'm not sure you are.
What do you mean?
I mean you said this
hearing is tomorrow,
but you're just now
coming to me.
Which means
something's going on.
What's going on is the
woman who put me away
managed to get herself
on the committee,
and now she's slamming
the door in my face.
And why would she do that?
Julius, I'm not...
Mike, how did you
even get a hearing?
What are you
talking about?
I applied
like everyone else.
No. You're not
You didn't go
to law school.
It doesn't matter. There's an
exception called Reading the Law.
You see?
Right there, Mike.
That sounds like the bullshit
artist I met in prison.
So you tell me right now.
Did you pull some shit
to make this happen?
Damn, Mike.
If you can't be
straight with me,
this conversation
ends right here.
Yes. I did.
Ah...
Finally,
some truth in the night.
Julius, I work at a law
clinic, but not as a lawyer.
An opportunity
presented itself for me
to become one
and I turned it down.
But then, I had to sit
there and watch a woman
get put on the street
because I couldn't
help her.
And I knew that I'd have
to watch that happen
over and over
and over.
So, when that opportunity presented
itself for the second time, I took it.
Because I knew it would
never come along again.
You don't know that, Mike.
I do know that.
So you can say no
if you want to,
but don't say
I haven't changed.
Because the Mike you met
that night in prison
never would have told you
the truth just now.
Julius, please.
I need this.
This is the address.
It's tomorrow at 9:00.
I don't have anyone else.
Mike, hey.
Harvey, tell me
you've got some good news.
I do.
I took care of Seidel.
He's still going
to back you.
I'm not talking
about Seidel.
I'm talking about getting
Gibbs off that committee.
It's not that simple.
What's not that
simple about it?
I haven't found
anything on him yet.
Harvey, I am struggling
to get someone on my side.
And every second
that she is on that committee,
she is turning
people against me.
I need your help.
Mike.
I told you I'd get it done.
I'll get it done.
Anything?
No.
It's the same as when
you called an hour ago.
If he killed somebody and hid the
body, nobody knows where it is.
Then why don't you tell me
who's next on the list?
Harvey, I have been
at this all day.
And you said we don't
have much time.
Why don't you
just bluff the guy
into giving you
whatever you need?
Because we've only
got one shot at this.
The more information I have, the better
chance a bluff is going to work.
Harvey, what's going on?
It isn't like you to stay
in and make phone calls
instead of confronting
someone face-to-face.
What if I can't do it and Mike
doesn't get into the Bar?
How can you say that?
You are the best poker
player I have ever seen.
You can do it.
I don't think
you understand, Donna.
A bluff only works
if he's dirty.
What if the guy
really is clean?
Harvey, Gibbs got him off the committee.
He's not clean.
Now, enough is enough.
Go do what you do.
Louis, you mind
telling me what this is?
Where did you get that?
That is a lawsuit against
Donna's new business.
I know what it is.
Well, why haven't you
told her about it yet?
Because she's going to
think that I blew it
because I was upset
about Tara.
Louis, did you go full-blown
you on some poor bastard
and ruin Donna's
chance at success?
Gretchen, I went there
in good faith
to get a settlement,
and I was ambushed.
I swear.
Then you need
to fix it.
I can't.
Why not?
Because I cannot stop
thinking about Tara.
We got into a huge fight.
And I was such an asshole.
So I went to apologize.
She said she wasn't sure
she could stay with me
and I haven't
heard from her since.
So now, instead of not
knowing how to fix things
with one woman
in my life,
I don't know how to
fix things with the other.
Louis, I was married
a long time.
And I'll tell you, Carl
and I had some doozies.
Tell you the truth,
I wasn't always sure
we were going
to pull through.
But we always did, because
we loved each other.
What if she
doesn't love me anymore?
It doesn't turn off
like that, Louis.
And from where I'm standing,
you're worth loving.
Now, do you think
you can fix this thing
or do you need me
to get us some help?
I don't need any help.
I'm going to blow those guys
out of the water.
Walter Samson?
Yes?
I saw you out there.
First time playing?
I'm sorry,
do I know you?
The question is, "How do
you know Anita Gibbs?"
Because you gave her your seat on
the character and fitness committee
and the woman who prosecuted Mike
Ross has no business being there.
And who is Mike Ross?
I get it.
We're going that way, huh?
He's the reason Gibbs strong-armed
you into giving up that seat.
I gave up that seat
because I wanted to
spend more time
with my family.
Bullshit.
She found out whatever dirty
little secret you're hiding.
If you don't come
clean with me,
I'm going to find out what it is
and I'm going to squeeze harder.
I don't know who you are,
but it must be nice
living in a world
where everyone has a weak
spot and is unethical.
But in this case,
I took a leave of absence
and I replaced myself
with a worthy attorney.
So you can look for a
pressure point all you want,
but I'm sorry
to inform you
you're not going
to find one.
You want to know who I am?
My name is Harvey Specter.
And you can say you never
heard of Mike Ross,
but I know you heard of me.
So maybe
she didn't blackmail you.
Maybe she promised
to do something for you.
Either way, I'm going
to find out what it is,
and you're going to wish
you told me right now.
You think you're
showing strength,
but intimidation
is only weakness.
And for your information,
I never met Anita Gibbs
until the day I appointed her
as my replacement.
When I first met
Mike Ross,
I thought he was like every
other criminal I work with.
An entitled fraud who spent
his life cutting corners.
But I'm here
to tell you,
he went into prison one man
and he walked out another.
And in my professional
opinion,
he has the integrity
to serve his community
as a lawyer.
While I don't doubt
your sincerity, Mr. Rowe,
just because he was
able to fool you
doesn't mean he's going to
be able to fool this board.
It's Dr. Rowe.
And I'm glad you were the one
who responded to my statement.
And why is that?
Because you tried to paint a
false picture of his release
and I'm here to set
the record straight.
The record is straight.
And you're not qualified to talk
about the deal that he made.
No. We're going
to hear this.
Thank you.
It's true Mr. Ross entered into
an early release agreement,
but it's also true
that he stayed in longer
than he had to,
to keep his cellmate safe.
And while he was there,
he risked his own life
to prevent a violent man
from falsely
obtaining parole.
And for all we know, he did
that for self-serving reasons.
And for all I know, that's
what you're doing right now.
You're out of line.
I'm not the one
under examination here.
Neither am I.
I'm a prison psychologist.
And in my experience,
self-serving men do not risk
their lives to help people.
I don't call defrauding your
fellow man helping people.
And I certainly don't
call it having integrity.
With all due respect, ma'am, I'm
done wasting my breath on you,
because the purpose
of this hearing
was to determine if
Mike Ross had reformed.
But you don't seem
to be interested in that,
because you've already
made your mind up.
Maybe I have.
Then maybe you shouldn't
be on this committee,
because as I said, in my
professional opinion,
the world could use
a lawyer like Mike Ross.
And if you're looking
for my personal opinion,
he has more integrity
in his little finger
than you have
in your whole body.
Harvey, where
have you been?
I've been trying to
level the playing field.
That's the thing.
We just did.
You should have seen
Julius up there.
I mean, if those
members vote no
after hearing
what he had to say...
It doesn't matter
what he had to say.
You haven't found a way to get
Gibbs off that committee.
No.
I'm sorry, Mike.
You don't have to
be sorry, Harvey.
She warned us that she'd never
let me get into the Bar.
We just didn't listen.
Listen to me.
This vote isn't
until tomorrow morning.
There's still time for us
to think of something.
Yeah, you keep trying,
Harvey.
I've got something else
I need to take care of.
What's going on?
Gretchen said you wanted to
talk to me about the patent.
What are you guys
doing here?
I went back
to them, Donna.
And the reason I asked Stu
and Benjamin to be here was
so that you'd know
that I didn't shit the bed.
Are you telling me you couldn't
get them to back off the lawsuit?
He's telling you we won't be
able to patent The Donna at all.
What?
Donna, they weren't authorized
to let us partner with them.
That's what I sent you over
there to take care of.
I know.
And then they said they would fight
us to the ends of the earth.
Sol pulled out
every trick in the book
and I got them
to make you an offer.
An offer sounds
like a buy-out.
That's because
it is a buy-out.
With a special provision
that allows us
to produce The Donna
for in-house use.
That's not good enough.
Donna, we're talking
about a lot of money.
I don't care
about the money, Stu.
I care that Louis
didn't fight for me.
I did fight for you,
Donna. I swear.
They've got us
dead to rights.
There's nothing more
I can do.
Bullshit. Louis Litt does
not roll over for anybody.
He didn't
roll over, Donna.
I went over it
with Benjamin,
and we can't get
the overlap under 30%
I also ran it
by my own attorney
and he was shocked at what
Louis was able to get us.
So you're telling me
you want to take it.
We do.
But The Donna
wouldn't even exist
without you,
and we're partners.
So, if you don't want to,
then we won't.
I'm going to need
to think about it.
What's that?
Liberty Rail.
I tried to give it
to you once before.
You wouldn't take it.
You said it should
come without strings.
Well, here it is.
No strings.
It's still got strings
and you know it.
You want me to let
Mike in the Bar.
I do.
But I'm giving you this
whether you do that or not.
And why would you do that?
Because I'm hoping if I
showed you I could change,
maybe you'd believe
he could, too.
You for him.
What?
Tomorrow morning,
I'm going to ask Mike
if anyone knew
he was a fraud
while he was at
Pearson Specter.
He admits you knew,
I'll let him in the Bar.
I do that,
they'll kick me out.
That's what
"you for him" means.
You said you'd do it
for him once.
This is your chance to put your
money where your mouth is.
He won't go for it.
He wants to be a lawyer
so bad he can taste it.
You can make him
go for it.
Just remember,
you didn't like
being too late last time.
You're not too late
this time.
Good. You're both here.
Thanks for staying.
Of course we stayed. Your
message said it was urgent.
What's going on? Is there a
problem with the settlement?
No.
But I gave Oliver my word that
I would tell you the truth.
So, I'm here
to tell you the truth.
The truth
about what?
I made a deal.
A quid pro quo that we would
handle the miners' case
in exchange for the chance
to be admitted to the Bar.
Are you goddamn
kidding me?
I asked you point blank
if something was going on
and you lied to my face?
Nathan, I'm sorry.
But I didn't want to tell you until
there was something to tell.
You weren't going to tell me
until you got away with it.
No. I wasn't.
But as it turns out, I'm not
going to get away with it.
And I'm telling you anyway.
You're fired.
Nathan, please.
I don't give a shit what's about
to come out of your mouth.
Clean out your office and never
show your face around here again.
Wait. Don't do it.
Did you hear
what he said?
He lied.
Not once, not twice...
I don't care,
because we need him.
We don't need him.
Sofia needed him and she got
me, and look what happened.
Yeah, Nathan, that was
some shady shit he pulled.
But you've got to be blind if you
can't see that he actually cares.
And I don't remember us beating
down a place like Velocity Data
before he got here.
So, if it's all the same to
you, I'd like him to stay.
Well, it's not all the
same to me, Oliver.
It's up to me.
Not to the person that kept it
from me as much as Mike did.
He didn't keep it
from you, Nathan.
He said that if I didn't
tell you, he would.
So here I am.
And I know that I don't
have a leg to stand on,
but I'd like to stay.
Monday morning, you better start
putting your money where your mouth is
and find us
another $50,000 case.
Louis,
do you have a minute?
Sure, Harvey.
I don't know how
much you know about
what's going on
with Mike's hearing.
Enough to know that look on your
face means it's not going well.
It's not.
And I may have
a way to change it,
but I wanted to run it
by my partner first,
because it may mean that
I need a little time off.
What do you mean,
a little time off?
I mean Gibbs
offered me a deal.
Mike goes on record admitting
I knew he was a fraud,
she'll vote to
let him in the Bar.
Are you insane?
You do that, it won't
be a little time off.
You'll get disbarred.
And by then,
he'll be a lawyer,
and we can argue that he said
that just to appease Gibbs.
Bullshit.
You do this, two out of three
names on that wall will be gone,
and I won't be able to
keep this firm going.
And if you can't, we'll have done
it for Mike. Zane will hire you.
I don't want
to go to Zane's.
I want to do what we said
we were going to do
and rebuild this
place together.
Louis, I owe him.
Well, what about what you owe me?
You said we were partners.
We are partners, which is why
I came to you with this.
No.
You didn't come
to ask my permission,
you came to tell me that
you were going to do this.
And what if I did?
Then you're not just an
asshole, you're an idiot.
Because there's
no way Mike Ross
ever agrees to
trading you for him.
Well, I'll make him agree.
No, you won't.
Mike.
Harvey, whatever deal she's offering
you, I'm not going to take it.
You don't even
know what it is.
I don't care
what it is.
I'm not getting into the Bar if
it means getting you kicked out.
Mike, she wants me.
She always has.
No, Harvey.
She wants both of us.
And she's not going to stop
until she gets both of us.
You don't know that.
Yes, I do.
And if you
don't get that,
then she's got you
right where she wants you.
So you're just going
to sit there tomorrow
and let her take
everything away from you?
She's not
taking anything away.
She's keeping things
exactly the way they are.
You mean working
for that clinic.
Harvey, I'm lucky to still
have a job at that clinic.
So tomorrow morning,
I'm going to go in there
with my head held high.
But what I'm not going to do is let her
strip you of everything that you are.
Harvey, he's right.
Let it go.
Whatever it is, Donna...
Harvey, I know you're in
a rough place right now.
But whatever's going to happen
with Mike is going to happen.
You've done
everything you can.
And I'm tired of
putting my wants on hold.
What is it?
You know about my product
with Benjamin.
I do.
Well, it turns out
we have a 32.5% overlap
on our software
with another company's.
They refused to budge,
and Louis said he pulled out every
trick in the book to get us this.
Can you get it under 30%? No.
Then take the money.
I don't want the money.
Donna.
I want something more.
And I've never
said that out loud.
But I can't pretend
that's not true anymore.
What do you mean, "more"?
I don't know.
I guess I'm going to
have to figure that out.
Good night, Harvey.
I'll see you tomorrow
at the hearing.
Mr. Ross, we are prepared to
hear your final statement.
Before we do, I have
one last question.
Mr. Ross, you say you're a changed
man and you care about the truth,
but I want to know if you're
capable of telling the truth.
So I'm going to
ask you a question
and I suggest that you consider
your answer very carefully,
because as far
as I'm concerned,
your answer will determine whether
or not you become a lawyer.
During your time at
Pearson Specter Litt,
did anyone there have knowledge of
the fact that you were a fraud?
Mr. Ross.
Did anyone else know?
I knew.
And if you're looking for a
scalp, you can have mine.
But I was under the
impression that this hearing
was not about
my old firm,
but whether or not Mr.
Ross should be a lawyer.
I say he should.
It doesn't
matter what you say.
He's already had
someone testify for him.
I'm not here
to talk about him.
I'm here to talk
about someone else.
Someone else has
nothing to do with...
I'd like to
hear this.
Fifteen years ago,
a young woman was arrested for illegally
obtaining prescription drugs.
Turns out she had
chronic pain
and didn't want to drop out
of med school,
possibly never to return.
So, she stole a couple
of prescription pads
from the hospital
where she was interning.
A crime with a mandatory
sentence of seven years.
But instead of throwing
the book at her,
the prosecuting attorney
showed mercy,
had the charges knocked
down to a misdemeanor,
recommended probation,
and sealed the records.
That's a touching story,
but I don't see
what a random attorney
has to do with
these proceedings.
She's not talking about a random attorney.
She's talking about me.
But just because
I showed compassion once
doesn't mean
he deserves it now.
Maybe he doesn't.
But that young woman
is now an ER doctor.
She saves lives.
And the world is a better
place because you saved hers.
Thank you, Ms. Pearson.
Mr. Ross?
I don't think I can add
anything to that.
I've made my case.
I leave the choice to you.
Then this hearing
has concluded.
We will deliberate
and let you know
our decision
by day's end.
Thank you.
So, what do we do now?
They said they would let us
know by the end of the day.
So we wait.
Well, it is the end of
the day, which means...
It doesn't
mean anything, Louis.
Whatever is going on in there,
Seidel's going to fight like hell...
It's not going to
make a difference.
She's never going
to change her mind.
I think she will.
What do you mean?
I mean that story
wasn't any old story
and that woman
wasn't really a woman.
It was a man
named Joseph O'Neal.
And it was
Walter Samson's godson.
So she did call in
a favor.
Yes, she did.
Then we need to get her
kicked off that board.
No, Harvey.
We don't.
Because I didn't fly all the way
down here to strong-arm that woman.
And I know the story of
The Wind and The Sun.
What the hell
are you talking about?
She's talking
about Aesop's fable,
which basically says that if you
want a man to take off his coat,
you don't blow it off.
You make him feel warm and
he'll take it off on his own.
That's not a strategy,
it's a prayer.
Louis, I already admitted
that I knew about Mike
and I reminded her
of her own compassion.
That's the best
we're going to do.
You know they could
disbar you for that.
In New York,
they might.
In Chicago,
nobody's going to care.
Thank you, Jessica.
Don't thank me.
Thank Harvey.
He's
the one that called me.
It's Seidel.
Hello.
I'll tell him.
Thanks for calling.
You're in.
Oh, my God.
It happened.
I'm going to go
get us some champagne.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for flying in.
I wouldn't miss this
for the world.
Hey.
You said you had to go to the
bathroom a half hour ago.
But you never came back
for your champagne.
I know.
Louis, what's wrong?
You never asked me
how it went with Tara
and telling her
about Mike.
I'm so sorry.
I just got caught up
with the hearing.
The thing is, I...
I told her.
We got into
a huge fight.
And she said she
needed to think about
whether or not she
could forgive me.
And?
She just called when Harvey was
giving us the news about Mike.
Left a 15-second
voicemail.
I'm afraid
to listen to it.
Louis.
She's either
going to tell me
that she never wants
to see me again
or that she wants
to make up.
Do you want me
to listen for you?
No.
But I'd like it if you
stay with me while I do.
Of course.
Okay.
What's that?
I wanted to
give you a present.
Your first year's
salary in advance.
Welcome back.
Harvey, I'm running
out of ways to tell you
I don't want to be
a corporate lawyer.
Before you answer, you might want
to take a look at this check.
You trying to bribe me?
I'm trying to close you.
I told you.
Yeah, I get it.
You want to do good.
Well, do you
really want to do good?
Donate half of this
to the clinic.
You'll fund
the place for a year.
Oh, so that's what
you think I'm all about.
Just giving money.
No, but I think you're about more
than just working at that place.
And you know it.
What are you
talking about?
I'm offering you a deal.
One for you,
one for me.
You can save the spotted owls,
stop global warming,
and help as many damsels
in distress as you'd like.
And the good news is you'll
be doing it from here.
What makes you think
I'd take you up on that?
Because here's
the thing, Mike.
You want to be here
and you know it.
That's not true.
Uh-uh.
I saw the look on your face
when you strong-armed Palmer
and you took on Seidel and
every other talented attorney
you've beaten
over the years.
And I've told you
this once before.
This is
the major leagues.
You don't get this
feeling anywhere else.
And I'm offering you
the best of both.
Why are you giving
me a peace sign?
Double it.
What?
I don't want to just fund the clinic
for a year. I want to fund it for two.
And while we're at it,
I want some leftover for a little
something nice for me and the wife-to-be.
That's all it's
going to take.
Oh, not even close.
I wouldn't have it
any other way.
Any case I want to bring
the clinic onto, I can.
Done.
Anyone I want to bring over
from the clinic, I can.
Louis doesn't get a say, you don't
get a say, no Harvard rule.
Done.
And there's
one more thing,
and you are not
going to like it.
You are not
getting my office.
Oh, yes, I am.
And I will tell you why.
Why?
Because she's gone, Harvey.
And she's not
coming back.
It's time for you
to take the reins.
^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
P® Krishna_Teja P®