This is an offer letter.
We need you.
I just got out of prison.
I'm not trying to go back.
You're not going back. Your
title's gonna be "consultant."
You don't have to
do this for me.
Do me a favor.
Just think about it.
Your last LSAT score
was significantly
higher than your
previous ones.
I studied incredibly
hard the last time.
Did you study hard? Or did your
fiancé study hard for you?
I'm pregnant.
This has to be some kind of record...
Louis.
It's his.
You make
impulsive decisions
and you go back on them
all the time.
This is different.
How?
Because it's a baby!
You want to merge?
Jessica, you got
knocked down the mountain.
Without help, you're not going
to be able to get back up.
I've had my name first
for too long.
I can't go back
to having it last.
Tara Messer,
will you marry me?
Yes, Louis, I'll marry you.
You can’t just
throw this all away
after we gave
everything to save it.
No one's saying you have to
give up the firm, Louis.
You just
have to let me go.
You sure about this?
I'm not sure
about anything.
And it scares
the shit out of me.
You going to be okay?
She was my mentor.
But, yeah,
I'm going to be okay.
Hey. If it's going to be
much longer,
I can just get some
on the way.
Hold your horses, mister.
That was the best
cup of coffee I've ever had.
I told you
it was worth the wait.
That was nice.
It was.
And as much as I'd like to
spend all day doing it,
we should get going.
Just do me a favor...
Harvey,
I don't think
you understand.
I told you,
once this happened again,
I don't work
for you any more.
Donna, you can't leave me.
I'm not leaving you, Harvey.
I just don't work for you.
That's leaving me.
No, Harvey.
That's not leaving you.
Jessica left you.
And you need to get it
through your head.
She's never coming back.
What are
you thinking about?
I'm just thinking
about names.
I always wanted
a boy named Cooper
and a girl named Lucy.
Louis, I appreciate you
thinking about this, but...
I know,
I'm not the father.
It's just that, if I'm
gonna help raise him,
I'd like to
give him something.
It doesn't matter.
Because whatever
his first name
ends up being,
you're going to be the one
who gave him his last name.
Louis, I'm gonna be a Litt.
Which means our children
are going to be Litts.
You really mean that?
Of course I do.
Tara, I've got to get going.
What... What's wrong?
Oh, nothing's wrong.
Jessica left last night,
which means Harvey and I got to
figure out what we're going to do.
Dad, what are you
doing here?
I know
I'm a little early, but...
I came to bring you
a graduation present.
What?
This is a job offer.
Not just any job offer.
An associate
at Rand Kaldor Zane.
I already have a job
when I graduate.
Rachel, we talked
about this.
When you graduate, you're going
to have to stand before the Bar
and pass the character
and fitness test.
And you think
working at your firm
looks better
than working at mine.
Yes, I do.
Dad. I...
Rachel, I understood
when you wanted
to work there
when Jessica
was still there.
But now that she's gone,
that firm is going to turn
upside down.
And I don't want you there
when it does.
Dad, you are my family, and I
would do anything for you.
But Pearson Specter Litt
is my work family
and they've always
been there for me.
I'm not going to leave them
when they need me the most.
But just remember,
as long as
I'm running my firm,
the offer
will always be there.
Mike, what are you
doing here?
Can I come in?
Of course.
You want
a cup of coffee?
Yeah. That would be good.
Look, I wanna talk to you
about your offer.
You thought about it.
I did.
Good.
Don't tell me you're here to renegotiate
the terms. I'm not taking it.
Mike...
Just listen to me.
When I was on trial, I said
that I was given a gift
and I threw it away.
Well, I wasn't just trying to
bullshit the jury-I meant that.
And as easy as it would be
for me to just come back
and pick up
right where we left off,
I can't look myself
in the mirror
if all I'm doing is going
back to corporate law.
Why don't you just
come back for a month?
What are you
talking about?
Well, it's easier to find
a job when you have one.
Come back,
pad your resume
while you look
for something else.
Come on, Harvey. If I
come back for one month,
it'll be two months.
Then six months.
The next thing I know,
I won't have helped a
single person in ten years.
That's not true.
You'll have helped me.
That's not what I meant
and you know it.
I don't care
what you meant.
Jessica left last night.
I know you know that.
I just need somebody I can trust
until we figure things out.
Harvey, I'm not doing this.
God damn it, you stood
in front of me once
begging me to hire you
and I did.
And now, I'm asking you
to do the same thing
and you're telling me
to go screw myself.
That's not what I'm doing
and you know it.
Mike, I need this.
I'm sorry, Harvey.
I... I can't.
I just can't.
See the money,
wanna stay for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
P® Krishna_Teja P®
Harvey, where you been?
We need to talk.
Louis, if you're here
to tell me
our bank account is empty
and we're on our knees,
then I need to have this
conversation some other time.
Well, you're in luck. Because I'm
here to tell you the opposite.
What?
I've been here since 6:00,
going through the books.
You're never going to
believe this,
but between not having
to pay any of the partners,
signing a few new clients
and subletting our space,
we're actually flush
with cash.
Are you kidding me?
Take a look.
Finally, some good news.
Now if it's not
too much to ask,
can we go back to your office
and work on a game plan?
No, Louis, it's not
too much to ask.
Uh, we don't open
for another 15 minutes.
But if you've got a
delivery, I can take it.
Oh, I appreciate that.
But I'm...
I'm not here
to deliver anything.
I'm here for a job.
Not a lot of lawyers
show up to work on a bike.
I'm not like
a lot of lawyers.
To tell you the truth,
I'm not like
any other lawyer.
I like you.
If it's up to me,
you'd be starting today.
But what I can do is let
you go on in there.
So you'd be the first person
they see when they get in.
Thanks.
Hey, what's your name?
Darryl.
Mike.
Good luck in there, Mike.
I think the first thing
we should do
is send a message
that we're back
by hiring a new class
of associates.
Yeah, I love the idea
of sending a message,
but I'm not ready to talk about
hiring associates right now.
Why not?
Because I'm not.
In that case, maybe you're
ready to talk about a merger.
Robert, what are you
doing here?
Jessica didn't tell you?
Before she left,
I offered her a lifeline.
And now, I'm going to offer
the same thing to you.
We appreciate
your offer, but...
But what? But we don't
need your charity.
Yes, you do.
You were struggling
before she left.
And at noon today, the whole
world is going to know
that you suffered
another blow.
The only thing
the world's going to know
is Jessica had such
confidence in our abilities
that she decided to move on to
another phase of her career.
I don't care
how you want to spin it.
Even if you manage to
keep your clients,
you've got a boulder headed
your way and you know it.
What are you
talking about?
Which one of you two is going to
take Jessica's seat at the table?
Because you can only avoid
that question for so long.
And my money says that the
second I leave this room,
you two are gonna
fight to the death.
And what's left of this firm
is gonna be ripped apart.
So, come see me
when that reality sets in.
You were right.
We should hire
a new class of associates.
What, are you kidding me?
You're gonna ignore that
gauntlet he just threw down?
He wasn't throwing down
a gauntlet, Louis.
He was trying to capitalize
on an opportunity.
Bullshit, he challenged
our leadership.
And if we don't
get it together right now,
he's gonna tell
the entire city
that we can't even agree
on who's in charge.
Louis, Jessica's flight
hasn't even touched down yet.
I'm not going to get in a
pissing contest with you
over who should run
the firm.
I knew it. You don't think I
should be the one in charge.
What I think is you were here at 6:00 a.m.
looking at the books,
figuring out a game plan that
I wasn't ready to implement.
And now, I am.
So, instead of
picking a fight with me
that I'm not
in the mood to have,
why don't you do what you
said you were going to
and hire a new class
of associates?
Hey. Oliver.
Oh. Uh, Mike.
Mike. Sorry to keep you waiting.
What can I do for you?
I'd like to apply
for a job.
That's great. We are definitely
short-handed right now.
Are you a lawyer?
Not exactly.
Okay.
I mean, no.
I'm... I'm not.
That's all right. We need
help across the board.
Do you have
any legal experience?
A lot, actually.
It's a long story.
Well, I look forward
to hearing it
after you fill this out.
Great. Um, do you want me
to take it home with me or...
It's only two pages. Why don't you
do it here and get it back to me?
I'm just
right back there.
There's about a dozen miniature
Deadpools on my desk.
Don’t judge. It's a great
movie and you know it.
I do know it.
I saw it three times.
You bullshitting me?
Of course I am.
I want to work here.
Get it back to me.
I'll take care of you.
Thanks, Oliver.
Anytime, Mike.
You wanna talk about it?
Talk about what?
You saw Mike this
morning, didn't you?
How did you know?
Because instead of
telling Louis
that you need to be
managing partner
because you know
he can't handle it,
you avoided the conflict
because you already
had one this morning.
He turned me down because he
wants to do good in the world.
Good for him. No, Donna.
Not good for him.
Jessica left, I need him, and
he's hanging me out to dry.
He's not hanging
anyone out to dry.
And in case you forgot,
he went to prison.
So, he's probably trying to
figure out a way to make up
for what put him there
in the first place.
That's my point, Donna.
He's a convicted criminal.
I don't care if he tries
Mother Teresa.
Any place he goes isn't going
to give him the time of day,
which means he's not going to
be able to do good for anyone.
Then maybe
instead of telling me
why he'll never be able to
accomplish his dream,
you should be figuring out
a way to help him do it.
What are you
doing here, Gretchen?
I heard you were looking for
a new class of associates.
So, I went ahead
and contacted
every top law school
in the country.
These are the resumes
of the best 100 candidates.
Throw them away.
What?
Louis, you're not telling
me you're still going
with that Harvard-only
bullshit, are you?
I'm saying instead of picking
fresh fruit off the vine,
I'm gonna steal some ripe bananas
right out of the grocery store.
The question is, whose grocery store
are you planning on knocking over?
It's Robert Zane.
And before you try to
talk me out of it,
he just said that I'm not fit
to lead right to my face.
Then give me a gun
and point me up the hill.
Because if he's coming after
you, he's coming at me.
And I got your back.
You convince
Simms Chemical
they had no proprietary right
to your client's patent?
Not only that, I got them to
pay for half the research.
It's good
to see you, Louis.
It's good to
see you too, Katrina.
Listen, if you came here to make
sure that I kept my word...
Oh, Katrina,
that was a long time ago.
I'm here because I
want you to come home.
Back to the firm?
Yes.
Back where you belong.
Louis, I can't do that.
Yes, you can.
And not only that, you can
get the ten best associates
from Robert Zane's stable
to come with you.
Louis, assuming I agreed
to do that,
what makes you think
I could even convince
the ten worst associates
to come with me?
This does.
What is this?
It's the class list of Rand
Kaldor Zane associates
in the last 20 years.
Back then,
six of 10 made partner.
Ten years ago, it was down to three.
The class of '09...
Don't tell me. Zero.
Look it up.
None of you are ever
going to make partner
because there is no room
at the top.
And what's in this for me?
You make this happen
by the end of the week,
I'll make sure that you are the youngest
senior partner we have ever had.
Michael.
What are you...
What are you doing here?
It's a long story,
but I, uh...
I ended up
getting out early.
I'm glad.
Uh, what's on your mind?
I've been out
job hunting all day.
Nice.
What kind of work?
Uh, legal clinics.
I want to find a way
to give back.
Well, you didn't come here
just to tell me that.
I came to tell you that every
application I filled out today
asked if I was
a convicted felon.
Michael,
please tell me
that you're not thinking
about lying again.
No, I'm not. I just
don't know what to do.
You know, I know that none of
these places are gonna hire me
after seeing
I checked that box.
You don't know that, Michael.
It's the first day.
I know I saw 30 different
looks on 30 different faces
and they all said
the same thing.
Well, what if I told you
I know a place
where they won't
give you that look?
Are you offering me
a teaching job?
Yeah. I am.
And a legal clinic isn't
the only way to give back.
Father, I'm not sure
if you heard me.
I'm a convicted felon.
Michael, you... You came from here.
And if we can't offer
redemption to one of our own,
then what kind of church
are we?
I don't know, Father.
Father Conroy's going
on vacation for two weeks.
Just take his classes.
See what it's like.
The worst thing is you'll realize
that this isn't right for you.
Dean Herrick?
Is this a good time?
Of course.
Have a seat, Rachel.
What's on your mind?
I wanted to know what you
think my chances are
of passing the character and
fitness portion of the Bar?
Why are you coming to me
with this?
Because you questioned my
integrity once before and I...
I want to know
did you mean it
or were you just helping
Anita Gibbs?
You want the truth?
That's why I'm here.
Then my answer is if I were
on the ethics committee,
I don't know whether
I'd pass you or not.
Because the fact is,
you're engaged to a man
who pretended
to be a lawyer.
And I find
it hard to believe
that you didn't know
about it the whole time.
And since then,
he's paid his dues.
And what about you?
What about me?
Do you think the committee
would have me break up
with the man that I love just
because he went to prison?
What does that say about
character and fitness?
You make a good point.
And if I were you, I'd be
prepared with some others.
Because I'd say
one day soon,
you're going to
have to make your case.
And do you think I have a
better chance of making my case
if I work for my father instead
of at Pearson Specter Litt?
Yes, I do.
Hey.
You look like that famous
professor, Henry Gerard,
but there's no way that guy's
still teaching at his age.
I don't think
you could ever call
what that clown did
"teaching."
He had his moments.
Good to see you, Harvey.
I'd ask you to join me
for dinner,
but I'm pretty sure that that's
not what you came here for.
Mike Ross
got out of prison.
As far as I'm concerned,
there's no reason
he shouldn't be able to
practice law again.
I don't disagree.
But technically, he didn't
practice it in the first place.
Well, that's exactly
why I'm here.
If Mike's gonna have
a chance to pass
the character portion
of the Bar,
he's gonna need someone like
you to testify on his behalf.
Someone like me, or me?
I didn't fly all the way up
here for someone like you.
Harvey, I'd love to help.
But you know
as well as I do,
I'm not the one
you should be coming to.
You're exactly who
I should be coming to.
It's the New York Bar.
I'm a Massachusetts professor.
Henry, please.
Harvey.
Even if I did
what you're asking,
I'm not the one that's going
to make the difference.
Then who is?
You know who is.
You're just afraid
to go and see them.
Hey. What's going on?
What do you think?
Blue or this maroon one?
You got a job in one day?
Yeah, I wouldn't be
trying on ties if I didn't.
Mike, that's amazing.
I knew people would see
the real you.
Wait, don't tell me. The
clinic in Morningside Heights.
Actually, uh,
the church in Queens.
What?
Father Walker offered me a
teaching position at St. Andrews
and I said yes.
So, you're gonna be
a teacher.
Why?
You think it's a bad idea?
No. No. I just...
I thought that you wanted to
stay connected to the law.
I do.
But none of those places are
ever going to call me back.
You don't know that because
it's only been one day.
Rachel, it's time for me
to accept the truth.
I am a convicted felon.
I am never gonna be able
to practice law again.
At least this way, I'll
be able to do some good.
Then I'm glad.
Because you are going to
make a great teacher.
Hey, everyone.
Good morning.
As most of you are aware, Father
Conroy is on a well-deserved vacation.
I should know.
I don't think he's had one since
I had him here 15 years ago.
I get it.
I wouldn't be impressed
by me either. Um...
I don't know
if you guys like movies,
but, uh, every movie
I've ever seen
starts with the sub writing
his name on the board,
then the kids
can throw something at him.
So, why don't we get that part
out of the way right now?
I have a short name,
so I'll take my time.
Mr. Ross.
But you guys
can call me Mike.
Okay, what did you guys
come up with?
Who did this?
Team effort.
You think this is funny?
I sure do.
How about you, Chris?
Cracks me up that our teacher
was in prison last week.
All right. Well, now that
we've all had our fun,
we open up our textbooks
to Chapter 7,
"The Battle of Appomattox."
We did that yesterday.
No, you didn't.
Father Walker gave me
your syllabus.
This is what we're covering today.
Come on.
Yeah, well, we all
forgot our books.
Well, then, I guess
we have no choice
but for you
to read from mine.
I just have one question
before I read.
You ever drop the soap
in the shower?
Donna, do you mind calling
Dr. Lipschitz for me?
Gretchen's at her
grandson's play.
I know where
Gretchen is, Louis.
I've been answering
her phone all morning.
Now, would you like to
tell me why
a Katroina Bonnett
just called to say
Operation Fly the Coop
was a resounding success?
Sounds like the wrong number.
Hmm.
Sounds like you just got
Katrina Bennett's help
poaching half
Robert Zane's associates.
How could you possibly
guess that?
Gretchen's grandson
could have guessed that.
Louis, Robert Zane is a bear,
and you just poked him.
I didn't poke him. He poked me
when he came all the way down here
to question my ability
to be managing partner.
No, he came all the way down here
because he's trying to help us.
And if you're trying to prove something
to him, it's not gonna work.
Oh, it is going to work.
And for your information,
I'm just getting started.
What's that supposed
to mean?
It means
that Gretchen's still out,
and I need you to set up a
meeting with Jeremy Cohen.
Louis, that's Zane's
biggest client.
I know he goddamn is.
He's about to be my biggest client.
I don't believe this.
You're trying
to tell the world
that you should be
managing partner
and the first thing you do is
burn every bridge in sight?
I don't care if I burn
every bridge ever built.
I am not letting
Robert Zane come in here
and push me around the day
after Jessica leaves.
So, get Jeremy Cohen on
the goddamn phone, Donna,
or I'm not gonna
forget you didn't.
Then don't forget it, Louis.
Because when this comes back
to bite you in the ass,
I want you to remember that I tried
to stop you and you didn't listen.
What are you
doing here, Harvey?
I'm here
for a fresh start.
I assume by fresh start, you
mean you want me to do something
to help Mike Ross now that
he's out in the world.
Anita, you heard his
speech to that jury.
He was given a gift
and he threw it away.
And the reason it was so
effective is 'cause he meant it.
Get to the point, Harvey.
If Mike puts himself
in front of
the character and fitness
committee,
will you stand up there
with him?
I don't believe this.
He's not been in there
three months
and you want me to help
him con more people?
He's not trying
to con people.
He's trying to help people.
Then let him go work
in a soup kitchen.
Look, you proved your point.
The whole world knows
he's a fraud
and he may not have served
his entire sentence,
but he deserves a chance to
lead a life now that he's out.
So, why don't you go back
to the same person
that got him out
in the first place?
What?
Don't act like you don't
know what I'm talking about.
Sean Cahill has as much sway
over that committee as I do,
and he owes Mike.
I don't.
So, why aren't you
going to him?
Because a word from the
woman who put him away
is worth 1,000 from the
guy who got him out.
Nice try, but you two did
something to get that kid out,
and you don't want to
shine a light on that
by appearing together
in public.
That's not true.
No? Well, let's get Cahill
on the phone right now
and see if his lies
match your lies.
I didn't think so.
You're the same man you were
when Mike went in.
And the fact that he made a
crooked deal to get himself out,
lets me know
that he is, too.
Anita.
Sell it somewhere else, Harvey.
Because I'm done.
Now I know
why school ends at 3:00.
Why is that?
Because if it went
till 6:00,
no teacher would
ever come back again.
I take it you had
a rough first day.
You never told me
you were going to put me
in a class full of
juvenile delinquents.
Would you have
taken my offer if I had?
I don't know.
Michael, you said
you wanted to help people.
These kids need
your help.
I wanted to help people as a
lawyer, not as a teacher.
What's the difference?
The difference is clients
actually want my help.
Michael, these kids
need it.
They just don't know it.
I don't know, Father.
This is...
Michael, if I just needed someone to
grade papers and take attendance,
I could have got a trained
monkey to do that.
I wanted you
because I thought you,
of all people,
could get through to them.
And how am I supposed
to do that in two weeks?
If it takes more than
two weeks, so be it.
Father Conroy's
not on vacation, is he?
No, Michael, he's not.
He's got cancer.
He's probably
never coming back.
And when exactly were you planning
on letting them in on that?
Because you're not doing them any
favors by keeping it from them.
You're right, I'm not.
[was going to tell them this
week, but then you showed up.
I know you don't think things happen
for a reason, Michael, but I do.
I thought maybe the reason you
came to see me when you did
is because teaching's
your real calling.
I'll understand if you don't
wanna come back tomorrow.
Just let me know.
I'll take
the class myself.
All right, everyone,
take your seats.
Would you...
Put the ball away.
Cell phones, too.
I'm not gonna
say it again.
Sit the hell down!
I was gonna
come in here
and talk about
what happened yesterday.
I figured if you guys had the balls
to put that picture on my desk,
then you're probably old enough to
hear about what prison was like.
What I did to get there.
How I thought about being
killed every single day.
I don't wanna
talk about me. I'm...
I'm nobody to you.
Father Conroy is dying.
What?
That's right.
He's got cancer.
He's probably
not gonna make it.
That's the reason that
I'm here and he's not.
So, we can get to work or we can spend
the morning sharing our memories
of a man who spent
the last 40 years
giving his life
to kids like you and me.
Third grade, camping trip
to Lake Kanawauke.
Fishing with a stick.
He's still fishing
with a stick?
Still coming up empty.
He taught me how to swim
on that trip.
Yeah. Me, too.
I don't mean to interrupt
you, but I'm pretty sure
you didn't mean to leave
this in the Mackenzie file.
Oh, my God.
Gretchen, I'm sorry to put
you in this position,
but I have to ask you to
please don't tell anyone.
You don't have to
ask me anything.
What you do
is your business.
You don't understand.
It's not what you think.
Doesn't matter what I think.
You got to
take care of yourself.
If my father offered me a job
in a firm with my name on it,
well, I'd be leaving things
in files by mistake, too.
Gretchen.
If this was just
about that, then I...
I wouldn't be thinking twice.
I would just tell him no.
Then if you don't mind my
asking, what is it about?
My father thinks I have a better
chance of getting past the Bar
if I'm not still working at
the firm that hired Mike.
But you're loyal
to the people here
and you don't want to leave them.
Yes.
But if it means that I can't
be a lawyer at all, I...
I can't help you with that
part of the equation.
But...
If Tweedledee and Tweedledum
don't get it together,
you may not have to make
that decision at all.
Katroina Bonnett,
as I live and breathe.
Pouis Pitt, I do declare.
No, uh, you see.
Katrina, you need to work
on your code name for me,
because it's
way too obvious.
You're right, Louis.
Katroina Bonnett is the
gold standard in spy craft.
Precisely.
Now, get your game face on,
because I just set up our
first meeting for tomorrow.
I was born with my game face on.
Who are we going after?
J.C. Analytics.
What?
That's Zane's biggest client.
Yeah.
That's exactly why
we're going after him.
Listen to me.
Whatever time
you set up that meeting,
I guarantee you Jeremy Cohen
called Robert two minutes later.
Which means we need to figure
out a way to make amends.
No, I don't need
to make amends.
I need to make
a statement.
And that statement is
do not mess with the new managing
partner of Pearson Specter Litt.
Louis, that is the wrong
statement to make.
And if you insist
on making it,
I won't come
work for you.
God damn it, Katrina. I thought
you were a killer. I am.
But I'm not gonna
take a shot at the man
who's doing
both of us a favor.
What?
Louis,
we have non-competes.
And I was working on a way
to get around them
when Zane caught wind
of what we were doing.
And he not only waived
them, he wished us luck.
Oh, my God.
He really was trying to help
us and I couldn't see it.
Does that mean you're not
going to go after his client?
It means a whole lot
more than that, Katrina.
It means I'm not ready
to be managing partner.
You wanted
to see me, Father?
Yeah. Uh, sit down,
Michael.
Look. If this is about what
happened in class today,
I know it wasn't
my news to share.
But if I'm gonna
get through to them,
I have to be
honest with them.
It's not about that.
One of the students told his
parents that you were in prison.
The parents called the Archdiocese
to see if it was true and then...
Don't say it.
I'm sorry, Michael.
I tried to explain the situation
to them, but they wouldn't budge.
You have nothing to
feel bad about, Father.
You took a chance.
Someone else will, too.
I'll see you around, Father.
Take care
of yourself, Michael.
I know it's only been a
couple of days, but, uh,
will you say goodbye
to the kids for me?
Of course I will.
Robert.
Twice in one week.
What brings you by?
Do you really think
you could try to poach
my oldest client
without me finding out?
What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm talking about
Jeremy Cohen.
I don't know anything
about Jeremy Cohen
and I'm not trying
to poach anyone.
Then you're even less prepared
to be a leader than I thought.
Because your partner's out
there coming after my firm
and you don't even
know it.
Maybe Louis wouldn't
be doing that
if you hadn't come here
with some bullshit merger
designed to rip us apart.
Are you really
that stupid?
Are you really telling me
that isn't what you wanted?
If I wanted
to rip you apart,
you'd be in a million
pieces right now.
Because Jessica is gone
and you're not in my league.
I offered the merger
because my daughter has some
kind of misguided loyalty to you
and I didn't want to
extinguish that spark in her.
If I'm not in your league, why is
she loyal to us instead of you?
Watch yourself, Harvey.
Robert, I'm not looking
to get in a fight with you.
But as my partner
told you before,
we don't need your charity.
Then I'll stop
giving it to you.
But you better
put that dog on a leash
and shut that shit down,
or I'll shut you down.
The next time you want
something from me, Mr. Ross,
at least have the balls
to ask me yourself.
What are you
talking about?
You're gonna tell me
you had nothing to do
with Harvey asking me to
help you get a law license?
That's exactly
what I'm telling you.
I didn't even know
about it
until you just showed
up here and told me.
Then why did I get five calls
from five different legal clinics
all asking
about your case?
Because the day after
I got out,
I followed through on my promise to
that jury to try to do some good.
If that's all
you came here to say,
why don't you
leave me alone?
I've had a rough day.
I'm going to
leave you alone.
But not before I tell you what
I tried to tell your old boss.
You want to do good,
be my guest.
But do it
in another profession.
Because if I ever even
catch wind
of you trying to get work
at any of these places,
you can bet your ass I will do
everything I can to stop it.
Did you know
what Louis was up to?
I did.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I said Louis wasn't
ready to be managing partner,
but maybe
you aren't either.
Because you're not
around enough to know
what's going on
around here.
I don't believe this. You're the one
who said do something about Mike.
Yes, I did.
But I didn't say
that you should spend your
entire existence doing it.
Donna... Harvey, you can't
do whatever you want.
Jessica's not here to pick
up the slack anymore.
You think
I don't know that?
Well, if you do, then it's time you
do what she would have done already.
You need to tell Louis he
can't be managing partner.
He doesn't want to hear it.
I know that.
But the real reason we're
having this conversation
is that you're afraid
to say it.
It's up to you, Harvey.
Either step up
and take the reins
or start looking
for another job.
Because if you don't tell Louis
he's not ready to run this firm,
we're going to be out of
business one way or the other.
What the hell
did you do?
Mike, not now.
I'm not in the mood.
Well, I wasn't in the mood when I got
home to find Anita Gibbs waiting for me.
Mike, I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
She came to my house
to tell me
that if I even so much as try
to get a job at a legal clinic,
she's going to make it her
life's mission to stop me.
She can't do that.
Did you hear me?
I wasn't even
on her radar.
I had one thing
I wanted to do
and you ruined it
for me
just because you can't
accept the fact
that I don't want to
come back here.
I wasn't trying to get you back.
I was trying to help you.
I don't believe you.
Mike.
Are you telling me you don't
want me to come back here?
Of course I do, and you
can come back anytime.
But that
doesn't mean that...
I don't care
what it means.
And just to make it absolutely
clear in case there is any doubt.
If by some miracle,
the hand of God touches me
and I'm somehow able
to practice law again,
this is the last place that
I am ever coming back to.
Mike...
Stop messing with my life.
Harvey. I'm glad
you're here.
I was just going to come talk to you.
What for?
To tell me how you tried
to ruin everything
that Jessica
has ever worked for
by making an enemy
of the one man
who's been trying
to help us?
That's what I wanted
to talk to you about.
You couldn't even shine
Jessica's shoes
and now you're trying
to tear her legacy down.
I was trying to live up
to her legacy.
Yeah, I don't give a shit what
you think you've been doing.
Harvey, please. Just let me
say what I was going to say.
You know what? I don't care what you
were going to say to me, Louis.
Because all you care about
is proving to me
that you should be
managing partner
when everyone in the world
knows that you shouldn't.
Me, Robert Zane,
even Donna.
Harvey, please.
Jessica didn't want
your name up on the wall.
So, if you think I'm gonna let you be
managing partner while she's still breathing,
you're out of
your goddamn mind!
Harvey.
That's enough.
I have the start paperwork
for those associates
in case you wanna
look it over.
I'll just leave it here.
I was gonna tell him,
you know.
I was gonna tell him
that he...
He's the one that should
be managing partner.
Louis, you may have
your flaws,
but he had no right
to talk to you like that.
Yes, he did.
I did everything he said I
did and the reason I did it
is because
all I ever care about
is for people to see me
as more than I am.
Louis...
The funny thing is,
all I ended up with
was the shortest,
most humiliating run
as managing partner
in the history
of the world.
If you ask me, you may
have had a short run,
but you made your mark.
What are you talking about?
Well, unless I'm mistaken,
we have ten associates
starting tomorrow
who chose to come here
over one of the best
law firms in the city.
They did that
because of you.
It was because of me,
wasn't it?
Yeah.
And you did that
all on your own.
Nobody asked you
to do it.
Where I come from, they
call that stepping up.
You're right.
It is.
Thank you
for being the secretary
to the shortest tenured
managing partner in history.
Well, now that
you mention it.
Before you hand over
your reins,
there's something you can do to
cement the future of this firm.
What's that?
Show a little love to someone
who's been loyal to us
for as long
as I've known her.
Rachel, you have a minute?
Honestly, Louis,
I am swamped.
So, if it can wait
until tomorrow...
I wish it could,
but it can't.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, except for one thing.
I have been derelict in my duties
as head of the associates.
I don't understand.
Rachel, you've given
your heart and soul
to this firm
for almost ten years.
And now that you're about
to become a lawyer,
I'd like to formally
extend you an offer
to work here
as soon as you graduate.
This says
second-year associate.
I know it does.
I... I don't know
what to say.
I think you do.
You're right.
Yes, Louis,
I accept your offer.
All right,
you drive a hard bargain.
Third-year associate it is.
Thank you, Louis.
No.
Thank you, Rachel.
She's not coming back,
you know.
I know she's not.
Do you?
Because you just
lashed out at Louis
when your intention
was to let him down gently.
And I find it hard
to believe
it had nothing to do with
this office being empty.
She didn't even
come back to say goodbye.
She just
packed up her things.
Harvey...
They're all leaving, Donna.
First Jessica, now Mike.
They're family.
And family's
not supposed to...
Harvey, I've always
stayed away
from a certain subject with
you, but I can't anymore.
You always talk like
we're your only family.
We're not.
You have another one, and you
need to reconcile with them.
Donna, I am not
gonna go...
Enough is enough.
You need to go make things
right with your mother.
Because as long as you
keep her at arm's length,
you're gonna keep looking
to us to fill that void
and I'm not sure
that any of us can.
Please.
Go see her.
^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
P® Krishna_Teja P®