(HARVEY READING)
I've been after Sutter
for three years now.
This guy's one slippery
son of a bitch.
Wait a second.
William Sutter?
He came to me a week ago
to take him on.
You cross one line
that puts me in jeopardy,
I'm going to pull the plug
on this whole thing.
I need a large,
expensive home
in the Hamptons.
Why are you buying
a vacation home?
Because I told Tara Messer
that I have
a property out there
and I hired her
to remodel it for me.
Damn it, Harvey!
I am not colluding on this,
and you're in here
trying to get me
to bring an indictment
against your own client.
Because when you bring
that indictment,
I'm gonna beat it,
and if you don't bring it
and continue
investigating my client,
I'm going to sue you.
I think it's pretty goddamn
funny that you don't trust me
when you're the one
that won't even tell me
what you're in here for.
Okay.
I'll do it.
Excuse me?
Your pro bono.
Bring me the file
tomorrow morning.
It was a good fix, Sean.
It was a good move, Harvey.
Want to get a drink?
Why don't we just
have one here?
Why? As of right now,
you have no action
pending against my client.
But as of tomorrow, I do.
Because those indictments are
coming down in the morning.
Kevin, what did you do?
I got in a fight
with my wife.
I got drunk.
I got into my car and...
I almost killed someone.
I'm missing
a thousand chances
to hug my kids
in the morning
(VOICE BREAKING)
and kiss my wife goodnight.
All because
I couldn't control myself.
What were you fighting
with your wife about?
I can't.
I just can't.
Harvey.
What are you
doing here?
Mike, sit down.
I need to tell
you something.
What's going on?
I'm working on
getting you out of here.
Yeah, I know you are.
I'm not talking
about what we're
doing for Cahill.
I'm talking about
something else.
Harvey, we're in a room
full of people.
You can't be talking
about Cahill.
If Kevin
finds out, then...
It doesn't matter
if Kevin finds out now.
He's done.
What do you mean,
he's done?
I mean,
Rachel's dead
and Kevin killed her.
What?
It's true.
You son of a bitch.
You're lying to me.
God damn it,
he told you he did it.
Bullshit.
He got drunk.
He got in a car,
he murdered
the woman you love.
Stop saying that.
And now, you're gonna be
stuck in here with him
for the rest
of your life.
Stop it.
Kevin would never
do that to me.
Mike, wake up!
No!
Mike. Wake up.
No.
Wake up.
No!
Mike, wake up.
No! No! No!
KEVIN:
Wake up!
(PANTING)
Hey, you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
You sure? 'Cause that,
that was some dream
you were having.
I'm fine.
(SIGHS)
I'm just...
I'm going back
to sleep.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Harvey, good,
there you are.
What's going on?
Sutter just called.
Let me guess.
The indictments
came down.
He wants you
in his office
an hour ago.
I'll tell him
you're on your way.
No, tell him
you couldn't reach me.
You want him
to start sweating.
But why?
Because when people
start sweating,
they start talking
to their lawyer.
I'll tell Ray
to be on hold.
No, tell him
to pull around.
But you just said
you weren't going
to Sutter's.
I'm not. I'm going
somewhere else.
Oh, look who it is.
The man of the hour.
Did you get
my indictments?
I sure as hell did.
And now that
the party's started,
why don't you tell me
what Kevin Miller knows.
What are you
talking about?
You went after the guy
to try to get him
to flip on Sutter.
So, what did you think
he was gonna give you?
I'm not gonna
tell you that.
Why not?
Because I told you
when I started this thing,
I'm not gonna collude.
We're not colluding.
It's called discovery.
So, why don't you tell me
what the hell
Kevin Miller knows.
He developed
the trading programs
that Sutter claims
to use to get his
"superior" returns.
And that program's
got to be full of shit
because if it isn't...
Then Sutter's
not inside trading.
Which he sure as shit is.
So, you're looking
to have Kevin testify
that software
is bullshit
and Sutter knows it.
Bingo.
Then let me
ask you this.
What exactly did you put
Kevin away for?
And why do you need
to know that?
Because it might
help us figure out
what his weak spot is.
We got him
on vehicular assault
while driving
under the influence.
Are you kidding me?
Why didn't you think
to tell us that?
Why would I?
Mike's parents
were killed
by a drunk driver.
And how the hell was I
supposed to know that?
I don't know.
It would've been nice
to know
what this asshole did
before we sent Mike
back into a cell with him.
Hey, what happened
to you this morning?
What do you mean?
You skipped breakfast.
I wasn't hungry.
That all it was?
What are you
talking about?
Come on, Mike.
You had a nightmare
last night,
you've been avoiding me
all morning,
and you're acting
weird right now.
What's going on?
Nothing's going on.
Then why the hell
were you in a cold sweat
muttering something about
someone not finding out,
and then
calling out my name?
All right, Kevin,
you want to know
what's going on?
I had a dream
that you killed Rachel
in a car accident.
That's probably why
I don't particularly
feel like
hanging out with you
this morning.
Because of what you told
me about your parents.
Mike, I'm really sorry.
Are you?
What? What's that
supposed to mean?
I mean, last night,
you told me you almost
killed someone.
Are you sorry about that?
You've got to be kidding me.
You have a dream and
now you're questioning
if I feel bad about
what I did that night?
You still haven't answered
whether or not you do.
You know what?
You need to be pissed off
at me to deal with your shit,
you go right ahead.
But I feel horrible about
what happened that night.
And for your information,
the guy that I hit
is fully recovered
right now
and I'm still in here
paying for this shit.
See the money, wanna stay
for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
P® Krishna_Teja P®
Break out the
champagne, Louis.
That house in the Hamptons
is gonna be yours
in 60 to 90 days.
They accepted my offer?
That they did.
Well, then, I have something
much better than champagne.
Wood.
I don't really see
how that's better
than champagne.
Of course you don't.
Because you don't know
that I'm having a replica
of my house made for Tara
so she can see
her designs come to life.
Louis, that's
actually really sweet.
I know.
Now all I need to do...
Is pick the perfect wood.
I don't follow.
Donna,
the kind of wood you get
says everything
you need to know
about what kind
of man you are.
How hard or soft it is.
How much it bends
when you're working it.
How firm it is
compared to...
I got the picture, Louis.
No, I don't think you do.
Making Tara love my wood
is the first step
towards making her love me.
Okay, Louis, calm down.
No, no, I don't really want
to calm down,
because all I can
think about is my wood.
So, tell me exactly
how many different
kinds of wood
have you sampled in your day?
All of them.
Mahogany, chestnut,
walnut, all the nuts.
Ebony?
Don't even get me
started on ebony.
When I see ebony,
all I want to do is
put my hands all over it.
Oh, God. (CHUCKLES)
I want to live in it,
I wanna smack it,
hit it, rub it down.
I just want to eat it.
What's so funny?
Nothing.
Um, I just think that
a man needs to, uh...
To follow his heart
and choose the wood
that just feels right.
Feels right.
Yeah.
That's it. Donna.
I need you to help me
feel my wood.
Oh, dear God.
(LAUGHING)
Goddamn it, Julie.
Call his office again,
and this time
tell them to find where the...
If you're talking about
my office,
there's no need.
I'm right here.
What the hell took you
so long?
I was unavailable.
Well, I just
got indicted,
so from now on,
you make yourself
available.
I get it.
This all just
got real for you.
So, why don't you
tell me right now?
How real
is the rest of it?
What are you saying?
I'm saying
Cahill claims
that you can't make
the returns you do,
you say you can,
and I want to know
how you do it.
We use a proprietary
trading algorithm.
Developed by who?
My son-in-law.
Good, then we can
give it to Cahill,
'cause he just
subpoenaed it.
No, we can't.
Why the hell not?
Because the trades
on which I make
the most money
have nothing to do
with that program.
Are you kidding me?
You're admitting
to inside trading?
I'm not admitting
to anything
except that sometimes
I trade with my gut.
Well, I got news
for you, William.
To a jury,
that's gonna sound
like you're full of shit.
Okay, smart guy.
Pick up that journal.
Give me a stock.
NASDAQ, New York
Stock Exchange.
I don't give a shit.
Just pick one.
All right, Computech.
Computech.
One point five nine
billion shares
outstanding.
Yesterday's close,
32 flat.
Today's opening,
33 and a quarter.
PE's at 17.
Earnings expected
to grow at 2% a year.
What it doesn't
say in there
is that the earnings
aren't gonna grow,
because their CEO
doesn't give a shit.
Which makes it a value trap
dressed up like a princess
and I wouldn't touch it
with a 10-foot pole.
That's a pretty
neat trick, William.
But it isn't gonna
stop this subpoena.
It's not a trick.
It's what I do.
And what you're
gonna do
is stop that
son of a bitch
from getting his hands
on my program.
Rachel, whatever it is,
it's going to have
to wait.
Okay, but you told me
to bring you
everything I have
on the Bailey case
this morning.
Great. Leave it
on my desk,
and I'll get to it
sometime this week.
Oh, I'm sorry,
Jessica.
I was really hoping
that we could
go over it today.
I was hoping to be
out the door by now.
Look, I know
that I said
this wouldn't take up
too much
of your time, but...
Rachel, I said
I would do this
and I will,
but you just
have to be patient.
I understand.
It's just, Leonard Bailey's
been patient for 12 years.
And I have sympathy
for the man,
but today's not the day.
Don't bother
with another menu.
I'll just have
the Cobb salad.
What do you think
you're doing?
What does it look like
I'm doing?
I'm having lunch
with a client
to discuss his
investment business.
You don't represent
my investment business.
Which is exactly
why we need
to have lunch.
No, we don't need
to have anything.
Because the deal was
Harvey gets me cleared
of criminal charges,
then you get the rest
of my business.
I don't care what
the deal was, William.
I care
what the deal is.
Because now that that
indictment's come down,
Harvey is going
to be spending
all of his time on you.
That's not my problem.
I'm making it
your problem.
We get all of your business
or we handle none of it.
Bullshit.
You quit, you lose billables
you can't afford to lose.
We quit and it looks
like we realized
your case was a loser
and wanted
distance from it,
which you can't afford.
You really wanna start
a business relationship
this way?
I don't give a shit
how it starts, William.
I give a shit
how it looks.
Oh.
That's why
you did this here.
You want it to look like
you already
represent my firm.
Well, look at that.
Looks like I'm worth
hiring after all.
So, are we actually
going to talk business
or am I just gonna
bill you for the pleasure
of my company?
Mike, what can
I do for you?
You can tell me if you do
straight up therapy or not.
What's on your mind?
You didn't answer
my question.
I didn't think
I needed to,
since we've been doing
straight up therapy
since you got here.
So, you want to tell me
what you're here for?
My parents were killed
by a drunk driver
when I was 11.
And yesterday,
I found out
that Kevin almost killed
someone drunk driving.
So, I need you to help me
act normal around him
so that I can get
what I need
so I can get out of here.
Oh, well, that's gonna
be a problem.
Because
the goal of therapy
is not to act normal,
it's to be normal.
Yeah, well,
I'll be normal
when I'm home
with the woman I love
instead of dreaming
that the guy I'm sharing
a cell with killed her.
What?
I had a dream last night
that I didn't have
to inform
on Kevin anymore
because he killed Rachel
in an accident.
And I must have been
talking about it
in my sleep
because he asked me
about it today.
So, I told him
the accident part
and then
we got in a fight.
A fight about what?
I asked him
if he even felt bad
about the guy he hit.
So, you turned it
back on him.
What is that even
supposed to mean?
It means that
I think you picked
a fight with Kevin
because you didn't
wanna think about why
you had that dream.
I know why
I had that dream.
It's because he almost
killed someone the same way
my parents were killed.
No, you had the dream
because you don't
wanna deal with
what you're doing
to your friend.
Oh, this again.
Yes, this again.
Mike, why do you think
that part of the dream
was finding out
that you didn't have
to inform on him anymore?
God damn it,
I did not come here
to second-guess
my decision.
Do you know what?
I don't care.
Because I wouldn't
be doing my job
if I didn't inform you
that actions
have consequences.
And you seem to think
that the only consequence
of what you're doing
is getting
out of here early,
but it's not.
No. I think
you don't know shit about
what I've been through.
It was a mistake coming
to you for help.
...and this is the
fifth bedroom.
And I'm completely open
to you knocking
down walls
or removing windows,
by the way.
Oh, no,
I love the windows.
They let in
so much light.
I agree, we should add
a wall of glass.
What do you think?
I think the place
is beautiful
and I appreciate
you bringing
these photos over,
but when can we go
see it in person?
Uh, in person?
Yes, of course.
I need to see the space
before I can
start drafting anything.
I was just thinking
we could work
closely together
for the next
60 to 90 days
before you started that.
That wouldn't
be productive.
But I couldn't possibly
make it out there
in less than seven
to 10 business days.
That's too bad.
I was gonna be out there
the day after tomorrow.
I was thinking
we could see the space
and then maybe
go have lunch.
Lunch?
Together?
Well, I wasn't
thinking of eating
in separate restaurants.
(LAUGHS)
Of course you weren't.
The day after tomorrow
is perfect.
But I thought
you couldn't...
I can and I will.
And I will meet you
at my ancestral home
that I have owned
for quite some time,
the day after tomorrow.
Your Honor,
I'm simply requesting
Mr. Sutter hand over...
Something he has
no right to.
I have every right
to make sure that
your client is operating
within the law.
And what exactly
is your basis to say
that he isn't?
Your Honor,
when you break
the home run record
and someone says
your bat is corked,
you turn it over
to show it's not.
Except when that bat
is the reason
you hit
all those homers.
Because the second
he gets it,
everyone in the world
is gonna know
what's in it,
and my client
might as well go out
of business right now.
That is a
ridiculous supposition
without a shred
of proof to back it up.
How's this for proof?
Your Honor,
six years ago,
Mr. Cahill went
on a fishing expedition
just like this one.
That has nothing
to do with this.
Oh, doesn't it?
He subpoenaed
a proprietary
trading program
from Kessler Capital,
it proved no wrong-doing,
and 10 months later,
they were out
of business.
That has nothing to do
with my subpoena.
And I have
an affidavit here
from Mr. Kessler saying
it was directly because
of your subpoena.
Mr. Cahill,
is what he's saying true?
Did you go after Kessler
in the same manner
and did he go under
10 months later?
Yes, but...
No buts.
Do you have
any other evidence
to present to the court?
Not at this time,
Your Honor.
Then your request
is denied.
(GAVEL BANGING)
LOUIS:
Oh, there you are.
What the hell are you doing
in the executive kitchen?
What does it look like
I'm doing?
I'm being executive.
But you're not
an executive.
Until I made
the executive decision
that I was.
Now, is there something
I can help you with?
Yeah, I want you
to forget that latte
and get me
unfettered access
to my new home
after thoroughly
cleansing it
of any trace of its
former occupants.
And why exactly do you
need me to do that?
Because Tara wants
to see the house
and then have
lunch with me
the day after tomorrow.
Louis, your offer
was just accepted
and there's never been
a one-day escrow
in the history of escrows.
You don't think
I know that?
I just spent
the last hour arguing
with five different
escrow officers.
I get it.
You want me
to get people
to do things
they'd never be
willing to do
in a time frame
that makes it impossible
for them to do it in.
Exactly.
Then make me
a double latte and get
the hell out of my way
because I'm about to
executive-decision your
sorry ass into that house.
HARVEY:
What are you drinking?
A 60-year-old bottle
of the finest single malt
in the world.
Then get me a glass.
Not until I know
what happened
in court today.
Well, let me
put it this way.
The only thing that
Sean Cahill's gonna
be drinking tonight
is a shit-out-
of-luck daiquiri.
How did you get it done?
I established a pattern
of him going fishing
without enough bait.
Then have a drink before
you get back in there
and knock the bastard out
before he can throw
another punch.
What are you saying?
I'm saying I want you
to get this
entire action dismissed.
William, that's
a terrible idea.
Not to me,
because he's got nothing.
I don't care,
what you're suggesting
is a mistake.
You still haven't
told me why.
Because you only get
one shot at dismissal
and now's not the time
to take it.
Well, I say it is and
I'm not suggesting it.
I'm flat out
telling you to do it.
I didn't get where I am
by letting my clients
bully me.
And I didn't get where I am
by allowing my employees
to dictate terms.
Which I already did
once today and I'm not
gonna do it again.
What's that
supposed to mean?
It means Jessica Pearson
convinced me
to give your firm
the rest of my business
this afternoon.
So, if you don't move
to have the charges
against me dismissed,
I'll have her
do it for you.
Harvey, I was just
on my way out.
Well, you can be
on your way back in,
because I just came
from Sutter's.
I take it he told you
about our little
conversation today.
If by conversation
you mean going
behind my back
and getting his
investment business,
then yeah, he told me.
I didn't go
behind your back.
I saw an opportunity
and I took it.
Well, now he's seeing
an opportunity
and he's taking it.
What are you
talking about?
He's leveraging
what you did
to get me to move
for an immediate dismissal.
And don't tell me,
you think
it's gonna work.
I sure as hell do.
And the second it does,
Mike's chance at getting out
goes with it, thanks to you.
Hang on there, tiger.
You're not in this position
because of something I did.
You're in it
because of Sutter.
And he'd be
demanding you to have
this case dismissed
whether we have his
other business or not.
Well, that's not
the point.
No, Harvey, the point is
I have been out there
busting my ass
trying to find us
new business for days.
And do you know
what they keep asking?
Why don't we have
Sutter's investment business?
Goddamn right.
We needed it,
I got it,
and now they're not
asking anymore.
What's gonna happen
when we lose this case
and his business goes away?
What happens is
we're already built
back up by then.
So, instead of
blaming me
for the position
Sutter has put you in,
I suggest you go ahead
and find yourself
a way out of it.
Rachel, what can I
do for you?
I was hoping
you could do something
for Leonard Bailey.
I drafted a motion
to reopen his case,
but I need
a current member
of the Bar to file it.
And what happened
to the person you said
was gonna take this on?
She can't get to it
until later this week,
but I want to get on this
as soon as possible.
Rachel, I'm sorry,
but I told you before,
I don't have the resources
to work on this case now...
Professor,
this man has a wife
who gave up on him
and children
that he doesn't see.
His entire life
is passing him by,
and the only way for him
to start getting it back
is to just have someone
who cares enough
about him
that they give him
a half hour
of their time.
Let me see your motion.
(SIGHS)
This is well drafted.
Thank you.
But I'm afraid
it won't work.
No, what are you
talking... No, look.
There's no reason
that he should've
been convicted.
Look at the evidence.
That's not the point.
Rachel, I've worked
on dozens of these cases.
And like it or not,
the standard to reopen
is higher than what
it says in the books.
You need
something undeniable.
Then what am I
supposed to do?
You're supposed
to use your gumption
to find that something
and get Leonard Bailey
the justice
he's been waiting for.
Harvey, it's late.
Whatever you're doing here,
it's gonna have
to wait until morning.
It can't.
Why is that?
Because Sutter
wants me to move
for an
immediate dismissal.
What?
You leveraged me into
bringing this indictment
and now
you want to toss it?
I don't want to toss it.
But if I don't,
he's gonna find
someone else who will.
What are you doing
here, Harvey?
Nothing, I'm just
finishing my dinner.
Thing is,
I don't like to litter.
So, why don't you
do me a favor.
If I forget this
when I go,
why don't you
take it upstairs
and throw it away?
What's in the bag,
Harvey?
A wrapper,
a couple napkins,
and a few extra fries.
What the hell
is in the bag, Harvey?
What you needed to keep
this case going
and I stopped you
from getting.
Damn it, you said
you were gonna defend him
to the best
of your ability.
And I meant it,
but I also knew
if push came to shove,
I'd do what I had to
to get Mike out.
And I made
my peace with it.
Yeah, well, I haven't.
Yes, you have.
What are you
talking about?
You've been giving me
this song and dance
about not colluding
and it didn't matter
what I said back to you
as long as
it was something
to let you believe
we wouldn't.
Because that song
wasn't for me,
it was for you.
Oh, for me?
Bullshit.
I don't think so, Sean.
Because you don't break
a guy out of prison
just to advance
your career.
This means
something to you.
I don't need to know
what it is,
but it means something
to me, too.
So, let's just admit
that we're in this together
and get this thing done.
Take that garbage
and throw it away.
Now can I
have champagne?
You got the realtor
to give you
the key to the house.
Not only that,
I got him to agree
to take the Kellmans
to brunch tomorrow
from 10:00 to 2:00
to celebrate
their big sale.
Well, that is great,
Donna,
but I don't just need
to get into the house,
I need Tara to believe
that it's my house.
Which means...
No lockbox on the door,
no for sale sign
in the yard,
and no personal belongings
in the house.
Which is why we are
gonna be there at 10:01
to stage the shit
out of that place.
Oh, and these are
coming with us.
You reframed pictures
of Bruno.
In the style of the house.
And not just Bruno.
Mikado.
(CHUCKLES)
It's perfect, Donna.
I just thought showing
Tara your wood
wasn't the only way
to show her what
kind of man you are.
Thank you, Donna.
You're welcome, Louis.
(SIGHS)
Since when do
we get a room
instead of having to use
those damn phones?
Since I officially became
part of your legal team.
My legal team?
That's right.
The firm that I work for
is taking your case.
After all this time.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
But we still need to get
the case reopened.
And to do that, we need
to find something new.
So, where do we
get that?
I was going through
the state's case file,
and I read
your police report.
You said there was
a woman with you
that night
who can testify
that you didn't kill
that couple.
That's right. Maria.
But that's not new.
Well, it's new as far as
the court's concerned,
because it was
never admitted at trial.
Well, let's admit it.
It's not that easy.
I need to understand
why it was never admitted.
Because the damn woman
up and disappeared
before my trial.
My lawyer
didn't do a thing.
You had an alibi witness
and your public defender
let her get away?
That's what
I've been saying.
Maria could have
told the jury
that I didn't do it.
Instead,
no one told them.
Two weeks later,
I'm in here.
And I've been here
ever since.
Is there anything else
I need to know?
Then I need to find
Maria Gomez.
Look, man, please,
I really don't
want to talk.
Good,
'cause I just want
you to listen.
When I was a kid,
I thought we had it good.
And we did.
Had a nice house,
nice neighborhood
except for one thing.
Turns out my father
was a criminal.
One day, he got caught,
he went to prison,
and my whole life
fell apart.
How old were you?
Fifteen.
Let me tell you something.
I hated that man for doing
what he did to me.
So, I did what messed up
15-year-olds do.
You started acting out.
Acting out?
Brother, I was on my way
to a place worse than this.
Finally, my mom
made me see someone.
And he helped me realize
that if I didn't change,
I was gonna ruin my life.
So, I straightened out
and turned my life around.
And that's why you do
what you do.
Yeah.
Why are you
telling me this?
Because the way that man
got through to me
was to open up
about himself.
And I realize
that if I really want
to help you,
I gotta do the same.
All right, I dragged this out
as long as I can,
but I'm pretty much done
drafting this motion,
so I'll need you
to proof it, then...
Harvey, before I do that,
I think you should
take a look at these.
What is it?
Cahill issued subpoenas
to deposition
William Sutter
and Kevin Miller.
That sneaky
son of a bitch.
Why are you smiling?
Because last night
I went to Cahill
and tried to give him
Sutter's trading program.
You did what?
It was the only way
I could see to stop the case
from getting dismissed.
But he wouldn't take it.
And this buys you time.
It does if the judge waits
to rule on our motion
until after Cahill conducts
these depositions.
Harvey,
even if that works,
what if Cahill
doesn't get enough
from the depositions
to keep the case alive?
Then Mike's chance
of getting out
of prison is gone.
Which means Cahill's
not the only one
that needs to use this
to try and get something.
I have to admit,
Miss Zane,
when you said
you were looking
into the Bailey case,
my interest
was piqued.
That was a long time ago.
Well, you've obviously
come a long way
since your public
defender days.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
You don't exactly see
the best of humanity
at that job,
which makes it one
you can only do
for so long.
But you didn't come here
to be my therapist.
No, I came to talk
about Maria Gomez.
What about her?
I'm curious as to
how you can have
an alibi witness
on a murder case
and your client
ends up on death row.
Because I didn't have
an alibi witness.
I had a no-show
who vanished
into thin air
and I didn't have
the resources
to find her.
And you didn't think
to ask the police at trial
why they didn't follow up
on Leonard's alibi?
I did think of it,
and they would have said
what they always say.
Every murderer claims
to have an alibi.
And if I couldn't
produce her,
why should they?
Well, you could have at least
asked for a postponement
to have time to find her.
And I would have,
except for one thing.
I wasn't sure a drug addict
with a prior conviction
would have done
Leonard Bailey much good.
That's about her character,
not the facts of the case.
Her character
is a fact of the case.
And when I pressed her
as to what the two of them
were doing at the time
of those murders,
she admitted they were
both on meth,
and it wasn't
the first time.
Which, by the way,
might have something to do
with why she never
showed up at trial.
So, you can try
to reopen this case
if you want, Ms. Zane.
But I am telling you,
you're wasting your time.
What's going on?
What's going on is
the clock's ticking.
Sutter wants me to get
the case dismissed.
What?
If that happens...
I know.
Now, listen to me.
I bought us
a little time,
but I need you
to do something.
Okay.
What is it?
Sutter doesn't
know this yet.
But he and I are gonna
be here tomorrow
to have a practice
deposition with Kevin.
So, I need you to do
the best Sean Cahill
you have
to get them talking.
You want me
in the room?
I don't think
that's a good idea.
Didn't you hear me?
We're running
out of time.
I heard you,
but I don't think
it's a good idea
for me to be
in the same room
as Kevin right now.
The drunk driving.
You knew?
I just found out.
Well, then,
you also know
it's probably not
the best time for me
to chum up to him.
I'm not asking you
I'm asking you
to piss him off.
What are you
talking about?
Kevin knows something
and he's not talking.
So, we could
sit around here
for the next two years
waiting for him
to tell you,
or we can light a fire
under his ass
by reminding him
that Sutter's out there
while he's in here.
Now, are you
with me or not?
I'm with you.
I take it you're here
to give me the good news.
I'm afraid not.
I thought
I made myself clear.
If you don't make
a motion to dismiss...
I did file
a motion to dismiss,
but it doesn't matter
because Cahill
filed subpoenas
to depose you
and your son-in-law first.
And until those
depositions happen,
the court won't file
on the motion.
Goddamn it.
How the hell
did he know to do that
when we're about to have
the case thrown out?
I don't know,
but that's not what
I came here to talk about.
Because we need
to get you
and Kevin Miller
in a room to prepare you
for your deposition.
You want us
to go prison?
Look, I don't see
any other choice.
So, you should call
whoever it is
you were gonna meet
this morning and tell them
you can't make it,
because you and I
are going to Danbury.
Were you really
serious about wanting
to help me?
Why do I get
the feeling that's not
a simple question?
Because I want to know
if you're willing to give me
access to certain records.
I'm, I'm sorry, Mike.
I cannot give information
on other inmates.
Well, that's okay,
because those aren't
the records I'm looking for.
Did you find Maria?
You know, I haven't even
started looking for her yet.
Because you lied to me.
What?
I didn't lie to you
about shit.
Well, you certainly
didn't tell me
that you and Maria
were high the night
of those murders.
(SIGHS)
Well, who told you that?
Georgina Casey.
You went to see
my old lawyer?
Yes, I did.
And now you're
sitting over there
looking at me like,
you know...
"Maybe he could've killed
those people after all."
Leonard, when I went
into that meeting,
I was on your side.
And you came
out of it, off it.
No. When I came out of it,
I had questions.
Okay, ask them!
I got nothing to hide.
Really?
Because you hid something
from me the last time.
That was different.
No, it's relevant.
No, it isn't.
You were high
the night of the murders
and you lied
to me about it.
Because I'm ashamed
of how I used to be!
I was a high-school dropout
on my way nowhere.
So, yeah.
I looked for an escape
when I could afford one.
I'm not saying I didn't
make some mistakes
or maybe even
commit a few crimes.
But killing those kids
was not one of them.
And that's the truth.
But I guess
it doesn't matter.
Because if you
don't find Maria,
someday they're gonna
walk me down that hall
and put me to death.
Then I guess I'd better
get back to finding her.
But, Leonard,
I'm telling you,
if you're not
straight with me,
this isn't gonna work.
Then I won't ever
leave anything out again.
This is ridiculous.
This kid's no Sean Cahill.
This kid made
Sean Cahill
look like a fool
without even having
a law degree.
Just so you know,
when you attack
opposing counsel,
it kind of makes
you look afraid.
(SCOFFS) I'm not
afraid of you.
Okay. Then why don't
you tell me this?
What's the best thing
about having
so much money?
What?
You heard me.
You've got the penthouse
in Manhattan.
You've got the villa
in the south of France.
You've got
two yachts.
So, what?
MIKE: So, what?
I wouldn't want
to give all of that up.
Would you, Mr. Miller?
Me?
Yeah, you.
I mean,
you had use of all
of these places, too.
Until you threw it
all away driving drunk,
that is.
What?
Objection, irrelevant.
MIKE: I think
it's very relevant.
For all I know,
Kevin could be
somehow involved.
That's insane.
That's insane?
You're the developer
of the trading software.
And I'm not the one
who's on trial here.
Then let's talk about
the one who is.
How do you feel
about the fact
that your father-in-law
never came to visit you
in prison?
Excuse me?
You heard me.
He hasn't come
to see you once.
How does that
make you feel?
It doesn't
matter to me.
It... (LAUGHS)
He could be lying
on a beach in the
French Riviera
while you can
barely see
your wife and kids.
And that doesn't
matter to you?
Mr. Miller's family
has nothing to do
with this investigation.
Mr. Miller's family
is the subject
of this investigation.
And his father-in-law
clearly doesn't
give a shit.
I'm grateful for everything
Kevin's done for me
and he knows it.
(SCOFFS)
Yeah, right.
I'm sorry,
what was that?
Are you disputing
the fact that
he's grateful to you?
I'm not answering
that question.
This isn't
getting us anywhere.
He's getting you
ready for Cahill.
I wouldn't have
to get ready for Cahill
if you'd done
your goddamn job
and gotten
this case dismissed.
KEVIN: That's right,
get someone else
to cover up your mess
like you always do.
You got something
you wanna say to me?
I got something
I wanna do to you.
You better remember
who you're talking to.
I know exactly
who I'm talking to.
The guy that doesn't give
a shit about anyone else
other than himself.
That's enough!
That is enough!
This is your trial,
it's not mine.
And I'm done with this
and I'm done with you.
Guard.
(BANGS DOOR)
Son of a bitch.
I knew that kid
would be a problem.
Relax.
That's the whole reason
I wanted Mike in here.
If Kevin gets
any funny ideas,
Mike's gonna
calm him down,
then let us know.
You guys really get
under each other's skin,
don't you?
You have no idea
how many times
I've thought about punching
that bastard in his smug face.
I'm guessing
he's thought about
punching you, too.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
It means his daughter
married a criminal.
He's got
to live with that.
You know what?
I've had just
about enough
of you giving me shit
for what I did.
Well, maybe I'll stop
giving you shit
when your story
starts adding up.
Excuse me?
You said you got
three years
for drunk driving.
But you've got no priors
and this guy made
a full recovery.
Ninety-nine times
out of a hundred,
that means you're
getting probation.
Then I guess I had
shitty representation.
Bullshit.
Money like yours doesn't
buy shitty representation.
Then I don't know
what to tell you.
How about you start
with telling me
the goddamn truth?
You want to know
the truth? I'll tell you,
because I'm sick
of holding it in, man.
I got three years
because when they
offered me a deal
to turn on him,
I said no.
You had
to turn them down.
He didn't do it.
No, I had
to turn them down
because he's not
the only one involved.
What?
You asked me
why I was drinking
that night.
It was because
I found out
the thing that
I worked so hard on
to get that prick's
approval was nothing
but a lie.
Your trading program.
Yeah, my program.
Turns out he wasn't
using it at all.
He was just
insider trading
the whole time.
Okay, so,
you got home,
you told Jill,
and she didn't
believe you.
No, Mike.
She not only
believed me, she...
She already knew.
(SIGHS)
She was in on it.
Yeah.
So, I went out
and I got drunk.
And the next thing I knew,
I had to choose
between going to prison
for three years
or the mother of
my children going away
for a whole lot more.
Kevin,
you've got...
DONNA: Okay, I...
Have removed
every possible trace
of the Kellmans' existence
and replaced it with yours.
Now, all I have to do
is fill the refrigerator
with prune juice
and then I've got
to set up the...
Okay, get out.
What? What do you
mean, get out?
I haven't set up the...
She's pulling up.
She's here, and I don't want
her to see us together
and get the wrong idea.
And exactly
what idea is that?
Okay.
Don't you understand?
No woman could
compete with you
if she thought
there was even a chance
of you and I
being together.
Really?
No, she blows you away.
Now, get
the hell out and use
the service entrance.
(SIGHS)
Tara, you're here.
Oh, my God.
Louis,
this place
is wonderful.
How long
have you had it?
(CHUCKLES)
I've had it
for generations.
Great Grandma Litt,
she used to make wool
right over there
by the fire.
The natural light
is phenomenal.
Phenomenal.
There's a wildness
to the landscape.
An uninhibited energy.
Wild.
Uninhibited.
It's perfect for us,
Louis.
I'm glad you like it.
I don't just like it.
I love it.
Just like I love you.
Oh, Tara, I love you.
What?
It, your idea.
What you were talking
about earlier?
Which idea?
What happened?
(DOOR OPENS)
Louis, are you okay?
What the hell
is going on here?
Nothing's going on here.
What the hell are you
doing in my house?
Your house?
Louis, who are
these people?
These people are the
registered owners
of this property.
You mean the one you said
had been in your family
for generations?
That's a lie.
We built this
house ourselves,
and until five minutes ago,
we were gonna
sell it to him.
Tara, I can explain.
I don't need
you to explain.
I've heard enough.
Tara, wait.
Please.
Tara, please wait.
You know, I've heard
about people like you.
You're trying
to get free design
work out of me
so you can decide
whether or not you want
to buy this house.
That has nothing
to do with it.
Really? Because first,
you tried to get me
to work on this
without even
seeing the space.
Then you lured me out here
under false pretenses.
So, why don't you
tell me what exactly
is going on here?
I lied to you
about owning a house
in the Hamptons
so I could spend
time with you.
What? Why?
Why would you do that?
Because you are perfect,
and beautiful,
and intelligent,
and talented.
And so far
out of my league
it was the only thing
that I could come up with
to find the time I needed
to make you fall for me.
You were willing
to buy and remodel
an entire house
to do that?
I was.
That's the most
romantic thing
I've ever heard.
Really?
Yeah. Yes, really.
(CHUCKLES)
Tara, would you like
to have dinner with me?
I'd love to, Louis.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
RACHEL:
What are you working on?
An engagement letter.
You got a new client.
I got us two new clients.
So, that's what you had
to do the other day.
Well, something like that.
The one I got the other day
led to the one I got today.
That's great.
Yeah, what's
on your mind?
I know you said
that you'd give me
an hour of your time
later this week,
but I need
that hour tonight.
Rachel, it's been
a long day.
Can we talk about this
in the morning?
No, Jessica, we can't.
Leonard Bailey's
execution date's been set.
And I don't know
how to tell a man
that he's going to die.
You know, I always knew
that Jill and I were
from two different worlds.
I mean,
she was a Sutter
and I was just...
A guy who was good
with numbers
and didn't have much else.
I figured it was only
a matter of time
before she came
to her senses.
But she never did.
And let me guess.
William never
accepted it.
So, when he asked me
to develop that algorithm,
I thought...
This was my chance.
And when I gave it to him,
he acted so proud.
Started calling me
his genius son-in-law.
But I was really just
the world's biggest sucker,
because I let that
son of a bitch
get one over on me
and I'll regret it
for the rest of my life.
What if you could get
one over on him?
What are you
talking about?
You said yourself
they offered you a deal.
I bet they'd
still take it.
No way.
If I give them him,
they go after her.
Not if you get them
to give Jill
immunity first.
No.
Kevin, you have to.
It's too big a risk.
And, and you're my
father-in-law's lawyer.
You can't even be
saying this to me.
I am nobody's lawyer.
I am your friend,
and I am saying...
Well, my answer's no.
And I want your
word right now
that you won't tell
anyone what I told you.
Kevin, please...
Mike, I'm serious.
No one can
ever know anything
about what I told you.
You have my word.
Did I ever tell you
my mother was a teacher?
First grade.
Everybody always said
she was the best teacher
their kid ever had.
And she loved it.
But she also always
dreamed of seeing Spain
when she retired.
That was supposed
to be six years ago.
But then the
State Teachers
Pension fund
decided to invest
its money with
William Sutter.
She died last year,
still working.
And every year,
I tried to pay
for her trip,
but she just
wouldn't let me.
Sean, why are you
telling me this?
Because the judge decided
to rule on your motion
to dismiss after all.
Which means
we're out of time.
And you didn't just
come here to tell me
about your mother.
No.
I came here to ask
for that trading program.
^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
P® Krishna_Teja P®