(HARVEY READING)
You had an alibi witness
and your public defender
let her get away?
That's what
I've been saying.
I told you
when I started
this thing
I'm not going to collude.
HARVEY: We're not colluding.
It's called discovery.
So, why don't you tell me
what Kevin Miller knows.
He developed
the trading programs
that Sutter claims
to use to get his
"superior" returns.
So, you're looking
to have Kevin testify
that software
is bullshit
and Sutter knows it.
The thing that
I worked so hard on
to get that prick's
approval was nothing
but a lie.
You told Jill.
She already knew.
She was in on it.
What the hell
is in the bag, Harvey?
What you needed to keep
this case going
and I stopped you
from getting.
So, let's just admit
that we're in this together
and get this thing done.
I want your
word right now
that you won't tell
anyone what I told you.
Kevin, please...
Mike, I'm serious.
No one can
ever know anything
about what I told you.
The judge decided
to rule on your motion
to dismiss after all.
Which means
we're out of time.
I came here to ask
for that trading program.
Leonard Bailey's
execution date's been set.
And I don't know
how to tell a man
that he's going to die.
(SIGHS)
(DOOR OPENING)
Who are you?
Mr. Bailey, my name
is Jessica Pearson.
And I'm lead counsel
on your case.
Well, you coming here,
it must be about
something important.
It is.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Leonard.
Your execution date
has been set.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
When?
Just because they've
set the date doesn't...
When?
Thirty days.
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(INHALES AND EXHALES SHARPLY)
Leonard, I'm so sorry.
I don't need
your sorry.
I want to know
what you're doing
about this.
We're going to file
a motion to delay.
I don't give a shit
about delaying.
I mean, what
are we doing
to get me out?
We're... We're
working on it.
But I...
I do think, Leonard,
that it's really important
that you take some time
to process the news.
I've been "processing"
for 12 years!
You said you were
gonna find Maria.
So, tell me.
What are you doing here
instead of out there
tracking her down?
Leonard, I know that
this is difficult and...
Mr. Bailey,
what Rachel means is
that's exactly what
we're going to do.
Mr. Cahill, you better have
a compelling reason
why I shouldn't grant
Mr. Specter a dismissal
or this thing is going to be
over before it gets started.
Oh, I have the most
compelling reason of all.
A copy of Mr. Sutter's
trading program.
HARVEY: Bullshit.
He was in here
trying to subpoena
this thing last week,
and now it miraculously
falls in his lap?
What are you implying?
I'm implying
I don't know what you did,
but Santa sure as hell
didn't put that thing
under your tree last night.
Well, unless you have proof
that I did something wrong,
you can shut the hell up.
JUDGE DORSEY:
All right, that's enough.
Now, assuming
this thing is legitimate,
what's it going to show me?
It's going to show you
it's responsible for 95%
of Mr. Sutter's trades
over five years.
Are you trying
to win this case
for me?
Because my entire defense
is that my client
makes his trades
using that program.
Exactly.
It's not the 95%
I'm concerned with,
it's the other five.
Those are the ones
he made billions
of dollars on.
And the only way
he could have done that
is by trading
on inside information.
Motion for dismissal denied.
Gentlemen,
we're going to trial.
But, Mr. Cahill,
if it comes to light
that you obtained
this program illegally,
not only am I
going to toss this case,
you're going to be
faced with a charge
of malicious prosecution.
Here's what
we're going to do.
I don't give a shit
what we're going to do.
I want to know
where the hell
he got that thing.
I don't know.
But that's not
the only question
we need to answer.
What other question
is there?
William, I don't know
if you've noticed,
but you've got
an employee
that's looking
to take you down
and we need
to figure out
who it is.
How exactly
are we going to do that?
We're going to start
conducting interviews
with every employee
you have.
But before we do that,
I'm going to make sure
Sean Cahill isn't
hiding anything else
from us in discovery.
So, if you'll excuse me,
I need to handle this myself.
What are you coming
to me here for, Harvey?
Sutter's 30 feet away.
Relax, he thinks
I'm making sure
that you didn't
pull another fast one
with discovery.
So, as long as it
looks like we're arguing,
we're fine.
That's not going
to be a problem,
'cause I got some news.
What are you talking about?
Two seconds after you left,
she put us on the docket.
We go to trial
in five days
and right now,
I don't have shit!
What do you
want me to say, Sean?
I'm already using
what we did
to shake the trees
with his employees.
That's not good enough.
So, you need to go
back to that prison
and tell Mike that he
better get me something,
and get it fast.
'Cause I didn't
sell my soul last night
to watch that bastard
ride off into the sunset.
(SINGING) See the money,
wanna stay for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
P® Krishna_Teja P®
Thank God
you are both here.
French cruller
for goddess number one.
Cinnamon sugar
for goddess number two.
While I do appreciate
a tasty donut,
I'd like to know what
the occasion is.
There are exactly
three reasons
for Louis to come
bearing pastry.
Esther got
a bad haircut,
he found someone
to fix his crooked thumb,
or he wants our advice.
I wish like hell
it was the thumb,
but it's
actually advice.
Last night, I had the most
amazing time with Tara.
And now you're both picturing
it involved fantastic sex.
Nope.
Not a bit.
In any event, Tara and I
have a date on Friday night,
and I'm hoping it ends
with our souls merging as one.
And I'm out.
What? Why?
Because I am a professional
secretary, Louis.
I'm not here
to help you play
hide the Litt
with some strumpet.
She so doesn't get me.
You know
what, Louis?
She has a point.
What are you talking about?
A lot of manpower
has been devoted
to your pursuit
of this virtual stranger.
And by "manpower," I mean
my precious time.
So, I think it's time
that you took care
of this yourself.
Goddamn it. Don't you think
if I could have, I would have?
What I think is,
if you can't figure out
how to have
a simple date
with a woman
who's already agreed
to go out with you,
then maybe
you don't deserve
to go out with her
in the first place.
How's that for advice?
Harvey.
What are you doing here?
What do you mean,
what am I doing here?
I need to know
if you have anything yet.
I don't.
Are you
kidding me?
After the way those
two guys got into it,
you're telling me
Kevin didn't start talking
the second he left the room?
No. He didn't
say a word.
Well, we need to get him
to say something
to get you
out of here.
Yeah, I know, but I can't
just push a button
and get Kevin
to turn on Sutter.
Yes, you can.
What are you
talking about?
You can tell him his algorithm
was leaked to Cahill.
When the hell
did that happen?
Last night,
when I leaked it.
Jesus Christ.
So, you're just out
and out colluding now.
Look, I didn't
have a choice.
The judge was going
to toss this case
unless Cahill came up
with a Hail Mary.
All right. I...
I'll use it the best
I can with Kevin, but...
Harvey, he's sensitive.
This is going to take
a little time.
That's the thing, Mike.
We don't have time.
The judge set a trial date.
Which means, if you don't
get Cahill something soon,
you're going to be sitting
here for the next two years.
JESSICA: What's
going on, Rachel?
You haven't said a word
the entire ride back.
Nothing.
It's just a lot harder
than I thought it would be.
You didn't think
he'd be angry?
I didn't think
that he'd be angry at us.
Well, he wasn't angry at us.
There just wasn't
anybody else in that room.
So, now what?
Now we try to fix
this damn thing.
You mean
by finding Maria Gomez.
I mean
by delaying this execution.
Jessica, Leonard's right.
What good does it do
to delay the execution
if we can't stop it
from happening?
Because if we don't,
we don't have time
to find Maria Gomez.
Hey.
KEVIN: Hey.
I was thinking about
what you told me
last night.
About getting Jill immunity.
Mike, I told you,
I don't want to
talk about this.
Maybe you want to talk about
what's going to happen to her
if Sutter goes down anyway.
That's
not going to happen.
You don't know that.
Yeah, well, I know
what happens if either
one of us turns on him.
We won't have
a penny to our name.
Are you kidding me?
Is he paying you
to be in here?
Listen to me.
Everything we have
is tied to that man.
And if he goes away,
we lose it all.
That's not what I asked.
Did he promise you money
if you kept quiet?
Of course
he goddamn did.
And the day
I get out of here,
Jill and I are going
to take that money
and start a new life.
Or you could both
cut a deal
and start a new life
right now.
What kind of life
is that going to be?
Because I come from nothing,
and I'm not going to do that
to my kids.
Well, I'm telling you,
there are worse things
you could be.
Why are you so interested
in my well-being?
Because
I'm your friend.
And I was in your position,
and I decided it was better
to give it all up than
to keep looking over
my shoulder
waiting for the axe
to fall.
What are you
talking about?
You know I was a fraud, right?
You know I did it
for years.
But what you don't know
is that I quit 20 minutes
before I got arrested.
And it was 20 of the
most peaceful minutes
of my entire life.
Yeah, well,
look what happened
to you anyways.
Kevin, that's not
the point.
That's enough.
I told you
I'm done talking about it,
and I'm done!
And if you're
really my friend,
you won't ever
bring this up to me again.
Get backstage seats
to Hamilton.
Mmm... Rent out
Central Park.
(TSKS)
Fly the Concorde to Paris.
No, wait, that's stupid,
because they don't have
the Concorde anymore.
Holy shit, that's it.
Find the last existing
Concorde,
rent it,
and fly that to Paris.
Louis, whatever
you're doing, I need
you to put it down.
Not now, Harvey.
I'm planning the ultimate date
for the love of my life.
This is for Mike.
All right.
What do you need me to do?
This is every big
money trade
William Sutter's made
in the last five years.
I need you to
go through it,
reverse-engineer it,
and find
any evidence you can
of insider trading.
That would be a lot
easier if I had access
to Sutter's files.
Well, I can't
get that to you
right now.
Why not?
Because he can't know
we're doing this.
Okay, Harvey. Last week,
you told me that you were
protecting me
by not telling me
what's going on.
Stop protecting me.
And what the hell
is going on?
I cut a deal
with Sean Cahill.
Sutter goes down,
Mike gets out.
Holy shit.
I know.
And don't tell me.
Mike still doesn't have
anything for you.
No, he doesn't.
And this trial starts
in five days.
Well, I better get on it.
Thank you, Louis.
Hey, Mike.
How's it going?
What are you
doing here, Gallo?
You know, when I was
on the outside,
I wasn't the biggest,
I wasn't the strongest,
I wasn't even the smartest,
but they let me run things.
You know why?
Nope.
But I have a feeling
you're about to tell me.
I had a knack for knowing when
something didn't smell right.
Something
doesn't smell right
with you.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You going to tell me Harvey
didn't stop by this morning
to see you?
Tracking my every move now?
I sure as hell am.
Do you think I'm going
to trust the two of you
with my freedom?
Harvey said that he'll
get you out, and he will.
And what if
he already tried
and he can't?
That didn't happen.
Yeah, well, let me run
a little scenario by you.
He filed whatever you filed
and it didn't fly.
Then he came to tell you that,
so the two of you would have
your stories straight
so you could string me along.
That's not
what happened, Gallo.
He came here
to see me about my case.
You want to
know something, Mike?
I don't give a shit
about your case.
So you tell Harvey,
next time he comes here,
he better come
with some progress
'cause I got
that sense of smell,
and something
in here stinks.
(RINGING)
Donna Paulsen's office.
How can I help you?
OPERATOR: You have
a call from Danbury...
I'll accept the charges.
Please hold while your call
is being connected.
MIKE: Donna.
My birthday's
not for another week,
but I appreciate the call.
Your birthday's not
for another five months
and six days,
and you know
I know that.
And I also know
that you'll be here
helping me celebrate
with everyone.
Thanks, Donna.
You doing okay?
Yeah, I'm hanging in.
Good.
Now, what's the favor
you were going to ask me?
How did you know?
Because you called my line
and not Harvey's,
and I know
when my friend needs me.
So why don't you tell me
how I can help?
Remember that time you
impersonated someone for me,
and then almost
went to prison?
Rings a bell.
I need you to do
the exact same thing.
Only this time, I found a way
to make it totally legal.
Let me get this straight.
You want me
to delay this man's execution
based on his own assertion
from 12 years ago
that there's an alibi witness.
Your Honor, we understand
that's not enough to re-open
the case.
We're just asking for more
time to locate the witness.
You've had 12 years
to locate the witness.
Not to mention that the day
the execution is set
is the day that their client
just happened
to suddenly
remember the witness
in the first place.
RACHEL: He didn't
"suddenly remember."
He's been saying it
for 12 years,
and he finally
found someone
who cares enough
about the truth to
help him find her.
How dare you?
I care about the truth,
and I convicted a murderer.
Your Honor, this was
a brutal murder of two
16-year-old children.
And the families
of both of those children
are here today
because they've waited
12 years for their
nightmare to finally end
and there is no legal reason
to prolong their suffering.
Your Honor...
You have the power to push
Leonard Bailey's execution
if you see fit.
Isn't it worth doing
if there's even a 1% chance
that he is innocent?
You have one week
to find a witness.
After that, you cannot move
to re-open his trial
and his execution date
is set in stone.
(GAVEL THUDS)
Hey, there you are.
I've been looking
for you all morning.
I had something important
to do, Louis.
And now, I have actual work
to catch up on,
so I can't really talk to you
about your date right now.
No, no, no. It's not
about my date.
It's about
Harvey's case.
And I know
it's for Mike.
What is it?
Harvey wants me
to reverse engineer
Sutter's trades,
but I can't do that without
access to a trading database.
And we can't ask
the SEC
because they're supposed
to be on the other side.
So, why are you
coming to me?
Because
Stu "Dickface" Buzzini
has a database.
And he's the last person in
the world who would help you.
Donna, please,
I would not be
coming to you
if there was
another way.
But I have been up all night
and there is no other way.
I'll take care of it, Louis.
Here.
What's this?
That's my guy.
Your guy?
My private investigator.
Why doesn't it
say it on the card?
Because a guy that good
isn't in the phone book.
Listen, Rachel, when you
get to a certain level,
everybody has
their person.
Harvey has Vanessa.
I have Carter.
And now, I do, too.
No, you have him for this
because we don't have time.
After that, you get
your own guy.
I don't understand.
Why can't I use your guy, too?
Because then
he wouldn't be
my guy.
What can I do for you, Red?
I'm in the middle
of something.
You can turn away
from that screen
for two seconds
and introduce
yourself to me
like a gentleman.
Why is it any time someone
from your office comes to me,
they've always got some kind
of comment on my manners?
Maybe that's a question you
should be asking yourself.
But I don't have time
to delve into why
you'll never do that
because I need you to give
Louis Litt access to your
entire securities database.
Listen to me.
I don't know who
the hell you are,
but why exactly
am I going to do
that for you?
Because when you do,
I'll owe you one.
And if you don't
know it already,
that's like anyone
else owing you 50.
I don't buy it.
Then why don't you
call your friend Larry
at Merrill Lynch
or Kenny at Morgan Stanley
or Howard Jaffe
from you know where?
How the hell do you
know about Howard?
I know about
all of them.
Because
it's what I do.
Okay, uh, you can have
whatever you want.
Good. And since you
questioned my abilities,
you're not only
going to give Louis
that database,
you're going to treat him
with the respect he deserves
for the rest of your life.
I never did
anything wrong to him.
And if you think
that's true,
then you need to
take a good look
in the mirror
because you violated
his bullpen and his mugs.
And with the exception
of my friendship,
those are the two most
important things in his
entire life.
(EXHALES)
I can see
by that look
on your face,
you're wondering
who I am after all.
Let me save you
the trouble.
I'm Donna,
and I'm awesome.
Oh, excuse me. I think
I'm in the wrong room.
No, you're not.
Where is Kevin?
I'm his cellmate,
and where he is isn't
important right now.
I got a phone call
from a guard
saying that my husband
wanted to see me
and I want to know
what's going on.
No, you got
a phone call
from someone saying
they were calling
from Danbury,
which is exactly where
that call was made.
And now, it's exactly
where I'm headed out of.
I know you're helping your
father make illegal trades.
What?
You can go ahead and deny it,
but Kevin told me everything.
What do you want?
I want to help you.
Well, I don't believe you.
I don't care if you
believe it or not.
But you have a small window
to come clean with the
SEC and save yourself.
Not that it's any of your
business, but I would never
turn on my own father.
That's too bad.
Because if you don't,
you're both going
to end up behind bars.
What exactly
is in this for you?
There's nothing in it for me
besides the fact that I care
about Kevin.
Listen to me.
I used to work
for Harvey Specter,
your father's lawyer.
If he found out that I was
doing this, he would kill me.
And what if I tell my father
about all this?
You're not going to do that.
Because Kevin already told me
that you guys are planning
to go away on William's dime.
So, if your father
finds out that Kevin's
been talking to me,
that dime's going to go away.
Like I said...
I'm in the wrong room.
(DOOR CLOSES)
HARVEY: Have a seat, Bryan.
I just have a few questions,
then you can be on your way.
What exactly
is this about?
You don't know?
No.
I talked to ten people here,
and no one will tell me
a thing
except that this isn't
going to be easy.
That's because the SEC
got an anonymous copy
of William Sutter's
trading program,
and I want to find the son
of a bitch who leaked it.
Well, I can tell you
it wasn't me.
Which is exactly what those
ten other clowns just said.
And I'll tell you
what I told them.
It didn't magically appear
on their doorstep.
I don't care
how they got it.
And if that's
your only question,
I need to
get back to work.
You'll leave
when I say you can leave.
What did you say?
I said
sit the hell down.
(CLEARS THROAT)
You've been a V.P.
for five years,
but you took meetings
at Goldman and Morgan,
last summer?
Which I disclosed
to Mr. Sutter.
I don't care.
You didn't get those jobs
because they didn't want you.
And now, you're pissed off
that people under you
are making
twice your salary,
so you went running
to the SEC.
I already told you
I didn't do that.
Where were you
three nights ago?
I was at dinner.
You can check.
Was it with your old
buddy, Henry Reese,
who just happens to play
rec-league basketball
with five SEC lawyers?
I haven't seen Henry
in six months,
and I'm getting a little
sick and tired of this
interrogation.
Well, I'm getting sick and
tired of assholes like you
not taking this thing
seriously.
What? I... I didn't say
I wasn't taking it seriously.
Yeah, I don't give a shit
what you said.
I give a shit that
you start listening
to what I'm goddamn
telling you.
Because when the SEC
gets you on the stand,
they're going to
go through your life
with a fine-toothed comb.
And if you've got
something to hide,
they're going to find it.
I'm sorry.
Good.
Now, get the hell of my sight
and send the next asshole in.
Louis, can I talk to you
for a minute?
Only if you're here
to bring me what I need.
I am.
That baby will link you
directly to our mainframe.
You need anything else,
you come to me.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
But that's not all.
I also brought a little
something to make things
right between us.
I took the liberty
of updating the design.
I hope you like it.
I love it.
Good.
'Cause there's six dozen
more in the file room.
Fresh start, bro?
Fresh start.
Hey, Stu.
What exactly did Donna say
to get you to do all this?
She just held up a mirror.
And the truth is,
it never hurts
to get a second opinion on
how you treat other people.
Jessica, you were right
to give me Carter.
I never would have
found out what happened
to Maria Gomez
without him.
Let's have it.
She filed for a name change
in New Jersey in 2008.
What's her new name?
That's just it.
Carter couldn't get it.
The only reason he
couldn't get it is if the
state is denying access
to those records
for her own safety.
Exactly. She filed numerous
restraining orders against
her ex-husband.
And now
her records are sealed
for the next two years.
All right. I'll see if there's
someone at the Newark DA's
office who can help us.
If not, maybe Harvey
knows someone.
I know someone.
My father
went to law school
with Jim Rogers,
the Newark District Attorney.
And you don't want to go to
your father because you don't
want to ask him for a favor.
I don't want him
to keep seeing me
as some little girl
who's always
asking for help
with something.
Rachel, being a lawyer
means you have to ask
people for help,
no matter who they are.
Which means
if you want to let your
father know that you're
not a little girl anymore,
then show him
you're not afraid to
ask him for a favor.
Have a seat, Jennifer.
I just have a few questions,
then you can be on your way.
SUTTER: I think
I'll stand.
You're not Jennifer.
No, I'm not.
And I'm not sending
another person in here
until you tell me what
the hell you're doing.
I'm doing what I said
I was going to do.
You said you would
shake the trees,
not burn down
the whole forest.
Listen to me.
No, you listen to me.
You're driving
my people away,
and that ends now.
William, I don't think
you understand.
The sooner
the son of a bitch
who leaked this thing
stops helping them,
the better for us.
What makes you think
whoever it is
is going to stop
helping them?
Look, they handed it in
anonymously.
Which means
whoever this asshole is,
the one thing
that he showed us is,
he's a coward.
And the only way
to stop a coward
is to scare
the shit out of him.
Well, if winning my case
means losing
all my employees,
then forget about
the whole thing.
William, we can't stop.
That's enough!
Instead of
looking for someone
who did something
they already did,
you're going to get back
to preparing my defense.
And the next time I see you,
you'd better be giving
the most kickass
opening statement
the world's ever seen.
Hey. Hey.
What the hell
did you do?
All right, Kevin,
let me explain.
Explain what?
That you called
my wife in here
pretending to be me?
Just listen to me.
You know, I can't
believe you, man.
I told you
not to tell anyone
what we talked about.
And I didn't tell anyone
who didn't already know.
And I don't give a shit
because this is none of
your goddamn business.
Yeah, well, I made it
my goddamn business
because there is a freight
train headed right at you,
and if I didn't do
everything I could
to stop it,
I wouldn't be able
to live with myself.
Well, you didn't stop it.
You slammed it
right into my marriage.
Because Jill and I,
we haven't fought
like we just did
since the night that
landed me in here.
So, from now on,
take your goddamn
good intentions
and go to hell.
You know what?
You should be
thanking me.
Thanking you? For what,
screwing up my life?
In case
you haven't noticed,
your life is already
screwed up.
You're in here because
of some other guy's crime.
And if he gets caught, you're
going to be in here together.
And then all of that
fictional money
that he's dangling
in front of you
isn't going to
be there anymore.
Now I get why you're going
to all this trouble.
You regret that you took
a deal for someone
and he's out there
while you're in here.
Well, I don't.
Because I didn't take this
deal for that son of a bitch.
I took it for my wife,
who I love.
And if you ever contact her
again without my blessing,
I swear to God, I will beat
the shit out of you.
Donna, where
the hell is Louis?
He's working
on what you wanted.
Well, find him,
because I need him.
Harvey,
what's the matter?
What's the matter is
I just spent the whole day
at Sutter's
trying to flush out
whoever's in on this
with him
and I got nowhere.
I don't understand.
It's going to take time.
This was only one day.
Which would be true,
except Sutter shut me down
and I don't have another day.
And like I said,
while I was there,
I didn't see a guilty look
on a single person's face.
Because the person you're
looking for doesn't work
for William Sutter.
Holy shit. You found him?
I didn't just find him.
I got back-up.
The one commonality
on all the trades
Sutter made money on
was they preceded
some sort of transaction
involving
an investment bank.
I know that, but there
were 50 different trades
with 20 different banks.
Twenty different
agent banks.
What the hell
other kind of bank is there?
The kind of bank you hire
to give you a second opinion.
Holy shit.
The consulting banks.
LOUIS: Exactly.
Which, by the way,
are not required
to be disclosed.
How many different banks
were they?
Just one. And that bank's
consulting division
happens to be run by a man
whose first job on Wall Street
was working
for William Sutter.
Sorry to be showing up
at your place again, Sean.
But this can't wait.
That's okay, Harvey.
You caught me
in a good mood.
Well, I'm about
to make it better
because we found the guy
who's been feeding Sutter
his information.
His name is...
Phillip Allen, I know.
How do you know?
He came by to cut a deal
two hours ago, so I gave
him one.
No, you goddamn didn't.
What's your problem?
My problem is
I drove him to you.
So what? We're at the
finish line, Harvey.
This is what we've been
after the whole time.
This is what you've been
after this whole time.
What I've been after
is getting Mike out.
So, if you think you
can weasel out of
this deal after I...
Harvey, relax.
As far as the SEC
is concerned, Mike led
directly to the witness
that's going to put
that piece of shit away
for the rest
of his miserable life.
So, Mike's deal
is still intact?
Rock solid.
We got him, Harvey.
The good guys won.
Then I guess
the next time you see me,
I'm going to
be pretending
to be outraged
that you
hadn't notified us
of your new witness.
And I'll be pretending
to be outraged
at whatever bullshit
you try to pull.
I'll try not to be
too outrageous.
You do that.
Thanks, Sean.
You're welcome, Harvey.
Rachel.
Did I mess something up?
I didn't think
we had plans tonight.
I'm not here
for plans.
Then what
are you here for?
I need your help
with a case.
You're not seriously
asking me to help
my rival firm, are you?
No, it's not corporate.
This is from the
Innocence Project.
And since when
did Jessica Pearson
take on an Innocence
Project case?
Since I asked her to.
Well, that's great, Rachel.
I'm proud of you.
What do you need?
There's a privacy statute
in the state of New Jersey
that's preventing me
from finding a witness.
And Jim Rogers won't
take a call from you,
but he will from me.
Exactly.
And if you do this for me,
I will owe you one.
Rachel, you're my daughter.
You'll never owe me one.
Mmm-mmm. I'm not here
as your daughter.
I'm here as a lawyer.
Then, don't forget this,
because someday,
I'm going to come calling.
Mike, sit down.
I hope you didn't come
all the way down here
just to tell me
that we're running
out of time,
because I already
know that.
I didn't.
I came here to tell you
that we got the guy.
What guy?
The guy who's been feeding
inside information to Sutter.
And I drove him to Cahill,
which means
you're getting out.
Mike, did you hear me?
You're getting out.
No, I... I know.
I...
Look, the problem is
that if you're going
to get Sutter
you're also going
to get Kevin's wife.
What the hell
are you talking about?
(SIGHS)
Kevin told me
that the reason he
never cut a deal
was because his wife
was in on it.
Are you kidding me?
You've been keeping this
to yourself?
I haven't just been
keeping it to myself.
I've also tried to
convince Kevin and Jill
to both come clean.
Both of them?
You went to her?
Harvey, listen to me.
No, you listen to me.
I don't give a shit
what your conscience
is telling you.
We got the guy.
We're going to take him down.
That means you get out.
I know that.
And I love that,
but all I need you to do
is convince Cahill to cut
Jill a deal, too.
I don't think
you understand.
This guy came forward.
He's the guy
that gets the deal
and you're the guy
that gets the deal.
There's no third deal.
Harvey, please.
I've betrayed this man enough.
I need you to convince Cahill
that one person makes a case,
but two people is a slam dunk.
Okay, Mike.
I'll make it happen.
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
Louis?
Do you have a second?
Actually, I don't, Donna,
because I'm going on
the most important date
of my life tonight,
and I have no idea
where I'm taking her.
Yes, you do.
Never heard
of this place.
That's because it's
an intimate restaurant
that's been there 50 years
and no one knows about it.
Which makes it
the perfect place to
get to know someone
you think you might
be falling in love with.
Donna, I need
to blow her away.
No, Louis. You need to
let her get to know you
and let fate
take care of the rest.
What if I'm not good enough?
You are good enough.
Hey. I thought you were
too busy to help.
The truth is,
when you asked me for help,
it wasn't a great morning
for me to be thinking about
that kind of thing.
I don't understand.
I had been seeing someone
for the last few months
and we broke up.
Tell me the son of a bitch's
name right now and I'm going
to freeze his assets
by the end of the week.
His name is Mitchell,
and you don't have to do that.
Yes, I do, Donna.
You're everything to me
and that asshole has no idea
what he's got...
It was my decision, Louis.
Well, then,
why were you so upset?
It's the same thing it was
with you and Sheila.
Just because you were the one
to break it off with her
doesn't mean that your heart
wasn't still broken.
I love you, Donna.
I love you, too, Louis.
Sir, may I help you?
Yes.
You can direct me
to Jessica Pearson.
Ms. Pearson's gone
for the evening
but I can take down your
information and she'll get
back to you in the morning.
You're not
taking anything down.
I need to speak
with someone now.
RACHEL: You can speak
with me, Mr. Forrest.
I assume you're here
to talk about Leonard Bailey.
I'm here
to show you this.
This is what that man
did to my daughter.
Mr. Forrest, I know that
this must be incredibly
difficult.
And it may not seem
that way to you,
but I am seeking justice
for your daughter.
We got justice when that
animal was sentenced
to death.
So, don't you try to tell me
you're doing this for her.
I'm doing this
for everyone.
The case
was grossly mishandled.
That's not
for you to decide.
You're right, sir.
It's for a jury to decide.
A jury did decide!
And they weren't presented
with all the facts.
The facts are
he killed my girl!
Mr. Forrest,
I'm so sorry for your loss,
but I believe in my heart
that Leonard Bailey
is innocent.
And I'm going to make sure
that he gets the fair trial
that he never had.
By tracking down
some junkie witness?
Drug user or not,
Maria Gomez never had
a chance to be heard.
If you'll excuse me,
I need to go to my office.
I'm not going
anywhere!
Not until you understand that
if you are "sorry" for me,
you wouldn't have taken this
case on in the first place,
instead of using it
to make a name for yourself.
GRETCHEN: That's enough.
You said everything
you needed to say.
Now, walk yourself
out of here
before I have security
remove you.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Hey.
You all right?
I will be.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Thank you, Gretchen.
Can we talk?
There's nothing
to talk about.
There is for me.
All right, then,
go ahead.
It won't make any difference
'cause I already
put in for a transfer.
You're moving
to another cell?
Yeah, I am.
So, whatever it is
you were going to say,
let's just pretend
you said it
and I let it go,
and we move our
separate directions.
Okay?
No. I can't do that.
Why not?
Because you were right.
I am pissed that
I took a deal to
save other people.
And now, I'm sitting in here
for two goddamn years
while they're out there.
If you still want to
transfer cells, I get it.
I won't hold
any hard feelings.
But I want you to know
that hurting you and Jill
is the last thing
that I wanted to do.
I'm going to head
to movie night.
Hope to see you there.
Jessica, I thought you
went home for the night.
I came back.
I heard you had some trouble
with the victim's father.
Gretchen told you.
Yes, she did.
And I'm glad she did.
Did he threaten you?
No.
I guess I should
have told you
people don't always
act rationally when
they're suffering.
They look
for someone to blame.
Yeah, well, he's blaming me.
Yes, he is.
And he's wrong.
I know.
And that's an easy thing
to understand,
but a harder thing
to endure.
Well, it just got
a little bit easier knowing
that you're in it with me.
Let's go get a drink.
After what happened before,
I think I might have two.
Louis, this place is...
It's too quiet in here,
isn't it?
And the seats aren't padded.
You hate it. I know it.
No, Louis, it's perfect.
It's exactly
what I'd hoped for.
Well, I wanted to show you
how much you mean to me.
Louis...
I get it.
You don't feel the same way.
It's not that.
I have something
to tell you
and I didn't know
how to bring it up,
or even when.
But you made
such a romantic gesture
that it feels wrong
not to tell you about it.
What is it?
I have a boyfriend
who lives in Los Angeles
six months of the year.
We care about
each other deeply,
but living across the
country takes its toll.
So we came up
with an arrangement
where we allow each other
to see other people.
You... You're saying
you want to date both of us?
I know it sounds
crazy. (SIGHS)
The truth is, I've never
actually taken him up on it,
but then I met you,
and here we are.
Louis, please
say something.
I need a second.
I... I understand
if you want to go.
No.
I'd like to stay.
You want to
go for dinner
or just drinks?
What do you want?
The truth? I'd rather
just go to a dive bar.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Sounds perfect to me.
Dad, what are
you doing here?
I came to talk
to both of you.
What is it?
Jim Rogers found your
missing witness.
She died three years ago.
Hey, look who it is.
I'm headed
to movie night, Gallo.
I don't have time
for this.
This will just take a second.
I won't even
make you miss
the previews.
Let's get this
over with.
It's been brought
to my attention
that Harvey came
to visit you and not me
again today.
And like I told you,
he came here to talk
about my case.
Yeah, that's what
you said the last time.
But I got to thinking.
And the thing is,
you took a deal,
which means
you don't have a case.
Gallo, look,
I'm telling you.
Harvey is going
to get you out.
I know he is.
Because I know what
you're up to in here.
And the reason I know is
because I did the
same thing myself.
What are you talking.
You're informing
on your roommate.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
Don't I?
Everybody in here
knows that guy's
their ticket out.
It doesn't take a genius
to figure out you have
access to him.
So, I did some checking.
Turns out Harvey's
representing the kid's
daddy-in-law.
And I know
Harvey does dirty tricks,
because that's what
landed me in here.
Gallo...
You guys
are going after Sutter.
I know it
and you know it.
And I'll tell you
something else.
You don't get me
out of here soon,
your bunkmate's
going to know it, too.
Sean, good,
you're here.
I need you to do
something for me
and you're not
going to like it.
Harvey, I need you
to sit down.
What do you mean,
"Sit down"?
They pulled Mike's deal.
What did you
just say to me?
Harvey...
'Cause it sounded like
you just said that thing
that you told me
was rock solid was nothing
more than a bucket of shit.
What do you
want me to say?
I want you to say
you'll get his deal back.
I can't do that.
They pulled the plug.
Goddamn it. I drove
that guy to you.
Don't you think
that I know that?
But if I tell them that,
they're going to know
what we did.
Then don't use
Phillip Allen.
Cut him loose
and let Mike get you
what you need.
Wait, are you crazy?
Even if I wanted to do that,
they're not going to let
their star witness get away.
You are the head
of the department.
They will listen to you.
You tell them
this guy turned out
to be full of shit.
Then let me put it
a different way.
I'm not letting
my star witness get away
'cause I'm not letting
that bastard get away
with bilking people out of
their hard-earned money.
Sean, please.
There's got to be
another way to
make this happen.
I'm sorry, Harvey,
there isn't.
Then, get the hell
out of my sight.
^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
P® Krishna_Teja P®