[GASPS]
You made me jump.
Daisy, what is the matter with you?
You're all thumbs.
Sorry. I hate this room.
Why? What's the matter with it?
ANNA: Daisy?
Who's that from, Papa?
-You seem very absorbed.
-Your aunt Rosamond.
-Anything interesting?
-Nothing to trouble you with.
Poor Aunt Rosamond.
All alone in that big house.
-I feel so sorry for her.
-I don't.
All alone with plenty of money
in a house in Eaton Square?
I can't imagine anything better.
Really, Mary,
I wish you wouldn't talk like that.
There will come a day when
someone thinks you mean what you say.
It can't come soon enough for me.
Carson, I'll be in the library.
Will you let me know
when her ladyship is down?
-Certainly, my lord.
-Sybil, darling. This one's for you.
SYBIL: I saw another opening
for a secretary and I applied.
-But you never said.
-I didn't want you to be disappointed.
I thought you'd given up.
I'll never give up and nor will you.
Things are changing for women, Gwen.
-Not just the vote but our lives.
-But it's tomorrow! At 10:00.
Last time we waited for weeks
and weeks, and this one's tomorrow!
Then we must be ready
by tomorrow, mustn't we?
I thought I'd write to Edith
-to settle our promised church visit.
-If you want.
We can't just throw her over
when she made such an effort
to arrange the last one.
-It's all in your head.
-I don't think so.
Then she's barking up the wrong tree.
Poor Edith. I hope there's a right tree
for her somewhere.
Ma'am, I was wondering if
I might take some time this afternoon
-to help in the village hall.
-Why? What's happening?
It's the flower show, sir, next Saturday.
I'll give my father a hand with his stall,
if I may.
-Of course you must go.
-And so, I'm afraid, must I.
Is Mr. Carson about?
I don't think so.
I was just looking for him, myself.
[EXHALES]
Busy?
I'm just trying to sort out
the wretched flower show.
-I've had a letter from Rosamond.
-Don't tell me.
She wants a saddle of lamb and all
the fruit and vegetables we can muster.
She enjoys a taste of her old home.
She enjoys not paying for food.
There's something else...
Apparently, the word is going round London
that Evelyn Napier
has given up any thought of Mary.
That he's going to marry
one of the Semphill girls.
She writes as if, somehow,
it reflects badly on Mary.
Your dear sister is always
such a harbinger of joy.
No, as if...
As if Mary had somehow been
found wanting. In her character.
I don't believe Mr. Napier
would have said that.
-Neither do I, really, but...
-She ought to be married.
-Talk to her.
-She never listens to me.
If she did, she'd marry Matthew.
What about Anthony Strallan?
Anthony Strallan is at least my age
and as dull as paint.
I doubt she'd want to sit next to him
at dinner, let alone marry him.
She has to marry someone, Robert.
And if this is what's being said
in London, she has to marry soon.
You shouldn't do that in here.
I don't like being in
the pantry all alone.
And Mr. Carson won't mind.
He's gone into the village.
He'll mind if I tell him.
-That's pretty.
-Do you think so?
She wants it put onto a new shirt,
but it's a bit old-fashioned to my taste.
Oh, no, it's lovely.
Have you recovered, Daisy?
-What from?
-She had a bit of a turn.
When we were in Lady Mary's room.
-Didn't you?
-I'm fine, thank you.
What sort of a turn? Did you see a ghost?
Will you leave her alone,
if she doesn't want to talk about it?
I've often wondered if this place
is haunted. It ought to be.
By the spirits of maids and
footmen who died in slavery.
But not, in Thomas's case, from overwork.
[O'BRIEN SCOFFS]
Come on, Daisy. What was it?
I don't know. I was thinking...
First we had the Titanic.
-Don't keep harping back to that.
-I know it was a while ago, but we knew 'em.
I think of how I laid the fires for Mr.
Patrick, but he drowned in them icy waters.
For God's sake.
And then there was the Turkish gentleman.
It just seems there's been
too much death in the house.
But what's that got to do
with Lady Mary's bedroom?
Nothing. Nothing at all.
Afternoon, ma'am.
When do you put that magnificent display
of prizes on show?
Not till the day itself.
I remember a superb cup from last year.
The Grantham Cup.
It was donated by the late Lord Grantham
for the best bloom in the village.
-And who won it?
-I did.
Well done.
-And the year before?
-Her Ladyship won that one, too.
Heavens, how thrilling. And before that?
You've met my father.
Good afternoon, Mr. Molesley.
-What are you showing this year?
-Oh, this and that.
MOLESLEY: Only the finest roses
in the village.
Really? What an achievement.
It's a wonderful area for roses.
We're very lucky.
We'll see some beautiful
examples right across the show.
-Won't we, Mr. Molesley?
-If you say so, your ladyship.
-What's up with you?
-Nothing.
His lordship's blaming Mr. Napier
for spreading gossip about Lady Mary,
-but it was you, wasn't it?
-Why do you say that?
Because Napier wasn't in on it.
Only four people know
he was in her room that night.
You, me, Lady Mary and possibly Daisy.
And I haven't said nothing to nobody.
Well, I didn't tell about Pamuk.
I just wrote that Lady Mary
was no better than she ought to be.
-Who did you write it to?
-Only a friend of mine.
Valet to Lord Savident.
Oh, you know what they say
about old Savident.
Not so much an open mind
as an open mouth.
-No wonder it's all round London.
-You won't tell, will you?
-I'm in enough trouble as it is.
-Why? What's happened?
I think Mr. Bates saw me nicking
a bottle of wine.
-Has he told Mr. Carson?
-Not yet.
But he will when he's feeling spiteful.
I wish we could be shot of him.
Then think of something quick.
Turn the tables on him,
before he has the chance to nail you.
I thought you went to bed hours ago.
I was writing a note for Lynch.
I need the governess cart tomorrow.
Oh?
-I'm going into Malton.
-Don't risk the traffic in Malton.
Not now every Tom, Dick and Harry
seems to have a motor.
-Hardly.
-Last time I was there,
there were five cars
parked in the market place,
and another three drove past
while I was waiting.
Get Branson to take you in the car.
-Neither of us is using it.
-I thought I'd pop in on old Mrs. Stuart.
Will you tell Mama, if I forget?
You're late this morning.
The library grate
needed a real going-over.
-Are any of them down yet?
-Lady Sybil's in the dining room.
-I'll start with her room, then.
-Daisy?
You know when you were talking
about the feeling of death in the house.
I was just being silly.
I found myself wondering
about the connection between
the poor Turkish gentleman, Mr. Pamuk,
and Lady Mary's room.
Only you were saying how
you felt so uncomfortable in there.
Well, I've got to get on.
I'm late enough as it is.
Hello.
-Is everything all right?
-Oh, hello. I am about to send a telegram.
Oh.
Papa's sister is always nagging
him to send supplies to London,
and then we cable her so her butler
can be at King's Cross to meet them.
-It's idiotic, really.
-Is this Lady Rosamond Painswick?
-You have done your homework.
-She wrote to welcome me into the family,
which I thought pretty generous,
given the circumstances.
It's easy to be generous
when you have nothing to lose.
So are you doing any more
church visiting with Edith?
My mother's trying to set something up.
Watch out. I think she
has big plans for you.
Then she's in for
an equally big disappointment.
-Is it all right to do the fire?
-Why are you so late?
I went back to my room
after I'd woken everyone,
and I just shut my eyes for a moment.
I've been trying to catch up ever since.
-ANNA: Have you had any breakfast?
-Not a crumb.
Here.
-Wait! You can't take her biscuits.
-She never eats them. None of them do.
They're just thrown away
and changed every evening.
Thanks. She wouldn't mind anyway.
She's nice, Lady Sybil.
[EXCLAIMS]
-Gwen?
-[GASPS]
May I ask why you are sitting
on Lady Sybil's bed?
Well, you see, I had a turn, like a
burst of sickness, just sudden-like.
I had to sit down.
-It's true.
-Well, you'd better go and lie down.
-I'll tell Mrs. Hughes.
-I don't need to interrupt her morning.
I'm sure I'll be fine
if I could just put my feet up.
And how many bedrooms
have you still got to do?
-Just one. Lady Edith's.
-And you can manage on your own?
Well, she's no use
to man or beast in that state.
Go on. Shoo.
Daisy?
May I ask why you are holding
Lady Sybil's biscuit jar?
I was just polishing
it before I put it back.
See that you do.
MRS PATMORE: I'm sorry, my lady,
but I can't do more than my best.
Is there some difficulty, your ladyship?
Dear Mrs. Hughes, as you know,
we're giving a dinner on Friday
for Sir Anthony Strallan.
Yes, my lady.
Well, it seems he is particularly fond
of a certain new pudding.
It's called apple
charlotte. Do you know it?
I'm not sure.
His sister, Mrs. Chetwood,
sent me the receipt,
I'm trying to persuade Mrs. Patmore
to make it.
And I'm trying to persuade her ladyship
that I have already planned the dinner
with her, and I can't change it now.
Why not?
Because everything's been
ordered and prepared.
Well, there's nothing here
that looks very complicated.
Apples, lemons, butter...
I cannot work from a new receipt
at a moment's notice!
But I can read it to you,
if that's the problem.
Problem?
Who mentioned a problem?
How dare you say such a thing
in front of her ladyship!
Very well. We'll try it another time,
when you've had longer to prepare.
We'll stay with the raspberry meringue.
-And very nice it'll be, too.
-I'm sure.
MRS PATMORE:
Have you taken leave of your senses?
I'm so sorry about that, my lady.
Never mind. I was asking a lot.
-Do look after that girl.
-Daisy?
-She's used to it. She'll be all right.
-I wonder.
Mrs. Patmore looks ready to eat her alive.
I was only trying to help.
Oh, like Judas was only
"trying to help" I suppose,
when he brought the Roman soldiers
to the garden!
I had to let your skirt down a little,
but I can put it back.
No, it's yours.
What will happen if one of the
maids finds your room is empty?
Oh, but it'd only be Anna,
and she wouldn't give me away.
She's like a sister.
She'd never betray me.
[CHUCKLES] Then she's not like my sisters.
Walk on.
-Shall I give you a hand?
-Oh, would you?
It takes half the time with two.
-I always feel a bit sorry for Lady Edith.
-Me too.
Although I don't know why,
when you think what
she's got and we haven't.
Mrs. Hughes said she was after
the other heir, Mr Patrick Crawley.
-The one who drowned.
-That was different.
-She was in love with him.
-What happened?
She never got a look in.
He was all set up to marry Lady Mary.
Then he was a braver man
than I am, Gunga Din.
Sad to think about.
It's always sad when you love someone
who doesn't love you back.
No matter who you are.
No, I mean it's sad that he died.
Oh. Yes.
Very sad. He was nice.
Well, thank you for that.
-Much appreciated.
-My pleasure.
Perhaps Mr. Patrick did love her back,
he just couldn't say it.
Why ever not?
Sometimes we're not at liberty to speak.
Sometimes it wouldn't be right.
Take a seat.
[DOOR OPENING]
COUNTESS: The flower show?
Oh, I thought I was in for another
telling off about the hospital.
No. This time it's the flower show.
I've been to see old Mr. Molesley's garden.
And his roses are the most beautiful
I've ever laid eyes on.
-Go on.
-You may not know it,
but I believe the committee feel
obliged to give you the cup
for the best bloom
as a kind of local tradition.
No. No, I do not know that.
I thought I usually won the prize
for "best bloom in the village"
because my gardener had
grown the best bloom in the village.
Yes, but you don't "usually" win, do you?
You always win.
Yes. I have been very fortunate
in that regard.
But, surely, when Mr. Molesley's garden
is so remarkable
and he is so very proud of his roses...
You talk of Mr. Molesley's pride?
What about my gardener's pride?
Is he to be sacrificed on the altar
of Molesley's ambition?
All I'm asking is that you release them
from any obligation to let you win.
Why not just tell them to choose
whichever flower is best?
But that is precisely
what they already know.
And do.
I'm sorry, my lord.
I didn't think you'd be in here.
Are my eyes deceiving me
or is one of these missing?
-I don't know them well enough.
-No. Why would you?
But there's a very pretty little blue one,
with a miniature framed in French paste.
It was made for a German prince.
I forget who.
Unless it's been moved for some reason.
But why would it be?
Can you help? I should be so grateful.
Our horse has cast a shoe.
Is there a smithy nearby?
Aye. You can try old Crump
in the next village.
BOTH: Thank you.
See, help's at hand.
And at least it happened on the way home.
Oh, they'll be worried about you.
And if they check on me, I'm finished.
-Is her ladyship wearing that now?
-Oh, no. This is for Friday night.
I just thought I'd give it a press
while I had the time.
You don't know what's happened
to Lady Sybil, do you?
I've got the changes ready for the
other two, but there's no sign of her.
Don't you start. I've had Her Majesty
on at me all afternoon.
Mr. Carson says he'll fetch the police
if she's not back soon.
Sorry, Miss. But Mr. Crump's staying
over at the Skelton estate tonight.
He's working there all week.
-Is there anyone else?
-Not that I know of.
SYBIL: Come on, Dragon, come on!
Dragon, if you don't move now,
I'll have you boiled for glue!
But what if she's overturned?
What if she's lying in a ditch somewhere?
I'm sure she'll be back
in the shake of a lamb's tail.
The truth is they're all getting
too old for a mother's control.
-They're growing up.
-They've grown up.
They need their own establishments.
I'm sure they'll all get plenty of offers.
No one ever warns you
about bringing up daughters.
You think it's going to
be like Little Women,
and instead they're at each
other's throats from dawn till dusk.
You look done in.
I'll bring you some food up later
when we've finished dinner.
Where were you?
-You came up, then?
-Of course I did.
-I had to change for the afternoon.
-Did you cover for me?
What do you think?
I don't suppose this had
anything to do with Lady Sybil?
Oh, Anna, it was a nightmare.
I don't know how I got in
without being seen.
I'm sure I've left a trail
of mud up the stairs.
So, did you get the job?
We'll have to wait and see.
[CHUCKLES]
Sorry to bother you, my lady,
but your mother wanted you
to know Lady Sybil's back.
She's changing now,
so dinner won't be late, after all.
-What happened to her?
-The horse went lame.
Is there anything else?
There is something
that's been troubling me.
You remember the Turkish gentleman,
Mr. Pamuk?
-The one who died all sudden-like?
-Of course I remember.
Well, it's Daisy, my lady.
The kitchen maid.
Only she's been talking recently as if
she had ideas about Mr. Pamuk's death.
What sort of ideas?
Well, I've no proof and maybe I'm wrong.
But I've a sense she knows something,
but won't say what.
Something involving Lady Mary.
How absurd.
Well, what could she know?
Whatever it is, she won't say.
Not to us, anyway.
Have you spoken to Lady Mary about this?
I didn't like to, my lady.
It seemed impertinent somehow.
But I thought someone in the family
ought to know about it.
Quite right.
Bring the girl to my room tomorrow,
after breakfast.
-What did she want?
-Nothing.
Just a message from Mama to say
that Sybil had turned up alive.
Poor darling.
She had to walk for miles.
I don't think I'd have got down,
however lame the horse.
No. I don't believe you would.
I couldn't say, my lady.
I don't know what Miss O'Brien means.
I didn't see nothing.
Well, not much.
O'Brien, I wonder if you might leave us?
Now, it's Daisy, isn't it?
Yes, my lady.
I'm sure you see
O'Brien only acted as she did
-because she is concerned.
-I suppose so, my lady.
She seems to think that you are
in possession of some knowledge
that is uncomfortable for you.
[SNIFFLING]
Because if that is the case,
then I don't think it fair on you.
Why should you be burdened
with Mary's secret?
My dear, my heart goes out to you.
It really does.
There, there.
You've been carrying too heavy a burden
for too long.
Just tell me, and I
promise you'll feel better.
COUNTESS: You seem well prepared.
They'll add a few more flowers
before we open in the morning,
but I think we're nearly there.
Do look at Mr. Molesley's display.
He's worked so hard.
They're rather marvelous, aren't they?
Lovely. Well done, Mr. Molesley.
Thank you, my lady.
I think everyone is to be congratulated.
It's splendid.
But do look at these roses.
Have you ever seen the like?
My dear, Mrs. Crawley believes
I am profiting from an unfair advantage.
Oh?
She feels, in the past,
I have been given the cup
merely as a matter of routine
rather than merit.
That's rather ungallant, Mother. I'm
sure when we see Cousin Violet's roses,
it will be hard to think
they could be bettered.
Hard. But not impossible.
You are quite wonderful the way
you see room for improvement
wherever you look.
I never knew such reforming zeal.
I take that as a compliment.
I must have said it wrong.
[LAUGHS]
Poor Granny.
She's not used to being challenged.
Nor is Mother. I think we should
let them settle it between them.
So are you interested in flowers?
I'm interested in the village.
In fact, I'm on my way
to inspect the cottages.
You know what all work
and no play did for Jack?
But you think I'm a dull boy anyway.
Don't you?
I play, too. I'm coming
up for dinner tonight.
I suspect I'm there to
balance the numbers.
-Is it in aid of anything?
-Not that I know of.
Just a couple of dreary neighbors,
that's all.
-Maybe I'll shine by comparison.
-COUNTESS: Mary! We're going.
Maybe you will.
[CHATTERING]
CARSON: Might I have a word?
I want to say something
before I ring the gong.
I'm afraid it's not very pleasant.
His Lordship is missing
a very valuable snuff box.
It appears to have been taken
from the case in his room.
If one of you knows anything about this,
will he or she please come to me.
Your words will be heard
in the strictest confidence.
Thank you.
I am sorry, Mr. Bates.
What an unpleasant thing to have happened.
Why are you picking on him?
Because he's the only one of us
who goes in there.
But don't worry. I'm sure it'll turn up.
Thank you for your concern.
I hate this kind of thing.
I hope to God they find it.
Better get a move on.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
I'm coming.
Does this brooch work? I can't decide.
It's charming.
Oh, dear. Is it another scolding?
Of course not.
You're too grown up to scold these days.
Heavens. Then it's really serious.
I'd like you to look after
Sir Anthony Strallan tonight.
He's a nice, decent man.
His position may not be quite like Papa's
but it would still make you
a force for good in the county.
Mama, not again!
How many times am I to be ordered to marry
the man sitting next to me at dinner?
As many times as it takes.
I turned down Matthew Crawley.
Is it likely I'd marry Strallan
when I wouldn't marry him?
I am glad you've come to think
more highly of Cousin Matthew.
-That's not the point.
-No.
The point is, when you refused Matthew
you were the daughter of an earl
with an unsullied reputation.
Now you are damaged goods.
-Mama...
-Somehow, I don't know how,
there is a rumor in London
that you are not virtuous.
-What? Does Papa know about this?
-He knows it and he dismisses it,
because, unlike you and me,
he does not know that it is true.
Let's hope it's just unkind gossip.
Because if anyone heard about...
Kemal. My lover.
-Kemal Pamuk.
-Exactly.
If it gets around,
and you're not already married,
every door in London
will be slammed in your face.
Mama, the world is changing.
Not that much, and
not fast enough for you.
I know you mean to help.
I know you love me.
But I also know what I'm capable of,
and forty years of boredom
and duty just isn't possible for me.
I'm sorry.
I do love you and I want to help.
I'm a lost cause, Mama.
Leave me to manage my own affairs.
Why not concentrate on Edith?
She needs all the help she can get.
You mustn't be unkind to Edith.
She has fewer advantages than you.
MARY: Fewer? She has none at all.
Open the oven.
[SHRIEKS]
What's happened?
It's that bloomin' Daisy!
I said she'd be the death of me,
and now my word's come true!
I didn't do nothing!
Get away! Get back to the stables!
What'll you serve now?
Why, them, of course.
I ain't got nothing else.
Daisy give us a hand, get that cloth.
What's the matter with that?
Are you sure? Shouldn't we tell?
-Certainly not.
-Is the remove ready to go up?
Here we are.
ANNA: Daisy, give him a hand
with the vegetables.
They're up in the servery, in the warmer.
Well, I'm glad I don't have to eat them.
What the eye can't see,
the heart won't grieve over.
Hmm, there's no doubt about it.
The next few years in farming
are going to be about mechanization.
That's the test,
and we're going to have to meet it.
-Don't you agree, Lady Mary?
-Yes, of course, Sir Anthony. I'm sure I do.
Are we ever going to be allowed to turn?
Sir Anthony, it must be so hard
to meet the challenge of the future
and yet be fair to your employees.
That is the point, precisely.
We can't fight progress, but we must
find ways to soften the blow.
I should love to see
one of the new harvesters,
if you would ever let me.
-We don't have one here.
-I shall be delighted.
I hope they find that snuff box.
What happens if they don't?
They'll organize a search, won't they?
I wouldn't be Mr. Bates.
Not for all the tea in China.
Wouldn't you, Thomas? I dare
say he feels just the same about you.
-What's the matter with you?
-Nothing.
Oh! Just a minute.
I don't like to put it on earlier.
It sinks in and spoils the effect.
Mama has released me, thank God.
Sir Anthony seems nice enough.
If you want to talk farming
and foxes by the hour.
I'm rather looking forward
to the flower show tomorrow.
Where Mr. Molesley's roses
will turn everybody's heads.
But if you tell Granny I said so,
I'll denounce you as a liar.
I wouldn't dare.
I'll leave that to my fearless mother.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
-How were the cottages?
-They're coming on wonderfully.
I'd love to show you.
Obviously, it's an act
of faith at this stage.
Good God!
[CHOKING]
What on earth?
I do apologize, Lady Grantham.
But I had a mouthful of salt.
What?
Everyone, put down your forks.
Carson, remove this.
Bring fruit, bring cheese,
bring anything to take this taste away!
Sir Anthony, I am so sorry.
Fains I be Mrs. Patmore's
kitchen maid when the news gets out.
Poor girl.
We ought to send in a rescue party.
-You must think us very disorganized.
-Not at all.
These things happen.
[LAUGHING]
[CRYING]
Hey! Come on. It's not that bad.
Nobody's died.
I don't understand it!
It must have been that Daisy!
-She's muddled everything up before now!
-But I never...
Don't worry, Daisy.
You're not in the line of fire here.
I know that pudding!
I chose it 'cause I know it!
Which is why you wouldn't let her ladyship
have the pudding she wanted.
Because you didn't know it.
Exactly!
I don't see how it happened.
Come on, everyone. Let's give Mrs. Patmore
some room to breathe.
-You, too.
-I don't think I should leave her.
Yes, you should.
Mr. Carson knows what he's doing.
Don't do that.
Get William or the hall boy to do it.
It's beneath your dignity.
It won't kill me.
Now.
All in your own good time…
I think you've got something to tell me,
haven't you?
ANNA: I think I know
where that snuffbox is.
Where?
-Hidden in your room.
-You don't think...
'Course I don't, you silly beggar.
-Then?
-I bet Thomas'd like it
if they took you for a thief.
Yes, I expect he would.
Go upstairs now and find it.
And when you have, you can
choose whether to put it in Thomas's room
or give it to me,
and I'll slip it into Miss O'Brien's.
-You naughty girl.
-Fight fire with fire.
That's what my mum says.
Poor Mrs. Patmore. Do you think
you should go down and see her?
Tomorrow. She needs time
to recover her nerves.
I knew there was something going on.
It seems hard that poor Sir Anthony
had to pay the price.
Good God!
[LAUGHS]
As for your giggling like a ridiculous
schoolgirl with Cousin Matthew!
-It was pathetic.
-Poor Edith.
I am sorry Cousin Matthew's
proved a disappointment to you.
Who says he has?
Matthew. He told me.
Oh, sorry. Wasn't I supposed to know?
You were very helpful, Edith,
looking after Sir Anthony.
-You saved the day.
-I enjoyed it.
We seemed to have a lot to talk about.
-Spare me your boasting, please.
-Now who's jealous?
Jealous? Do you think I couldn't
have that old booby if I wanted him?
-Even you can't take every prize.
-Is that a challenge?
If you like.
I could almost manage for a long time,
knowing the kitchen
and where everything was kept.
-Even with that fool girl.
-I think you might owe Daisy an apology.
Maybe.
I've had a lot to put
up with, I can tell you.
And you've not been to a doctor?
I don't need a doctor to tell me
I'm going blind.
A blind cook, Mr. Carson.
[EXCLAIMS] What a joke.
Whoever heard of such a thing?
A blind cook.
I hope our salty pudding
didn't spoil the evening for you.
-On the contrary.
-I'm glad you and Mary are getting along.
-There's no reason you can't be friends.
-No. No reason at all.
I don't suppose there's any chance
that you could sort of start again?
Life is full of surprises.
Ah! I've been waiting for you.
I've found a book over here
and I think it's just the thing
to catch your interest.
Oh, really? I'm intrigued.
What could it be?
Well, I was looking
in the library and I...
I was very taken by
what you were saying over dinner
-about the way we...
-You're so right, Lady Mary.
How clever you are. This is exactly
what we have to be aware of.
There's a section just here
that I was rather unsure about.
It seems we have both been
thrown over for a bigger prize.
Heavens, is that the time?
You're not going?
The truth is my head's splitting.
I don't want to spoil the party,
so I'll slip away.
Would you make my excuses
to your parents?
Excuse me, Sir Anthony.
-Has Mr. Crawley left?
-Yes, my lady.
But what about the car?
Branson can't have brought it round
so quickly.
He said he'd rather walk, my lady.
Thank you.
-Mary can be such a child.
-What do you mean, darling?
ROBERT: She thinks if you put a toy down,
it'll still be sitting there
when you want to play with it again.
-What are you talking about?
-Never mind.
Mr. Carson?
We were wondering about that snuff box.
-Has it turned up yet?
-I'm afraid not.
Well, I think we should have a search.
What?
It doesn't do to leave
these things too long.
Mr Carson can search the men's rooms,
Mrs Hughes the women's.
And it should be right away,
now we've talked of it.
So no one has a chance to hide the box.
Don't you agree, Mr. Carson?
Well, perhaps it's for best.
Although I'm sure I won't find anything.
I'll fetch Mrs. Hughes.
-I think I'll just...
-I'd better check it's tidy.
The bastard's hidden it
in my room or yours.
Why did I ever listen to you
in the first place?
Miss O'Brien?
My, my. You have been busy.
I was expecting you later than this.
I'll tell Molesley to lock up.
Thanks. Good night, Mother.
How was your evening?
Did you enjoy yourself?
Quite.
The thing is, just for
a moment I thought...
Never mind what I thought.
I was wrong. Good night.
My word, Molesley,
splendid roses as usual.
-Well done.
-Thank you, your lordship.
All the stalls are set
out very well this year.
This is enchanting. Do we grow this?
I doubt if you've got
that one, your ladyship.
-I've only just found it, myself.
-CORA: is it a secret?
-Or could you tell Mr. Brocket?
-I'd be glad to, my lady.
He should come and see the rose garden.
He could give us some ideas.
Old Molesley's a champion.
Or he would be, in a fairer world.
Don't you start.
I'm afraid I've been annoying
Cousin Violet on that score.
If Mr. Molesley deserves
the first prize for his flowers,
-the judges will give it to him.
-They wouldn't dare.
Really, Robert. You make me so annoyed.
Isn't it possible
I should win the thing on merit?
I think the appropriate answer
to that, Mama, is, "Yes, dear".
I don't know why we're bothering.
-We'll have missed the speeches as it is.
-Don't be such a grouch.
You should have punished
one of them at least.
They know that I know,
that's worth something.
What do you think will happen
to Mrs. Patmore?
She'll muddle through with Daisy for help.
In the long term, we'll just have to wait
for the doctor to give his opinion.
I hope there's something they can do.
I hope so, too.
But if there isn't,
I hope they tell her there isn't.
Nothing is harder to live with
than false hope.
I wish you'd just come out with it.
With what?
Whatever it is you're keeping secret.
I can't.
-You don't deny it, then?
-No, I don't deny it.
And I don't deny you've a right to ask.
But I can't.
I'm not a free man.
Are you trying to tell me
that you're married?
I have been married, yes.
But that's not all of it.
Because...
Because I love you, Mr. Bates.
I know it's not ladylike to say it,
but I'm not a lady and
I don't pretend to be.
You are a lady to me.
And I never knew a finer one.
If you want a lift,
I can take one of you, but not more.
-One of the women.
-No, you must go.
-Then we can all hurry and meet you there.
-Yes, you're right.
I mustn't slow you down.
There's been too much of that already.
Have you recovered from our ordeal?
I got a letter this morning.
They must have written it
as soon as I left the office.
They are pleased to have met me,
but I do not quite fit their requirements.
So it was all for nothing.
I don't agree.
Only a fool doesn't know
when they've been beaten.
Then I'm a fool, for I'm a long way
from being beaten yet.
When you ran off last night,
I hope you hadn't thought me rude.
Certainly not. I monopolized you at dinner.
I'd no right to any more of your time.
You see, Edith and I
had this sort of bet...
Please don't apologize.
I had a lovely evening
and I'm glad we're on speaking terms.
Now, I should look after my mother.
Why was Cousin Matthew
in such a hurry to get away?
Don't be stupid.
I suppose you didn't want him
when he wanted you,
and now it's the other way round.
You have to admit it's quite funny.
I'll admit that if I ever wanted
to attract a man
I'd steer clear of those
clothes and that hat.
You think yourself so superior, don't you?
[MARY GROANS]
Well, I think she who laughs last
laughs longest.
CORA: Did that missing box of yours
ever turn up?
It was a fuss about nothing.
They must've put it back on the
wrong shelf when they were dusting.
Bates found it this morning.
Next time, have a proper look
before you start complaining.
I'm sure the servants
were frightened half to death.
Mea culpa.
And now, the Grantham Cup
for the best bloom in the village.
And the Grantham Cup is awarded to...
Mr. William Molesley
for his Comtesse Cabarrus rose.
Bravo! Well done! Bravo!
-Congratulations, Mr. Molesley.
-Thank you, my lady.
Thank you for letting me have it.
It is the judges who decide these things,
not me.
But very well done.
Congratulations!
Bravo, Mama.
That must have been a real sacrifice.
And bravely borne.
I don't know what everyone's on about.
-But I...
-All is well, my dear.
All is well.