There you are, Mr. Bates.
It's in. Came this morning.
They said it would,
which isn't quite the same thing.
[DOOR BELL JINGLING]
Hello.
I could have posted that for you.
Well, I prefer to do it myself.
I'll wait outside.
Lovely.
[GASPS]
What are you doing?
If you must know,
I'm trying to find some space
on top of the cupboard
to make life easier.
[SIGHS] So, what's in it, then?
What?
The bleeding great packing case
that weighs a ton, that's what.
-Can't you just leave it?
-No, I can't.
And you'll tell me right now.
-Anything interesting?
-Not particularly.
It's from Evelyn Napier.
You met him with the Delderfields
last November, at Doncaster races.
-Is that Lord Branksome's boy?
-It is.
Do you like him?
-I don't dislike him.
-And what's he writing about?
Nothing much, he's out with
the York and Ainsty next week.
The meet is at Downton.
He'll want some tea when he's up here.
Where's he staying? With friends?
He says he's found a pub
that caters for hunting.
Well, we can improve on that.
He must come here. He can
send the horses up early if he wants.
He'll know why you're asking him.
I can't think what you mean.
His mother's a friend of mine.
She'll be pleased at the idea.
Not very pleased, she's dead.
All the more reason, then.
You can write a note, too,
and put it in with mine.
Should I tell him about your friendship
with his late mother?
I am sure you, of all people,
can compose a letter
to a young man without any help from me.
-How much did it cost?
-Every penny I'd saved. Almost.
And is this the mystery lover?
I've been taking a correspondence course
in typing and shorthand.
That's what was in the envelopes.
-Are you any good?
-Yes.
I am, actually.
[DOOR OPENING]
Her ladyship wants the fawn skirt
Lady Mary never wears.
The seamstress is going to fit it to
Lady Sybil, but I can't find it.
I'll come in a minute.
-They're waiting now.
-One minute.
I'm just changing my cap and apron.
Have you told anyone?
What did your parents say?
I can't tell them till I've got a job.
Dad will think I'm a fool to leave a good place
and Mum will say I'm getting above myself,
-but I don't believe that.
-Nor do I.
It's not of my doing.
It's all Mary's own work.
But I think we should encourage it.
Branksome's a dull dog,
but I don't suppose that matters.
-Did you know his wife had died?
-He only ever talks about racing.
Cora is right.
Mary won't take Matthew Crawley,
so we'd better get her settled
before the bloom is
quite gone off the rose.
Is the family an old one?
Older than yours, I imagine.
-Old enough.
-And there's plenty of money.
-Oh, really?
-Hmm.
Mama, you've already looked him up
in the stud books
and made inquiries about the fortune,
don't pretend otherwise.
[SCOFFS] Are you afraid someone will think
you're American if you speak openly?
I doubt it'll come to that.
-Shall I ring for tea?
-No, not for me.
I'm meeting Cripps at five.
I'll see you at dinner.
You don't seem very pleased.
I'm pleased.
-It's not brilliant, but I'm pleased.
-So?
I don't want Robert to use a marriage
as an excuse to stop fighting
for Mary's inheritance.
It won't make any difference.
I don't think he has the slightest
intention of fighting as it is.
The price of saving Downton is to accept
Matthew Crawley as his heir.
What about you?
I don't dislike Matthew.
In fact, I rather admire him.
Is that sufficient reason
to give him your money?
-Of course not.
-Then there's nothing more to be said.
Are we going to have tea or not?
[BICYCLE BELL RINGING]
-Oh!
-Hello.
-I'd offer you a lift if I could.
-It was you I was coming to see.
Well, then, your timing is matchless.
I've just got off the train.
The other day, at dinner,
Cousin Isobel was saying you wanted
to see some of the local churches.
She's right. I do.
I want to know more about the county
generally, if I'm to live here.
Well, I thought I might show you
a few of the nearer ones.
We could take a picnic
and make an outing of it.
-That's very kind.
-Nonsense. I'll enjoy it.
It's too long since
I've played the tourist.
Well, it would have to be a Saturday.
The churches work on Sunday
and I work all the weekdays.
Then Saturday it is.
I'll get Lynch to sort out the governess
cart and I'll pick you up at about 11:00.
[EDITH CHUCKLES]
-How does it work?
-Well, it's easy.
You just press the letters
and they print on the paper.
Get back, please.
They were trying to hide it,
so I knew it was wrong.
Where's Gwen now?
Doing the dining room with Anna,
they'll be finishing.
Then I'll wait.
With all due respect, Mr. Carson,
Gwen is under my jurisdiction.
Indeed she is, Mrs. Hughes, and I have
no intention of usurping your authority.
I merely want to get to the bottom of it.
Why shouldn't Gwen have a typewriter,
if she wants one?
THOMAS: Mind your own business.
-What's that doing here?
-Ah, Gwen. Come in.
Why is that down here?
Who's been in my room? They had no right.
See here. In the first place,
none of the rooms in this house
belong to you.
And in the second,
I am in charge of your welfare
-and that gives me every right.
-This is you, isn't it?
All we want is to know
what Gwen wants with a typewriter
and why she feels the need
to keep it secret?
She wants to keep it private, not secret.
-There's a difference.
-Amen.
I've done nothing to be ashamed of.
I've bought a typewriter and I've
taken a postal course in shorthand.
I'm not aware that either
of these actions is illegal.
Will you tell us why,
preferably without any more cheek?
Because I want to leave service.
I want to be a secretary.
You want to leave service?
-What's wrong with being in service?
-Nothing's wrong with it.
And there's nothing wrong
with mending roads, neither,
but it's not what I want to do.
I should remind you
that there are plenty of young girls
who will be glad of a
position in this house.
And when I hand in my notice
I shall be happy
to think one of them
will be taking my place.
What makes you think we'll wait till then?
Are you hiring and sacking now,
Miss O'Brien?
I thought that lay
with Mr. Carson and Mrs Hughes.
Enough of this.
I'm going to ring the dressing gong
and we'll have no
more talk of this tonight.
Can I have my machine back now?
Very well, but I wish I were sure
you know what you're doing.
Daisy, what's happened to you?
I said you could go for a drink of water,
not a trip up the Nile.
-ANNA: Which churches will you show him?
-I can't decide.
Kirby, possibly, or perhaps Easingwold.
-You don't think you're being a bit obvious?
-Coming from you, that's rich.
There was a letter from Mr. Napier
in the evening post.
-Oh. Did he accept?
-Not yet.
-Perhaps he thought it was too obvious.
-Apparently, he's bringing a friend with him.
An attaché at the Turkish embassy.
A Mr. Kemal Pamuk.
He's the son of one of the sultan's ministers
and he's here for the Albanian talks.
-What's that?
-To create an independent Albania.
-Don't you read the papers?
-I'm too busy living a life.
Since Turkey's signature is vital,
Mr. Napier's been given the job
of keeping him happy
until the conference begins.
And he's eager to try an English hunt.
I shall invite this Mr. Pamuk
to stay here as well.
Who knows,
a little hospitality in an English house
may make all the difference to the outcome.
And Mary, you will ride out with him.
Oh, Mama, must I?
My boots are at the menders
and I haven't ridden for weeks.
Anna? Please see that Lady Mary
is fully equipped to go hunting.
Yes, your ladyship.
[DOOR BELL JINGLING]
Yes?
I saw this advertisement
for a limp corrector.
Yes?
What does it do, exactly?
It corrects limps.
Does it work?
Well, as I make it and I advertise it,
is it likely I'd say no?
Could I see one?
Here we are.
You adjust this to the right height
to minimize the limp.
You tighten these, gradually,
as tight as you can stand,
and as the legs straighten
the foot lowers to the floor.
Can't say it's going to be easy.
And you can't slack.
Every day, all day, if you mean business.
All right.
How much?
She asks if we can both dine on Saturday?
There are two young men staying,
so you won't be so outnumbered for once.
What men?
A Turkish diplomat called
something I can't read
And "Lord Branksome's charming son",
who's to be flung at Mary, presumably.
When it comes to Cousin Mary,
she's quite capable of doing
her own flinging, I assure you.
ANNA: Ah, open the door, can you?
[SIGHS]
I couldn't find her breeches anywhere,
so I asked Mr. Bates and he looked among
his lordship's riding clothes
and there they were.
I only hope to god I've got everything.
Hat, I'll do here.
Gloves and crop are in the hall.
[SNIFFLING]
Gwen?
Whatever's the matter?
Hey, come on, sit down.
-Hey?
-[CRYING]
What's up?
Oh, I'm just being silly.
You should get that brushed.
He won't be up for another half an hour.
Now, what is it?
Well, I suppose I've just realized that
it's not going to happen.
-What isn't?
-Oh, none of it.
I'm not going to be a secretary.
I'm not going to leave service.
-I doubt I'll leave here before I'm 60.
-Hey.
-What's all this?
-You saw their faces.
And they're right. Oh, look at me.
I'm the daughter of a farmhand,
I'm lucky to be a maid.
I was born with nothing
and I'll die with nothing.
Don't talk like that.
You can change your life if you want to.
Sometimes you have to be hard on yourself,
but you can change it completely, I know.
[GRUNTS IN PAIN]
Mr. Bates?
Are you all right?
Take her upstairs, dry her off.
-Come on, Gwen, hey?
-[GWEN SNIFFLING]
Mr. Bates, what's the matter?
Nothing. Not a thing. I'm fine.
Let me help you.
I'm perfectly all right,
thank you, Mrs. Hughes.
Are you sure? You're as white as a sheet.
That's my wonderful complexion,
inherited from my Irish mother.
[ALL CLAMORING]
Take it. Take it, don't dawdle.
[SIGHS]
[INDISTINCT]
Ah, thank you.
[DOGS BARKING]
-Can you see them, my lady?
-Not yet.
MARY: Oh, wait a minute. Here's Mr. Napier.
I was beginning to give up on you.
We're moving off.
We were fools not to accept
your mother's invitation
and send the horses down early.
As it is, my groom only got here
an hour or two ago.
My mount's as jumpy
as a deb at her first ball.
What about Mr. Pamuk?
I gather if he takes a tumble,
you'll be endangering world peace.
Don't worry about Kemal.
He knows what he's doing on a horse.
-Oh, well, where is he?
-Fussing. He's rather a dandy.
And I can see him now.
A funny little foreigner
with a wide, toothy grin
and hair reeking of pomade.
I wouldn't quite say that. Here he is now.
Lady Mary Crawley, I presume?
-You presume right.
-Sorry to be so disheveled.
We've been on a train since dawn
and we had to change in a shed.
You don't look disheveled to me.
[HORN BLOWING]
[DOGS BARKING]
-Lynch, you don't have to stay with me.
-But his lordship asked me to.
It's a waste of your day.
Help Mr. Napier's man
get their things back to the house.
-His lordship said...
-Don't worry. I'll look after her.
We'll make it our business
to keep her from harm, I promise.
I hope the day
is living up to your expectations?
It is exceeding them in every way.
And where's Mr. Napier?
-He's gone over the bridge, look.
-Oh!
And what about you, will you follow him
or will you come over the jump with me?
Oh, I was never much one
for going round by the road.
Stay by me and we'll take it together.
EDITH: I wish we could talk
a little more about you.
What was it like, growing
up in Manchester?
Does it say anything
about the side aisles?
"The side aisles were added in the
14th century by Bishop Richard De Warren."
Yes, you can see that
in the treatment of the stone.
It's wonderful to think of all those
men and women
worshiping together through the centuries,
isn't it?
Dreaming and hoping.
Much as we do, I suppose.
Was the screen a Cromwell casualty?
I dare say.
Wonder how Mary's getting on?
All right, I should think.
-Why?
-I just wondered.
Will she stay with the hunt the whole day?
Oh, you know Mary.
She likes to be in at the kill.
Where shall we go next?
-Not home?
-Oh, not yet.
We've time for one more at least
before we lose the light.
I underestimated your enthusiasm.
Come on.
[ALL LAUGHING]
THOMAS: is that one mine?
Home is the hunter, home from the hill.
Heavens, you have been in the wars.
Papa, this is Mr. Pamuk.
My father, Lord Grantham.
-How do you do, my lord?
-Did you have a good day?
-Couldn't have been better.
-This is Thomas, sir.
He will be looking after you.
-You remember Mr. Napier.
-Of course. How are you?
So kind of you to have us, Lady Grantham.
And this is Mr. Pamuk.
-How do you do?
-My lady.
-Well, what would you like?
-Just baths. We're worn out.
Your cases are upstairs, sir.
If you'd like to follow me.
Yes.
ROBERT: Well, I hope Mary hasn't
left you too exhausted, Mr. Napier?
NAPIER: No.
He doesn't look Turkish at all.
Well, he doesn't look like any Englishman
I've ever met, worse luck.
I think he's beautiful.
-Is there some crisis of which I am unaware?
-No, Mr. Carson.
I cannot think of another reason
why you should congregate here.
No, Mr. Carson.
Have you seen our visitor?
Quite a treat for the ladies.
Indeed, my lord.
-Are they settled in all right?
-I believe so.
Mr. Napier's valet seems a competent
fellow, and Thomas knows what he's doing.
Why doesn't the gorgeous Turk
have his own chap?
Apparently his man speaks no English,
so Mr. Pamuk decided to
leave him in London.
Probably very wise.
I hope Thomas doesn't mind.
You know Thomas, my lord.
He has to have a grumble,
but I gather he cheered up
when he saw the gentleman.
[EXCLAIMS IN PAIN]
-Bates, is anything wrong?
-Nothing at all, my lord.
-Is that strap too tight?
-Hmm.
Shall I adjust it, sir?
Now, I'm relying on you to see
that I go downstairs properly dressed.
Don't worry, sir. I've got sharp
eyes for anything out of order.
-Then I put myself entirely in your hands.
-You do right, sir.
I should love to visit Turkey.
Yes, it's a wonderful country.
My man always does this, can you?
I'm very attracted to the Turkish culture.
Then I hope your chance
will come to sample it.
I hope so, too.
You forget yourself.
I'm sorry, sir. I thought...
That will teach you to believe
what the English say about foreigners.
I ought to report you.
-I think you must have...
-I mistook nothing.
But I will make you an offer.
Later tonight, I may need some help
with the geography of the house.
-The geography?
-Yes.
I'm not sure yet,
but I may wish to pay someone a visit.
If that is the case, you will help me…
And I will say nothing of your behavior.
I don't understand.
Why would she want to be a secretary?
-She wants a different life.
-But why?
I should far prefer to be a maid
in a large and pleasant house
than work from dawn till dusk
in a cramped and gloomy office.
-Don't you agree, Carson?
-I do, my lady.
Why are we talking about this?
What does it matter?
It matters that the people that live
and work here are content.
Of course. We should be helping Gwen
if that's what she wants.
I agree. Surely, we must all
encourage those less fortunate
to improve their lot where they can.
Not if it isn't in their best interests.
Isn't the maid a better judge of that
than we are?
What do say, Mr. Pamuk?
Should our housemaid be kept enslaved
or forced out into the world?
Why are you English so curious
about other people's lives?
If she wishes to leave and the
law permits it, then let her go.
Perhaps the law should not permit it,
for the common good.
So you hanker for the days of serfdom?
I hanker for a simpler world.
-Is that a crime?
-I, too, dream of the simpler world.
As long as we can keep our trains
and our dentistry.
[ALL LAUGHING]
I wish I shared your enthusiasm.
Our dentist is horrid.
Well, why go to him, then?
Oh, he treated all of us
when we were children.
You know how the English are
about these things.
Mmm.
[INDISTINCT]
Well, the next time you feel a twinge,
you must come to Istanbul.
Wouldn't the journey be painful?
Sometimes we must endure a little pain
in order to achieve satisfaction.
-Lady Mary rode very well today.
-Why did you send Lynch back?
I had my champions to left and right.
It was enough.
Did you enjoy the hunt today, Mr. Napier?
Mary said you had a tremendous run.
It was like something
out of a Trollope novel.
[CHUCKLES]
What about you, Mr. Pamuk.
Was your day successful?
Oh, yes, Lady Grantham.
I can hardly remember a better one.
[INDISTINCT]
Mary has more suitors tonight
than the Princess Aurora.
-But will she judge them sensibly?
-No one's sensible at her age.
Nor should they be. That's our role.
KEMAL: Well, if you will excuse me.
Thank you.
-Was it fun to be back in the saddle?
-Yes. Although I'll pay for it tomorrow.
Would you ever come out with me?
Or aren't we friends enough for that?
Oh, I think it might be...
That run reminded me
of a day last month up in Cheshire.
-We came down the side of a hill...
-Excuse me.
It seems we must brush up
on our powers of fascination.
I was a fool to bring him here.
MATTHEW: Don't you like him?
EVELYN: I like him very much.
But so does everyone else, unfortunately.
Excuse me.
-Hope I didn't wear you out today.
-Oh, not at all. I enjoyed it.
We must do it again.
Next time, let's take my mother.
She was so jealous, she made me promise
she could come with us.
EDITH: Of course. How nice that would be.
What is it?
Is this picture really a delta Francesca?
I think so...
The second Earl brought back
several paintings from his...
-Mr. Pamuk!
-Let me come to you tonight, please.
I can't think what I have said
that has led you to believe...
Please, I don't know
when we'll meet again.
So, let it be tonight.
Mr. Pamuk,
I will not repeat your words to my father,
since I should hate to see you
cast out into the darkness.
But can we agree to consider them unsaid?
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I shall rejoin my mother and sisters.
[DOOR OPENING]
You must be mad.
I am. I am in the grip of madness.
Please leave at once or I'll...
Or you'll what?
I'll scream.
No, you won't.
I'll ring the bell, then.
And who's on duty now? The hall boy?
Will you really let him find a man
in your bedroom? What a story.
Do you have any idea what you're asking?
I'd be ruined if they even knew
we'd had this conversation,
-let alone if...
-What?
Don't worry. You can still
be a virgin for your husband.
-Heavens! Is this a proposal?
-Hmm...
Alas, no. I don't think our union
would please your family.
-I'm afraid not.
-Nor mine.
But a little imagination.
You wouldn't be the first.
You and my parents
have something in common.
Oh?
You believe I'm much more of a rebel
than I am.
Now, please go.
I am not what you think I am.
If it's my mistake,
if I've led you on I'm sorry, but I'm not.
You are just what I think you are.
No. I have never done anything.
Of course not.
One look at you would tell me that.
Oh, my darling.
Won't it hurt?
Is it safe?
Trust me.
[MUFFLED GASP]
[WHISPERS] He's dead. I think he's dead.
No, I'm sure he's dead.
But how?
We were together and... he's dead.
In your room?
We've got to get him back to his own bed.
But how? It's in the bachelor's corridor,
miles from my room.
Well, could we manage him between us?
He weighs a ton.
I can hardly shift him at all.
We need at least one other.
What about Bates?
He couldn't lift him.
William can't keep a secret.
And Thomas wouldn't try to.
We've got to do something.
Then who else has as much to lose as you
if it ever gets out?
Not Papa.
Please don't say Papa.
I couldn't bear the way he'd look at me.
No. Not his lordship.
-[WHISPERING] What happened to him?
-[SHAKILY] I don't know.
Heart attack, I suppose or a stroke or...
He was alive and suddenly he cried out
and then he was dead.
But why was he here at all?
Did he force himself on you?
Well, we can talk about that later.
Now, we must decide
what to do for the best.
There's only one thing we can do.
I couldn't. It's not possible.
If you don't, we will figure
in a scandal of such magnitude
it would never be forgotten
until long after we're both dead.
I'll be ruined, Mama.
Ruined and notorious, a laughingstock,
a social pariah.
Is that what you want
for your eldest daughter?
Is it what you want for the family?
We must cover him up.
CORA: [WHISPERING]
Hurry, the servants will be up soon.
ANNA: We've got time.
[EXCLAIMS]
-Mama.
-Sorry.
[MARY GRUNTS]
I can't make his eyes stay shut.
Leave that and come away.
[CRYING] He was so beautiful.
Your ladyship's right.
We must get back to our rooms.
I feel now that I can never forgive
what you have put me through this night.
I hope in time
I will come to be more merciful.
But I doubt it.
You won't tell Papa?
Since it would probably kill him,
and certainly ruin his life, I will not.
But I keep the secret
for his sake, not for yours.
Yes, Mama.
Anna.
I will not insult you by asking that
you also conceal Lady Mary's shame.
Let us go.
[DOOR CLOSING]
I imagine you've heard what's happened?
Yes.
Terrible thing. Awful.
Ghastly for your parents.
I don't suppose I shall ever
make it up to them.
Well, it wasn't you fault.
Well, I brought him here.
If it isn't my fault, whose is it?
I was wondering if you might
show me the gardens before I go?
We could get some fresh air.
I won't, if you'll forgive me.
I ought to stay and help Mama.
Of course.
I am so sorry about all this.
I've told your father
I'll deal with the embassy.
There won't be any more annoyance for you.
Thank you.
Actually, he was a terribly nice fellow.
I wish you could have known him better.
I took him on as a duty, but I liked him
more and more the longer I knew him.
Perhaps you saw his
qualities for yourself.
[MARY CRYING]
Which obviously, you did.
I had an uncle who went like that.
Finished his cocoa, closed his book,
and fell back dead on the pillow.
I don't think Mr. Pamuk
bothered with cocoa much, or books.
He had other interests.
I meant you can go just like that,
with no reason.
That's why you should treat every day
as if it were your last.
Well, we couldn't criticize Mr. Pamuk
where that's concerned.
What do you mean?
Nothing. Careful with that.
[MAIDS CHATTERING]
Gwen, are you busy?
Your ladyship.
I saw this. It came out yesterday. Look.
It's for a secretary.
It's a new firm in Thirsk. See?
Well, I don't understand.
How did you know?
That you wanted to leave?
Carson told my father.
And you don't my mind?
Why should I? I think it's terrific
that people make their own lives,
especially women.
Write to them today
and name me as your reference.
I can give it without ever specifying
precisely what your work here has been.
My lady...
Thank you.
Lady Grantham!
I've come to say goodbye.
They're bringing the car around
to take me to the station.
Have you said goodbye to Mary?
I have.
Will we be seeing you here again?
Nothing would give me more pleasure,
but I'm afraid I am a little busy
at the moment and...
[SIGHS]
I wonder if I might risk embarrassing you?
Because I should like to make myself clear.
The truth is, Lady Grantham,
I am not a vain man.
I do not consider myself
a very interesting person.
But I feel it's important that
my future wife should think me so.
A woman who finds me boring
could never love me
and I believe
marriage should be based on love.
[CHUCKLES] At least at the start.
Thank you for your faith in me, Mr. Napier.
Your instincts do you credit.
Good luck to you.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Did Mr. Napier get off all right?
He did, my lord.
And poor Mr. Pamuk has been taken care of?
We got Grassbys, from Thirsk, in the end.
They're very good and they didn't mind
coming out on a Sunday.
Is everyone all right downstairs?
Well, you know.
He was a handsome stranger
from foreign parts one minute
and the next, he was
as dead as a doornail.
It's bound to be a shock.
Of course, upstairs or down.
It's been horrid for the ladies.
And for the female staff, I expect?
[SIGHS] It's particularly hard
on the younger maids.
Indeed.
Don't let the footman be too coarse
in front of them.
Thomas likes to show off.
We must have a care
for feminine sensibilities.
They are finer and
more fragile than our own.
[BATES GRUNTING]
Mr. Bates?
I am going to have to insist that
you tell me what is the matter.
I thought it was for Mr. Carson
to give me orders.
Mr. Carson's no better than any other man
when it comes to illness.
Now, tell me what it is
and I'll see what I can do.
It's nothing, truly.
I twisted my bad leg
and walked on it too soon,
it'll be fine in a day or two.
Well, if it isn't, I'm
sending for the doctor.
CARSON: The Dowager Countess.
Oh, my dears.
Is it really true? I can't believe it.
Last night he looked so well.
Course, would happen to a foreigner.
It's typical.
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm not being ridiculous.
No Englishman would dream of dying
in someone else's house,
especially someone they didn't even know.
Oh, Granny. Even the English
aren't in control of everything.
Well, I hope we're in control
of something, if only ourselves.
But we're not! Don't you see that?
We're not in control of anything at all!
Edith,
go and tell Mary to come back at once
and apologize to her grandmother.
COUNTESS: No, leave her alone.
She's had a shock. We all have.
Just let her rest.
[DOOR OPENING]
Oh! Just the ticket.
Nanny always said
sweet tea was the thing for frayed nerves.
Though why it has to be sweet,
I couldn't tell you.
What did you mean, Mr. Pamuk
lived each day as if it were his last?
-What I said.
-Well, how did you know?
Can't keep William waiting. Gangway.
I'll be asking the same question later,
so you'd better have an answer ready.
Daisy, where have you hidden the flour?
I can't see it anywhere.
It's just there, Mrs. Patmore.
Well, fetch it to me, then.
Oh, you're all in a daze today.
Do you think we should have gone up there,
to see how they are?
I sent a note, but I thought
I'd be in the way. Why?
I thought Mary was rather struck with him
last night, didn't you?
Well, it must have been frightful
for all of them.
But there it is.
In the midst of life, we are in death.
I suppose Mr. Napier
will have to manage everything.
I suppose he will.
We all thought him a very nice gentleman.
Yes, he is nice.
Will we be seeing a lot of him?
I don't expect so, no.
Because we rather hoped Lady Mary
might have taken a shine to him.
Seems not.
Oh, well.
There are plenty more fish in the sea
than ever came out of it.
Are you looking for something?
Lady Mary?
I just wanted to make sure the room
had been tidied up after the...
After the people had left.
Life can be terribly unfair, can't it?
It certainly can.
Everything seems so golden one minute,
then turns to ashes the next.
Can I ask you a question, Carson?
Have you ever felt your life
was somehow slipping away
and there was nothing
you could do to stop it?
I think everyone feels that
at one time or another.
The odd thing is I feel,
for the first time, really,
I understand what it is to be happy.
It's just I know that I won't be.
Oh, don't say that, my lady.
Don't raise the white flag quite yet.
You'll still be mistress of Downton.
Old lady Grantham hasn't given up
the fight, not by a long chalk.
Oh, that...
I wasn't even thinking about that.
And if I may say so, my lady,
you're still very young.
Am I? I don't feel it.
We're all behind you, my lady.
The staff. We're all on your side.
Thank you, Carson.
You've always been so kind to me. Always.
From when I was quite a little girl.
Why is that?
Even a butler has his favorites, my lady.
Does he?
I'm glad.
ANNA: Lady Mary.
Oh, my lady, I thought...
Carson and I were just making sure
that everything was ship-shape
and Bristol fashion.
And it is.
Good night, Carson.
Good night, my lady.
Of all the men on earth.
I mean, he looked so fit.
Dr. Clarkson said it was a heart attack.
Did you see any signs?
Didn't have much of a chance
to study the gentleman.
You don't suppose there's anything
sinister in it, do you?
Every day the papers warn us
of German spies
and they did say his presence
was essential for peace in Albania.
I doubt it, my lord.
Anyone wanting to poison his food
would have to get pass Mrs. Patmore.
[CHUCKLES] Blimey, that's a thought.
Unless, of course, she's a spy herself.
[EXCLAIMS IN PAIN]
I wish you'd tell me what's wrong, Bates.
You'll be in no trouble. I only want to help.
I know that, your lordship.
And I am grateful, truly,
but there is nothing I need help with.
-Good morning, Mrs. Hughes.
-Good morning, my lord.
I wonder if you...
[GRUNTING IN AGONY]
[INHALES]
[MRS HUGHES SIGHS]
Now will you kindly explain
what in heaven is going on?
I'm perfectly well, Mrs. Hughes.
Bit stiff, that's all.
Just so long as you know,
I'm not leaving until you tell me.
[SIGHS]
I hope you have a strong stomach.
Oh, my god!
Cousin Mary?
Hello.
Are we expecting you?
No, but I wanted to see you.
I looked for you yesterday at church.
I wasn't feeling up to it.
None of us were.
Must have been a horrible shock.
Yes.
And he seemed a nice fellow.
He was.
A very nice fellow.
So, if there's anything
I can do, please ask.
There isn't.
But thank you.
[SIGHS] Well, here goes.
Do you not think
we ought to say a few words?
What? Good riddance?
That and your promise.
Very well.
I promise I will never
again try to cure myself.
I will spend my life happily
as the butt of others' jokes
and I will never mind them.
We all carry scars,
Mr. Bates, inside or out.
You're no different to the rest of us,
remember that.
I will try to.
That I do promise.
MRS HUGHES: Good riddance!
-So he definitely went in?
-I saw him walk through the door.
But you don't know if he went back
to his own room?
Yes, I do, 'cause I was the one
who found him there the next day.
What I mean is, you don't know
if he went back under his own steam.
I suppose not,
but how else would he have done it?
That's what they call the big question.
I don't want to get in
any trouble over this.
Don't worry, you won't.
Your secret's safe with me.