Last June saw Emily Davison
crushed to death
beneath the hooves of the King's horse!
Will the summer of 1914
prove as fatal for the hopes of women?
It cannot!
This historic by-election
had been a first step of the journey
to women's equality.
If you're so keen on women's rights,
let a woman speak!
Why stop there? Let's get the dogs up
and listen to them bark!
[ALL SHOUTING]
[CROWD JEERING]
-Are you all right, my lady?
-Isn't it exciting?
[CROWD SHOUTING]
MAN: You're an idiot!
Sybil, I think it's time for Branson
to take you home.
-Not yet.
-I think so.
I applaud your spirit in coming, and I will
applaud your discretion when you leave.
-But you agree with everything he says?
-I do, my dear.
But I also know if anything happens
to you, Branson will lose his place.
Better safe than sorry, my lady.
...is an act of mercy? I disagree!
The car's just here.
Women must get the vote,
mustn't they, Branson?
Why does the Prime Minister
resist the inevitable?
Politicians can't often recognize
the changes that are inevitable.
I hope you do go into politics.
It's a fine ambition.
Ambition or dream?
If I do, it's not all about women
and the vote for me,
nor even freedom for Ireland.
It's the gap between the aristocracy
and the poor, and...
And what?
I'm sorry. I don't mean to speak
against his lordship.
Why not?
You obviously don't approve of him.
Not as a representative
of an oppressive class.
But he's a good man and a decent employer.
Spoken like a true politician.
What do I look like?
Could you sneak me round the back?
I should hate for Papa
to see me like this.
MRS PATMORE: Where?
I'm not a mind-reader.
Mrs. Patmore is very
cruel to that poor girl.
Mrs. Patmore is frightened.
Is she right to be?
Well, Doctor Clarkson has confirmed
she has cataracts.
What can be done about it?
There are treatments,
but even the best are uncertain.
And she doesn't want to risk losing
what sight she still has.
I don't blame her. But
it can't go on forever.
No.
Oh, dear. Have you had bad news?
-I shouldn't have bothered you.
-No. You weren't to know.
-[EXCLAIMS]
-Blimey! Excuse me, my lady.
William, will you find Anna and tell her
I've gone upstairs?
Very good, my lady.
-[EXCLAIMING] You clumsy clodhopper.
-Sorry.
You will be sorry
when I've finished with you. Look at this!
-Leave him alone.
-Anna, Lady Sybil's back from Ripon.
-She's gone up to her room.
-Thank you.
Why does she waste her precious time
on politics?
Hear, hear.
Oh, don't you believe in
rights for women, Thomas?
What's it to you?
Well, I know you don't believe in
rights of property.
I think some people
might find that interesting.
Who's going to tell them? You?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Mr. Carson, are you all right?
Why shouldn't I be?
You've never rung the dressing gong,
and Mrs. Patmore's doing a soufflé
for the first course.
Oh, my God.
Rather unlike Carson.
We'd better go straight in to dinner.
I shall tell Miss O'Brien and Anna.
Any more news of the by-election?
Mr. Crawley was here earlier.
He said his mother had gone
to the Liberal rally in Ripon.
I heard it was quite lively.
I dare say the townies will make the usual
stink when the Tory candidate's returned.
I'm not sure. I heard the Liberal
was given a hard time today.
Mr. Branson said it was getting out of hand
when they left.
Typical Branson to be there.
I hope he squared it with Carson.
Who went with him?
Uh... I'm not sure
anyone went with him, my lord.
You just said "they". Who was with him?
I'd rather not say.
Bates, who was with him?
Lady Sybil.
Lady Sybil? Why?
I should never have mentioned it, my lord.
I thought you knew.
No, I did not know.
I gather you went to hear
the Liberal candidate today.
There were several speakers, actually.
He was the last.
Did he speak well?
I thought so.
But there was quite a brouhaha.
You know what these things can be like.
I do. Which is why I am astonished
you should not feel it necessary
to ask my permission to attend.
-I assume this was Branson's scheme.
-No.
I confess I was amused at the idea
of an Irish radical for a chauffeur,
but I see now I've been naïve.
I told Branson to take Sybil.
What are you saying?
Sybil needed to go to Ripon.
I asked Branson to drive her.
I thought it would be sensible.
In case there was trouble.
I want to do some canvassing.
The by-election isn't far off...
Canvassing?
Oh, it's quite safe. You're in a group
and you knock on doors.
Yes, I know what canvassing is.
-I think that Sybil is...
-What? Are you canvassing, too?
Or would you rather take in washing?
I was only going to say
that Sybil is entitled to her opinions.
No, she isn't until she is married,
then her husband will tell her
what her opinions are.
-Oh, Granny.
-I knew you wouldn't approve.
Which, presumably, is why
you all hid your plans from me.
Her ladyship will have a smacked bottom
if she's not careful.
Hurry up. I don't want anything else
to go wrong tonight.
Where's the sauce?
Doesn't this have Hollandaise?
-I'll get it. I won't be a jiffy.
-Would you do that for me?
I'd do anything for you.
Does this mean you won't be
presented next month?
Certainly not. Why should it?
Well, I doubt I'd expect to curtsy
to Their Majesties in June
when I'd been arrested at a riot in May.
But then I'm old.
Things may be different now.
She hasn't been arrested
and it wasn't a riot.
-But it might be next time.
-There will not be a next time.
[SIGHS]
Her ladyship's not best pleased
at being told off in public.
William said she was looking daggers.
-I'm sorry I started all this.
-Oh, it's not your fault.
Anyway, he ought to be glad
he's got a daughter who cares.
Her ladyship's ready to leave.
I'll bring the car around.
Are you pleased with yourself?
Silly chump.
He's nervous. He thinks I'm planning
to tell Mr. Carson about the wine.
Well, he shouldn't have stolen it then,
should he?
No.
But I don't want anyone to lose their job
because of me.
Even Thomas?
Even after what they tried to do to you?
Even then.
-Your ladyship, do you have a moment?
-Of course.
I've received a letter, my lady,
from a friend of mine.
He's valet to the Marquess of Flintshire.
I don't envy him.
[CHUCKLES] Lord Flintshire is a minister
at the Foreign Office.
As you know,
Lady Flintshire is his lordship's cousin.
Oh, of course, of course. The point is,
he has dealings with
the Turkish Ambassador.
It seems His Excellency has made him privy
to a scurrilous story
concerning Lady Mary
and the late Mr. Pamuk.
May I read this letter?
Is there anything you
want me to do about it?
No, thank you.
Sometimes, even to deny these things
is only to throw paraffin onto the flames.
-I did try to inform his lordship...
-What?
But I couldn't seem to
find the right moment.
Quite right. Please
leave his lordship to me.
O'BRIEN: I'm sorry.
The only sure way to get rid of a servant
is to have him or her suspected of stealing.
Aren't you forgetting we've tried that
and it didn't work?
But last time we invented a theft.
What we need to do is to make him a suspect
when something's really been stolen.
How do we know anything's been stolen?
Because you stole it, you noodle.
-Oh. You mean the wine.
-Yeah, the wine.
But that's the whole point.
Bates knows I took it.
He was threatening to tell Mr. Carson.
Well, he can't, can he?
Not if we get to him first.
Are you telling me you saw him
take the cellar key?
Not exactly. But I saw him in here
and I thought the key was swinging
on its hook.
I just wondered if you'd noticed
if any of the wine was missing?
I think I owe you an apology
after the way I spoke at dinner.
Next time you want to treat me
like a naughty schoolgirl
you might do it in private,
not in front of the servants.
You're right. I'm sorry.
Of course, it gave your mother
her best evening since Christmas.
Even so, we must try
to keep control of Sybil.
Robert, believe me,
Sybil is not your problem.
We've got to support Mary this year,
when we get to London.
But it's Sybil's first season.
We can't have Mary stealing her thunder.
Sybil will do well enough.
It's time Mary was settled.
High time.
Poor old Edith.
We never seem to talk about her.
I'm afraid Edith will be the one
to care for us in our old age.
What a ghastly prospect.
Mama? Anna said you wanted me.
Look who's paid us a visit.
Sir Anthony. How nice.
We all thought we'd driven you away
with that horrible salty pudding.
[CHUCKLING] No, indeed.
But I have been away.
He's been in Austria and Germany.
-How interesting.
-Interesting. And worrying.
Sir Anthony is here to
show you his new car.
-Oh.
-I've rather taken to driving myself,
and I have to keep finding destinations
to justify it.
What kind of car is it?
It's an open Rolls-Royce and I wondered
if you might like a spin in it.
Oh, how kind. But alas, not today.
I've had Diamond saddled
and he's waiting for me.
You could ride this afternoon.
But it's arranged now.
But thank you, Sir Anthony.
Do ask me again.
I don't suppose you'd take me.
Of course. I should be delighted.
What is it that I am accused of?
Oh. Nobody is accusing you of anything.
But there has been a suggestion
that you were handling the cellar key,
and before I take it any further
I want to find if there's
a simple explanation.
Because some wine is missing.
How do you know that?
Right. Well, we'll leave it there for now.
The Kaiser is such a mercurial figure,
one minute the warlord,
the next a lovelorn poet.
But a poet in need of an empire.
That's very good.
"A poet in need of an empire." Yes.
My late wife used to say that...
-What did Lady Strallan used to say?
-Oh, never mind.
-But I should like to hear it.
-Really? Would you, really?
She used to say that Kaiser Bill
loved uniforms and medals
but he never really connected them
with fighting.
[BOTH LAUGH]
-What was she like?
-Maud? Oh, she was awfully funny.
Some people couldn't see it, but she was.
-Is Lynch anywhere about?
-Oh, I haven't seen him, my lady.
-My horse is lame.
-I could have a look at him.
Do you know about horses?
I looked after the horses
on me father's farm.
-It was the best job in the world.
-Then why did you leave it?
Me mother wanted me to have a chance
of bettering myself.
As a second footman?
It's a good place for me, my lady.
Of course it is. I'm sorry.
She hopes, one day,
that I might be first footman,
-or even get to be...
-Carson had better watch out.
Stranger things happen at sea.
I've seen Mr. Bates with a bottle
from time to time.
I must have thought he was helping you.
Why would I order a valet
to help with the wine?
Well, when you put it like that,
of course you wouldn't.
So, Mr. Bates is taking wine.
And why would this be?
To drink it?
It's not to clean his boots.
Thank you, Thomas.
Daisy? Thomas says you have something
to add to this.
-Well...
-You are not in any trouble,
or any danger of trouble.
You remember what you saw.
I may have seen him
coming out of the cellar.
"May". Did you or didn't you?
It's very hard for the girl, Mr. Carson.
You're frightening her.
I'm sorry. Thank you. You may go.
Thank you, O'Brien.
How is everything downstairs?
All right, I think, my lady.
Though Mr. Carson's a bit cast down.
Oh? Why? What's the matter with him?
He's found out something about...
Well, a person he admires,
and it isn't very nice.
Has he said who this person is?
Who's proved a disappointment.
I don't like to say, my lady.
-Please do, if you know.
-Oh, I know.
It's Mr. Bates.
Oh, Bates. Why? What's he done?
You should ask Mr. Carson, my lady.
It's not my place to tell.
Papa?
Can Branson drive me into Ripon
on Friday evening?
I don't think so, no.
Not after the last time.
Oh, please.
There's a meeting of my borstal charity.
I've missed two and I
simply must be there.
You'd have to take Mary or Edith with you.
Don't make me. Those meetings are deadly
at the best of times,
and you know what they're like
when they're bored.
Why are all your causes
so steeped in gloom?
Because it's the gloomy things
that need our help.
If everything in the garden's sunny,
why meddle?
Well, I agree with that.
Talking of sunny, are you looking forward
to your coming season?
I am, rather.
Hello. What are you doing here?
I'm in search of your father.
Carson thought he was outside.
-He's in the library.
-Oh.
What is it?
Nothing much. I've had an
inquiry about one of the farms.
Oh.
So, what's new at the big house?
Sybil, mainly.
She's discovered politics,
which of course makes Papa see red.
I admire Sybil's passion, though.
Of course. But then I
like a good argument.
Papa does not.
If you really like an argument...
-Yes?
-We should see more of each other.
So, it's all right? I can go?
[DOG WHIMPERING]
-Will you be late?
-I think I'll miss dinner.
Well, remember to tell Branson
to take a sandwich for himself.
CORA: But who's it from?
COUNTESS: Susan Flintshire.
-What does she say?
-Well, prepare for the worst.
Not the first page.
My poor niece never uses one word
when 20 will do.
Start there. "I'm sorry..."
"I'm sorry to have to tell you that Hugh
has heard a vile story"
"about your granddaughter Mary..."
Sorry? She's thrilled.
Now, first I must ask,
and I want you to think carefully
before you answer.
Is any of this true?
I see.
Some of it is true. How much?
Oh, dear.
She didn't drag him.
I wondered about that.
I mean, obviously Susan's
forgotten the distance
between the girls' rooms
and the bachelors' corridor.
She couldn't manage it alone.
So how did she do it?
I helped her.
She woke me up and I helped her.
Well. I always thought
this family might be
approaching dissolution.
I didn't know dissolution
was already upon us.
Does Robert know?
No. And he isn't going to.
Oh.
Of course it was terribly wrong.
It was all terribly wrong.
But I didn't see what else...
Please! I can't listen to your attempts
to try and justify yourself.
I know this is hard for you to hear.
God knows it was hard for me
to live through.
But if you expect me
to disown my daughter,
I'm afraid you will be disappointed.
Good day.
I thought you must be out here.
And you'd be right.
-I know you're upset.
-Yes. I'm upset.
I have been working here two years,
and yet Mr. Carson has no difficulty
believing the worst of me.
I think he has a great deal of difficulty,
which is why he hasn't
told his lordship yet.
-Can't you just explain about Thomas?
-Not now.
It would sound like a false accusation.
You can't take it lying down.
Because you're not guilty of any wrong,
and before it's over
I'm going to tell the world.
Are you? I'm not sure
the world is listening.
Sorry. I'm a bit late tonight.
Not to worry. How are you?
Bearing up.
This isn't the end. You mustn't give up.
We'll get there.
Forgive me, my lady,
but, well, you don't get it.
You're brought up to think
it's all within your grasp,
that if you want something enough,
it will come to you.
But we're not like that.
We don't think our dreams
are bound to come true because...
Because they almost never do.
Then that's why we must stick together.
Your dream is my dream now.
And I'll make it come true.
Why hasn't he done anything?
He's had the story and the witnesses.
"The witnesses"? What do you
think this is, a murder mystery?
Well, Mr. Bates can't accuse me now.
It'll sound as if
he's trying to get his own back.
If I lose my job over this,
I swear to God I'll swing for you.
Is there any stale bread
you're throwing out, and some salt?
Why?
Well, I thought I'd make a last
hot poultice for Diamond.
It'll give him a better night.
You big softie. What'll Mr. Lynch say?
Why, he doesn't mind.
He says I've got the touch.
He thinks I should pack this in
and be a groom.
Why don't you?
My mum.
She was so excited when I came here.
They're proud of me
and I'd hate to spoil that.
Do you miss them?
I never had that in my childhood,
someone you could always trust.
I trust them. They trust me.
There are no lies in our house.
Thanks. That's enough.
I'm glad to catch you.
We have a conundrum at the hospital,
and I would value your opinion.
Of course.
We've been treating the mother
of your footman, William Mason.
What's the matter with her?
Heart, I'm afraid. She's forbidden us
to say anything to her son.
That's ridiculous.
She's gone home now,
but she's still very ill.
Clearly the boy should go and see her.
And I assume you would have
no objections?
Of course not.
So, do we break a patient's confidence
and disobey her orders? Or not?
We can't. If she's forbidden it.
-I must say I agree with you.
-Well, I'll tell him.
No, you will not. She has rights, too.
And there are rules.
I don't care a fig about rules.
-Where to from here, my lady?
-SYBIL: What do you mean? We've arrived.
The meeting's in one of
these buildings here?
SYBIL: This is the meeting.
We're here for the counting of the votes.
I don't understand. I thought that...
Don't be silly, Branson.
You didn't think
I'd miss my very first by-election?
-I don't think his lordship would approve.
-Let me worry about him. [CAR HONKS]
I have to park the car! Don't move.
Stay where you are!
Really, Branson. I
thought I gave the orders.
Well, I said to...
Sir Anthony Strallan.
-Sir Anthony?
-Don't worry, Lady Grantham.
I haven't got the date wrong.
What a relief. I could hear Cora wondering
if the dinner would stretch.
[CHUCKLES] No. I'm not really here at all.
But I was driving past your gates
on the way to the Callender-Becketts,
and I thought I'd take a chance.
See, the thing is, I've got two tickets
for a concert in York next Friday...
How nice. Although, I can't...
No. I was hoping that Lady Edith
might like to accompany me.
But I'd love to.
Shouldn't you ask
what sort of concert it is?
Just Hungry Hundreds stuff, mostly,
you know.
Bellini, Puccini, Rossini.
I'm not up to anything complicated.
I'd like that very much.
Excellent. Well, it's quite a hike,
so I'll pick you up around 6:00.
Lady Jervas has asked us
for a bite to eat afterwards.
-If that's all right with your mother?
-By all means.
Well, I must run.
I hope I haven't spoiled your dinner.
We may have to hire a nurse, after all.
MRS PATMORE: Oh, for heaven's sake,
hold it steady
if you don't want to start again
from the beginning.
Do these biscuits go up?
-No, I put them out for the fairies.
-Oh.
Of course they're going up.
What's wrong with you?
You're always dozy, but tonight
you'd make Sleeping Beauty look alert.
I was just thinking.
Oh, blimey! Batten down the hatches.
-I think I've let myself down.
-It can't be a new sensation.
[CROWD CLAMORING]
The Honorable Joseph Gerald Ansty,
for the Conservative and Unionist Party,
6,363 votes.
Martin James Dillon,
the Socialist Party, 2,741 votes.
Can we call it a day, my lady?
Don't be silly.
This is the moment we've come for.
Trevor Andrew Morgan, the Liberal Party...
This lot aren't interested in politics.
They're spoiling for a fight.
...5,894 votes.
I hereby declare that
the Honorable Joseph Ansty...
Out you get, lads!
We'll soon wipe the smile off their Tory,
bloody faces.
...is duly elected... is duly elected
to serve as a member of Parliament...
A member of Parliament...
-Sybil!
-...for the Ripon constituency.
-What on earth are you doing here?
-I couldn't miss this.
Couldn't you? I could.
BRANSON: I don't like the look of this,
my lady.
Look, I'm on your side.
Don't cause any trouble.
You have to believe me!
What's your problem then, Mr. La-di-da?
-My problem is you.
-Oh, aye?
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Oh, no. Oh, please God, no!
This way.
I've fetched a coat.
-Why? What do I need a coat for?
-I've come to fetch you, my lady.
We've taken Lady Sybil to Crawley House
in the village.
What's happened?
I took her to Ripon for the count.
She got injured in a fight.
Take me there at once.
My God! Oh, my darling...
I didn't know what to do,
so I had Branson bring her here.
Quite right.
Mama would have fainted if she'd
seen her like this. As for Papa...
This will sting a bit.
But it's stopped bleeding.
Did you know she was planning this?
-Of course not.
-Well, what were you doing there?
I was working late.
I'd forgotten it was election night
or I wouldn't have stayed.
I'm so grateful you did.
Oh, I could wring Branson's neck.
What was he thinking?
I'm afraid it'll cost him his job.
No. I told him he was taking me
to a committee meeting.
When he realized what it was,
he wanted to come straight back.
You'll have to stick up for him,
because Papa will skin him alive.
Are you feeling strong enough to go home?
I think so. If you'll take me.
Here, wear my coat to cover the blood.
You'll look more normal.
Lean on me.
Thank you so much for this.
By the way, what happened
to William's mother?
Not good, I'm afraid.
She's home but she's still very weak.
Another attack should finish her.
And he still doesn't know?
She's adamant. I've tried to explain
how hard it'll be on him,
but she won't have him disturbed.
To hear her talk,
you'd think he was a cabinet minister.
He's made her proud.
There are plenty of children
in grander circumstances
who'd love to say the same.
I wish you'd tell me what's troubling you.
If it's this business with Mr. Bates...
Oh, it's not that. I'll get
to the bottom of that.
Well, I hope you'll do it soon.
If there's one thing I hate,
it's an atmosphere.
And we've got a real atmosphere going now.
It's an unfair rumor
which needs to be scotched.
It's very hard to hear the names of
people you love dragged in the mud.
You feel so powerless.
Well, I respect Mr. Bates,
but I'm not sure that I love him.
I wasn't thinking of Mr. Bates.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Mr. Carson, have you got a minute?
What is it, Daisy?
Mr. Carson's a very busy man.
I know he is.
But I think he'll want to hear this.
I told you something that wasn't true.
Why would you do that?
I did it as a favor for a friend.
But I know now he was
wrong to ask it of me.
She's not badly hurt, is she?
I don't think so, no.
Thank God.
Better be prepared. I'm afraid
Lord Grantham will hit the roof.
I never would have taken her there.
I may be a Socialist
but I'm not a lunatic.
I'm not sure Papa knows the difference.
You'll let me know how she gets on?
Please.
If you wish.
How dare you?
How dare you disobey me in this way?
Robert, I'm sure...
Are you so knowledgeable
about the great world
that my instructions are to be set
as nothing?
Papa, I'm sorry I disobeyed you.
But I'm interested!
I'm political! I have opinions!
-Of course, I blame Branson.
-I don't think that's fair.
We had none of this, none of it,
until he set foot in our house!
I suppose I should give thanks he hasn't
burnt the place down over our heads!
Branson didn't know anything about it
until we arrived there.
He leaves tonight!
If you punish Branson,
I'll never speak to you again. Never!
I don't believe this is Branson's fault.
Truly, Papa.
-Blame me.
-I do blame you!
Robert, can we do this in the morning?
Sybil needs rest.
If I find tomorrow that Branson is
missing, I'll run away. I warn you.
[LAUGHS SARCASTICALLY]
Oh? And where would you go?
Well, I can't think now.
But I will go, and you'll be sorry.
[SCOFFS]
I should be sorry. Very sorry, indeed.
How is she?
MARY: She'll be perfectly fine.
I gather you're the
shining knight in all this.
Not really. But I'm glad I was there.
So am I, by heaven. If it had been
left to that bloody fool Branson...
You should see what he reads.
It's all Marx and Ruskin and
John Stuart Mill, I ask you.
Papa prefers the servants to read
the Bible and letters from home.
There are sandwiches for Mr. Crawley
in the dining room, Lady Mary.
Thank you, Mrs. Hughes.
-We couldn't let you starve.
-You really didn't have to.
Mary, look after Matthew,
I'll go up and revive your mother.
Do you stand by your story?
I don't have a story.
You saw Mr. Bates in here alone,
hanging up the cellar key.
To me, that is a story.
I only said I might have seen him.
I suppose I was wrong.
And Miss O'Brien, were you then wrong
when you thought you saw Mr. Bates
carrying a bottle?
-You wicked creature...
-Anna.
You are here to watch,
not to participate.
I don't think I was wrong, no.
What do you say to that, Mr. Bates?
I know this to be untrue
because I have no need of it.
Since I arrived at Downton,
you have never seen me drink
one drop of alcohol.
Let us say, then,
that Miss O'Brien was mistaken.
Mistaken, my eye.
And, Daisy, we all know the value
of your contribution.
Yes, Mr. Carson.
But I must ask one thing, Mr. Bates,
how did you know the wine had been taken?
I'm afraid I cannot answer that.
We can drink to Sybil's safe return.
Why not?
-I'll ring for a glass.
-Never mind that. Here.
You're not very fastidious about
doing things properly, are you?
Are you?
Less than you might think.
Are you at all political?
Yes.
But with a hung Parliament, it's
hard to get excited about a by-election.
You know nothing will change,
whoever gets in.
If I might keep you
for a minute more, Mr. Carson.
If you'd like me to leave...
No. I would like you to stay, please,
Mrs. Hughes. And you, Anna.
You have decided not to take action
over the allegations
Thomas has made against me
because you believe them to be untrue?
-That is correct.
-And you are right. There's no truth in them.
But if you were to proceed with the
matter, you would find them to be proven.
Thomas has tried to convince you
that I'm a drunkard and a thief.
Which we never believed.
Because you know no different.
Until a couple of years
ago, I was a drunkard.
And I was imprisoned as a thief.
I have repaid your kindness very poorly.
I masqueraded as a man
of honor and integrity,
but by any moral code, I am disgraced.
That can't be the whole story.
Perhaps not. But it's enough of it
to demand my resignation.
Do you want to leave, Mr. Bates?
No. But I feel I have no choice.
You owe me a say in the matter, surely?
If you wish.
Then I will consider the case
and give you my decision
when I have discussed
it with his lordship.
Until then,
I hope you will remain in your post.
Thank you for coming to Sybil's rescue.
You were very brave.
She told me you knocked a man down.
I hope did my duty.
Are you a creature of duty?
Not entirely.
When you laugh with me, or flirt with me,
is that a duty?
Are you conforming
to the fitness of things?
Doing what's expected?
Don't play with me.
I don't deserve it. Not from you.
You must be careful
not to break Sybil's heart.
I think she has a crush on you.
That's something
no one could accuse you of.
Oh, I don't know.
I assume you speak in a spirit of mockery.
You should have more faith.
Shall I remind you
of some of the choicest remarks
you made about me when I arrived here?
Because they live in my memory
as fresh as the day they were spoken.
Oh, Matthew. What am I always telling you?
You must pay no attention
to the things I say.
-Mr. Bates.
-Anna.
Will you really leave?
I doubt his lordship wants a thief
in the house.
-Now go to sleep and dream of a better man.
-I can't.
Because there isn't one.
[DOOR OPENING]
[BOTTLES CLANKING]
Has Matthew gone?
-Yes.
-Thank the Lord he was there.
I hope you thanked Matthew properly.
I got them to make him some sandwiches.
It's not quite what I meant.
And he asked me to marry him.
Heavens. What did they put in them?
I'm serious. He proposed to me.
Oh, my dear.
Have you given him an answer?
Only that I'd think about it.
Well, that's an advance on
what it would have been a year ago.
-Do you want to marry him?
-I know you want me to marry him.
What we want doesn't matter.
At least, it's not all that matters.
Do you love Matthew?
Yes.
I think perhaps I do.
I think I may have loved him
for much longer than I knew.
Oh, my darling.
Let's not pretend this isn't the answer
to every one of our prayers.
I'd have to tell him.
Oh
Is it absolutely necessary?
If I didn't, I'd feel as if
I'd caught him with a lie.
[DOOR OPENING]
I hope you know that really smart people
sleep in separate rooms.
I always keep the bed made up
in the dressing room,
so at least I pretend we sleep apart.
Isn't that enough?
No. Never mind. Good night.
Mmm.
Haven't you gone up yet?
Blow this out. You're the last.
-Good night.
Good night.
I'm going to bloody get him.
I don't care what you say.
What would I say?
Everything comes to him who waits.
Well, I've waited long enough.
Does Carson know you're here?
I heard you were going out
and I wanted to see how he was walking.
Lynch is happy for me to ride him.
Oh, yes. He's better.
But I'll wait and see what he's like
when you're up.
William, are you planning to go home soon?
Well, it's a bit far for my half day,
but I can maybe get the time to go in July
when the family's in London.
That's if I don't go with you, of course.
I think you should take a few days off
and go now.
I'll fix it. I'll speak to father
and to Carson. No one will mind.
But why, my lady?
Your mother's not been well.
How do you know?
I heard someone mention it in the village.
I forget who.
-I had a letter and she never said.
-Oh, I'm sure it's nothing.
But I know it would cheer her to see you.
Well, if it wouldn't be a bother.
It won't. I'll arrange it
as soon as I get back.
Thank you very much, my lady.
She ought to spend some time
with the people she loves.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
The Dowager Countess, my lady.
Good afternoon, my dear.
Good afternoon.
There's no need to be so prim.
I come in peace.
Shall I sit here?
Now, I've been thinking...
I confess I do not know if I would have
had the strength, mentally or physically,
to carry a corpse the
length of this house.
But I hope I would have done.
You were quite right.
When something bad happens,
there's no point in wishing
it had not happened.
The only option is to minimize the damage.
Or try to. But if the
Flintshires have got hold of it...
I've written to Susan.
I said it was a story made up
by Mr. Pamuk's enemies to discredit him.
Even if she doesn't believe me,
she won't tell,
in case it reflects badly on her.
The Ambassador is dangerous.
But then, how many people really go
to the Turkish Embassy?
It only takes one.
Well... I mean, that just can't be helped.
We can't have him assassinated,
I suppose.
Robert still doesn't suspect.
Oh, I should hope not.
No, our only way forward is to get
Mary settled as soon as possible.
I have news on that score.
Matthew has proposed.
[GASPING] My, my. Has she said yes?
She hasn't said anything yet, except that
she's going to have to tell him about Pamuk.
For heaven's sake, why?
She thinks to keep it secret
would be dishonorable.
She reads too many novels.
I mean, one way or another,
everyone goes down the aisle
with half the story hidden.
The question is, will she accept Matthew?
I'm not sure.
[SIGHING] Well, if she doesn't,
we'll just have to take her abroad.
In these moments, you can normally
find an Italian who isn't too picky.
We'll give her till the
start of the grouse.
Very well. If she turns Matthew down,
we'll take her to Rome in the autumn.
It's official.
Thank you for not turning against her.
I know that you have rules,
and when people break them
you find it hard to forgive.
I understand that and I respect it.
In this case Mary has the trump card.
What?
Mary is family.