[TELEGRAPH MACHINE BEEPING]
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING]
Oh, my God.
That's impossible.
-I'll take it up there now.
-Don't be stupid.
None of them will be up for hours.
What difference will it make?
Jimmy will do it when he comes in.
[BEEPING]
DAISY: Six o'clock!
Thank you, Daisy.
Anna.
[SIGHING]
[GROANING]
Just for once in my life I'd like to sleep
until I woke up natural.
-Is your fire still in?
-Yes, Mrs. Patmore.
Oh, my, my, will wonders never cease?
-Have you laid the servant's hall breakfast?
-Yes, Mrs. Patmore.
-And finished blacking that stove?
-What about the bedroom fires?
-All lit, Mrs. Patmore.
Right, well, take your things and get
started on the fires on the ground floor.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
Now, hurry up.
-Any sign of William?
-MAID: No.
-Where have you been?
-I'm not late, am I?
You're late when I say you're late.
Daisy, whatever are you doing there,
crouching in the dark?
You weren't here and I didn't like to
touch the curtains with me dirty hands.
Well, quite right, too.
-Why didn't you put the lights on?
-I daren't.
Well, it's electricity
and not the devil's handiwork.
You'll have to get used
to it sooner or later.
At Skelton Park,
they've even got it in the kitchens.
What for?
[MRS PATMORE GIVING ORDERS]
GIRL: Yes, Mrs. Patmore.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
-Breakfast is ready, Mr. Carson.
-Ah, William, any papers yet?
-They're late.
-They certainly are.
Get the board out so you can
do them as soon as they're here.
-Is the library tidy?
-Yes, Mrs. Hughes.
Good. I want the dining room given
a proper going over today.
You can do it
when they've finished their breakfast.
Oh, heavens, girl!
You're building a fire, not inventing it.
-How many have you done?
-This is me last till they come downstairs.
Very well.
Now, get back down to the kitchens
before anyone sees you.
[BICYCLE BELL RINGING]
-And they're off.
-No rest for the wicked.
-Lady Mary. Are the tea trays ready?
-All ready, Mrs. Patmore.
If the water's boiled.
Could you give us a hand
to take the other two up?
-I've got her ladyship's to carry.
-[DOOR BELL RINGING]
-I'll help.
-Back door.
The papers, at last. William!
[DOOR OPENS]
-You're late.
-Yeah, I know, but...
-But what?
-You'll see.
Do THE TIMES first,
he only reads that at breakfast.
And the sketch for her ladyship.
You can manage the
others later, if need be.
-Why are their papers ironed?
-What's it to you?
To dry the ink, silly.
We wouldn't want his lordship's hands
to be as black as yours.
[BELLS RINGING]
Mr. Carson, I think you ought to see this.
-I can't make myself believe it.
-MRS PATMORE: Me neither.
-His lordship's dressed.
-William!
Will you stop talking
and take this kedgeree up.
-And mind the burners are still lit.
-Yes, Mrs. Patmore.
-Is it really true?
-Afraid so.
Nothing in life is sure.
-Good morning, Carson.
-Good morning, my lord.
-Is it true what they're saying?
-I believe so, my lord.
I'm afraid we'll know some people on it.
I don't suppose there are any lists
of survivors yet?
I understand most of the ladies
were taken off in time.
You mean the ladies in first class?
God help the poor devils below decks.
On their way to a better life.
What a tragedy.
When Anna told me,
I thought she must have dreamt it.
Do we know anyone on board?
Your mother knows the Astors,
at least she knows him.
We dined with Lady Rothes last month.
There are bound to be others.
I thought it was
supposed to be unsinkable.
Every mountain is unclimbable
until someone climbs it,
so every ship is
unsinkable until it sinks.
-Good morning, Papa.
-Good morning. What's that?
Just arrived. Telegram.
[SIGHS]
-Is her ladyship awake?
-Yes, my lord.
-I'm just going to take in her breakfast.
-Thank you.
-[KNOCKING]
-CORA: Hello.
May I come in?
Isn't this terrible?
When you think how excited
Lucy Rothes was at the prospect.
It's too awful for any words.
Did J.J. Astor get off?
Of course that new wife of his
is bound to have been rescued.
I've had a telegram from George Murray.
-One of his partners is in New York.
-Yes?
It seems James and Patrick were on board.
What? They can't have been.
They weren't going over until May.
Then they changed their plans.
They're definitely on the passenger list.
Thank you, O'Brien.
That'll be all for the moment.
But surely they were picked up?
-Doesn't look like it.
-What?
Neither of them?
You must tell Mary.
She can't hear about it from anyone else.
Neither of them were picked up,
that's what he said.
-Mr. Crawley and Mr Patrick?
-That's what he said.
Her ladyship was the color of this cloth.
Well, it's a terrible shame if it's true.
It's worse than a
shame, it's a complication.
-What do you mean?
-What do you think?
Mr. Crawley was his lordship's cousin
and heir to the title.
I thought Lady Mary was the heir.
She's a girl, stupid. Girls can't inherit.
But now Mr. Crawley's dead
and Mr Patrick was his only son.
-So, what happens next?
-ANNA: It's a dreadful thing.
Hello.
I've been waiting at the back door.
I knocked, but no one came.
So you pushed in?
I'm John Bates, the new valet.
-The new valet?
-That's right.
-You're early.
-Came on the milk train.
Thought I'd use the day
to get to know the place, start tonight.
I'm Anna, the head housemaid.
How do you do?
And I'm Miss O'Brien, her ladyship's maid.
You better come along with us.
-But how can you manage?
-Don't worry about that, I can manage.
-Because we've all got our own work to do.
-I can manage.
CARSON: All right, Mrs.
Hughes, I'll take over. Thank you.
Good morning, Mr. Bates. Welcome.
-I hope your journey was satisfactory.
-It was fine. Thank you.
I am the butler of Downton.
My name is Carson.
How do you do, Mr. Carson?
This is Thomas, first footman.
He's been looking after his lordship
since Mr. Watson left.
It'll be a relief to get back to normal,
won't it, Thomas?
[CLEARS THROAT]
I assume that everything is ready
for Mr. Bates' arrival?
I've put him in Mr. Watson's old room.
Though he left it in quite a state,
I can tell you.
But what about all them stairs?
-I keep telling you, I can manage.
-Of course you can.
Thomas, take Mr. Bates to his room,
show him where he'll be working.
Thank you, everyone.
-Well, I can't see that lasting long.
-Thank you, Miss O'Brien.
BATES: Oh, yes.
[SIGHS] I should be comfortable here.
Does this mean I'll have to
go into full mourning?
My first cousin and his son
are almost certainly dead.
-We'll all be in mourning.
-No, I mean with the other thing.
After all, it wasn't official.
If you're saying you do not wish to mourn
Patrick as a fiancé, that is up to you.
Well, no one knew about it
outside the family.
I repeat, it is up to you.
Well, that's a relief.
There's some cedar-lined cupboards
in the attic
for things that aren't often worn,
traveling clothes and such.
Mr. Watson used them to
rotate the summer and winter stuff.
I'll show you later.
What about studs and links?
Do I choose them or does he?
Lay them out unless he asks
for something in particular.
These for a ball, these for an
ordinary dinner, these only in London.
-I'll get the hang of it.
-Yeah, you'll have to.
Snuff boxes, he collects them.
BATES: Beautiful.
-Funny our job, isn't it?
-What do you mean?
The way we live with all this
pirate's hoard within our reach.
But none of it's ours, is it?
No, none of it's ours.
I can't believe I've been passed over
for Long John Silver.
You should have spoken up
when you had the chance.
Don't make the same mistake next time.
Who says there'll be a next time?
Is this a public holiday
no one's told me of?
She was certainly reluctant
to go into mourning.
Well, she'll have to. We all will.
O'Brien's sorting out my black now.
And I've told Anna to see
what the girls have that still fits.
Of course, this alters everything.
You won't try to deny it.
You must challenge the entail now, surely.
Can't we at least wait until
we know they're dead before we discuss it?
Don't talk as if I'm not brokenhearted,
because I am.
Of course, I've never understood why
this estate must go
to whomever inherits your title.
My dear, I don't make the law. What is it?
CARSON: The Dowager Countess is
in the drawing room.
-I'll come now.
-She asked for Lady Grantham.
I wonder what I've done wrong this time.
Oh. And the new valet
has arrived, my lord.
Has he? Thank you, Carson.
[CLEARS THROAT]
What is it?
I'm not entirely sure
that he'll prove equal to the task.
But your lordship will
be the judge of that.
Better go.
Tell her about James and Patrick.
She won't have heard.
Of course I've heard.
Why else would I be here?
Robert didn't want you to read about it
in the newspaper and be upset.
He flatters me.
I'm tougher than I look.
I'm very sorry about
poor Patrick, of course.
-He was a nice boy.
-We were all so fond of him.
But I never cared for James.
He was too like his mother
and a nastier woman never drew breath.
-Will you stay for some luncheon?
-Thank you.
-I'll let Carson know.
-I've already told him.
Shall we sit down?
-Do you know the new heir?
-Only that there is one.
He's Robert's third cousin, once removed.
I have never to my knowledge
set eyes on him.
Of course, if your late husband hadn't forced
me to sign that absurd act of legal theft...
My dear, I didn't come here to fight.
Lord Grantham wanted
to protect the estate.
It never occurred to him
that you wouldn't have a son.
-Well, I didn't.
-No, you did not.
But when Patrick had married Mary
and your grandson been hailed as master,
honor would have been satisfied.
[SIGHS] Unfortunately, now...
Now, a complete unknown has the right
to pocket my money
along with the rest of the swag.
The problem is, saving your dowry
would break up the estate.
It would be the ruin of everything
Robert's given his life to.
-And he knows this?
-Well, if he doesn't, he will.
-Then there's no answer.
-Yes, there is, and it's a simple one.
The entail must be smashed in its entirety
and Mary recognized as heiress of all.
-There's nothing we can do about the title.
-No.
She can't have the title,
but she can have your money.
And the estate.
I didn't run Downton for 30 years
to see it go lock, stock and barrel
to a stranger from God knows where.
[SIGHS]
Are we to be friends, then?
We are allies, my dear,
which can be a good deal more effective.
Downton is a great house, Mr. Bates.
And the Crawleys are a great family.
We live by certain standards and those
standards can at first seem daunting.
Of course.
If you find yourself tongue-tied
in the presence of his lordship,
I can only assure you
that his manners and grace
will soon help you to perform your duties
to the best of your ability.
I know.
Bates, my dear fellow.
I do apologize, I should have realized
you'd all be at luncheon.
-Not at all, my lord.
-Please, sit. Sit, everyone.
I just want to say a quick hello
to my old comrade in arms.
Bates, my dear man, welcome to Downton.
Thank you, sir.
I'm so sorry to have disturbed you all.
Please forgive me.
You never asked.
Thomas, take that up.
Leave it, Daisy! He's a grown man.
I suppose he can lift a meat pie.
Now, put that apple
tart in the lower oven.
Oh, and take that away.
Mr. Lynch shouldn't have left it there.
-What is it?
-Salt of Sorrel.
I asked him for some
to clean the brass pots.
So, put it somewhere careful. It's poison.
Seems like a lot of food
when you think they're all in mourning.
Nothing makes you hungrier or more tired
than grief.
When my sister died, God rest her soul,
I ate my way through four platefuls
of sandwiches at one sitting
and slept round the clock.
Did it make you feel better?
Not much, but it passed the time.
Oh, my Lord! What was this chopped egg
supposed to be sprinkled on?
-Was it the chicken?
-It was. Take it upstairs now.
-I can't go in the dining room.
-I should think not.
Find Thomas or William
and tell them what to do.
And for heaven's sake get a move on, girl,
before they get back from church.
Well, we've given them a memorial
in London and a memorial here.
MURRAY: I prefer memorials to funerals,
they're less dispiriting.
We could hardly have held a funeral
without the bodies.
I gather they're putting up a stone to
mark those whose bodies were never found.
In fact, I hear the Canadians are making
quite a thing at the Titanic cemetery.
I'm surprised at the number they found.
You'd think the sea
would've taken more of them.
So, Murray, what have you to tell me
about the lucky Mr. Crawley?
Nothing too terrible, I hope.
[CHUCKLES] I've only made a few inquiries
but, no, there's not much to alarm you.
Matthew Crawley is a solicitor
based in Manchester.
Manchester?
His special field is company law.
His mother is alive and he lives with her.
His father obviously
is not. He was a doctor.
I know.
It does seem odd that
my third cousin should be a doctor.
There are worse professions.
Indeed.
Do me a favor. This is supposed to be
sprinkled on the chicken.
-But isn't there more to go up?
-Oh, please, it won't take a moment.
-Go on then, give it here.
-Okay.
MURRAY: We ought to talk about
the business of the entail.
As you know, on your death,
the heir to the title inherits everything,
except for the sums set aside
for your daughters and your widow.
Yes.
Owing to the terms of her settlement,
this will include the bulk
of your wife's fortune.
[SIGHS] It has been our sole topic
of conversation
since the day the ship went down.
MURRAY: Of course it must seem
horribly unjust to Lady Grantham,
but that is how the law stands.
Is there really no way to detach her money
from the estate?
Even to me, it seems absurd.
Your father tied the knots pretty tight.
I'd say it's unbreakable.
I see.
Really, Edith, do you have to put on
such an exhibition?
She's not.
I was supposed to be engaged to him,
for heaven's sake, not you.
And I can control myself.
Then you should be ashamed.
Oh, and don't tell me
you've not sent up the egg yet.
Oh, God, help me! Please, God, help me!
Well, what on earth's the matter?
Just run upstairs to the dining room
and find William. I beg you.
-I can't do that now.
-You've got to.
-I'll be hanged if you don't.
-What?
Daisy, is that you?
Is it the chicken in a sauce
or the plain chicken with sliced oranges?
Oh, thank you, blessed and merciful Lord!
Thank you.
It's the chicken in the sauce.
I'll never do anything sinful
again, I swear it. Not till I die.
Mr. Murray, how lovely to see you.
Do come in.
You're very kind, Lady Grantham,
but I must get back to London.
-But you'll stay for luncheon?
-Thank you, but no, I'll eat on the train.
In fact, if you'd be so good as to ask
for the motor be brought round?
But didn't you want the afternoon
to talk things through?
I think we've said everything we
have to say, haven't we, my lord?
For the time being, yes.
Thank you, Murray. You've given
me a good deal to think about.
Mary, try to get everyone
into the dining room.
Edith, make sure old Lord Minterne
sits down.
-[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
-Mmm-hmm.
-They've all gone?
-They have, thank the Lord.
-Oh, what about the lawyer?
-Oh, he was the first away.
Didn't even stay for the luncheon.
I wish they'd make their minds up.
Gwen's put clean sheets
on the Blue Room bed.
Now she'll just have to strip it again.
-Can't you leave it for the next guest?
-Well, only if you don't tell.
[CHUCKLES]
So, has it all been settled?
No. I don't know if
anything's been settled.
There's a fellow in Manchester
with claims to the title, I gather,
but it's all a long way from settled.
-You mustn't take it personally.
-No, I do take it personally, Mrs. Hughes.
I can't stand by and watch our family
threatened with a loss of all they hold dear.
-They are not our family.
-Well, they're all the family I've got.
I beg your pardon.
Do you ever wish you'd gone another way?
Worked in a shop or a factory?
Had a wife and children?
Do you?
I don't know. Maybe.
Sometimes.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
William's laid tea in the library,
but her ladyship hasn't come down.
Oh, she'll be tired.
Take a tray up to her bedroom.
-Is Thomas back?
-Not yet, Mr. Carson.
He asked if he could run down the village,
I didn't see why not.
It's iniquitous.
They can't expect you to sit by silent
as your fortune is stolen away.
Can't they?
His lordship would never let it happen.
How's Bates working out?
Well, I don't like to say.
Only it seems unkind to criticize a man
for an affliction, my lady.
Even if it means he can't do his job.
How are you settling in?
Very well, I think.
Unless your lordship feels differently.
No complaints?
If I had any, I should take them
to Mr. Carson, my lord, not you.
[LAUGHS]
You're probably right.
And the house hasn't worn you out
with the endless stairs and everything?
I like the house, my lord.
I like it as a place to work.
-What happened?
-Oh, it's only the old wound.
After I left the army,
I'd a spot of bother
and just when I got through that about
a year ago my knee started playing up.
A bit of shrapnel got left in or something
and it moved, but it's fine.
It's not a problem.
And you'd let me know if you felt
it was all too much for you?
I would. But it won't be.
Thomas.
-And where have you been?
-The village.
-To send a telegram, if you must know.
-Ooh, pardon me for living.
Well, Murray didn't stay long.
-Does her ladyship know how they left it?
-No.
They talked it all through
on the way back from the church.
If I was still his valet,
I'd get it out of him.
-Bates won't say a word.
-He will not.
I bet you a tenner he's a spy
in the other direction.
I wanted that job.
We were all right together,
his lordship and me.
Then be sure to get your foot in the door
when Bates is gone.
You can't get rid of him
just because he talks behind our backs.
There's more than one way to skin a cat.
-Perhaps she misunderstood.
-No, it was quite plain.
O'Brien told her
Bates can't do the job properly.
Why was he taken on?
Oh, he was Lord Grantham's batman
when he was fighting the Boers.
I know that, but even so.
-I think it's romantic.
-I don't.
How can a valet do his work if he's lame?
He's not very lame.
There. Anything else before I go down?
No, that's it. Thank you.
Oh, I hate black.
It's not for long.
Mama says we can go into
half-mourning next month.
And back to colors by September.
-Still seems a lot for a cousin.
-But not a fiancé?
-He wasn't really a fiancé.
-No?
I thought that was what you call a man
you're going to marry.
I was only going to marry him
if nothing better turned up.
-Mary, what a horrid thing to say.
-Don't worry.
Edith would have taken him, wouldn't you?
Yes, I'd have taken him.
If you'd given me the chance,
I'd have taken him like a shot.
I just think you should know
it's not working, Mr. Carson.
Do you mean Mr. Bates is lazy?
Not lazy, exactly.
But he just can't carry.
He can hardly manage his lordship's cases.
You saw how it was when they went up
to London for the memorial.
He can't help with
the guests' luggage neither.
And as for waiting at table,
we can forget that.
-And what do you want me to do?
-Well, it's not for me to say.
But is it fair on William
to have all the extra work?
I don't believe you'd like to think
the house was falling below
the way things ought to be.
-I would not.
-That's all I'm saying.
I'm going down. Coming?
In a moment. You go.
I know you're sad about Patrick.
Whatever you say, I know it.
You're a darling.
But you see, I'm not
as sad as I should be.
And that's what makes me sad.
Thank you.
-I'll do that.
-No. No, thank you, my lord.
-I can do it.
-I'm sure.
I hope so, my lord. I hope you're sure.
Bates, we have to be sensible.
I won't be doing you a favor in
the long run if it's too much for you.
No matter what we've been through,
it's got to work.
Of course it has, sir. I mean, my lord.
Do you miss the army, Bates?
I miss a lot of things, but you have to
keep moving, don't you?
[CHUCKLING] You do, indeed.
I'll show you, my lord, I promise.
I won't let you down.
We've managed so far, haven't we?
Yes, we have. Of course we have.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
-You look very nice.
-Thank you, darling.
-Did Murray make matters clearer?
-Yes, I'm afraid he did.
By the way, O'Brien says Bates is
causing a lot of awkwardness downstairs.
You may have to do something about it.
She's always making trouble.
Is that fair when she hasn't mentioned it
before now?
I don't know why you listen to her.
It is quite eccentric, even for you,
to have a crippled valet.
Please, don't use that word.
Did he tell you he couldn't walk
when he made his application?
Don't exaggerate.
Doesn't it strike you as dishonest
not to mention it?
-I knew he'd been wounded.
-You never said.
You know I don't care
to talk about all that.
Of course I understand what it must be like
to have fought alongside someone in a war.
-Oh, you understand that, do you?
-Certainly I do.
You must form the most tremendous bonds.
-Even with a servant.
-Really?
Even with a servant?
Oh, Robert, don't catch me out.
I'm simply saying I fully see
why you want to help him.
But?
But is this the right way,
to employ him for a job he can't do?
Is it any wonder if the others' noses
are put out?
I just want to give him a chance.
Mama, I'm sorry,
no one told me you were here.
Oh, dear, such a glare.
-I feel as if I were on stage at the Gaiety.
-ROBERT: We're used to it.
I do wish you'd let me install it
in the Dower House. It's very convenient.
The man who manages the generator
could look after yours as well.
No. I couldn't have electricity in
the house. I wouldn't sleep a wink.
All those vapors seeping about.
Even Cora won't have it in the bedroom.
She did wonder about the kitchens,
but I couldn't see the point.
Well, before anyone joins us,
I'm glad of this chance for a little talk.
-I gather Murray was here today?
-News travels fast. Yes.
I saw him and he's not optimistic
that there's anything we can do.
-Well, I refuse to believe it.
-Be that as it may, it's a fact.
-But to lose Cora's fortune to...
-[ROBERT SIGHS]
Really, Mama, you know as well as I do
that Cora's fortune
is not Cora's fortune any more.
Thanks to Papa, it is
now part of the estate.
And the estate is entailed to my heir,
that is it. That is all of it.
-Robert, dear, I don't mean to sound harsh...
-You may not mean to, but I bet you will.
Twenty-four years ago you married Cora,
against my wishes, for her money.
Give it away now, what was the point of
your peculiar marriage in the first place?
If I were to tell you she'd made me
very happy, would that stretch belief?
It's not why you chose her,
above all those other girls
who could've filled my shoes so easily.
If you must know, when I think of my
motives for pursuing Cora, I'm ashamed.
There's no need to remind me of them.
Don't you care about Downton?
What do you think?
I've given my life to Downton.
I was born here and I hope to die here.
I claim no career beyond the nurture
of this house and the estate.
It is my third parent and my fourth child.
Do I care about it? Yes, I do care!
I hope I don't hear
sounds of a disagreement.
[CHUCKLING] Oh, is that what they call
discussion in New York?
Well, I'm glad you're fighting.
I'm glad somebody's putting up a fight.
You're not really fighting Granny,
are you, Papa?
Your grandmother merely wishes
to do the right thing. And so do I.
Dinner is served, my lady.
Does anyone else keep dreaming
about the Titanic?
-I can't get it out of my mind.
-Not again. Give it a rest.
Daisy, it is time to let it go.
But all them people, freezing to
death in the midnight icy water.
Oh, you sound like a penny dreadful.
I expect you saw worse things
in South Africa. Eh, Mr. Bates?
Not worse, but pretty bad.
Did you enjoy the war?
I don't think anyone enjoys war,
but there are some good memories, too.
I'm sure there are.
Mr. Bates, would you hand me that tray?
[CUTLERY CLATTERING]
[BATES EXCLAIMING]
-I'll do it.
-Sorry.
The ladies are out, we've given them coffee.
The lordship's taken his port to the library.
Anna, Gwen, go up and help clear away.
Uh, Daisy, tell Mrs. Patmore
we'll eat in 15 minutes.
[CARSON SIGHING]
Well, I keep forgetting. Does this go
next door or back to the kitchen?
Those go back, but the dessert service and
all the glasses stay in the upstairs pantry.
Put it on here.
What is it?
Her ladyship's told him
she thinks Mr. Bates ought to go.
She said to me, "if only his lordship
had been content with Thomas."
Did she really?
-What are you doing up here?
-It's a free country.
Well, I'm going for my dinner.
You two can stay here plotting.
So, the young Duke of Crowborough
is asking himself to stay.
And we know why.
You hope you know why.
That is not at all the same.
You realize the Duke thinks
Mary's prospects have altered.
-I suppose so.
-There's no "suppose" about it.
Of course, this is exactly the sort
of opportunity that will come to Mary
if we can only get things settled
in her favor.
-Is Robert coming round?
-Not yet.
To him, the risk is we succeed in saving
my money but not the estate.
He feels he'd be betraying his duty
if Downton were lost because of him.
-Well, I'm going to write to Murray.
-He won't say anything different.
Well, we have to start somewhere.
Our duty is to Mary.
[SIGHING] Well, give him a date
for when Mary's out of mourning.
No one wants to kiss a girl in black.
Oh, do stop admiring yourself.
He's not marrying you for your looks.
That's if he wants to marry you at all.
He will.
-I think you look beautiful.
-[DOOR OPENING]
Thank you, Sybil darling.
We should go down. They'll be back
from the station at any moment.
Hmm. Let's not gild the lily, dear.
And Mary, try to look surprised.
You all ready?
Very well. You should
go out to greet them.
-And me, Mr. Carson?
-No, Daisy, not you.
Can you manage, Mr. Bates?
Or would you rather wait here?
I want to go, Mr. Carson.
Well, there's no obligation
for the whole staff to be present.
-I'd like to be there.
-Hmm.
Well, it's certainly a
great day for Downton
to welcome a duke under our roof.
Remember to help me with the luggage.
Don't go running off.
I'll give you a hand.
Oh, I couldn't ask that, Mr. Bates,
not in your condition.
How long do we have to put up with this,
Mr. Carson, just so I know?
Welcome to Downton.
Lady Grantham, this is so kind of you.
Not at all, Duke.
I'm delighted you could spare the time.
-You know my daughter Mary, of course.
-Of course, Lady Mary.
And Edith, but I don't believe
you've met my youngest, Sybil.
-Ah! Lady Sybil.
-How do you do?
Come on in, you must be worn out.
Oh, Lady Grantham,
I've a confession to make,
which I hope won't cause too much bother.
My man has taken ill
just as I was leaving, so I...
Oh, well, that won't be a problem,
will it, Carson?
Certainly not.
I shall look after His Grace myself.
Oh, no, I wouldn't dream of being
such a nuisance. Surely a footman...
I remember this man.
Didn't you serve me when I dined
with Lady Grantham in London?
-I did, Your Grace.
-Ah, there we are.
We shall do very well
together, won't we...
-Uh, Thomas, Your Grace.
-Thomas.
Good.
-Hope you had a pleasant journey.
-DUKE: Mmm.
-Bates, are you all right?
-Perfectly, my lord. I apologize.
Mr. Bates.
[BATES SIGHS]
-That's better.
-Please, don't feel sorry for me.
What shall we do?
What would you like to do?
-I think I'd rather like to go exploring.
-Certainly. Gardens or house?
Oh, house I think.
Gardens are all the same to me.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Very well, we can begin in the hall,
which is one of the oldest...
No, not all those drawing rooms
and libraries.
Well, what then?
I don't know. The...
The secret passages and the attics.
Well, it seems a bit odd but, why not?
-I'll just tell Mama.
-No, don't tell your mama.
But there's nothing wrong in it.
No, indeed. I'm... I'm only worried
the others will want to join us.
[CHUCKLES]
Mary's settling him in.
Cora, don't let Mary
make a fool of herself.
By the way,
I'll be going up to London next week.
Do you want to open the house?
No, no. I'll just take Bates
and stay at the club.
-I won't be more than a day or two.
-I see. Are things progressing?
What things?
It's just a regimental dinner.
It's a pity
Bates spoiled the arrival this afternoon.
He didn't spoil anything. He fell over.
It was so undignified.
Carson hates that kind of thing.
I don't care what Carson thinks.
[CARSON CLEARING THROAT]
A message from the Dowager Countess,
my lady.
She says she won't come to tea,
but she'll join you for dinner.
Oh, Carson, I hope you weren't embarrassed
this afternoon.
I can assure you the Duke
very much appreciated his welcome.
I'm glad.
-Is Bates all right?
-I think so, my lord.
It must be so difficult
for you, all the same.
-[DOOR CLOSING]
-Don't stir.
Do you realize this is the first time
we've ever been alone?
Then you've forgotten when I pulled you
into the conservatory at the Northbrooks'.
[MARY CHUCKLES]
-How sad.
-No, I haven't.
It's not quite the same with 20 chaperones
hiding behind every fern.
And are you pleased to be alone with me,
my lady?
Oh, dear, if I answer truthfully,
you'll think me rather forward.
I don't think we should pry.
It feels rather disrespectful.
Oh, nonsense.
It's your father's house, isn't it?
You've a right to know what goes on in it.
Where does this lead?
To the men's quarters.
With a lock on the women's side.
-Only Mrs. Hughes is allowed to turn it.
-Mrs Hughes...
And you.
-And here?
-A footman, I imagine.
[DRAWERS OPENING]
-Should you do that?
-[LAUGHING] Why not?
I'm... I'm making a study
on the genus "footman".
[LAUGHING] I seek to know
the creature's ways.
-[LAUGHS]
-[DOOR OPENING]
[GASPING] Someone's coming!
-Can I help you, my lady?
-We were just exploring.
Were you looking for Thomas, Your Grace?
No, as Lady Mary said,
we've just been exploring.
Would you care to explore my room,
my lady?
Of course not, Bates.
I'm sorry to have bothered you.
We were just going down.
[MARY BREATHING HEAVILY]
Why did you apologize to that man?
It's not his business what we do.
I always apologize when I'm in the wrong.
It's a habit of mine.
The plain fact is Mr. Bates,
through no fault of his own,
Is not able to fulfill the extra duties
expected of him.
He can't lift. He can't serve a table.
He's dropping things all over the place.
On a night like tonight
he should act as a third footman.
As it is, my lord, we may have to have
a maid in the dining room.
Cheer up, Carson, there are worse things
happening in the world.
Not worse than a maid serving a duke.
So you're quite determined?
It's a hard decision, your lordship.
A very hard decision.
-But the honor of Downton is at stake.
-Don't worry, Carson.
I know all about hard decisions
when it comes to the honor of Downton.
Don't I, boy?
William, you mustn't let
Thomas take advantage.
He's only a footman, same as you.
It's all right, Mrs. Hughes. I like to
keep busy. It takes your mind off things.
What things have you got
to take your mind off?
If you're feeling homesick,
there's no shame in it.
-No.
-It means you come from a happy home.
There's plenty of people here
would envy that.
Yes, Mrs. Hughes.
-Will that be all, my lord?
-Yes.
That is... Not exactly.
Have you recovered from your fall
this afternoon?
I'm very sorry about that, my lord.
I don't know what happened.
The thing is, Bates,
I said I'd give you a trial and I have.
If it were only up to me...
It's this question of
a valet's extra duties.
You mean waiting a table
when there's a large party?
That and carrying things and...
You do see that Carson can't be expected
to compromise the efficiency of his staff.
I do, my lord, of course I do.
Might I make a suggestion?
That when an extra footman is required,
the cost could come out of my wages.
Absolutely not.
I couldn't possibly allow that.
Because I am very eager to stay, my lord.
Very eager, indeed.
I know you are.
And I was eager that this should work.
You see, it is unlikely that I should find
another position.
But surely in a smaller house,
where less is expected of you.
It's not likely.
I mean to help until you find something.
I couldn't take your money, my lord. I
can take wages for a job done. That's all.
Very good, my lord. I'll go at once.
There's no need to rush out into the
night. Take the London train tomorrow.
It leaves at 9:00.
You'll have a month's wages, too.
That I insist on.
It's a bloody business, Bates,
but I can't see any way around it.
I quite understand, my lord.
I'm afraid we're rather
a female party tonight, Duke.
But you know what it's like trying
to balance numbers in the country.
A single man outranks the Holy Grail.
No, I'm terribly Flattered
to be dining en famille.
What were you and Mary doing
in the attics this afternoon?
I expect Mary was just showing the Duke
the house. Weren't you?
-Are you a student of architecture?
-Mmm, absolutely.
Then I do hope you'll come
and inspect my little cottage.
-It was designed by Wren.
-Ah.
-COUNTESS: For the first earl's sister.
-The attics?
Yes. Mary took the Duke up to the attics.
Whatever for?
CORA: Why was this, dear?
We were just looking around.
Looking around? What is there
to look at but servants' rooms?
What was the real reason, hmm?
[LAUGHING NERVOUSLY]
Don't be such a chatterbox, Edith.
I think we'll go through.
-I still don't understand...
-Will you hold your tongue!
How long do you think they'll be?
I'm starving.
-Have you settled the ladies?
-Yes, Mr. Carson.
Then it won't be long
once they go through.
DAISY: You think he'll speak out?
Do you think we'll have a duchess
to wait on? Imagine that.
You won't be waiting on her,
whatever happens.
There is no reason why the eldest daughter
and heiress of the Earl of Grantham
should not wear a duchess's coronet
with honor.
Heiress, Mr. Carson? Has it been decided?
It will be, if there's
any justice in the world.
Well, we'll know soon enough.
What are you doing, Anna?
I thought I'd take something up to Mr. Bates,
him not being well enough to come down.
-You don't mind, do you, Mrs. Hughes?
-I don't mind. Not this once.
No, take him whatever he might need.
Mr. Bates is leaving
without a stain on his character.
I hope you all observe that
in the manner of your parting.
Well, I don't see why he has to go.
I don't mind doing a bit of extra work...
It's not up to you.
I'll take care of his lordship.
Shall I, Mr. Carson?
Not while you're looking after the Duke,
you won't.
[CHUCKLES] I'll see
to his lordship myself.
[SOFT SOBBING]
[SIGHING]
[SOBBING CONTINUES]
Mr. Bates? Are you there?
[SIGHING]
I brought something up,
in case you were hungry.
That's very kind.
-I'm ever so sorry you're going.
-I'll be all right.
Of course you will.
There's always a place for a man like you.
Oh, yes. Something will turn up.
Tell us when you're fixed.
Just... drop us a line.
Else I'll worry.
Well, we can't have that.
[ANNA SNIFFLING]
We must go and let
the servants get in here.
I should be grateful
if we could stay just a minute more.
I have... I have something to ask you.
I was terribly sorry
to hear about your cousins.
You said.
Did you know them?
Not well. I used to see Patrick Crawley
at the odd thing.
I imagine it will mean
some adjustments for you all.
To lose two heirs in
one night, it's terrible.
-Indeed, it was terrible.
-Awful.
But then again, it's an ill wind.
At least Lady Mary's prospects
must have rather improved.
Have they?
Haven't they?
[INHALES DEEPLY] I will not be coy
and pretend I do not understand
your meaning,
though you seem very informed
on this family's private affairs.
But you ought perhaps to know
that I do not intend to fight the entail.
Not any part of it.
You can't be serious.
It pains me to say it, but I am.
You'll give up your entire estate?
Your wife's money into the bargain,
to a perfect stranger?
You won't even put up a fight?
I hope he proves to be perfect,
but I rather doubt it.
Ha.
Very odd thing to joke about.
No odder than this conversation.
So, there you have it.
But Mary will still have her settlement,
which you won't find ungenerous.
[COUGHS]
-[CLEARING THROAT] I'm sorry?
-I only meant that
her portion, when she marries,
will be more than respectable.
-You'll be pleased, I promise you.
-Oh, heavens.
-I hope I haven't given the wrong impression.
-You know very well...
-My dear Lord Grantham...
-Don't "My dear Lord Grantham" me!
You knew what you were doing
when you came here.
You encouraged Mary, all of us,
into thinking...
Forgive me, but I came to express
my sympathies and my friendship.
Nothing more.
Lady Mary is a charming person.
Whoever marries her will be a lucky man.
It will not, however, be me.
I see, and what was it you asked me
to stay behind to hear?
I... I forget.
Well, aren't you coming
into the drawing room?
I'm... I'm tired. I think I'll just slip
away. Please make my excuses.
I'm afraid I've worn you out.
Tomorrow we can just...
I'm leaving in the morning. Good night.
Oh, you might tell that footman...
-Thomas.
-Thomas. You might tell him I've gone up.
So he slipped the hook?
At least I'm not fishing with no bait.
I don't believe that.
Well, believe what you like.
He won't break the entail.
The unknown cousin gets everything
[SIGHING] and Mary's inheritance
will be the same as it always was.
Oh, how was I to know?
When the lawyer turned up, I thought...
You weren't to and you did the right thing
to telegraph me.
-It's just not going to come off.
-So what now?
[LAUGHS] Well, you know how I'm fixed.
I have to have an heiress,
if it means going to New York to find one.
What about me?
You... You will wish me well.
You said you'd find me a job
if I wanted to leave.
And do you?
I want to be a valet.
I'm sick of being a footman.
Yeah, Thomas, I don't need a valet.
I thought you were
getting rid of the new one here.
And I've done it, but I'm not sure
Carson's going to let me take over.
And I want to be with you.
Mmm.
I just can't see it working, can you?
[LAUGHING] We don't seem to have the basis
of a servant-master relationship, do we?
-You came here to be with me.
-Among other reasons.
And one swallow doesn't make a summer.
-Aren't you forgetting something?
-What?
[LAUGHS] Are you threatening me?
Because of a youthful dalliance?
A few weeks of madness
in a London season?
You wouldn't hold that against me, surely?
I would if I have to.
And who'd believe a greedy footman
over the words of a duke?
If you're not careful,
you'll end up behind bars.
I've got proof.
Mmm-hmm.
You mean these?
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[THOMAS PANTING]
You know, my mother's always telling me
never put anything in writing.
And now, thanks to
you, I never will again.
How did you get them?
-You bastard.
-Don't be a bad loser, Thomas.
Go to bed.
Unless you want to stay.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
I think I'll turn in.
-No big announcement, then?
-No.
Nor likely to be. He's
off on the 9:00 train.
He never is!
And when we've had a turkey killed
for tomorrow's dinner!
-I wonder what she did wrong.
-She did nothing wrong.
Not from the way his lordship was talking.
So His Grace turned out to be graceless.
Good night, Mrs. Hughes.
Good night, Mr. Carson.
If you knew that was your decision,
why put Mary through it?
But I didn't know it was my decision,
my final decision, until tonight.
But I find I cannot ruin the estate or
hollow out the title for the sake of Mary,
even with a better man than that.
I try to understand. I just can't.
Well, why should you?
Downton is in my blood and in my bones.
It's not in yours.
And I can no more be the cause
of its destruction
than I could betray my country.
Besides, how was I to know
he wouldn't take her without the money?
Don't pretend to be a child
because it suits you.
[SIGHING] Do you think she would've
been happy with a fortune hunter?
She might've been.
I was.
Have you been happy?
Really, have I made you happy?
Yes.
That is, since you fell in love with me,
which, if I remember correctly,
was about a year after we were married.
Not a year. Not as long as that.
-But it wouldn't have happened for Mary.
-Why not?
Because I am so much nicer
than the Duke of Crowborough.
I'll be the judge of that.
[ROBERT CHUCKLES]
Just don't think
I'm going to let it rest, Robert.
I haven't given up by any means.
-I must do what my conscience tells me.
-And so must I.
And I don't want you
to think I'll let it rest.
[ROBERT CHUCKLES]
My lord, would it be acceptable
for Bates to ride in front with Taylor?
Otherwise, it means
getting the other car out.
He and His Grace are
catching the same train.
Perfectly acceptable.
And if His Grace doesn't like it,
he can lump it.
You've been so kind, Lady Grantham.
Thank you.
Goodbye, Duke.
You'll make my farewells
to your delightful daughters?
They'd have been down
if they'd known you were leaving so soon.
Alas, something's come up
which has taken me quite by surprise.
Obviously.
Well, Grantham, this has been
a highly enjoyable interlude.
Has it? And I feared it had
proved a disappointment.
Not at all, not at all.
A short stay in your lovely house
has driven away my cares.
We ought to go, my lord,
if His Grace is to catch the train.
Goodbye, Bates, and good luck.
Good luck to you, my lord.
Wait!
-Get out, Bates.
-DUKE: I really mustn't be late.
Get back inside
and we'll say no more about it.
It wasn't right, Carson.
I just didn't think it was right.
-First post, ma'am.
-Thank you, Ellen.
-One for you.
-Hmm. Thank you, Mother.
-Oh, it's from Lord Grantham.
-Really? What on earth does he want?
He wants to change our lives.