[Music playing]
Advertise your product or brand herecontact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
[Tapping, spring rattling]
[Scrapes]
[Squeaking]
[Music playing]
- Wow.- Mmm.
- Wow.- Mm-hmm.
- Wow.- Yes, Marlin.
No, I see it.It's beautiful.
So, Coral, when you saidyou wanted an ocean view...
you didn't think you'd getthe whole ocean, did you?
[Sighs] Oh, yeah.A fish can breathe out here.
Did your man deliver,or did he deliver?
- My man delivered.- And it wasn't so easy.
Because a lot of other clownfishhad their eyes on this place.
You better believe they did...every single one of them.
Mm-hmm. You did good.
And the neighborhoodis awesome.
[Chattering and laughing]
[Snipping]
So, you do like it, don't you?
No, no. I do, I do.I really do like it.
But, Marlin, I know thatthe drop off is desirable...
with the great schoolsand the amazing view...
but do we really needso much space?
But do we really needso much space?
Coral, honey, these are our kidswe're talking about.
They deserve the best.Look, look, look.
They'll wake up,poke their little heads out...
and they see a whale!Right by their bedroom window.
And they see a whale!Right by their bedroom window.
Shh. You'll wake the kids.
Oh, right, right.
Aw, look. They're dreaming.
We still have to name them.
You want to nameall of them right now?
All right, we'll namethis half Marlin Junior...
and this half Coral Junior.
- OK, we're done.- I like Nemo.
Nemo. We'll name one Nemo...
but I'd like most of themto be Marlin Junior.
Just think,in a couple of days...
- we're going to be parents.- Yeah.
What if they don't like me?
- Marlin.- No, really.
There's over 400 eggs.Odds are, one will like you.
What?
- You remember how we met?- I try not to.
Well, I remember."Excuse me, miss...
"can you check and seeif I have a hook in my lip?"
You got a little closerbecause it was wiggling.
- Get away, get away!- Here he is. Cutie's here.
Where did everybody go?
[Breathing heavily]
[Marlin gasps]
Coral, get inside the house.
No, Coral, don't.They'll be fine.
Just get inside...You, right now.
[Roars]
No! Ow!
[Gasps] Oh!
Ooh! Ooh!
[Roar echoes]
[Dramatic music playing]
[Marlin mutters]
Coral!
[Panting]
Coral?
[Gasps]
[Crying]
Oh!
Ohh.
There, there, there.
It's OK. Daddy's here.
Daddy's got you.
I promise, I will neverlet anything happen to you...
Nemo.
[Dramatic music playing]
NEMO: First day of school!
Wake up, wake up!First day of school.
I don't want to go to school...five more minutes.
Not you, Dad, me.
- OK. Huh?- Get up, get up.
It's time for school,time for school.
All right, I'm up.
Whoa! [Thud]
- Nemo!- First day of school!
- Nemo, don't move.- Unh! Unh!
You'll never get outof there yourself.
I'll do it. Unh! [Pop]
- You feel a break?- No.
Sometimes you can't tell'cause fluid rushes to the area.
- Are you woozy?- No.
- How many stripes do I have?- I'm fine.
- Answer the stripe question.- Three.
No! See?Something's wrong with you.
I have one, two, three...That's all I have?
You're OK.How's the lucky fin?
- Lucky.- Let's see.
[Grunts]
Are you sure you want to goto school this year?
There's no problem if you don't.You can wait 5 or 6 years.
Come on, Dad,it's time for school.
- Forgot to brush.- Ohh.
Do you want this anemoneto sting you?
- Yes.- Brush.
- OK, I'm done.- You missed a spot.
- Where?- There.
Ha ha! Right there.And here and here.
[Music playing]
All right, we're excited.
The first day of school.Here we go.
We're ready to learnto get some knowledge.
What's the one thing we haveto remember about the ocean?
- It's not safe.- That's my boy.
First, we check to seethat the coast is clear.
We go out... and back in.
And then we go out...and back in.
And then one more time...out and back in.
And sometimes, if you wantto do it four times...
- Dad...- All right, come on, boy.
Maybe while I'm at school,I'll see a shark.
- I highly doubt that.- Have you ever met a shark?
No, and I don't plan to.
- How old are sea turtles?- I don't know.
Sandy Planktonfrom next door...
he says that sea turtles liveto be about 100 years old.
He says that sea turtles liveto be about 100 years old.
If I ever meet a sea turtle,I'll ask him.
After I'm donetalking to the shark, OK?
Whoa! Hold on.Wait to cross.
Hold my fin.
Dad, you're notgoing to freak out...
like you did atthe petting zoo, are you?
MARLIN:That snaiI was about to charge.
Hmm. I wonder wherewe're supposed to go.
ALL: Bye, Mom!
I'll pick you up after school.
Ha ha!
Come on, you guys, stop it!Give it back!
Come on,we'll try over there.
[Laughing]
Excuse me, is this wherewe meet his teacher?
Well, look who's outof the anemone.
Yes. Shocking, I know.
- Marty, right?- Marlin.
- Bob.- Ted.
Bill.Hey, you're a clownfish.
You're funny, right?Tell us a joke.
- Yeah.- Yeah.
Well, actually,that's a common misconception.
Clownfish are no funnierthan any other fish.
- Come on, clownie.- Do something funny.
All right, I know one joke.
There's a mollusk, see?And he walks up to a sea...
He doesn't walk up,he swims up.
Actually,the mollusk isn't moving.
He's in one place,and then the sea cucumber...
Well, they... I'm mixed up.
There was a molluskand a sea cucumber.
None of them were walking,so forget that l...
Sheldon! Get out ofMr. Johannsen's yard now!
- Whoa!- All right, you kids!
Ooh, where'd you go?
Dad, can I go play, too?Can I?
I would feel better ifyou'd play on the sponge beds.
[Squishing]
[Thud]
[Cries]
That's where I would play.
[Laughing]
- What's wrong with his fin?- He looks funny.
Ow! Hey, what'd I do?
Be nice.It's his first time at school.
He was born with it.We call it his lucky fin.
- Dad...- See this tentacle?
It's actually shorterthan all my other tentacles...
but you can't really tell.
Especially whenI twirl them like this.
I'm H-2-O intolerant.
- Ah-choo!- I'm obnoxious.
Oh
Let's name the zones,the zones, the zones
Let's namethe zones of the open sea
KIDS: Mr. Ray!
- Come on, Nemo.- You better stay with me.
Mesopelagic, bathyal,abyssalpelagic
All the rest are too deepfor you and me to see
Huh. I wonder wheremy class has gone?
ALL: We're under here!
Oh, there you are.
Climb aboard, explorers.
Oh, knowledgeexploring
Is, oh, so lyrical
When you think thoughtsthat are empirical
Dad, you can go now.
- Hello. Who is this?- I'm Nemo.
Nemo, all new explorersmust answer a science question.
- OK.- You live in what kind of home?
An anemon-none.
A nemenem-menome.
OK, don't hurt yourself.Welcome aboard, explorers.
Just so you know,he's got a little fin.
I find if he's havingtrouble swimming...
I let him take a break,10, 15 minutes.
NEMO: Dad, it's timefor you to go now.
Don't worry. We're gonnastay together as a group.
OK, class,optical orbits up front.
And remember, we keepour supraesophogeal ganglion...
to ourselves.That means you, Jimmy.
JIMMY: Aw, man!
Bye, Nemo!
Bye, Dad!
Bye, son!
Be safe.
You're doing pretty wellfor a first-timer.
You can't hold on to themforever, can you?
I had a tough time withmy oldest out at the drop off.
They got to grow up...The drop off?
They're going to the drop off?What are you, insane?
Why don't we fry them up nowand serve them with chips?
Hey, Marty, calm down.
Don't tell meto be calm, pony boy.
Pony boy?
For a clownfish,he really isn't that funny.
Pity.
Oh
Let's name the species,the species, the species
Let's name the speciesthat live in the sea
NEMO: Whoa.
There's
Porifera, coelenterata,hydrozoa, scyphozoa
Anthozoa, ctenophora,bryozoas, three
Gastropoda, arthropoda,echinoderma
And some fishlike you and me
Come on, sing with me.
Oh
[Continues singing indistinctly]
[Dramatic music playing]
Just the girls this time.
Oh, seaweed is cool
Seaweed is fun
It makes its food
OK, the drop off.
All right, kids,feel free to explore...
but stay close.
[Gasps] Stromaliticcyanobacteria! Gather.
[All gasp]
An entire ecosystem containedin one infinitesimal speck.
There are as many protein pairscontained in this...
Come on, let's go.
Come on, sing with me!
There's porifera,coelenterata
Hydrozoa, scyphozoa
Anthozoa, ctenophora,bryozoas, three
Hey, guys, wait up!
Whoa.
Cool.
Saved your life!
Aw, you guys made me ink.
[Both laugh]
What's that?
TAD: I know what that is.Sandy Plankton saw one.
He said it was called a butt.
- Whoa.- Wow.
That's a pretty big butt.
[Water bubbles]
Oh, look at me.I'm going to touch the butt.
- Ah-choo! Whoa!- Ha ha ha!
Oh, yeah?Let's see you get closer.
OK.
Beat that.
Come on, Nemo.How far can you go?
My dad says it's not safe.
- Nemo! No!- Dad?
You were aboutto swim into open water.
No, I wasn't...
Good thing I was here.If I hadn't shown up...
- He wasn't going to go.- He was too afraid.
No, I wasn't.
This does notconcern you, kids...
and you're luckyI don't tell your parents.
You know you can't swim well.
I can swim fine, Dad, OK?
No, it's not OK.You shouldn't be near here.
OK, I was right. You'll startschool in a year or two.
No, Dad! Just becauseyou're scared of the ocean...
Clearly, you're not ready...
and you're not coming backuntiI you are.
You thinkyou can do these things...
but you just can't, Nemo!
I hate you.
There's
Nothing to see.Gather. Over there.
Excuse me.Is there anything I can do?
I am a scientist, sir.Is there any problem?
I'm sorry. I didn't meanto interrupt things.
He isn't a good swimmer,and it's a little too soon...
for him to be out hereunsupervised.
MR. RAY: I can assure you,he's quite safe with me.
MARLIN: I'm sure he is,but you have a large class...
and he can get lost from sightif you're not looking.
I'm not sayingyou're not looking.
Oh, my gosh!Nemo's swimming out to sea!
[Gasps] Nemo!
What do you think you're doing?
You'll get stuck out there...
and I'll have to get youbefore another fish does.
Get back here!
I said get back here now!
Stop! You takeone more move, mister...
Don't you dare!
If you put one finon that boat...
Are you listening to me?
Don't touch the bo... Nemo!
[Whispering]He touched the butt.
You paddle your little taiIright back here, Nemo.
That's right.
You are in big trouble,young man.
Do you hear me? Big...
[Respirator hisses]
- Big...- Aah!
[Gasps] Aah!
Daddy! Help me!
I'm coming, Nemo!
[Gasps]
- Aah!- Get under me, kids!
Aah! Oh! No!
Dad!
Daddy!
[Panting]
Oh! Nemo!
Unh. Nemo!
Nemo, no! Nemo!
Nemo! Nemo! No!
[Panting]
No!
Aah!
Uhh. [Panting]
Nemo! Nemo!
[Dramatic music playing]
[Moaning]
Whoa! Hold on.
[Marlin panting]
Oh, no.
No. No, it's gone.It's gone.
No, no,it can't be gone.
No, no! Nemo!
Nemo! Nemo!
No! [Inhales]
No! No, please, no!
No, no!
[Panting]
Has anybody seen a boat?
Please! A white boat!
They took my son!
My son! Help me, please.
- Look out!- What?
Ooh. Ohh.
Ohh. Oh, oh. Sorry.I didn't see you.
- Sir? Are you OK?- He's gone, he's gone.
There, there.It's all right.
- He's gone.- It'll be OK.
No, no. They took him away.I have to find the boat.
A boat?Hey, I've seen a boat.
- You have?- It passed by not too long ago.
- A white one?- Hi. I'm Dory.
Where? Which way?
Oh, oh, oh.It went this way.
It went this way.Follow me.
Thank you. Thank you,thank you so much.
No problem.
[Dramatic music playing]
[Panting]
MARLIN: Hey...
Wait!
- Will you quit it?- What?
I'm trying to swim here.Ocean isn't big enough for you?
You got a problem, buddy?Huh? Huh?
Do you? Do you?You want a piece of me?
Ooh, I'm scared now. What?
- Wait a minute.- Stop following me, OK?
What? You're showing mewhere the boat went.
A boat?Hey, I've seen a boat.
It passed by not too long ago.It went this way.
It went this way.Follow me.
Wait a minute.What is going on?
You already told mewhich way the boat was going.
I did? Oh, no.
If this is some kind ofpractical joke, it's not funny.
And I know funny.I'm a clownfish.
No, it's not. I know it's not.I'm so sorry.
See, I suffer fromshort-term memory loss.
Short-term memory loss.I don't believe this.
No, it's true. I forget thingsalmost instantly.
It runs in my family.At least, I think it does.
Um, hmm. Where are they?
Can I help you?
Something's wrongwith you... really.
You're wasting my time.
I have to find my son.
[Gasps]
Hello.
- Ohh.- Well, hi!
Name's Bruce.
It's all right.I understand.
Why trust a shark, right?
[Laughs]
So, what's a coupleof bites like you...
doing out so late, eh?
We're not doing anything.We're not even out.
Great!Then how'd you morsels...
like to come to a littleget-together I'm having?
You mean, like a party?
Yeah, right. A party.What do you say?
I love parties.That sounds like fun.
Parties are fun,and it's tempting, but...
Oh, come on, I insist.
MARLIN: OK.That's all that matters.
DORY: Hey, look, balloons.It is a party.
BRUCE: Ha ha ha ha!Mind your distance, though.
Those balloonscan be a bit dodgy.
You wouldn't wantone of them to pop.
[Dramatic music playing]
[Gasps]
MARLIN: Oh.
Ohh.
Anchor! Chum!
There you are, Bruce.Finally.
- We got company.- It's about time, mate.
We've already gonethrough the snacks...
and I'm still starving.
We almost had a feeding frenzy.
Come on,let's get this over with.
[Bell rings]
BRUCE: Right, then.
The meeting has officiallycome to order.
Let us all say the pledge.
I am a nice shark,not a mindless eating machine.
If I am to change this image...
I must first change myself.
Fish are friends, not food.
Except stinkin' dolphins.
Dolphins. Yeah.They think they're so cute.
"Look at me.I'm a flippin' little dolphin.
"Let me flip for you.Ain't I something?"
Right, then.Today's meeting is Step 5...
Bring a Fish Friend.
Do you all have your friends?
Got mine.
[Hyperventilating]
- Hey, there.- How about you, Chum?
Oh, I... seem to havemisplaced my friend.
[Marlin gasps]
BRUCE: That's all right, Chum.
I had a feelingthis would be a difficult step.
You can help yourselfto one of my friends.
Thanks, mate.A little chum for Chum, eh?
BRUCE: I'll startthe testimonies.
Hello. My name is Bruce.
BOTH: Hello, Bruce.
It has been three weekssince my last fish.
On my honor, or may I bechopped up and made into soup.
- You're an inspiration!- Amen.
[Grunts]
Right, then. Who's next?
DORY: Pick me, pick me.
Yes. The littleSheila down the front.
- Whoo!- Come on up here.
Hi. I'm Dory.
- Hello, Dory.- And, uh, well...
I don't thinkI've ever eaten a fish.
- That's incredible.- Good on you, mate.
[Sighs] I'm gladI got that off my chest.
All right, anyone else?
How about you, mate?What's your problem?
MARLIN: Me?I don't have a problem.
Oh, OK.
- Denial.- Aah!
BRUCE: Just startwith your name.
OK. Uh, hello.
My name is Marlin.I'm a clownfish.
- A clownfish? Really?- Tell us a joke.
I love jokes.
I actually do know onethat's pretty good.
There was this mollusk...
and he walks upto a sea cucumber.
Normally, they don't talk,sea cucumbers...
but in a joke,everyone talks...
so the sea mollusksays to the cucumber...
[Dramatic music playing]
NEMO: Daddy!
Nemo!
Nemo! Ha ha! Nemo!I don't get it.
For a clownfish,he's not that funny.
No, no, no, no.He's my son.
He was taken by these divers.
DORY: [Gasps]Oh, my. You poor fish.
Humans... think they owneverything.
Probably American.
Now, there is a father...Looking for his little boy.
MARLIN: What dothese markings mean?
[Sobs]I never knew my father!
- Group hug.- We're all mates here, mate.
I can't read human.
DORY: We got to find a fishthat can read this.
- Hey, look, sharks.- No, no, no, Dory!
- Guys, guys.- No, Dory.
That's mine.Give it to me.
Gimme! Ow!
Oh, I'm sorry.Are you OK?
- Ow, ow, ow.- I'm so sorry.
You really clocked me there.Am I bleeding?
- Ohh.- Ow, ow, ow.
Dory, are you OK... Ohh.
Ohh, that's good.
BOTH: Intervention!
- Just a bite.- Hold it together, mate!
Remember, Bruce,fish are friends, not food!
- Food!- Dory, look out!
- Aah!- I'm having fish tonight!
Remember the steps, mate!
MARLIN: Aah!
- Aah! Whoa!- Aah!
- Just one bite!- Aah!
[Clanking]
G'day. Grr!
There's no way out!
There's got to be a wayto escape!
[Clanging]
Who is it?
Dory, help mefind a way out!
Sorry. Come back later.We're trying to escape.
[Clang]
- There's got to be a way out!- Here's something.
"Es-cap-e."I wonder what that means.
Funny. It's spelledjust like "escape."
- Let's go.- Aah!
Here's Brucey!
Wait a minute.You can read?
I can read?That's right. I can read!
Well, then, here.Read this now.
- Aah!- Ohh!
He really doesn't mean it.He never even knew his father.
CHUM:Don't fall off the wagon!
- Aah!- Aah!
[Roars]
Oh, no, it's blocked!
[Grunting]
No, Bruce, focus.
Sorry about Bruce, mate.
He's really a nice guy.
I need to get that mask.
You want that mask? OK.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Quick, grab the mask!
[Snarls]
Oh, no. Bruce?
[Sniffs] What?
[Dramatic music playing]
[Gasps]Swim away! Swim away!
DORY:Aw, is the party over?
[Dink, boom]
[Explosions]
[PIop]
Nice.
[Splash]
Dad?
[Panting]
Daddy?
Huh?
[Dramatic music playing]
Aah! Uhh!
[Tapping glass]
Uhh!
[Panting]
- Barbara.- Uh-huh?
Prep for his anterior crown,would you, please?
And I'm going to needa few more cotton rolls.
BARBARA: OK.
Hello, little fella.
Aah!
Heh heh heh!Beauty, isn't he?
I found that guystruggling for life...
out on the reef,and I saved him.
So, has that Novocainekicked in yet?
PATIENT: I think so.We're ready to roll.
[Gasps]
Bubbles!
[Muttering]
My bubbles.
He likes bubbles.
Aah! Ohh! No! Uhh!
[Fish murmuring]
[Whimpering]
- Bonjour.- Aah!
Slow down, little fella.There's nothing to worry about.
- He's scared to death.- I want to go home.
Do you know where my dad is?
Honey, your dad's probablyback at the pet store.
Pet store?
Yeah, you know, like,I'm from Bob's Fish Mart.
- Pet Palace.- Fish-O-Rama.
- MaiI order.- Ebay.
- So, which one is it?- I'm from the ocean.
Ah, the ocean. The ocean?
Aah! Aah! Aah!
He hasn't been decontaminated.Jacques!
- Oui.- Clean him!
Oui.
- Ocean.- Ooh, la mer. Bon.
[Accordion music playing]
Voila. He is clean.
[Pop]
Wow. The big blue.What's it like?
- Big and blue?- I knew it.
If there's anything you need,just ask your Auntie Deb.
Or if I'm not around,you can talk to my sister Flo.
Hi. How are you?
Don't listen to anythingmy sister says.
She's nuts.Ha ha ha ha!
[Muffled] We got a live one.
- Can't hear you, Peach.- I said we got a live one.
- Boy, oh, boy.- What do we got?
Root canal... and by the looksof those x-rays...
it's not going to be pretty.
[Drill whines] Ow!
- Dam and clamp installed?- Yep.
- What did he use to open?- Gator-Glidden drill.
He seems to favorthat one lately.
I can't see, Flo.
You're gettinga little too... Aah!
PEACH: Now he's doingthe SchiIder technique.
BLOAT: He's usinga Hedstrom file.
That's not a Hedstrom file.That's a K-Flex.
It has a teardrop cross-section.Clearly a Hedstrom.
- No, no, K-Flex.- Hedstrom.
- K-Flex!- Hedstrom!
There I go.A little help, over here.
DEB: I'll go deflate him.
[Deflates]
DENTIST: All right.Go ahead and rinse.
Oh, the human mouthis a disgusting place.
[Thud]
- Hey, Nigel.- What did I miss?
PEACH: Root canal... a doozy.
Root canal?What did he use to open?
- Gator-Glidden drill.- He's favoring that one.
Hope he doesn't get surplussealer at the portal terminus.
- Hello. Who's this?- New guy. Ha ha ha!
The dentisttook him off the reef.
An outie. From my neckof the woods, eh?
Sorry if I ever tooka snap at you.
Fish gotta swim,birds gotta eat.
Hey! No, no, no, no!
They're not your fish.They're my fish.
Come on, go.Go on, shoo!
Aw, the picture broke.
This here's Darla.She's my niece.
She's going to beeight this week.
Hey, little fella.
Say helloto your new mummy.
She'll be here Fridayto pick you up.
You're her present.Shh, shh, shh.
It's our little secret.
Well, Mr. Tucker,while that sets up...
I'm going to see a manabout a wallaby.
Oh, Darla.
What?What's wrong with her?
GURGLE: She wouldn't stopshaking the bag.
- Poor Chuckles.- He was her present last year.
BLOAT: Hitched a rideon the porcelain express.
[Toilet flushes]
PEACH: She's a fish killer.
I can't go with that girl.
I have to get backto my dad.
Aah! Daddy! Help me!
Oh, he's stuck.
GILL: Nobody touch him.
Nobody touch him.
[Nemo grunting]
Can you help me?
No. You got yourselfin there.
You can get yourself out.
- GiIl...- I want to see him do it.
Calm down. Alternate wigglingyour fins and your taiI.
I can't. I have a bad fin.
Never stopped me.
[Dramatic music playing]
[Gasps]
Just think aboutwhat you need to do.
[Grunting]
Come on.
Perfect.
- Yay!- You did it!
Good squirming.Ha ha ha!
Wow. From the ocean...just like you, Gill.
Yeah.
[Chuckles]I've seen that look before.
What are you thinking about?
I'm thinking...
tonight, we give the kida proper reception.
So, kid,you got a name or what?
Nemo. I'm Nemo.
Nemo. Nemo.
[Dory snoring]
[Mutters]
DORY: Are you gonna eat that?
[Metal creaking]
[Both snoring]
- Careful with that hammer.- Huh?
[Dramatic music playing]
[Panting] No, no.
What does it say? Dory!
DORY:A sea monkey has my money.
Wake up. Get up. Come on.
Come on!
- Yes, I'm a natural blue.- Get up!
DORY: Look out!Sharks eat fish! Aah!
[Rumbling]
- Aah!- Aah!
[Both screaming]
[Gasps] Aah!
[Loud thud]
[Both coughing]
DORY: Wow. Dusty.
MARLIN: The mask.Where's the mask?
[Water bubbles]
No! No, not the mask!
Get it! Get the mask!Get the mask! Get it!
[Panting]
DORY:Hoo doot doo dootdoot doo doot
Whoo-hoo!
La la la la la la
It just keeps going on,doesn't it?
Echo! Echo!
Hey, what you doing?
It's gone.I've lost the mask.
- Did you drop it?- You dropped it!
That was my only chanceof finding my son.
Now it's gone.
Hey, Mr. Grumpy Gills...
when life gets you down,know what you got to do?
- I don't want to know.- Just keep swimming.
Just keep swimming,swimming, swimming
What do we do?We swim, swim
Dory, no singing.
Ho ho ho ho ho ho
I love to swim
When you want to swim
See, I'm going to getstuck now with that song.
- Now it's in my head.- Sorry.
Dory, do you see anything?
- Aah! Something's got me.- That was me. I'm sorry.
- Who's that?- Who could it be? It's me.
DORY: Are you my conscience?
MARLIN: Yeah, yeah.I'm your conscience.
We haven't spoken for a while.How are you?
- Can't complain.- Yeah? Good.
Now, Dory,I want you to tell me...
Do you see anything?
I see a... I see a light.
- A light?- Yeah. Over there.
- Hey, conscience, am I dead?- No. I see it, too.
[Dramatic music playing]
What is it?
It's so pretty.
I'm feeling... happy...
which is a big deal for me.
I want to touch it.
- Oh.- Ooh.
Hey, come back.Come on back here.
I'm gonna get you
I'm gonna get you.
I'm gonna swim with you
I'm gonna beyour best friend
Good feeling's gone.
[Roars]
- Whoa!- Waah!
[Screaming]
MARLIN: I can't see!I don't know where I'm going!
DORY: Haah!
- The mask!- What mask?
OK, I can't see a thing.
[Roars]
- Oh, gee.- Hey, look, a mask.
Read it!
DORY: I'm sorry,but if you could just...
bring it a little closer,I kind of need the light.
Bring it a little closer,I kind of need the light.
That's great.Keep it right there.
- Just read it!- OK, OK.
Mr. Bossy. Uh, "P."
OK. "P. Sher..."
"Sher... P. Sher..."P. Shirley? P..."
[Roars]
Oh. The first line's"P. Sherman."
"P. Sherman"doesn't make any sense!
DORY: OK. Second line. "42."
MARLIN: Don't eat me.Don't eat me. Aah!
[Roars]
DORY: Light, please!
[Muffled screaming]
DORY: "Walla... walla..."
MARLIN: Waah! Waah! Waah!
DORY: The second line's"42 Wallaby Way."
MARLIN: That's great.Speed read. Take a guess.
No pressure. No problem.There's a lot of pressure.
Pressure! Take a guessnow with pressure!
- "Sydney"! It's "Sydney"!- Duck!
DORY: Aah!
MARLIN: I'm dead.I'm dead, I'm dead, I'm dead.
I died. I'm dead.
[Groaning]
[Dramatic music playing]
[Marlin laughs]
Whoo-hoo!
We did it, we did it
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah
No eating heretonight, whoo!
BOTH:Eating here tonight
No, no, no,eating here tonight
- Dory.- You on a diet
Dory!What did the mask say?
P. Sherman,42 Wallaby Way, Sydney.
[Gasps]I remembered what it said!
I usually forget things,but I remembered it!
Whoa, whoa, wait.Where is that?
I don't know.But who cares? I remembered.
- Raar!- Aah!
DORY: P. Sherman,42 Wallaby Way, Sydney.
I remembered it again!
[Ship's horn blows]
[Buoy rings]
JACQUES: Psst. Nemo.
NEMO: Mmm...
Nemo
- Huh?- Suivez-moi.
Follow me.
[Dramatic music playing]
[Fish chanting]
FISH:Ha hwa ha
Ha hwa ha
Ha hwa ha ho ho ho
Ha hwa ho ha
Hahoo wahoo yahoo ho
Hahoo ho ho wahoo ha hee
Ha ho wahee ha ho ho ho
Hoo!
[Music stops]
State your name.
Nemo.
Brother Bloat, proceed.
Nemo, newcomerof orange and white...
you have been called forth...
to the summit ofMount Wannahockaloogie...
to join with us inthe fraternal bonds of tankhood.
- Huh?- We want you in our club, kid.
- Really?- Lf...
you are able to swim through...
[Echoes]The Ring of Fire!
Turn on the Ring of Fire!
You said you could do it.
The Ring of Fire!
[Chanting]
Bubbles, let me... Oh!
Ha hwa ha ho ho ho
Isn't there another way?He's just a boy!
[Wailing]
[Chanting gets fasterand louder]
[Thump]
[Chanting stops]
From this moment on,you will be known as Sharkbait.
Sharkbait, oo-ha-ha!
Welcome,Brother Sharkbait.
- Enough with the Sharkbait.- Sharkbait!
Ooh... ba-ba-do.
Sharkbait'sone of us now, agreed?
- Agreed.- We can't send him to his death.
Darla's coming in five days.
So, what are we going to do?
I'll tell youwhat we're gonna do...
we're gonna get himout of here.
- We'll help him escape.- Escape? Really?
We're all gonna escape.
Gill, please.Not another escape plan.
Sorry,but they just never work.
Why should thisbe any different?
- Because we've got him.- Me?
- You see that fiIter?- Yeah.
You're the only one who can getin and out of that thing.
We need you to takea pebble inside there...
and jam the gears.
You do that,and this tank's gonna get...
filthier and filthierby the minute.
Pretty soon, the dentist'llhave to clean the tank...
and when he does, he'll take usout of the tank...
put us inindividual baggies...
then we'll roll ourselvesdown the counter...
out the window,off the awning...
into the bushes,across the street...
and into the harbor!
It's foolproof.Who's with me?
- Aye!- Aye!
I think you're nuts.
[Sighs]
No offense, kid,but you're not the best swimmer.
He's fine. He can do this.
So, Sharkbait,what do you think?
Let's do it.
DORY: I'm going to P. Sherman,42 Wallaby Way, Sydney.
Where are you going?
I'm going to P. Sherman,42 Wallaby Way, Sydney.
If you askwhere I'm going...
I'll tell youthat's where I'm going.
It's P. Sherman,42 Wallaby Way, Sydney.
Where? I'm sorry,I didn't hear you.
P. Sherman,42 Wallaby Way, Sydney.
MARLIN: Excuse me.
Hi.Do you know how to get...
Hello? Whoa. Wait.Can you tell me...
Hey! Hold it!I'm trying to talk to you!
Fellas, come back here.One quick question.
I need to...And they're gone again.
DORY: P. Sherman,42 Wallaby Way, Sydney.
Why do I have to tell youover and over again?
I'll tell you again.I don't get tired of it...
- OK, all right.- Huh?
- Here's the thing.- Uh-huh.
I think it's bestif I carry on from here by...
by myself.
OK.
- You know, alone.- Uh-huh.
Without... without...I mean, not without you.
But I don'twant you... with me.
- Huh?- Am I...
I don't want to hurtyour feelings.
- You want me to leave?- I mean, not... Yes.
I just can't affordany more delays...
and you're one of those fishthat cause delays.
Sometimes it's a good thing.
There's a whole group of fish.They're delay fish.
You mean... [Whimpers]
You mean you don't like me?
No, of course I like you.
It's because I like youI don't want to be with you.
It's a complicated emotion.
- Ohh!- Don't cry. I like you.
Hey, you!Lady, is this guy bothering you?
Um... I don't remember.Were you?
No, no, no, no, no.We're just...
Do you guys knowhow I can get to...
Look, pal, we're talkingto the lady, not you.
Hey, hey.You like impressions?
[Sniffles] Mm-hmm.
Just like in rehearsals,gentlemen.
So what are we?Take a guess.
DORY: Oh, oh.I've seen one of those.
I'm a fish with a noselike a sword.
- Wait, wait, um...- It's a swordfish!
LEADER: Hey, clown boy,let the lady guess.
Where's the butter?
Ooh! It's onthe tip of my tongue!
- [Coughs] Lobster.- Saw that!
Lots of legs!Live in the ocean.
- Clam!- Close enough!
Oh, it's a whaleof a tale
I'll tell you, lad...
They're good.
Will somebody pleasegive me directions?!
"Will somebody pleasegive me directions?!"
- Ha ha ha ha ha!- I'm serious!
"Blah blah blah,me, me, blah!
"Blah blah blah,me, me, me!"
Thank you.
Oh, dear. Hey!Hey, come back!
- Hey, what's the matter?- What's the matter?
While they're doing theirsiIly little impressions...
I am miles from home with a fishthat can't remember her name!
I bet that's frustrating.
Meanwhile,my son is out there.
- Your son Chico?- Nemo?
But it doesn't matterbecause no fish...
in this entire oceanis going to help me.
Well, I'm helping you.
Wait right here.
- Guys!- Is he bothering you again?
No, no. He's a good guy.
Go easy on him.He's lost his son Fabio.
Any of you heard of P. Sherman,42 Wallaby Way, Sydney?
Sydney? Oh, sure![Choir sings]
Ted here's got relativesin Sydney.
- Don't you, Ted?- Sure do!
Oh! Hey!They know Sydney!
[Gasps]
You wouldn't know howto get there, would you?
You want to follow the E.A.C.
That's the EastAustralian Current.
Big current.Can't miss it.
It's in... that direction.
And then you follow thatfor about...
I don't know.What do you guys think?
About three leagues?
That little baby will put youright past Sydney.
- Ta-da!- That's great!
Dory, you did it!
Oh, please,I'm just your little helper.
- Helping along. That's me.- Fellas, thank you.
LEADER: Don't mention it!Just loosen up, OK, buddy?
DORY: Oh, you guys.You really nailed him. Bye.
LEADER: Oh, hey, ma'am.One more thing.
When you come to this trench,swim through it, not over it.
DORY: Trench...through it, not over it.
I'll remember. Hey, hey!
Hey, wait up, partner!Hold on!
Wait, wait, wait!I gotta tell you something.
Whoa.
DORY: Nice trench.
DORY: Hello![Echoing]
- OK, let's go.- No, no. Bad trench.
Come on, we'll swim overthis thing.
Whoa, partner.Little red flag going up.
Something's telling meto swim through it, not over it.
Are you looking at this thing?
It's got deathwritten all over it.
I really, really, reallythink we should swim through.
And I'm really, really donetalking about this. Over we go.
- Trust me on this.- Trust you?
Yes, trust.It's what friends do.
Look! Something shiny!
- Where?- It just swam over the trench.
- Come on, we'll follow it!- OK!
Boy, it sure is clear up here.
Exactly. And look at that...there's the current.
We should be there in no time.
Hey, little guy.
You wanted to gothrough the trench.
I shall call him Squishy,and he shall be mine.
And he shall be my Squishy.Come here, Squishy.
Come here, little Squishy.
[Baby talk]
[Zap] Ow!
- That's a jellyfish!- Bad Squishy!
Shoo, shoo! Get away!
- Let me see that.- Don't touch it.
I won't touch it.I just want to look.
Hey! How comeit didn't sting you?
It did.It's just that...
- Ow! Ow! Ow!- Hold still.
I live in this anemone...
and I'm usedto these kind of stings.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
It doesn't look bad.You'll be fine.
But now we know, don't we...
that we don't wantto touch these again.
Let's be thankful this timeit was just a little one.
- Aah!- Aah!
Don't move.
- This is bad, Dory.- Hey, watch this!
Boing! Boing!
[Gasps] Dory!
You can't catch me
Don't bounce on the tops!
They will... not sting you!
- The tops don't sting you!- Two in a row! Beat that!
Dory, listen to me.I have an idea... a game.
- A game?- Yes.
- I love games! Pick me!- Here's the game.
Whoever can hop the fastestout of these jellyfish wins!
- OK.- Rules, rules, rules!
You can't touch the tentacles.Only the tops.
Something about tentacles.Got it. Go!
Wait! Not something about 'em,it's all about 'em!
- Whee!- Wait, Dory!
Gotta go fasterif you want to win!
Whoa! Dory!
Boing, boing, boing!
Wait a minute! Whoa! Dory!
Whee!
We're cheating death now.That's what we're doing.
But we're having funat the same time.
I can do this.Just be careful.
Yeah, careful I don'tmake you cry when I win!
I don't think so!
Ha ha ha ha!
Whoa!
Give it up, old man.
You can't fight evolution.I was buiIt for speed.
The question is, Dory,are you hungry?
- Hungry?- Yeah.
'Cause you're aboutto eat my bubbles!
Duck to the left!Right there!
The clownfish is the winner!
Whoo-hoo! We did it!Look at us!
Dory?
Oh, no.
Dory! Dory!
Dory!
[Gasps] Dory!
[Electricity surging]Ohh!
[Screams]
DORY: Am I disqualified?
MARLIN: No, you're doing fine!You're actually winning!
But you gotta stay awake.Where does P. Sherman live?
DORY: P. Sherman...Wallaby Way, Sydney...
MARLIN: That's it!
[Electrical shock]Uhh!
- Wallaby Way...- Uhh! Stay awake!
Stay awake!Ooh! Stay awake!
Stay... awake!
- Awake.- P. Sherman.
- Awake.- 42 Wallaby Way.
Wake up. Nemo...
You miss your dad,don't you, Sharkbait?
Yeah.
You're lucky to have someoneout there looking for you.
He's not looking for me.
He's scared of the ocean.
Peach, any movement?
He's had four cups of coffee.It's gotta be soon.
Keep on him.
My first escape...landed on dental tools.
I was aiming for the toilet.
Toilet?
All drainslead to the ocean, kid.
Wow. How many times haveyou tried to get out?
Ah, I've lost count.
Fish aren't meantto be in a box, kid.
It does things to you.
[Laughing]Bubbles! Bubbles!
Potty break! He grabbedthe "Reader's Digest."
- We have 4.2 minutes!- That's your cue, Sharkbait.
- You can do it, kid.- We gotta be quick.
Once you get in, swim tothe bottom of the chamber...
and I'll talk youthrough the rest.
- OK.- It'll be a piece of kelp.
[Inhales deeply]
[Grunting]
Nicely done!
- Can you hear me?- Yeah!
Here comes the pebble.
Ptoo.
[Splish]
Now, do you seea small opening?
Uh-huh!
Inside it,you'll see a rotating fan.
Wedge that pebble into the fanto stop it turning.
[Whirring]
[Buzz] Aah!
- Careful, Sharkbait!- I can't do it!
Gill, this isn't a good idea.
He'll be fine. Try again!
OK.
GILL: That's it, Sharkbait.
Nice and steady.
I got it! I got it!
- He did it!- That's great, kid!
Now swim up the tubeand out.
[Grunts]
[Clunk]
[Grunting]
[Creaking]
[Water rushing]
Oh, no! Gill!
- Sharkbait!- Oh, my gosh!
Get him outta there!
- What do we do?- Oh, no!
Stay calm, kid.Just don't panic!
Help me!
Sharkbait, grab hold of this!
[Buzz]
- No! No! No!- Feed me more!
- That's it!- Sharkbait! Grab it!
[Grunting] I got it!
Pull!
[Panting]
PEACH: Gill, don't make himgo back in there.
No. We're done.
[Whimpering]
CRUSH: Dude.
- Uhh.- Dude.
Focus, dude. Dude.
Ohh.
Oh, he lives.Hey, dude!
MARLIN:Ohh. What happened?
Saw the whole thing, dude.
First, you were all,like, "Whoa!"...
and then we wereall, like, "Whoa!"...
and then you were,like, "Whoa."
MARLIN:What are you talking about?
You, mini-man.Takin' on the jellies.
You got seriousthrill issues, dude.
- Ohh.- Awesome.
Uhh. Oh, my stomach. Ohh!
Oh, man. No hurlin'on the shell, dude, OK?
Just waxed it.
So, Mr. Turtle...
Whoa, dude.Mr. Turtle is my father.
The name's Crush.
Crush? Really?
OK, Crush. I need tothe East Australian Current.
E.A.C.?
[Laughs] Oh, dude.
You're ridin' it, dude!
Check it out!
[Dramatic music playing]
OK, grab shell, dude!
Grab wh-a-a-at?!
[Screaming]
Ha ha! Righteous!Righteous!
- Yeah!- Stop!
So... [Sighs]
What brings you on this fine dayto the E.A.C.?
Dory and I needto get to Sydney.
[Gasps] Dory!Is she all right?
Huh? Oh, little blue.
She is sub-level, dude.
Dory! Dory! Dory!
[Whispers] Dory.
[Muttering]
I'm so sorry.
This is all my fault.It's my fault.
Twenty-nine, thirty!Ready or not, here I come!
[Gasps] There you are!
[Giggling]
Catch me if you can![Laughing]
Dory?
KID: Nice wave!
Oh, wow!
Heh heh.
Up you go!
Whoo-hoo! Whoo-hoo!
Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa-oh-oh-oh!
[Sploosh]
- Oh, my goodness!- Kill the motor, dude.
Let us see what Squirt doesflying solo.
[Splash] Whoa!
Whoa! That was so cool!
Hey, Dad,did you see that?
Did you see me?Did you see what I did?
You so totally rock, Squirt!
So give me some fin.
Noggin. [Clunk]
- Dude.- Dude.
Oh... intro.
Jellyman, offspring.
Offspring, Jellyman.
- Jellies?! Sweet.- Totally.
Apparently, I must've donesomething you liked... dudes.
- You rock, dude!- Ow.
Curl away, my son.It's awesome, Jellyman.
The little dudesare just eggs.
We leave 'emon a beach to hatch...
and then, coo-coo-cachoo...
they find their way backto the big ol' blue.
- All by themselves?- Yeah.
But, dude, how do you knowwhen they're ready?
Well, you never really know.
But when they know,you'll know, you know? Ha.
[Laughter]
Hey, look, everybody.
I know that dude!It's the Jellyman!
DORY: Go on. Jump on him!
- Turtle pile!- Wait, wait, wait!
- Are you funny?- Where's your shell?
- I need to breathe!- Are you running away?
Did you really crossthe jellyfish forest?
- Did they sting you?- One at a time!
Mr. Fish, did you die?
DORY: Sorry, I wasa little vague on the detaiIs.
So, where are you going?
You see, my son was taken.
My son was taken away from me.
- No way.- What happened?
No, no, kids.I don't want to talk about it.
ALL: Aww! Please?
Please?
[Sighs] Well, OK.
I live on this reefa long, long way from here.
This is gonna be good.I can tell.
And my son Nemo...
See, he was mad at me.
And maybe he wouldn'thave done it...
if I hadn't beenso tough on him.
I don't know.
Anyway, he swam out inthe open water to this boat...
and when he was out there,these divers appeared...
and I tried to stop them,but the boat was too fast.
So, we swam out in the oceanto follow them...
They couldn't stop 'em.And then Nemo's dad...
he swims out to the ocean,and they bump into...
...three ferocious sharks.
He scares away the sharksby blowing 'em up!
Golly, that's amazing.
And then divesthousands of feet...
...straight downinto the dark.
It's wicked dark down there.
You can't see a thing.How's it going, Bob?
And the only thingthey can see down there...
...is the light fromthis big, horrible creature...
with razor-sharp teeth.Nice parry, old man.
And then he hasto blast his way...
So, these two little fishhave been...
searching the ocean for dayson the East Australian Current.
Which means that he may beon his way here right now.
That should put himin Sydney Harbor...
...in a matter of days.I mean, it sounds like...
this guy is gonnastop at nothing...
...till he finds his son.I sure hope he makes it.
That's one dedicated father,if you ask me.
GULLS: Mine! Mine!Mine! Mine! Mine!
Mine! Mine! Mine!Mine! Mine! Mine!
Would you just shut up?!
You're rats with wings!
Bloke's been lookingfor his boy Nemo.
- Nemo?!- He was taken off the reef...
- Take it! You happy?- Mine! Mine! Mine!
Hey, say that again!Something about Nemo.
Mine! Mine! Mine!
Whoooa...
Hyah!
Mine?
Last I heard, he's headingtowards the harbor.
Ho ho! BriIliant!
[Music swells]
[Sighs]
Is he doing OK?
Whatever you do,Don't mention D-a-r...
It's OK. I know whoyou're talking about.
[Smack]
[Bubbling]
Gill?
Hey, Sharkbait.
I'm sorry I couldn't stop the...
No, I'm the onewho should be sorry.
I was so readyto get out...
so ready to taste that ocean...
I was willing to put youin harm's way to get there.
Nothing should be worth that.
I'm sorry I couldn't get youback to your father, kid.
[Panting]
All right.Hey, hey, hey...
- What the...- Aaah!
That's one way to pull a tooth.[Chuckles]
Huh. Darn kids.
Good thing I pulled theright one, eh, Prime Minister?
NIGEL: Hey, psst!
PEACH: Oh, Nigel!You just missed an extraction.
Has he loosenedthe periodontal ligament yet?
What am I talking about?Where's Nemo?
- I've got to speak with him.- What is it?
Your dad's been fightingthe entire ocean...
- Iooking for you.- My father? Really?
He's traveled hundreds of miles,battling sharks and jellyfish...
Sharks? That can't be him.
What was his name?Some sort of sport fish.
- Tuna? Trout?- Marlin?
Marlin! The little clownfishfrom the reef.
It's my dad!He took on a shark!
I heard he took on three.
- Three sharks?- That's 4,800 teeth!
After you were takenby Diver Dan over there...
your dad followed the boatlike a maniac.
Really?
He's swimming,giving it all he's got...
and then three giganticsharks capture him...
and he blows them upand dives thousands of feet...
and gets chased by a monsterwith huge teeth!
He ties this demon to a rock,and what's his reward?
He gets to battlean entire jellyfish forest!
Now he's with a bunch ofsea turtles on the E.A. C...
and the word is he's headedthis way right now... to Sydney!
- Wow!- What a good daddy!
He was looking for youafter all, Sharkbait.
[Gasps]
[Clatters]
GURGLE:He's swimming to the filter!
- Sharkbait!- Not again!
[Spits]
Sharkbait!
No!
You got your whole lifeahead of you!
- We'll help you, kid!- Get him out!
[Whirring]
Get him out of there!
Come on, kid!Grab the end!
[Clank] Sharkbait!
- No!- Can you hear me?
Nemo! Can you hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you.
Sharkbait, you did it!
Sharkbait, you're...covered with germs! Aah!
Ha ha!That took guts, kid.
All right, gang,we have less than 48 hours...
before Darla gets here.
This tank'll getplenty dirty in that time...
but we have to help it alongany way we can.
- Jacques? No cleaning.- I shall resist.
Everybody else,be as gross as possible.
Think dirty thoughts.
We're gonna makethis tank so filthy...
the dentistwill have to clean it.
- Good work!- Ha ha ha!
All right, we're here, dudes!
Get ready!Your exit's coming up, man!
MARLIN:Where? I don't see it!
DORY: Right there!I see it! I see it!
MARLIN:The swirling vortex of terror?
- That's it, dude.- Of course it is.
OK, first,find your exit buddy.
Do you have your exit buddy?
Yes!
Squirt give you a rundownof proper exiting technique.
Good afternoon!We'll have a great jump today!
OK, crank a hard cutbackas you hit the wall.
There's a screaming bottom turn,so watch out!
Remember...rip it, roll it, and punch it!
He's trying to speak to me,I know it!
You're really cute, but I don'tknow what you're saying!
Say the first thing again.
OK, Jellyman! Go, go, go!
[Screaming]
- Whoa!- Wahoo!
- Whoa!- Whoa!
[Laughing]
Whoo!
That was... fun!
I actually enjoyed that.
Hey, look, turtles!
CRUSH: Ha ha!Most excellent!
Now turn yourfishy taiIs around...
and swim straight onthrough to Sydney!
No worries, man!
No worries!Thank you, dude Crush!
- Bye!- Bye, Jellyman!
You tell your little dudeI said hi, OK?
SQUIRT:See ya later, dudes!
DORY: Bye, everyone!
Nemo would have loved this.
Ooh! Hey! Crush, I forgot!
How old are you?
CRUSH: 150, dude!And still young! Rock on!
150! 150!I gotta remember that.
Whoa.
- We going in there?- Yep.
P. Sherman,42 Wallaby Way, Sydney?
Yep. We're gonnajust swim straight.
Just keep swimming,just keep swimming
Dory...
[Dory humming]
MARLIN:Boy, this is taking awhile.
DORY:How about we play a game?
MARLIN: OK.
DORY: OK, I'm thinkingof something orange...
and it's small...
- It's me.- Right!
It's orange and small...
It's me.
All righty,Mr. Smartypants.
And it's orange and smalland white stripes...
Me. And the next one,just a guess, me.
- That's just scary.- Wait, wait, wait.
I have definitely seenthis floating speck before.
That meanswe've passed it before...
and that meanswe're going in circles...
and that meanswe're not going straight!
- Hey, hey!- Get to the surface.
We'll figure it outup there. Let's go!
- Hey! Relax.- What?
Take a deep breath.[Inhales]
[Exhaling]
Now, let's ask somebodyfor directions.
Fine. Who do youwant to ask, the speck?
- There's nobody here!- There has to be someone.
It's the ocean, siIly.We're not the only two in here.
Let's see.OK, no one there.
Nope. Nada.
[Gasps]
There's somebody.Hey! Excuse...
Dory, Dory, Dory!Now it's my turn.
I'm thinking of somethingdark and mysterious.
It's a fish we don't know.If we ask it directions...
it could ingest usand spit out our bones!
What is it with menand asking for directions?
I don't want to playthe gender card right now.
Let's playthe "Let's Not Die" card.
- You want to get out of here?- Of course I do.
How are we gonna do thatunless we give it a shot?
Dory, you don'tfully understand...
Come on. Trust me on this.
[Sighs]
[Sighs] All right.
Excuse me! Whoo-hoo!Little fella?
Hello!Don't be rude. Say hi.
Ha. Hello.
- His son Bingo...- Nemo.
- Nemo was taken to...- Sydney.
Sydney! And it'sreally, really important...
that we get thereas fast as we can...
so can you help us out?
Come on, little fella.Come on.
Dory, I'm a little fella.
I don't thinkthat's a little fella.
DORY: Oh! Big fella.Whale. OK.
Maybe he only speaks whale.
Mooo! Weee neeed...
- Dory?- Tooo fiind his son.
What are you doing?Are you sure you speak whale?
Can youuuu give usdiiirectionsss?
Dory! Heaven knowswhat you're saying!
- See, he's swimming away.- Cooome baaack.
He's not coming back.You offended him.
- Maybe a different dialect.
- Moooohhhmmooo...- Dory!
This is not whale.You're speaking upset stomach.
- Maybe I should try humpback.- Don't.
Wooooooo...
- You actually sound sick.- Maybe louder?
- Rah! Rah!- Don't do that!
Too much orca.Didn't it sound orca-ish?
It doesn't sound orca.
It sounds like nothingI've ever heard.
- Oooooo!- Ohh!
It's just as well.He might be hungry.
Whales don't eat clownfish.They eat krill.
- KRILL: Swim away!- Oh, look, krill!
[Gasps]Move, Dory, move!
- Aah!- Aah!
Look at that.Would you look at that?
FiIthy. Absolutely fiIthy.
All thanks to you, kid.You made it possible.
Jacques,I said no cleaning.
I am ashamed.
Look! Scum angel!
[Whimpering]
Ooh! Aaah!
Bubbles!I love the bubbles!
[Coughing]
Flo? Has anybody seen Flo?
9:00 and cue dentist.
Hello, Barbara.Sorry I'm late.
OK, here we go.Here we go, OK.
Little Davey Reynolds...
PEACH: Walks to the counter,drops the keys...
Bloat, that's disgusting!
Tastes pretty good to me.
- Urrrp!- Eww!
Don't you people realizewe are swimming in our own...
Shh! Here he comes!
NEMO: Aah!
Crikey. What a state.
[Squeaks]
Ohh. Barbara, what's my earliestappointment tomorrow?
- 10:00, luv.- Leave it open, would you?
I've gotta clean the fish tankbefore Darla gets here.
Did you hear that, Sharkbait?
NEMO: Yay!He's gonna clean the tank!
We're gonna be clean!
You ready to see your dad, kid?
- Uh-huh.- Of course you are.
I wouldn't be surprisedif he's out there...
in the harborwaiting for you right now.
Yeah.
[Marlin yelling]
[Water sloshing]
[Panting]
Aaah!
Oof! [Pants]
[Dory laughing]
[Grunting]
Whoo!
Yaahhh!
DORY: Here comes the big one.
Ooh! Come on!You gotta try this!
- Will you just stop it?- Why? What's wrong?
We're in a whale,don't you get it?
- Whale?- A whale!
You had to ask for help!And now we're stuck here!
Wow, a whale.I speak whale.
No, you're insane!You can't speak whale!
I have to get out!I have to find my son!
I have to tell himhow old sea turtles are!
[Sobs]
Ohhh!
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Hey...
you OK?
[Sighs]
There, there.It's all right.
It'll be OK.
No. No, it won't.
Sure it will. You'll see.
No. I promised him I'd neverlet anything happen to him.
Huh. That's a funny thingto promise.
What?
You can't never letanything happen to him.
Then nothingwould ever happen to him.
Not much fun for little Harpo.
[Sighs]
[Creaking]
- Hmm.- What's going on?
Don't know. I'll ask him.
[Making whale sounds]
- Dory...- Whaaat's goooing onnn?
[Whale groans]
I think he says we've stopped.
Of course we've stopped.Stop trying to speak whale.
You'll make things worse.What is that noise?
[Rumbling]
Oh, no. Look what you did.
The water's going down.It's going down!
[SIoshing]
Really? You sure about that?
Look!Already it's half empty!
I'd say it's half full.
Stop that! It's half empty!
[Whale groans]
OK, that onewas a little tougher.
He either said we should goto the back of the throat...
or he wants a root beer float.
Of course he wants usto go there!
That's eating us!
How do I taste, Moby?Do I taste good?
Tell him I'm not interestedin being lunch!
- OK. Heee...- Stop talking to him!
- Aah!- Aah!
What is going on?
I'll check. Whaaat...
No more whale!You can't speak whale!
- Yes, I can!- No, you can't!
You think you can do thesethings, but you can't, Nemo!
[Whale groans]
- OK.- Dory! Oof!
He says it's time to let go.
Everything's gonna beall right.
How do you know?
How do you know something badisn't gonna happen?
I don't!
[Gurgling]
[Whale groans]
[Splash]
- Aah!- Aah!
Ha ha ha!We're alive!
Look! Sy-d-ney... Sydney!
Sydney! Sydney again!
[Tenor sings]
You were right, Dory!We made it!
We're gonna find my son!
[Splashing]
Thaaank yoouuu, sirrr!
Wow. I wishI could speak whale.
All we gotta do is findthe boat that took him.
- Right!- We can do this!
[Birds chirping]
[Yawns] Morning.
It's morning, everyone!Today's the day!
The sun is shining,the tank is clean...
and we are getting out...The tank is clean.
The tank is clean!
DEB: But how?
Boss must've installed itwhile we were sleeping.
- What are we gonna do?- What's it say, Peach?
[Muffled]
I can't hear you, Peach.
The Aquascum 2003 isan all-purpose, self-cleaning...
maintenance-free,salt water purifier...
that is guaranteed to extendthe life of your aquarium fish.
Stop it!
The Aquascumis programmed to scan...
your tank environmentevery five minutes?!
Scan? What does that mean?
[Zap]
Aah!
AQUASCUM:Temperature... 82 degrees...
PH balance... normal.
- Ooh.- Nice.
Ooh... Oh!Curse you, Aquascum!
That's it for the escape plan.It's ruined.
Then what arewe gonna do about...
ALL: [Gasp] Darla!
Stay down, kid!
- False alarm.- Whew.
My nerves can't takemuch more of this.
BLOAT: What'll we dowhen that brat gets here?
- I'm thinking.- Oh! Gill!
- Nemo! I'm coming!- Help me! Help me!
Swim down! Come on, kid!
- Everybody jump in!- Swim down!
- That's it!- What the...?
- Yay!- Ha ha! Good work!
Gill!
- Nemo!- Sharkbait!
- Roll, kid!- Lean! Lean!
[Grunting]
DENTIST: Whoops.That would've been a nasty fall.
Gill!Don't let me go belly-up!
Just calm down, Nemo.You won't go belly-up.
I promise.You're gonna be OK.
[Crash]
["Psycho" theme plays]
ALL: [Gasp] Darla!
[Birds cawing]
Do any of these boatslook familiar to you?
No, but the boathas to be here somewhere.
Come on, Dory.We're gonna find it.
I'm totally excited.Are you excited?
Dory, wake up.Wake up, come on.
Duck!
That's not a duck.It's a... pelican!
- Whoa!- Aah!
[Splash]
[Gulp]
- Whoa!- Aah!
No! I didn't come this farto be breakfast!
[Gagging]
Hey, Nigel.Would you look at that?
What? What?
Sun's barely up and Gerald'shad more than he can handle.
Yeah. Reckon somebodyought to help the poor guy.
ALL: Yeah, right. Yeah.
Don't everybodyfly off at once.
[Gagging]
All right, Gerald.Fish got your tongue?
- Aah!- Love a duck!
I gotta find my son Nemo!
Nemo? He's that fish!
The one that's been fightingthe whole ocean!
I know where your son... Huh?
[Gasping]
Wait! Come back! Stop!
Dory, keep going!He's crazy!
I got something to tell you!
[Splat]
Mine.
Don't make any sudden moves.
Hop inside my mouthif you want to live.
Hop in your mouth?How does that make me live?
GULL: Mine?
NIGEL: BecauseI can take you to your son.
- Yeah, right.- No. I know your son.
He's orange witha gimpy fin on one side.
- That's Nemo!- Aah!
Mine! Mine! Mine! Mine!
DORY: Aah!
Fasten your seat belts!
Mine! Mine! Mine! Mine! Mine!
Mine! Mine! Mine! Mine!
DORY: Whoo! Whoo-hoo!
Ha ha ha ha!
MARLIN: Aah!
Everybody hold on!
- Aah!- Aah!
Mine!Mine! Mine! Mine! Mine!
[Clanging]
BUBBLES: Too loud!Too loud for me!
Twinkle, twinkle,little star
Find a happy place!Find a happy place!
Darla, your unclewill see you now.
["Psycho" theme plays]
All right, let's seethose pearly whites.
Raah! I'm a piranha.They're in the Amazon.
And a piranha's a fish,just like your present.
[Giggling]
DARLA:I get fishy, fishy
Oh, no.Poor little guy.
- He's dead.- Sharkbait!
Yay! Fishy, fishy, fishy!
Must've left your presentin the car, sweetie.
- Ohh!- I'll go and get it.
- He's still alive!- He's not dead!
What's happening?Why is he playing dead?
GILL: He's gonna get flusheddown the toilet.
- He's gonna get out of here!- He's gonna get flushed!
GURGLE:What a smart little guy!
GILL: Oh, no!Not the trash can!
Nemo! No!
- Hey! I found his dad!- Where's Nemo?
- Dentist!- He's over there!
What's a dentist?Nigel, get in there!
- I can't go in there!- Yes, you can! Charge!
[Squawks]
- Aah!- What the...?
Darla, sweetie, look out!
[Clang]
[Drill whirring]
- Aah!- Hold still!
- Aah!- Easy! Easy!
[Drill whining]
- Aah!- Hold still!
Nobody's going to hurt you!Oof!
[Gasps]
[Heartbeat echoing]
Nemo.
Oh, my goodness.
Gotcha! Keep down!
MARLIN: Nemo!
Daddy?
Out with you!And stay out!
Daddy? [Gasps]
Fishy?
Fishy! Wake up!
DEB: Oh, no!
GILL: To the top ofMount Wannahockaloogie!
Why are you sleeping?
- Hurry!- Bloat!
[Grunting]
Ring of Fire![Squeaking]
Fishy! Aah!
[Clank]
Crikey! All the animalshave gone mad!
Unh!
DARLA: Aaah! Get it out!
- Smack her in the head!- Go, Gill, go!
Fish in my hair!
Gill!
Sharkbait...tell your dad I said hi.
- Unh!- Eww!
[Yelling]
Go get 'em!
DENTIST: Ohh... [Gasps]
- He did it!- Yay!
- I'm so happy!- Is he gonna be OK, Gill?
Don't worry.All drains lead to the ocean.
Fishy!
Aah!
Aah! Whoa! Whoa!
Daddy!
[Whimpering]
[Skittering]
[Buoy ringing]
I'm so sorry.
Truly, I am.
[Flies away]
- Hey.- Dory...
if it wasn't for you...
I never would've evenmade it here.
So, thank you.
Hey, wait a minute.
Wait. Where are you going?
It's over, Dory.We were too late.
Nemo's gone,and I'm going home now.
No. No, you can't.
Stop!
Please don't go away.
Please?
No one's ever stuck with mefor so long before.
And if you leave, I just...
I remember thingsbetter with you.
I do. Look...P. Sherman, 42...
[Sighs] 42...
I remember it.I do. It's there.
I know it is becausewhen I look at you...
I can feel it.
I look at youand I... I'm home.
Please...
I don't want that to go away.
I don't want to forget.
I'm sorry, Dory, but I do.
[Dramatic music playing]
[Grunting]
- Manna from heaven.- Sweet nectar of life!
BOTH: Hey! Hey! Hey!
- This is our spot!- Get outta here!
[Grunting]
BOTH: Hey! Hey! Hey!
Yeah, that's it, fella.
Just keep on swimmin'.You got that.
Too right, mate!
Oh! I got a live one here!
Have you seen my dad?
Gotcha! Hey! Hey!Come back here!
You let him go!
BOTH: Hey! Hey!
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
[Moaning]
Ohh!
NEMO: Um, excuse me.
Are you all right?
I don't know where I am.I don't know what's going on.
I think I lost somebody,but I can't remember.
NEMO: It's OK.I'm looking for someone, too.
Hey, we can look together.
[Sniffles] I'm Dory.
I'm Nemo.
Nemo? That's a nice name.
[Gull squawks]
- Dad!- Dad!
Wait a minute.Is it your dad or my dad?
- My dad.- Got it. Dad!
- Where are we, anyway?- Dad! Dad!
Oh. Syl... Shi... Sydney.
[Gasps] P. Sherman,42 Wallaby Way, Sydney.
Aah! Nemo!
It's you! Aah!You're Nemo!
[Muffled]Yes, yes, I'm Nemo!
You're Nemo!You were dead. I saw you.
And here you are!I found you.
You're not dead.And your father... Your father!
You know my father?!Where is he?
This way!He went this way. Quick!
DORY: Hey, hey, hey!
BOTH: Hey! Hey!
Have you seenan orange fish swim by?
- It looks just like him!- But bigger!
Yeah, I saw him, bluey.
But I'm not tellin' youwhere he went...
and there's no wayyou're gonna make me.
GULL: Mine.
CRAB: Aah!All right! I'll talk!
He went tothe fishing grounds! Aah!
[Thump] Hey, look out!
I'm sorry.I'm just trying to get home.
NEMO, DISTANTLY: Dad! Dad!
Nemo?
- Daddy!- Nemo?
- Dad!- Nemo's alive!
Dory? Nemo!
Daddy!
Nemo! I'm coming, Nemo!
- Dad!- Nemo! Thank goodness.
It's all right, son.It's gonna be OK.
GROUPER: Turn around!You're going the wrong way!
[All shouting]
DORY: Aah! Look out!
MARLIN: Oh, my...
[Creaking]
[All screaming]
DORY: Help! He-e-elp!
- Dory!- Come on!
DORY: Help! Help!
Help! Get us out! Aah!
No, no, no! Dory!
- Dad, I know what to do!- Nemo! No!
We have to tell all the fishto swim down together!
- Get out of there now!- I know this will work!
No, I am notgonna lose you again!
There's no time!It's the only way to save Dory!
[Panting]
I can do this.
You're right.
I know you can.
- Lucky fin!- Now, go! Hurry!
Tell all the fish to swim down!
Well? You heard my son!Come on!
Dory, you haveto tell everybody to...
Swim down together!
Do you understandwhat I'm saying to you?
Swim down!
[Chain clacking]
Everybody swim down!
Come on,you have to swim down!
Down! Swim down!
MARLIN:Swim down! Swim down!
[Splashing]
[Gasping]
Don't give up!Keep swimming!
Just keep swimming!
[Creaking]
MARLIN: That's it!
[Gasping]
It's working!
ALL: Keep swimming!Keep swimming!
MARLIN: Just keep swimming!Keep swimming!
Come on, Dad!
- You're doing great, son!- That's my dad.
Let's get to the bottom!Keep swimming!
Just keep swimming,just keep swimming
Almost there!Keep swimming!
[Wood creaking]
ALL: Keep swimming!
Keep swimming!
[Snap]
[Thud]
[All cheering]
- Oof!- Hey!
- Dory! Where's Nemo?- There!
Oh, no. Nemo!
[Grunting]
[Moans]
Nemo?
It's OK. Daddy's here.Daddy's got you.
[Coughs]
Daddy?
Oh, thank goodness.
Dad... I don't hate you.
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm so sorry, Nemo.
- Hey, guess what?- What?
Sea turtles... I met one.
And he was 150 years old.
- 150?- Yep.
Sandy Plankton saidthey only live to be 100.
Sandy Plankton?
Do you think I wouldcross the entire ocean...
and not know as muchas Sandy Plankton?
- Ha ha ha!- He was 150! Not 100!
Who is this Sandy Planktonwho knows everything?
Time for school!Get up! Let's go!
- I'm gonna win!- No, you're not!
- I did it!- Aw, my own son beats me!
Climb aboard, explorers.
The sea cucumber looks overto the mollusk and says...
"With fronds like these,who needs anemones?"
[All laugh]
Hello, Nemo. Who's this?
- Exchange student.- I'm from the E.A.C., dude!
- Sweet!- Totally.
[Laughing]Seriously, Marty.
Did you really do allthe things you say you did?
BRUCE: Pardon me.
- Hello.- Ohh.
Don't be alarmed.
We wanted to make sure ournewest member got home safely.
- Thanks, guys.- See you next week.
- Keep up with the program.- Remember, fish are friends...
Not food! Bye!
MR. RAY:Hold on, here we go!
Next stop... knowledge!
Bye, son! Have fun!
NEMO: Bye, Dad!
Oh! Mr. Ray, wait.I forgot something.
[Panting]
Love you, Dad.
I love you, too, son.
Dad? You can let go now.
Sorry. Go have an adventure.
Good-bye!See ya later, dudes!
- Bye, Elmo!- Nemo.
- Bye, Nemo!- See you after school, Dory!
Bye, Dad!
Bye, son.
DENTIST: Barbara,I don't understand it.
Here this thing hasa lifetime guarantee...
and it breaks!
I had to clean the tank myself,take all the fish out...
put 'em in bags, and...
Where'd the fish go?
[Car horns honking]
- Come on, Peach!- Hurry!
- You can do it!- That's it.
Just a little further.
PEACH: That's the shortestred light I've ever seen!
- Come on, Peach!- Ohh. Aah!
[All cheer]
[Laughter]
[Laughter stops]
BLOAT: Now what?
[Music playing]
Somewhere
Beyond the sea
Somewhere,waitin' for me
My lover standson golden sands
And watches the ships
That go sailin'
Somewhere
Beyond the sea
She's therewatchin' for me
If I could flylike birds on high
Then straightto her arms
I'll go sailin'
It's far
Beyond the stars
It's near,beyond the moon
I know
Beyond a doubt
My heart
Will lead me there soon
We'll meet
Beyond the shore
We'll kissjust like before
Happy we'll bebeyond the sea
And never again
I'll go sailin'
I know
Beyond a doubt
My heart
Will lead me there soon
Oh, we'll meet,I know we'll meet
Beyond the shore
We'll kissjust as before
Happy we will bebeyond the sea
And never again
I'll go sailin'
No more sailin'
So long,sailin', sailin'
Good-bye, farewell,my friend
No more sailin'
So long
Sailin'
No more sailin'
No more
Farewell
Auf wiedersehen
Adieu to you and you
No more sailin'
No more
Ohh, no more sailin'
No more, no more
No more sailin'
No more
One more time
No more sailin'
[New music begins]
[Panting]
[Muttering]
[Growling]
[Chomp]
[Bubbles]
[Chiming]
[Tapping, spring rattling]
[Scrapes]
[Whirrs]
[Squeaking]