[Music]
so
wow
[Music]
hello hello
my name's tony
what's your name
name
my name's tony
what's your name
[Music]
my name's
gogo
[Music]
tony
hello
my name's gogo
what's your name
my name's jenny
[Music]
hello google
how are you
i'm fine thank you
[Music]
how are you tony
i'm fine thank you
how are you wow
wow
tony
jenny
[Music]
[Applause]
what's your name
my name's gogo what's your name
my name's tony how are you
i'm fine thank you how are you
i'm fine thank you what's your name
my name's jenny what's your name
my name's gogo
tony jennygogo
tony
jenny
goodbye goku goodbye go go
goodbye jenny
goodbye tony
[Music]
oh
my name's gogo
what's your name
[Music]
my name's
gogo
what's your name
[Music]
my name's
chibi
my name's chibi
[Music]
my name's cappy
what's your name
[Music]
your name's pod
hello my name's jenny
[Music]
hello
my name's tony
how are you
i'm fine thank you
wow
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
hello
my name's gogo
how are you
[Music]
hello
my name's gogo
what's your name
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
hello go go
hello goku
hello tony
hello jenny
how are you go go i'm fine thank you
[Music]
hello how are you
wow wow
oh go go
[Music]
his name's peter
peter
[Music]
her name's me
me
his name's peter
her name's may
[Music]
hello
what's his name
his name
is
his name's go go
[Music]
what's his name
his name's peter his name's peter
what's her name
her name's me
her name's jenny
what's his name
his name's tony his name's tony
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
what's his name
tony
his name's tony
what's her name
jenny
her name's jenny
what's his name
his name's peter
what's his name what's her name
what her name her name's mei
what's his name
his name's heart
his name's
[Music]
look out
hello go go hello tony
[Music]
she's my mother
he's my father
she's my sister
he's my brother
i'm your friend
hello goku
who's she
she's your sister
that's right goku i'm his sister
he's my brother
who's she
she's my mother
hello
who's he
he's my friend his name's gogo
hello gogo how are you
i'm fine thanks
how are you i'm fine thanks gogo
who's he
he's my father
hello dad
hello
go go
sorry
thank you go go
[Music]
who's she
she's my mother
who's he
he's my father
he's my brother
who's
she she's my sister
goodbye
go go
[Applause]
[Music]
who's hey
mother
father
brother
sister
who's she
she's my mother
she's your mother
yes that's right
who's he
he's your father
yes that's right
who's she
she's his sister
yes
she's my sister
who's he
um
he's my brother
who is he
who
is he
he's my father he's my brother i'm
your friend
who is she
who
is
she
she's my mother she's my sister
[Music]
oh wow
jenny
[Music]
hello jenny hello coco
look goku
[Music]
what's this
it's a box
open it please go go
[Music]
what's this
it's a plate
[Music]
what's this
it's a bowl
[Music]
this is a knife
this is a fork
[Music]
wow
goku
luke
a shark
[Music]
what's this
it's water go go jenny
[Music]
oh
hello go go
how are you
i'm fine thanks pod
[Music]
what's this
it's a bowl
[Music]
it's a
it's a bowl
what's this
it's a
it's a plate
[Music]
this is a fork
this is a knife
[Music]
knife
this is a knife
what's
this
it's a
[Music]
a knife
plate
this is a plate
what's
this
it's a plate
this is a plate
this is a knife
this
is a fork
[Music]
uh
look go go what's that
that's a panda
very good girl
[Music]
thank you go go this is a panda
that's a panda
what's that
that's a tiger
[Music]
this is a tiger
that's a tiger
yes it is
wow
[Music]
is that a tiger
no it isn't
it's a zebra
[Music]
this isn't a tiger
it's a zebra
that isn't a tiger
[Laughter]
what's that
that's a monkey
[Music]
is that a zebra
no it isn't
is it a tiger no it isn't
what is it
it's an elephant
my name's gogo
what's your name
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
this is an elephant
what's this
an elephant
very good it's an
elephant
[Music]
what's this
it's a panda
yes it is
cappy
is this a panda
no
it isn't a panda
it's a zebra
[Music]
what's this
it's a tiger
what's
that it's a monkey
[Music]
is
it's an elephant
[Music]
wow
hello tony hello jenny
hello go go hi coco
[Music]
what color is this
it's green
that's grass
this is grass it's
green what color is this tony
oh go go
it's red
this is a flower it's red
what color is this
[Music]
oh go go
it's blue
[Music]
this is yellow
wow
oh
that flower is blue
oops
that flower is red
that flower is yellow
[Music]
what color is this tony
it's brown
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you go go
[Music]
what color is this
it's red
it's yellow
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you go go
what color is that
it's green
[Applause]
what color is this gb
it's blue
[Music]
[Applause]
that's not blue
that's right tabby it isn't blue
it's brown
[Music]
[Applause]
what color is that
it's red
it's yellow it's yellow
what color is that
it's green it's green
red green yellow and blue
[Music]
hello tony
hello jenny
hello go go
[Music]
what are they
they're oranges
[Music]
thank you
thank you tony
[Music]
what are they
they're bananas
[Music]
are they apples
yes they are
[Music]
are they apples
no they aren't
they're pears
[Music]
these are
bananas these are oranges
[Music]
these are pears
what are they
they're bananas
they're oranges
what are they
they're pears
[Music]
are they bananas
yes they are
no they aren't
they're oranges
are they bananas
yes they are
no they aren't
they're pears
are they bananas
[Music]
yes they are
that's right they're bananas
[Music]
are they bananas
yes they are
no they aren't
they're pass
[Music]
that's a banana
they're bananas
[Music]
that's an
orange
[Music]
that's
an orange
they're oranges
[Music]
oranges
that's an apple
[Music]
that's an
apple
[Music]
they're
apples
they're apples
[Music]
yes they are
are they oranges
yes
[Music]
they are
yes they are
are they bananas yes they are
yes
[Music]
me
so
[Music]
happy birthday tony
thank you go go
one two
three four five
six
seven
eight
nine ten
one
two
three
four
five six
seven
eight
nine
ten
i'm ten
how old are you
i'm
five
how old are you jenny i'm nine
so
[Music]
one
two
one two three
one two three four
one two
three four
five six
[Music]
no go go that's my cake
i'm sorry tony
[Music]
one two three four five six seven
eight
nine ten
[Music]
one two three four five six seven eight
nine
ten
thank you go go
goodbye
one
[Music]
nine ten ten
four
[Music]
seven
nine
[Music]
three
eight eight
two
six
ten
five
one
[Music]
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten
[Music]
[Applause]
what are they
they're boats
boats
how many are there
one
two
three
there are three boats
[Music]
what are they
they're cars
cars
[Music]
how many are there
one
two
three
four
there are four cars
monkeys monkeys monkeys and bananas how
many are there
[Music]
monkeys monkeys monkeys and bananas how
many are there seven eight nine
what are they
they're birds
there are three birds
what are they they're planes
how many are there goku
one
two
three four
five oh
one
[Music]
there are 10 steps go go
very good taffy
how many are there chibi
how many are they
[Music]
there are six eggs
oh
[Music]
a car
one
car two cars
[Music]
how many are there
there are
four guys
very good
[Music]
a bird
one
bird
how many are there gb
there are
three
birds
that's right
there are three
birds
oh
[Music]
are they
birds no they aren't
they're planes
[Laughter]
[Music]
tony jenny hello
what's the time please
it's two o'clock
thank you
what's this
it's a watch
a watch
[Music]
what's that
it's a clock
what's the time gurgle
one
two
three
it's three o'clock
that's right it's three o'clock
[Music]
what's the time jenny
it's four o'clock
[Music]
[Applause]
what's the time
it's 11 o'clock
come down go go
[Music]
what's the time now
it's 12 o'clock
come down go go
one
two
three
four
five
six
seven
eight
nine
12.
[Music]
it's not 12 o'clock it's three o'clock
good
it's three o'clock
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
what's that
it's a clock
what's the time gb
[Music]
it's five o'clock
what's the time tapping
it's seven o'clock
what's the time pod
um
it's eleven o'clock
what's the time pod
um
[Music]
it's
it's 12 o'clock
very good part
[Music]
what's the time gp
it's 10 o'clock
what's the time pod
it's five o'clock
very good
[Music]
what's the time what's the time what's
the
time tabby it's three o'clock it's three
o'clock it's three a o'clock
what a time watch the time watch the
[Music]
it's 12 o'clock it's 12.
uh
[Music]
what's that
it's a supermarket
i like supermarkets
oh
i'm sorry
[Music]
tomatoes
they're tomatoes
i like tomatoes
[Laughter]
hmm
potatoes
they're potatoes
i like potatoes
thank you go go
what's this it's a carrot
i like carrots
what's that
it's an onion
i don't like onions
beans
[Music]
onions
i don't like onions
[Music]
tomatoes
potatoes
[Music]
carrots
beans
biscuits
i like biscuits
[Music]
carrots
i like carrots
tomatoes
[Music]
toes
potatoes
very good
they're potatoes
[Music]
i like potatoes
beans they're beans i like beans
[Music]
onions
i don't like onions
[Music]
[Laughter]
i don't like onions
[Music]
what do you like
i like carrots what do you like
i like carrots i like tomatoes i like
potatoes i
like
beans
[Music]
what's that
it's
do you like birds go go
yes i do
[Music]
wow
these are sausages gogo
do you like sausages
[Music]
yes i do i like sausages
what are these
those are donuts
do you like doughnuts
[Music]
yes i do
do you like donuts
i like sausages
and donuts
what are those go go
i don't know
those are sandwiches
[Music]
no thank you
oh
i don't like it
[Music]
shoes
hot dogs
do you like hot dogs go go
yes i do
do you like burgers
i like hot dogs
and burgers
[Music]
those
are donuts
what are those taffy
those are donuts
do you like donuts taffy
yes i do
this is a hot dog do you like hot dogs
chibi
yes
i do
i like hot dogs who
one hot dog
two
hot dogs
these are hot dogs
what are those these
are sandwiches
do you like sandwiches
gogo
no
i don't
what do you like
those
are sausages
[Music]
these
are burgers
i like sausages and burgers
do you like donuts do you like burgers
do you like sandwiches yes i do
do you like hot dogs do you like
sausages do you like burgers yes i do
[Music]
oh
go go
hi tony
[Music]
what
is it what
is
it
[Music]
what
is it what
is it what is it
hi
[Music]
what's your name
my name's tony
how are you tony
i'm fine thanks
how old are you tony
i'm 10.
what's your name
my name's goku
mom
look
who are they
we're tony and google
he's tony and he's dead
he's go go and he's five
[Applause]
[Music]
tony
what is it
it's an
elephant
that's right
it's an elephant
go go
is it
it's
it's a panda
that's right
[Applause]
tony
what is it
[Music]
what color is it
it's red
is it an apple
no
it isn't
go go
what is it
[Music]
it's a tomato
that's right
yes go go it's a tomato
tony one
go go to
[Applause]
[Music]
do you like cars go go
no i don't
do you like boots
no i don't what do you like
i like burgers
thank you
[Music]
thank you go go
is
it
is it an apple is it a pear
is it a monkey is this a bear
what
is it what
is
[Music]
have you got a ruler
yes i have i've got a ruler
have you got a rubber
yes i have i've got a rubber
have you got a pencil
yes i have i've got a pencil
[Music]
have you got a pen
yes i have i've got a pen
have you got a notebook
yes i have i got a notebook
[Music]
open the door please
come in tony
sit down please
[Music]
me
[Applause]
wow
what is it
i don't know
hello
my name's google
[Laughter]
oh go go
[Music]
very good sit on please girl
stand up please go go
have you got pen
[Music]
yes i have
i've got a pen
have you got a ruler
yes yes i have
have you got a notebook
[Music]
yes i have
i've got a notebook
stand up please tony
have you got a pen
[Music]
yes i have
oh i'm sorry
i haven't bought a pen
have you got a ruler
no
i haven't
i haven't got a ruler
have you got a notebook
no
i haven't
i haven't got a notebook
[Music]
go go
db what's this
it's a ruler that's right
have you got a ruler gb
yes i have
happy what's this
it's a pencil
have you got a pencil tapi
yes i have
pot
what's this
it's a rubber
have you got a rubber pod
yes i have
what's this
it's a notebook
it's a head
i've got a pen
and
a notebook
[Music]
[Applause]
yes
[Music]
[Applause]
jenny tidy your room please
[Music]
[Applause]
hello jenny
here you go
[Music]
let's read
ah
[Music]
[Applause]
let's paint
[Music]
jenny tidy your room please
[Applause]
[Music]
let's sing
jenny tidy your room please
[Music]
let's swim
jenny tidy your room please
[Music]
oh go
go i'm sorry jenny
[Music]
[Applause]
hmm
[Music]
very good jenny
let's eat
okay google let's eat
[Music]
hello
let's read
let's paint
let's sing
let's swim
let's eat
[Music]
[Applause]
let's read let's
let's read and read and read let's read
and read and read and read and read
let's
[Music]
paint and paint let's sing
eat
[Music]
can you see jenny
yes i can
can go go see
no he can't
yes i can
i can see
whose heat
his name's gogo
what can he do
he can dance
very good
can he sing
no he can't
i can
have you got a pencil yes i
can't sing
i can swim
watch
he can catch
he can climb
can he read
can you read go go
yes i can
i can read
hello cinderella
my name is prince charming
he called act
very good
he can fly
can you fly go go
yes i can
watch
[Applause]
he can fly
[Music]
oh go go
look
i can dance
look i can sing
i can swim i can catch
i can climb
i can read
i can fly
and i can eat
[Laughter]
[Music]
hahaha
let's dance
look
i can dance
can you dance happy
yes
i can
[Music]
very good
let's climb
[Music]
i can climb
i can't climb
can you climb pod
uh
uh no i can't climb
[Music]
catch
i can catch
and i can
eat
[Music]
thank you go go
i can dance
i can climb
i can catch and i can fly
can you fly
no i could fly
i can dance
i can climb
i can catch and i can fly
can you fly
yes i can
fly
[Music]
yes i can
fly
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
go go wait
what are they they're mirrors watch
[Music]
you're big go go
now i'm big
i'm small
[Music]
now i'm small
she's
big that's right go go
she's big
now i'm big
that's right
now you're big
look at me i'm tall
[Music]
now you're tall jenny
i'm not tall
no
you aren't tall
you're short
look tony
he's tall
[Music]
[Applause]
oh no
he isn't tall
he's short
[Music]
oh look
come on
you can't throw
yes i can
look
i'm old
[Music]
too
it's sweet
it isn't water
it's orange juice
your turn gogo
[Music]
[Laughter]
i'm hungry
i'm thirsty
i'm thirsty too
thank you go go
[Music]
what's that chibi
it's a flower go go
it's small
chibi
[Music]
it isn't small now gb
it's big
it isn't big now
it's small
[Music]
oh
big
small
good
[Music]
he's cold
she's young
[Music]
he's five
he's young
[Music]
it's 12 o'clock i'm hungry
it's 12 o'clock i'm thirsty
let's eat
and drink
it's 12 o'clock i'm hungry it's 12
o'clock
[Music]
thank you
hello tony
hello jenny
hello go go
i'm hungry
we're hungry too
good
let's eat
[Applause]
[Music]
let's go in
[Laughter]
[Music]
don't pull
we can sit there
noodles
curry
soup
yes
[Applause]
what's this
it's soup
i like soup
do you like soup tony yes i do
he likes soup
do you like soup jenny
yes i do
she likes soup
i like soup too
[Music]
what are they
they're noodles
we like noodles
they like noodles
i like noodles too
what's that
[Music]
oh
it's curry
curry is hot
we don't like curry
they don't like curry
i like curry
curry
thank you
this soup's good
these noodles are good too
water
it's hot
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's go go
let's go
[Music]
we can paint
i like yellow
he likes yellow
[Applause]
i like blue
she likes blue
[Music]
[Applause]
they like green too
[Music]
i like red
i like red too we light red
[Music]
they like red
he likes yellow she likes blue
we like red and they do too
uh
[Music]
hello jenny
hello tony
oh go go
[Music]
sorry
wow
he's cold and wet
have you got a towel
no
i haven't
she's got a towel
thank you
look they've got drinks
look
has he got drinks
[Music]
yes he has
he's got drinks
orange juice please
[Music]
oh
have you got towels
no we haven't
they haven't got towels go go
they've got towels now
oh
don't worry
the towels are magic
look out
[Music]
have you got a camera
no
we haven't
they haven't got a camera
jenny's got a camera
[Music]
look jenny
he's got an umbrella
[Music]
he hasn't got an umbrella now
and he hasn't got a towel
[Music]
[Laughter]
coco that's naughty
thank you
you're kind
[Music]
of
he hasn't got a drink
hmm
[Music]
thank you
they've got sausages pod
yes they have they've got sausages
have we got sausages
no
we haven't
what have we got
we've got eggs
good
[Music]
she's got an apple
have we got apples
no
we haven't
he's got a drink
[Music]
gb happy
come here please
they've got sausages
we've got eggs
she's got an apple
he's got a drink
[Music]
they've got sausages we've got eggs he's
got an apple he's got a tree
they've got sausages
[Music]
so
hello go go
hello tony hello jenny
brown
go go
[Music]
sorry jenny
sorry tony
go go my jumper is dirty my t-shirt is
dirty
what's that
it's a robot
what do you want
what do you want jenny
i want a t-shirt please
she wants a t-shirt
[Music]
that t-shirt is grey
i don't like gray
what color do you want
i want orange please
she doesn't like grey
she wants orange
thank you
what do you want tony
i want a jumper please
[Music]
what color do you want
uh
i want purple please
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm cold
do you want a hat and a coat
yes please
i'm cold too
i want a hat and a coat
we're cold we want hats and coats please
they want hats and colts
[Music]
do you want a hat and a coke go go
i want a hat and a coat please
[Laughter]
i want a car
what do you want chibi
[Music]
i want a boat please
she wants a boat
thank you goku
what do you want tapi
i want a plane please
he wants a plane
thank you go go
what do you want pod
uh
i don't know
do you want a zebra
no thank you i don't want a zebra i
don't like zebras
do you want a tiger
no thank you
i don't want a tiger i don't like tigers
um
i know
i want an elephant please
thank you go go
i like
elephants
do you want ice creams
yes we do
we want ice cream
they want ice creams
i want an ice cream too
for ice creams please
[Music]
thank you
hello tony
how are you hello go go i'm fine thanks
jenny go goes here
super
we can play hide and seek
all right you hide
[Music]
where's goku
i don't know
he's under the bed
come on go go i can see you
hide again goku
all right
don't look
one
two
three four
five
we can look now
[Music]
is he under the bed
no he isn't
is he on the desk
is he behind the door
no
he isn't
is he in the drawer
no
he isn't in the drawer
is she under the pillow
we can't find you go go
where are you
he's in the basket
[Music]
wow
i like this game let's play again
no
thank you
[Laughter]
[Music]
look
i'm on the ball
now i'm behind the ball
now i'm under the ball
yeah
under the egg
very good gb
i'm under the egg
where's the fork tabby
it's on
the egg
that's right taffy
the fork is on the egg
the egg is under the fall
yes pad the egg is under the fork
the plate is on the fork
[Music]
that bowl
is on the plate
[Music]
the apple
is in the bowl
[Music]
[Applause]
the elephant is on
the bow
where's the plate the plate is on the
fork
where's
oh
[Music]
elephants
so
[Music]
hello tony
hello gogo
what's that
it's my submarine
get in all right super
look
there's jenny
what's she doing
i don't know
she's diving
[Music]
she's not diving now
what's she doing
she's swimming
hello jenny
hello goku
get in jenny
the submarine doing
it's diving
[Music]
what can you see
i can see a park
i can see a man
what's he doing
he's walking
i can see a boy
what's he doing
he's fishing
you look tony
thank you
i can see a girl she's running
i can see a bridge
look out go go
the submarine is sinking
don't worry jenny
[Music]
[Laughter]
hmm
[Music]
what's gb doing
she's fishing
[Music]
what's she doing
she's diving
she's swimming
tap is walking
happy
[Music]
[Laughter]
happy is running now
[Music]
what
he's running
[Laughter]
[Music]
hello tony
hello jenny
hello gogo
what are they
their puppet go
this is her head
[Music]
these are her arms
what are these they're her hands
thank you gogo
these are her legs
these are her feet
[Music]
what are you doing
i'm painting
these are his eyes
these are his ears
this is his nose
and this is his mouth
i like puppets
what are they doing
they're sitting
now they're standing
can they dance go go
watch
they can sing too
listen
what are we doing
[Music]
behind the chairs
what are we doing
[Music]
what are they doing now
they're sleeping
[Music]
tony jenny it's time for bed
oh
it's nine o'clock
good night go go
good night jenny
good night tony
[Music]
what are you doing
we're painting
[Music]
these are birds girl girl
very good chibi what are they doing
they're flying go go
look
we're reading go go
very good
what are they doing pod
they're sleeping
[Music]
what's that go go
it's a puppet
head
arms
hands
legs
feet
[Music]
eyes
nose
ears
mouth
have you got arms gb
yes i have
have you got legs
no
i haven't
i've got eyes
[Music]
i've got eyes i've got legs and i've got
abs
you haven't got years
[Music]
how many hands have you got tabby
one
two
three
i've got three hands
have you got hands pod
uh
no
i haven't got hands
have you got legs pod
uh
no
i haven't got legs
[Music]
i've got a head
oh
huh
[Music]
[Applause]
hello tony
hello jenny
hello google
what are you doing
we're building a treehouse
can i help
yes please go go you can help jenny
what's she doing
she's cutting the wood
[Music]
stand back please jenny
thank you
that's all right
ouch
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's tony
he's using the hammer
what's he doing
he's making the floor
[Music]
[Applause]
can i help you tony
yes you can
[Music]
look jenny the hammer's hitting the
nails
ah jenny's climbing up the ladder she's
carrying the paint and the brushes
oh good
we can paint the house
what color have you got jenny
white
[Music]
that's not white
it's pink
i like pink
[Music]
purple
i like purple
hmm
this house is very small
oh go go
[Music]
look
the
opening
[Music]
that's right gibi
i'm opening the door good morning
good morning goku
come in
what are you doing
i'm closing the door
[Music]
what are tony and jenny building pod
they're building a tree house
what are they doing they're building a
tree house
[Music]
tony's making the floor
what's tony using taffy
he's using
[Music]
what's jenny carrying tabby
she's carrying paint
and brushes
very good taffy
i want a tree house
do you want a tree house gb
yes
please and you pod yes please
then let's build a treehouse
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm building a house
i'm making the floor
i'm painting the walls
and i'm painting the door
[Music]
we can paint
so
let's build a house
let's make a floor
let's paint the walls
[Music]
can you hear me tony
yes i can
i can hear you
i am
[Music]
gogo's coming
hello tony
hello go go where are you going
[Music]
where's gogo going
i don't know
let's find out
[Music]
what are you looking at go go
it's a map
[Music]
let's go
are we going to the park
no we aren't going to the park
[Music]
are we going to the cinema
no
we aren't going to the cinema
[Music]
where are we
[Applause]
we going to the supermarket
no
we aren't going to the supermarket
[Music]
we're going to the zoo
super i like the zoo
we're not going to the zoo
go go
where are we going
we're going to the beach
this isn't the way to the beach go go
[Music]
yes it is look
go go
that that's upside down
[Music]
i'm sorry
now we're going to the beach
[Music]
stand back please
what's that
it's a cinema
[Music]
that's a supermarket
that's right chibi it's a supermarket
what's that pod
that's a zoom
[Music]
that's a park and that's a beach
let's go
[Music]
where are we going
where are we going we're going to the
zoo
we're going to the zoo
[Music]
we're going
where are we going
where are we going we're going to the
beach
we're going to the beach
[Music]
look jimmy
that's a ship
it's coming this way
[Music]
i can see tony and jenny
tony
jenny
it's google
hello go go
hello go go how are you
i'm fine thanks
what are you doing
we're swimming
can you climb up the ladder
yes
we can
i'm wet
have you got a towel go go
thank you goku
do you want a hat and a coats jenny
yes please google
right
let's go
where are we going
[Music]
can you read a map tony
yes i can
good
we're going to that island
i'm looking for treasure
super let's go
have you got the map tony yes i have
this is the beach
those are the trees
one
two
three
four
five
six
seven
eight
nine ten
all right
walk ten steps this way
one
two
three
four
five six
seven
eight
nine ten
where's the treasure
it's behind the tree
i can't see the treasure
where is it it's under your feet
[Laughter]
[Music]
what can you see tony
i can see a box
i can climb down the ladder
[Music]
can you open the box jenny
yes i can
what's in it
it's a bird
a bird
can it sing
let's find out
[Music]
young and small you can dance
treats
[Music]
hello girl girl hello tony
hello jenny
he's not well
what's the matter go go
i don't know
he's changing color
[Applause]
goku
i'm sorry
i'm not
well may i lie down
yes of course
[Music]
i'm cold
may i have a blanket please
yes
of course you may
thank you jenny
do you want anything
yes i'm thirsty
may i have a drink please
of course you may
google's not well mom
may i phone the doctor is he very ill
he's sneezing and changing color oh dear
yes phone the doctor
hello
what's the matter
i don't know
may i touch you for it
yes
your heart
may i look at your throat
yes
open your mouth please
say
ah
have you got a sore throat
yes i have
[Music]
take two pins after meals
take two pills
after meals
meals
right
[Music]
is he very ill
no
he's got a cold it's not serious
thank you doctor
[Music]
what are you doing
i'm eating a meal now i can take my
pills
oh go go
[Music]
may we have lunch please
yes
you may
[Music]
[Applause]
may i have a burger please
here you are
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
may i have a sandwich please
yes you may
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
may i have a hot dog please
yes you may
[Music]
may i have an orange please may i have a
pear
please yes you may
may i have an apple piece may i have an
orange piece may i have a pan please yes
you may
[Music]
hello tony may i help you
of course
[Music]
hello
my name's gogo
how are you
[Laughter]
what's this
it's a dress
whose dress is it it's jenny's dress
don't be silly go go
[Music]
what's this
it's a shirt
[Music]
[Laughter]
no gogo this isn't my shirt
it's my dad's shirt
what's this it's jenny's skirt
[Music]
these clothes are dirty
what's that
it's a blouse
is it your blouse no it isn't it's mum's
blouse
this is my sock
you're right tony
it's dirty
this is your sock too
phone is ringing
[Music]
socks are very dirty
i'm sorry i can't play now
yes there goes here he's helping me
[Music]
oh no
bye
[Music]
gogo what are you doing
i'm washing
oh go go
[Laughter]
[Music]
do you want hats
oh yes
[Music]
please oh
whose hat is this
it's my hat
is that right tappy
yes it is it's her hat
part
is this your hat
no
it isn't
it's his hat
[Music]
whose hat is that
it's not his hat
it's not her hat
[Music]
it's not your hat go go
you haven't got a hat
i know
it's my hat
[Music]
whose hat is that it's her
hat
[Music]
whose coat is that it's his coat
whose coat is that it's her coat
his coat her coat your coat my coat we
like our coats
[Music]
so
look
that's a big dinosaur
don't touch please sorry
those are pretty butterflies
i like their wings
[Music]
i like butterfly wings but i don't want
them thank you go go
[Music]
that's a reindeer goku
reindeer live in co countries
hmm
he's not a cold reindeer now he's a hot
reindeer
this isn't right
you don't live in hot countries
[Music]
look at those ugly faces
[Applause]
look at these little soldiers
i like little
i soldiers believe this
what's happening yeah
i like this old car
i don't like old cars
i like new cars
[Music]
do you like this car jenny
yes i do
i like it now
[Music]
look at the car
is it an old car or a new car
it's an old car
where are you going
i'm going home i'm a sick man
[Music]
this is a big elephant
this is a small elephant
[Music]
this is a small hat
i like it
[Music]
this is a big hat i don't like it
are you thirsty
yes i have
do you want a drink
yes please
do you want a hot drink or a cold drink
a hot drink please
[Music]
do you want a hot drink or a cold drink
pod
uh
a cold drink
i want to call drink too please
[Music]
thank you
this is a new car
this is an old
[Music]
oh
our small boat is a green boat we like
our small green boat
[Music]
hello jenny
hello goku
where are you going
i'm going to the toy shop
a toy shop
may i go with you
of course you may
oh
look coco
i like that
oh
stop it
[Music]
may i help you yes
how much is that robot it's a hundred
dollars
have you got a hundred dollars jenny
no i haven't
how much have you got
i've only got fifty dollars
i haven't got a hundred dollars
what's that jenny
it's a lorry
i like lorries
10 20 30 40 50 60 70 80th 90th 100
i can buy the robot
oh thank you
i like this laura jenny can you buy it
i don't know
how much is it
it's two hundred dollars
i can't buy it
i've only got fifty dollars
[Music]
i like this lorry
may i buy it
have you got 200
yes
i have oh thank you
[Music]
how much is that
it's 80 dollars
i can't buy it
let's go home
here you are
thank you
oh goku
jump in
[Music]
happy
twenty
very good tabby yes that's twenty
thirty
that's not 40 that's ten
forty
fifty
[Music]
sixty
seventy
[Music]
uh
i like this book how much is it i like
this book how much is it
is it 10 is it 20 is it 30
no it's 40
today
i like that chair how much is it
is it 50 is it 60 is it 70
no it's 80
today
i like that clock how much is it
i like that plug how much is it
is it 80 is it 90 is it 100 yes it's 100
today
[Music]
may i use the telescope tony
i want to look at the moon
[Music]
hello jenny
hello tony
hello go go
what's that
it's a telescope
do you want to look at the moon
yes please i like the moon
i want to go to the moon
[Music]
let's go to the moon
i like to sit in the blue chair
where do you want to go
we want to go to the moon
we
want to go to the moon
[Music]
look at the sky
the stars are very bright
that's the earth
it's very small
[Music]
i want to walk on the moon
this is fun
hello
my name's gogo she's jenny he's tony
he can't speak english
what are you doing go go i'm trying to
speak to him
his name's black
he wants to take our pictures
what's he doing now
he's going to get his camera
[Music]
bye
i'm tired now
i want to go to bed
wake up tony it's time to get up
what's that
it's got three eyes
oh that's go-go's friend
[Music]
happy
what's this
i don't know do you know gb
no goku i don't
it's a star
it's your style
that's the moon
is the moon
that's the earth
it's the earth
[Music]
[Applause]
where do you want to go
i want to go to the moon
[Music]
where do you want to go
i want to go to the moon
[Music]
where do you want to go
where do you want to
go to the door
[Music]
all right
let's go
[Music]
hello tony hello jenny
hello gogo
what are you doing we're making kites
i like kites
whose kite is this
this one is mine and that one is hers
oh
good go go can you make a kite
watch me
[Music]
let's fly our kites
yes
we can go to the park
oh go go
whose kite is that
it's mine
[Music]
are you alright
yes
i'm all right
are those kites yours
yes they're us
is the yellow kite yours yes it is it's
mine
the yellow kite is hers
is the purple kite yours
yes it is it's mine
the purple kite is his
let's all fly our kites
oh
there's no wind now we can't fly our
kites
thank you
[Music]
look out go go
is this book yours gb
yes it is
thank you goku
the book is hers
whose book is it
is
very good
is this brush yours tappy
yes it is thank you goku the brush is
his the brush
who's is this
it's mine
i'm sorry pod
[Music]
is his he likes to eat the book is mine
i like to read the brush is mine i like
to paint the cakes are odd we like to
eat
[Music]
hello
jenny speaking
jenny it's ken
hello ken
how are you
i'm fine thanks
jenny can you come to my birthday party
when is your birthday it's july the 10th
wait a moment please
january
february
um
july
ah
first
second third
fourth fifth
6th
7th 8th
9th
10th
good
i can go
yes ken
i can go to your party
see you july the 10th
[Music]
[Applause]
hello google
hello jenny
what's this go go
it's my time machine
a time machine
jump in
[Music]
ah
are we in the past
yes we are
[Music]
[Applause]
gosh
are we in the future
yes we are
you can't pop here
oh sorry
date september 1st
time for 15.
[Music]
where do you want to go now
i know
let's go to a birthday party
all right
whoosh
let's go to ken's
he has good parties
when is his birthday
it's on july the 10th
january
february march
april may
june
july
1st 2nd
3rd
fourth
fifth
sixth
seventh
eighth
ninth
tenth
[Music]
[Applause]
hello kim happy birthday
happy birthday ken
[Music]
when's your birthday gb
when's your birthday when is it
when's your birthday when is it is it in
january is it in february
is it in march yes it
[Music]
is your birthday when is it when's your
birthday when is it is it in
[Music]
oh
go go
[Music]
hello tony
hello jenny
hello where are you going
i'm going around the world around the
world
can you take us with you
of course
[Music]
have you got tickets
ah
no we haven't
can you give us tickets
of course i can give you tickets how
many do you want
two please
thank you go go
me your tickets please
thank you
tony show him your ticket
may i help you
yes show us to our seats please
certainly
follow me please
[Music]
good morning this is your pilot speaking
my name is captain gogo
welcome to go go air
listen tony that's goku's voice he's
talking to us
please enjoy your flight
[Applause]
what's the time jenny
i don't know
gogo's gotta watch ask him
excuse me captain gogo
yes
can you tell me the time please
it's 8 45
oh no
go go we're late for school
can you take us to school please
all right
thank you for flying go go air
please fly with us again
thank you
goodbye
[Music]
tell me the time please pod uh
uh three
uh no
it's not three o'clock
four
uh no it's not four o'clock
[Music]
it's 3 30 pod
3 5
3 10
3 15
3 20
3 25
3 30.
tell me the time now please gibi
it's
it's 3
3 30
3 35
3 40
3 45
that's right bibi
it's 3 45
[Music]
i can tell you the time it's 3 45 gb
that's the time
tell me the time go go tell me the time
look at your watch and tell me the time
i'm looking at my watch taffy
i can tell you the time it's 3 46 happy
that's that time
and that's time for tea
[Music]
hello tony hello jenny
goku
what are you doing
we're building a railway
[Music]
may i have some wheels please jenny
i can't see any wheels tony
oh yes
here are some wheels
may i help you
thank you goku of course
gosh
i like making things
hmm
what can i make
i know
i can make
what can he make wait and see jenny
have you got any balls
no i'm sorry gogo i haven't got any
balls
[Music]
i've got some balls now
i've got some nails too
ah
do you want any balloons gogo oh yes
i want some balloons please
[Music]
i want to know
wait a minute jenny
go on go go
i want some cups
do you want any cards
can't
what a card
oh yes i want some cards please
go go what are you making
[Music]
now i want a hammer a teapot
and an egg
now i'm ready
[Music]
what is it
watch
[Music]
i like eggs
[Laughter]
what's that girl
it's a machine
it's a big machine what could it do
watch
[Music]
happy have you got any eggs happy have
you got any
[Music]
got eggs eggs
you've got some eggnog
yes i've got some eggs now
please put them here
gb have you got any balls gb have you
got any balls
[Music]
please put them here
[Laughter]
[Music]
hello tony
hello jenny
hello gogo
what are you doing i'm washing the
dishes
i'm drying them
what's that
it's a saucepan
aha
good i'm hungry
may i make some soup
all right
what do you want to put in it
let me think
have you got any meat
yes there's some meat in the fridge
good have you got any oil
there's some oil in this bottle
do you want any pepper
yes please
and some salt
that's a good idea
thank you
[Music]
some water
some curry powder
[Music]
a fish
some jam
[Music]
some cheese
some tomato sauce
do i want any sugar
yes i like sugar
some sugar
hmm
[Music]
go go
what's in this soup
ah some meat some pepper some jam
some cheese a fish some sugar some
oh
go go
we don't like this soup
i do
you may have ours
thank you
[Laughter]
[Music]
wow
hello
hello google
it's 12 o'clock i'm hungry
i'm hungry too
evie are you hungry
yes i'm very hungry
let's make a sandwich
[Music]
have we got any bread any bread any
bread have we got any bread any bread
[Music]
we haven't got any bread yes we have yes
we have we've got some bread now have we
got any butter any butter any butter
have we got any butter any butter
no we haven't snow we haven't we haven't
got any butter yes we have
[Music]
no we haven't no we haven't we haven't
it's a big sandwich
my sandwich is very big coco
my sandwich is very big too
thank you
[Music]
look jenny there's go go
he's riding a camel
hello tony hello jenny
where are you going goku
i'm going to egypt
do you want to come
yes please
get on jenny
may i help you
no thank you goku i can get on easily
i can get on easily too
egypt's a long way go go
camels move slowly
this camel doesn't move slowly
this camel moves quickly
watch
[Music]
gosh
you're right go go your camel moves
quickly very quickly
let's go into the pyramid
i can't see your way in
we can't go in
[Music]
let's go in
it's beautiful
hold it carefully jenny it's old
no jenny don't touch it
[Music]
look
the door's closing
[Music]
i'm sorry
what can we do
look
look carefully tony
don't talk loudly jenny talk quietly all
right sorry
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you go go
[Music]
this boat is moving slowly
it's moving quickly now
yes it is
let's go home for lunch i like lunch
[Music]
[Laughter]
i can dance too
play your drum quickly pod
uh
quickly
yes quickly
ah
quickly
i can't dance quickly
sorry gb
play your drums slowly pod
slowly
[Music]
now let's sing
play your drums slowly you can play
slowly i'm playing my drum slowly slowly
slowly play your drums
[Music]
quickly sing your song quietly you can
sing quietly i like to sing quietly
quietly quietly sing your song loudly
[Music]
hello tony well jenny
she's on stage look she's playing the
violin
go go no come back
that's jenny i'm her friend
[Applause]
i'm sorry jenny that's all right
and now ladies and gentlemen please
welcome
tony the magician
what are you going to do i'm going to do
some magic tricks
what trick is he going to do
he's going to take a rabbit out of his
hat
oh my first trick
i'm going to take a rabbit out of this
hat
there is nothing in the hat
there is nothing up my sleeves
i'm going to say a magic rhyme
rabbit rabbit soft and white
jump out of this hat tonight
where's the rabbit
oh jenny
what's he going to do
poor tony i don't know
help him please goku
[Music]
oh
tony may i do a trick
all right
and now ladies and gentlemen
please welcome my friend
go go
what are you going to do go go i'm going
to make tony disappear
ladies and gentlemen
i am now going to make my friend tony
disappear
watch carefully please
[Music]
[Applause]
where's tony
oh
yes
uh
[Applause]
where am i
help
think google think
ah i remember
go go
sorry tony
[Music]
let's have a concert
oh yes google
i like concerts
may i go first
all right gb
[Music]
what are you going to do gp
what
[Music]
what are you going to do tapi
what are you going to do
i'm going to
go go i'm going to do
dum dum dum
what are you going to do
hot
i'm going to sleep go go i'm going to
sleep
[Music]
what are you going to do
i'm going to do magic tricks my friends
i'm going to do magic tricks
[Music]
hello jenny hello tony hello goku
g
tv
what does it mean
go go tv of course
i'm going to the airport now do you want
to come yes please
good
get in
[Music]
hey
can you help me please tony
of course go go
let's ask him some questions
[Music]
excuse me
may i ask you some questions
all right
can you see me tony
yes go go i can see you clearly
can you hear me jenny
[Music]
yes
don't speak loudly
ready
yes we're ready
[Music]
hello
i'm gogo
i'm speaking to zach
uh
how old are you zack
i'm nearly 11.
uh when's your birthday my birthday's in
december
that's 11 and his birthday's in december
[Applause]
listen
they like me
i'm going to sing now he's going to sing
what are you going to sing zach
i'm going to sing a new song
zack is going to sing a new song
have you got a guitar
zack has got a guitar
[Music]
he's playing his guitar
he's getting ready
he's opening his mouth he's going to
sing do you like singing
oh talking be quiet
i'm not going to sing now
[Music]
i like singing
let's sing let's
sing and see sing and sing and sing
[Music]
thank you go go
good night from all of us at gogo tv
[Music]
good night my friends good night
it's time to go to bed
it's time to sleep it's time to dream
good night my friends good night
good night
[Music]
thank you for watching
sleep well
say good night happy
good night say goodnight gb
say good night pod
good night good
[Music]
night
good night
[Music]
do
you