Line drive to right field...
Solemnly swear the testimony
you're about to give will be the truth...
I have never,
ever failed a drug test.
Before, during and after the Olympics.
Over 160 drug tests.
I have never failed a test.
For the record,
have you ever used human growth hormone
or any other performance-enhancing
substance?
No.
I'm trying
to make sure your testimony's clear.
How many times
do I have to say it?
I've never taken drugs.
You're winning
the Tour de France...
How clear is that?
Win the Tour de France,
like the all-time greats
who've ever won this big event.
Extraordinary accusations...
must be followed up
with extraordinary proof.
And they have not come up
See...
We have...
this mountain bike.
Loading up the Thule rack.
And this is my entire life
in the car right now,
set up, ready for insanity.
I'm getting ready for the single hardest
amateur cycling event in the world.
It's basically a miniature Tour de France
for insane people.
Does it qualify for anything
if you do well with it?
Yeah, stupidity.
I've been riding for 28 years seriously,
but never as a professional.
Going to these massive amateur events
that are not professional,
but, I mean, there's serious guys there.
And the...
- Max! He loves... He's got a foot fetish.
- It tickles!
I certainly didn't know
when I started on this
what it was gonna lead to.
When LeMond won that first Tour de France,
I was in seventh grade, I think.
Can you believe it?
After over 2,000 miles...
His name in French means "the world,"
and this is the world of Greg LeMond
in Paris today.
Being the first American
to win it,
it really brought me into the sport.
I ate a wheel
going about 40 miles an hour.
I spent my entire freshman year of college
with plastic teeth in my mouth.
I would've kept racing
if it wasn't for that.
He's really hurting...
Later, Armstrong came along.
That was a whole other ball of wax.
Off the back wheel of Armstrong,
- they can't respond to pressure.
- The gap is there.
He is just going faster
and faster and faster.
This has to be
the greatest comeback in any sport.
The fact that Armstrong managed
to conquer cancer was unbelievable.
Now he's riding at the front
of the Tour de France like a Trojan.
I think I'm a year
and a half younger than Lance.
He was kind of my hero.
For now,
I'd just like a yes or a no.
Did you ever take banned substances
to enhance your cycling performance?
Yes.
I'd always suspected
that he had been doping.
I felt that I didn't really wanna know.
Because a lot of the guys
that he raced with
and guys who had raced against him
that I'd just known over the years...
they were my friends.
If you would've had your choice,
you would've never doped?
Ever?
Up until it directly affected me,
I was like, "I think Lance is
probably clean."
I don't know.
It's... messy.
The way they got him,
this is what nobody understood.
150 times
over the last six years, I've been tested.
In competition, out of competition,
at home, at a race,
Seven in the morning, seven at night,
whatever, and they're all clean.
He never failed a drug test.
Solemnly swear the testimony
you're about to give will be the truth?
It was his teammates
who had turned on him
as part of the federal investigation.
If this guy had passed, whatever it is,
500 doping tests over his entire career,
clearly the system didn't work.
How many times did you test Lance
during his career?
As the laboratory of record,
I'm estimating that I would've tested him
50 times. 5-0.
So you tested Lance 50 times
and never caught him?
Correct.
I developed and operated
the UCLA Olympic Laboratory for 25 years.
I'm known mostly for developing tests
so that athletes get caught
if they're using drugs.
How did you
personally feel every year?
Did you believe that it was just Lance?
- Do you think that...
- They're all doping.
Every single one of 'em.
Unfortunately, the drugs work.
With certain knowledge, you can
get around the testing all the time.
It's really easy to beat.
Very easy.
Originally, the idea that I had
was to prove the system in place
to test athletes was bullshit.
I had read about the hardest
amateur cycling race on the planet,
this seven-day race
through the French Alps,
called the Haute Route.
If you were to take the hardest seven days
in the Tour de France,
put 'em all together
back-to-back-to-back-to-back,
that would be
what this Haute Route course was like.
The first year I did it totally clean.
There were 440 masochists.
My goal was to be in the top 100.
After seven days, 75,000 feet of climbing
and 1,000 miles...
I was destroyed.
But I finished 14th.
There's about ten guys, it seems,
that are on just another level
than everybody else.
Then there's this next group,
and then there's me.
What did you think of the idea?
Well, in certain senses,
I like the idea.
It depends on what you consider
to be dangerous...
Right.
Testing yourself on these drugs.
But I was curious, you know,
how you were going to do it.
I might be willing to help
and advise and...
avoid positives.
Are you gonna take drugs?
Yeah. Basically, go through...
go through an entire doping program,
but overseen by the scientist.
I'm gonna have Don Catlin design
a program for me
that's gonna get through every single one
of the doping controls in the world...
clean.
If I could do that
and I could get away with it,
that would mean that pretty much
any athlete could do that
and any athlete could get away with it.
You're going to need a laboratory
to test your body fluids.
I wasn't sure how I was gonna get
my samples into the lab yet.
The only labs
that test professional athletes
are WADA-accredited labs.
WADA is
the World Anti-Doping Agency.
The labs are set up
that you can't just go do this.
Because if somebody could just send
their samples into a lab,
then anybody could figure out how
to game the system.
And then...
This could damage my reputation
that I've worked on for years...
He just started getting worried
about his legacy.
My involvement...
it's just not gonna work.
He backed out.
But, you know, God bless Don Catlin,
because he told me
that he knew this guy...
The director of the Olympic lab
in Moscow, Grigory Rodchenkov.
He's a great old friend.
We talk a few times.
He's in Moscow.
And that set off
this whole chain of events.
Tell something.
Hi.
Oh! Great.
- It's a secret window. Now it's clean.
- Hmm.
Yeah, you look good now.
Yes, you, too. Go ahead.
I met with this guy who's gonna at least,
like, prescribe me the protocol.
What is your ultimate purpose?
You would like to beat doping test?
You would like to start
your hormonal program?
- Yes.
- Then give sample... and prove negative.
Yes.
Ha, ha, ha.
You need a very serious advisor
because there are a lot of traps.
Normally drug... Okay.
My dog is playing.
I just came back,
and he's very much excited.
And he has a special toy...
Yeah, I hear it.
Hey, you wanna see my dog?
- Let me get him.
- Yes.
Oh!
Is it male, female?
Male.
Castrated?
No.
So with balls?
He's got the balls.
Yeah. There is the balls. Yes, yes.
- Yeah, this is Max.
- Max.
Max. Yeah.
Testosterone,
you have to have a prescription.
Yes, uh, injectable.
Injectable, right.
So, now you are clever, huh?
Like Lance Armstrong.
Send it to me.
Names, doses, for how long...
So everything should be orchestrated.
How do I do that?
Just send you everything I'm gonna take?
Yes, your one-month schedule.
Yes.
We've got three medications
that you'll take by injection.
- This is five times a week?
- Yeah, it's all on your regimen sheet.
We'll draw up half a cc.
- Looks like a big needle.
- It's a tiny needle.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Your testosterone comes ready to go.
This is very, very viscous.
It's a very thick substance,
so you need a big needle to draw it up.
Then we're gonna pull out.
So there's your .2 CC's.
And that one goes also in the top
of your thigh.
- I'm a little nervous, but all right.
- Okay.
Give me a thigh.
And does it hurt the muscle?
Do you flex?
It's not gonna go in your muscle.
It's gonna go above.
You just pinch it, and we're just gonna go
just through the skin.
That's it.
And then we're just gonna put that
underneath the skin.
- Did that hurt?
- No, not too bad.
- I mean, I see it there.
- It'll go away in no time.
- That's the HCG.
- Oh, shit.
And right next to it,
the testosterone.
Pop it through the skin.
That's all we're looking to do.
Just through the skin.
It's real thick now.
- And you are pumped up.
- Whoa!
How long till those bumps go down?
- They'll go quick. Within a half hour.
- Okay. Whoa.
And so we begin.
The ability to go day after day
will be brand new for you, I think.
Going to do an injection.
Exciting.
I work with one trainer
that does a lot of fitness
as well as nutrition coaching.
Almost there. Come on, Bryan.
We should be able to see
a 15 to 20% improvement.
What's your dog's name again?
Vrangei.
Okay. Did you start your program?
I did.
This is my morning pill-popping routine.
And then I prepare the testosterone.
Yes, testosterone propionate.
Yes.
It's really thick.
What made you think
that Grigory might help me?
Well, it's difficult for me
to answer that without...
saying things about Grigory
that aren't very kind.
Okay, let me think.
So, you've already did it for two weeks?
He's fucking me.
Just pee
and collect your urine today.
And drop into the freezer.
So just pee, take some urine
and put it in the freezer?
In the freezer.
There's day eight, day ten...
Needle.
The testosterone with the HGH,
it's a weird feeling because
it doesn't feel like I'm on anything.
Are you now training?
And you feel a little bit stronger?
Yeah, I really felt stronger.
That's good.
Forty milligrams each other day
is a very good protocol.
I still had no idea
why a WADA lab director
who did all the testing
for the Sochi Olympics
would agree to do this,
because his job was supposed to be
to catch athletes.
So you want me to do 24,000 units
in one month?
Yes.
Fuck, man. That's a lot of EPO.
You have just common fears,
and it's paranoia.
We are imitating... We are reproducing
Lance Armstrong's scenario.
I'm getting kind of bruises
all over my legs.
Don't disturb your thigh at all.
Stop it.
You can inject into your thigh muscle,
but better to the ass.
Into my ass?
Much more!
Okay.
This is starting to get ridiculous.
Ow!
- Wow! I'm bleeding from that.
- Okay.
Oh, fuck, I'm really bleeding
from that one, too.
Let me get some alcohol.
Um, okay, so then a half of this one.
Oh, fuck!
Um...
Okay.
So, that's that.
He was like,
"You don't do subcutaneous.
You put it right into your ass.
No, we go one inch into buttocks.
Show me that bottle again."
You're kidding me.
Have you seen movie with me?
- No.
- Separate movie.
- Which movie?
- No?
About me.
All athletes in Russia are doping.
The athletes that are
under Mr. Rodchenkov,
they don't get positive tests.
The laboratory was
internationally recognized for research.
Its head scientist is considered
an outstanding scientist.
Grigory Rodchenkov.
Dr. Rodchenkov
is informed about everything.
He knows how long the drugs need
to disappear from the body.
He is aware and instructs.
He's the most important specialist.
The ARD documentary
regarding the Russian whistle-blowers...
what did you think,
hearing these allegations?
It was inflammatory enough
that they were afraid to run it
while the whistle-blowers were still
in Russia.
So they got them out of Russia,
ran the program,
and it was a bombshell.
99% of Russian athletes
are guilty of doping.
That's according to a recent
German documentary aired on ARD.
WADA's president,
Craig Reedie, promised an investigation,
effective immediately.
It is wrong just to make
any kind of assumption
on allegations in the media.
Athletes must be presumed
to be innocent until proven guilty.
These are wild allegations,
and we'll have to check them out.
Reedie had to do something.
That's how the Independent Commission
was created.
I had investigative experience
for a decade and a half,
and some big investigations,
like US Olympic Committees
and Major League Baseball.
And Bonds hits one high!
It's a ding!
Our mandate was athletics,
track and field and Russia.
The WADA chairman
named this Independent Commission
and said, "Let's get at it."
The Anti-Doping Agency
wants a report by the end of the year,
and athletics officials say
they'll cooperate.
It's unclear, though,
what actions might be taken.
Thomas Daigle, CBC News.
Is it gonna be okay?
Is it gonna pass over?
Is this gonna cause you...
No, no, no. It's growing.
It's growing?
It's like a tornado coming.
Okay, so you are receiving how many units?
Grigory, the Moscow scientist
I was showing you,
who did all the testing for Sochi,
who's now at the center
of this big Russian doping scandal.
Russia was doping their athletes
in the '80s.
- Apparently, they've never stopped.
- Really?
The crazy thing is, Richard Pound,
the guy who was the head of WADA
for 15 years,
has actually been hired
to lead the investigation against Grigory.
Um... I don't know
what you want me to do with that.
Meaning?
I don't know how...
Shit. My computer's about to die.
- Let me grab my power cord. I'll be back.
- Do you have a charger? All right.
There might be someone else out there
that might be a better decision or choice.
You're using this guy as your coach.
What's your comfort level?
- Here's how I'm looking at it...
- You can find someone else.
I guess you call it "doping doctors."
I don't know what you would label Grigory.
Is he a biochemist? I don't even know.
It doesn't even matter.
I don't like this shit.
Look,
there's no finding someone else.
Your numbers look great.
Your testosterone is pretty much
right where we want you.
Grigory, what's the typical wash-out
for urine to go to negative
from a full treatment of testosterone?
How many days does that take usually?
Seven?
For Bryan,
two weeks will be nice.
Is there any way that we could test
that here in the States,
or it's gotta go back to you
to test those frozen urines?
It's the only way.
But again, I am under heavy control.
WADA now, they have an inquiry about me.
Yes.
So you see, like, me...
I'm a very dangerous person.
How do you think is the best way
to basically get that test done?
Maybe, hopefully...
I would like to do this,
to come to, maybe, LA,
and to smuggle something to Russia.
Some urines from you.
Um...
Could we send 'em to Salt Lake City
or another lab?
No, no, no. It's strictly prohibited.
You are so skinny!
You're skinny.
No!
All the urine in my freezer,
we have to unfreeze it?
Yes, we unfreeze,
then we homogenize
to make sure everything is melted.
I took special bottles
for smuggling urine, and...
we will make a scenario
like I am collecting my urine.
"Grigory one, morning."
"Evening, 28th. Grigory two."
Then we recode them.
Perfect.
Otherwise, what is the source
of the urine and why?
Right.
The goal during
this two-to three-week period
is to push you to an extreme
on a chronic level, not just acute.
- Okay, we...
- Max!
He loves me.
Yeah. Max...
No, no, don't kick Max. It's okay.
- Max, go away. Out.
- No, no, no.
It's not good time.
Later.
A fifteen-second acceleration
whenever you want. Good.
We need girls, cheerleaders.
Right? Exactly.
Maybe we should get you some pom-poms.
- And like this...
- Right.
I was working here in 1989,
when Catlin was in big power.
Laboratory was located in UCLA.
The campus.
Twenty years ago,
we had decided to develop a way to get
actually friendly
with what was then the Soviets.
We, the US,
would invite Soviets to come to the US
and pick and choose athletes
that they wanted to test,
bring 'em in and test them
where the Soviets were watching.
Grigory was the first representative.
He shows up at the second day of work
in bright orange shorts
and announces that he's gonna enter
the Santa Monica Marathon.
And he won the darn thing.
He's a good athlete.
I was almost
a professional in running.
1,500 meters and five kilometers
at Moscow University.
My mother always pushed me
to swim, to ski.
I realized that some people
are using something.
Last year, he was nobody.
Next year, he has muscles.
Of course, I also started
to use the best of the best,
stanozolol.
And all injections were done by my mother.
And, of course, it was 50 milligrams,
this simple thing.
Wait, wait.
Your mother injected you?
Yes, of course.
But if you are not national team level,
like Olympic,
you cannot afford any more training camp.
So, I graduated to Moscow University,
to the chemical department.
I liked doping control. I liked sports.
And since 1985, I worked in the top field
of laboratories in the world.
And then, Moscow laboratory
was doing mistake by mistake.
"We need a new director,
and it will be upheld by WADA."
That's how I became director.
Should I be taking the HGH
and the testosterone now?
Let's look at your protocol.
I have to sketch all schematics,
starting from the new year.
- We'll sit down with a piece of paper.
- Yes.
With the piss and then with the tubes.
We take just a fraction.
And then it will be coded
and took for analysis.
So, here's day one. Okay?
Here's day two.
Here's day three, day four, day five.
Seven, eight, nine.
We have nine urines. Okay.
- So we are starting...
- And that one, I just took.
Is that enough? Or do I need any more?
It's okay.
Okay.
- Three, three, three.
- I hear you got the real code.
I am mafia.
This is mafia.
Chased by WADA.
Could you imagine, the best laboratory
will be puzzled with your piss?
In Russia, the empire of evil.
Propaganda.
- Fantastic.
- Oh, God. What is that?
It's flakes. Your flakes.
What is that? What is that?
Your sins.
And on the top.
When I come to Moscow
in September, after the race, I can drink.
Okay, next time. Next time, if I survive.
At my lab, WADA is keeping laboratory
on a very short leash. Leash?
Asking many questions.
All sort of bullshit.
Like, "Where is your...
underground laboratory for pre-testing?
Where is the shadow laboratory?"
Of course, my laboratory is fully under...
cameras and everything,
computers, barcodes...
But they were looking for something.
- Like a secret lab?
- Yes, yes, yes, yes, underground.
- Batman?
- Yes, yes.
Who owns the lab?
- The state.
- The state does?
Yes.
Okay, we have Terminal One,
departing flight.
- Yeah.
- ♪ I am a woman in love ♪
Keep it. It's my donation.
- No, no, no!
- No, no, no.
I have a lot, you see.
All people are presenting me with pens,
so I have full collection.
- Remember me.
- I will.
- So I'm gonna see you...
- So, so, so nice with you.
- Grigory, thanks for coming.
- Yes.
Be very careful
with what you are recording.
It's not permitted.
It's like pornography and erotics.
Sports pornography and erotics.
Now we are...
And I see you, uh, in September.
Yes, definitely.
Did you go to Moscow?
No, I did not, and Dick Pound did not.
We wanted to send an investigative group
of WADA specialists into the Moscow lab.
The director of the lab,
he was the last fail-safe position, right?
If there is a sample
that's potentially positive,
where can you stop it from being reported?
In the lab.
So he was interviewed.
Didn't provide us with much information.
Please tell me all my frozen piss
didn't explode in your bag.
But this is big secret.
Bryan, I have all urines.
We analyzed urines
for your steroid profile.
Everything is kept frozen.
- I have a full agenda, so don't worry.
- Okay.
We did preliminary tests,
but not much.
When WADA will leave...
They are leaving tomorrow night.
Then maybe Friday,
or maybe Monday, anyway...
WADA's there bothering you?
It's much more challenging.
WADA is sniffing
and asking tons of questions.
- Dick Pound... You know, Dick Pound?
- Yes
He's starting to understand
it's very difficult to prove something.
What do you see the outcome
or the solution as?
We will see.
You just focus on racing.
Keep digging, keep digging.
Keep digging, come on.
Come on, you got it.
Come on. Four, two, one.
Taking it down. Taking it down.
This is already better than last time.
Last year, 250 watts. This year, 349.
It's 100 watts.
My power right now is 20% more
than I had last year.
Yes, yes, finally you have some gains.
Some gain, some progression.
I can't wait to come to Moscow.
Bryan, it will be fantastic.
I shouldn't bring any EPO with me
to Europe, right?
- No.
- Okay.
You complete everything
until 17th.
- The last injection is on US soil.
- Okay.
Before passing the border
and the customs.
Then you're taking urine with you to me,
and we'll complete
your biological passport.
That's it.
Words cannot describe
what you'll be living through this week.
Your body's gonna shut down.
It's gonna break down entirely.
We are on
the French Cycling Federation calendar,
and we do have an anti-doping policy.
As far as testing for PEDs,
the race says that they do.
They may come and test,
just so you're aware.
As I came to learn, they don't.
- Don't worry.
- But I had Grigory.
He had helped me dope,
and he was gonna test my samples
through his WADA lab in Moscow.
So, be clever.
I have not done a urine sample
since I've been here.
You are like a pioneer.
So I'm gonna pee
in this little bag here.
You are a victim of your ideas.
August 21st.
See you at the end.
And good luck tomorrow.
Start time tomorrow morning,
7:15.
- Right here.
- I am like a priest.
I am healing your doping paranoia.
You are free. You have enough power,
and God is with you.
You are sentenced to win.
So the scheme was now in place.
Raise your arms!
Are you ready?
Start!
Ninety, ninety. That's it.
Pouly!
You did great.
You were three and a half minutes
behind Pouly.
- That's not bad.
- No, that's fucking great.
You guys were hauling ass.
Bryan's in that group data.
He's in there with the top ten guys.
All the guys in the top ten
are incredible.
Very good.
They could be pro.
You are a monster.
Medium-sized monster.
Bryan Fogel, can you hear me?
Can't raise him on the walkie-talkie.
Bryan, come back.
- Bryan!
- Yeah?
It has to be charged.
The battery's dead.
It needed to be charged.
Now it won't go up. You see?
Dead. It's totally dead.
Fuck!
My derailleur, my shifting,
it broke.
- Your bike?
- Yes.
You cannot shift your gears?
For 100 kilometers.
My goodness.
- I dropped ten places in the rankings.
- Okay. Hmm.
My God.
I feel
that I'm really stronger this year.
- Like, that I'm recovering.
- Yeah.
I mean, I'm hauling ass,
but they're...
I'm not beating 'em.
They're in a different...
There's guys that I don't know
that you could've beat on your best day.
My whole plan was
to have a substantially
better performance this year.
And...
I'm not.
Did you just get separated
or what?
Neutral descent now?
Does it hurt that you did
better last year than you did this year?
I mean, I could have been 21 years old
and taken all the blood bags
and EPO in the world,
and I was still not going to be
a Tour de France champion.
It doesn't matter.
Just stay optimistic.
Because now, we can change nothing.
The winner, Peter Pouly.
- I felt pretty good. I just had...
- No, no, no.
I've just had some bad luck days.
Bryan, look at me.
Stop it.
You are what you are. I am what I am.
It's a turning point, what we are doing.
You should be happy
that we have such fantastic material.
We have ten times more information
than Dick Pound and Armstrong together.
- Really?
- We will continue. Don't worry.
You are just like in the reception.
You did not enter the first floor.
Then there is a second and so on.
What's on the second floor?
When you go to Moscow,
you will see.
So cool.
How many tests...
I've probably had 15 or 20 blood tests.
- It's more than enough.
- Okay.
- Is this the laboratory?
- Yes.
Oh, you see, this is bloody RUSADA.
Bringing samples, it's not too good
to show our camera to them.
- Oh. You want us to hide?
- Yes, yes, yes.
Okay.
Be very careful with all your material.
- People are very sensitive also, you know.
- Yes.
This is my director place.
It's the most famous laboratory
in the world.
We cannot say explicitly
that you have been analyzed.
It's coming.
I already solved everything yesterday.
You will have it until, let's say...
Within two weeks, we will do this.
But it should be done still,
say, under the table, not...
- Okay.
Smile. Your race is over.
We have to go downstairs.
Are there scientists,
or those working
in WADA laboratories today,
that you suspect
could have been corrupted?
Each director of laboratory,
like me...
I have to sign a code of ethics,
that what we are doing
is not harmful or detrimental
to the whole anti-doping society.
We go down this emergency exit.
What did Russia have to do
with the hiding blood passports
of all the athletes?
Let's talk in my office.
If you hide fight against doping,
you cannot be 50% honest.
You have to be honest,
or you have to hide the ends.
It's the same as Orwell, 1984.
WADA is like a religion,
and you cannot escape.
You have to think about money,
but you cannot steal money.
You have to think about women,
but you have to be married
and don't go to prostitution.
But again...
almost everybody has some period
when they were sinners.
So what to do?
There is no answer.
For the last five months,
I took urine and then I did blood...
Yes, we have a good database.
How do we go about the analysis?
What do we wanna show?
How do we put together
- the bigger story arc?
- Bryan, be optimistic.
Smile.
I have vodka for you.
- You do?
- Yes.
- The best vodka.
- What kind?
From Mordovia.
- Oh, awesome!
- You do drink vodka?
- Yeah, I like vodka.
- You like... I have vodka for you.
I've decided I'm not gonna leave Russia.
I'm gonna stay here.
You would like to stay?
Russia is the most relaxing country
in the world.
You think?
No.
You having fun?
Yes, we have fun!
Smile.
Bryan!
Ladies and gentlemen,
members of the media, welcome to Geneva.
Almost a year ago,
very serious doping allegations
were first raised
on German television channel ARD.
The WADA president, Sir Craig Reedie,
announced that a full and thorough inquiry
would be conducted.
The founding president
of the World Anti-Doping Agency,
Mr. Dick Pound,
the chair of that commission.
Overwhelming portions of the allegations
made on the ARD program
have been found
by the Independent Commission to be true.
It's worse than we thought.
We have found cover-ups.
We found destruction
of samples in the laboratories.
We found payments of money
in order to conceal doping tests...
among others.
Our conclusion was that all
of this could not have happened,
and continue to happen,
without the knowledge of
and either actual or implied consent
of the state authorities.
You reading this?
Forty pages of this report is Grigory.
It's hard to imagine
what the Russian state interest
in athletes' urine would be.
One of our big concerns about tests
were the 1,400 that were destroyed
by the director of the Moscow laboratory.
In fact, our recommendation
is the director of the laboratory
be removed from his position,
that the WADA accreditation be withdrawn,
and the Russian Federation be suspended.
- Bryan, hi.
- Hi.
Where did Grigory go?
I've been crying.
Yes, I am with him,
and I think maybe you want
to speak with him.
Maybe he's a little bit nervous.
- I'm so sorry.
- Bryan.
I'm not... I'm sorry. I'm trying
to understand what you're saying.
I'm absolutely saying
that we will overturn all this bullshit,
and it will be upside down.
So, Bryan,
I hardly could talk to you tonight.
The details are damning
and could have a profound impact
on the future of Russian athletics.
This WADA commission
has accused Russian athletics
of state-sponsored doping.
We are preparing our response
to again provide any explanation needed.
That's all I can say at this point.
Does this mean they could potentially miss
next year's Olympics?
Well, that is certainly
one of the potential outcomes here.
The International Olympic Committee
have released a statement.
You will see athletes
being sanctioned by the IAAF.
and officials being excluded.
And you will see an action led by the IOC.
We'll apply this zero-tolerance policy.
Decision time for the IAAF
on whether Russia's
track and field athletes
will be allowed
to compete at the Rio Olympics.
I want to hear
what the Athletics Federation of Russia
is actually saying
in answer to those allegations.
The Sports Minister,
Vitaly Mutko, has said,
"Russia took all the necessary measures,"
he says, "to fight the doping problem.
Moscow's anti-doping lab
was recently recognized
as one of the best in the world."
You don't want to talk to us?
Well, the employees at this lab
are clearly being very tight-lipped,
but the report
from the World Anti-Doping Agency
goes into great detail
describing the alleged activities
inside that building.
There are around
50 correspondents
behind my fence, but I am here.
And I am not supposed to talk.
Bryan, stay quiet.
You're a lucky man.
Only you, knowing me.
Holy shit.
The World Anti-Doping Agency suspended
Russia's sports drug-testing lab,
and the head of the lab resigned.
Grisha,
be careful what you tell him now.
Don't tell me. I am just...
They're holding
on the phone for you.
- Tell them I'll call back...
- It sounds serious.
I'll call back in five minutes!
- Okay, but will you?
- Yes, go away!
Fine.
Bryan...
It's a disaster.
They're just killing people.
Cutting heads, you know,
without who is guilty.
Yesterday, you know,
I went to Minister Mutko,
and we started to discuss.
He was talking,
blah, blah, blah, about football.
Uh, blah, blah, blah, about Formula 1.
Then to say what to do with bloody doping.
But he say, "Could you resign?"
I go, "Yes."
"Today?" "Yes, today."
And I resigned.
And...
they lost director.
I have a lot of calls,
but I'm just changing my telephones.
People are looking for their job,
but laboratory is almost empty.
Empty.
I don't know what's going on.
I just know what I'm reading
in the newspaper and in the press and...
You know.
Oh, really? Really?
I mean, will they come after you?
Are they gonna arrest you?
Are they gonna...
Would they try to put you in jail?
In jail? No.
What is the reason for jail?
- You know.
- No.
Are you in any danger?
Yes, but not jail.
It could be some... I don't know.
- I mean...
- Do you know that I am now moving
with a security man?
Security guard.
No.
Just a security guard in my home.
- In your home?
- Coming to my car.
I'm following behind.
It's recommended
until the end of the week,
because I am the only man
who can kill both sides.
Russia and WADA, so...
Stay quiet.
Let me say this.
In reality,
the Independent Commission's report
and statements made by Mr. Pound
are exaggerated.
We've even built a modern,
state-of-the-art anti-doping laboratory
that is renowned for its testing
for the Olympics, Paralympics,
championships and more,
and received the highest merits
for its contributions.
The government is merely financing
the laboratory operation.
They don't accept
this Independent Commission at all.
They're deliberately lying.
Bryan, Bryan...
- look at me.
- Okay.
It means I could be tossed
under the bus anytime.
I'm not sure
that we are connecting freely.
Because now we are on radar,
that's for sure.
You know Snowden?
Yeah, of course.
Now you see.
We still don't know...
We still don't know
whether Russia is participating
in Olympic Games or not.
The outcome, why I am very much
cautious about my life...
If me will be purged...
okay, Russia will go to the Olympics.
The problem is to survive.
- Listen, I, uh...
- Yes.
- Joking, you know, seriousness aside...
- Stop it. Stop, stop.
I'm just... I'm worried about you.
Yes, yes.
Tomorrow, I drop you.
And then, when I say...
"How is weather in Los Angeles?"
or anything related to weather...
it means that we will talk
in 15, 20 minutes.
Be ready to talk.
Tonight, our sport
finds itself in a shameful situation.
And that is why I can confirm
the council has overwhelmingly voted,
with immediate effect,
to suspend the Russian Federation.
It's done so, uh, by 22 votes to one.
It is the strongest sanction...
Regarding the recent events
connected to our track and field team,
I urge the sports minister
and all my sports colleagues
to make this their number one priority.
This is the first step.
Secondly, it is vital to conduct
our own internal investigation.
Sport should be fair.
Responsibility should be personalized
and absolute.
Bryan...
I need... Wait, look at me.
Yeah.
I need to escape and to walk... to walk...
You can go wherever you want.
- Okay.
- I will be doggy-sitting at your home.
So you wanna get out?
Yes. Simply.
What do you want to, uh...
It's very suspicious when you have
one-way ticket, you know.
Yeah, right.
You have to book a round trip.
They're watching us.
- Bryan?
- Yeah.
What I am doing,
myself, I can do nothing.
- So...
- Okay?
I'll send you... Let me figure out
some flight options, okay?
Okay.
I'm gonna get the flight,
right now.
- Yes, right now.
- Okay.
Go.
Also, some security measures will be set.
How will I know
that you made it through okay?
Um...
I don't know.
Okay?
Okay.
- Bryan?
- Yeah, I'm right here.
- Okay, just left my security man.
- Okay.
I am very much dizzy, paranoid.
We'll get you here.
My wife and children decided
maybe it's better to stay in Russia.
Just gotta make sure in the US
that you're okay also.
My daughter...
Yes?
She's getting married.
Right.
Married, everything.
It's time.
Okay.
- Cross fingers now.
- You, too.
Remember Orwell.
"We will meet each other
where there is no darkness."
When I first interviewed you
a year ago,
I asked you if you thought
your investigation
would be a defining moment
in the history of sport.
How would you answer that question now?
Yes, it can be a defining moment,
and I think it should.
You've got your number one
Olympic sport in the crosshairs,
and you've got one of the major
Olympic countries in the world
in the crosshairs,
even if it's the crosshairs
only on athletics at the moment.
That has the potential of affecting
the credibility of all sport
and, therefore,
the continued viability of all sport.
Why would I watch an event that's fixed?
There he is.
- I'm here, yes!
- He's escaped.
This is... Yes. Escaped alive.
Come on.
Then you did what?
Destroyed my computer
from my working place.
I took hard disk.
And also, I have three copies.
It's a historical moment.
Grigory, I want you to know
that I understand your desire
to be visible
and I think that's very important
for you, to be safe.
I was on the phone yesterday
with the lawyer for Edward Snowden.
They have some recommendations.
I have everything with me,
and also I destroyed my office computer.
Put it in a very safe place
and dropped there like a dummy.
We'll talk in a few hours.
- This is, uh... This is it.
- Uh-huh.
It's like a labyrinth.
Yeah.
Okay, this is the place.
- Good.
- Here's, um...
bed, bathroom.
Secure place.
It's a good thing.
This'll work, at least till we get
what the plan is
and what we're gonna do.
He goes to me.
He remembers me since May.
You will be learning Russian.
You will be learning Russian very soon.
I'm missing dogs.
There was one thing
that I noticed in the IC report,
and that was that there were KGB people
hanging around the lab.
And that's a real no-no.
You know, KGB people are not nice people.
So I am at home.
We will banish all those
who have a suspicious reputation
from the leadership of Russian athletics.
In 60 days, we will present
the renewed athletics with new people...
So, if the KGB...
I guess they're called the FSB now...
they're in the lab,
who else could finance them
but Vitaly Mutko?
Oh, I don't think Vitaly Mutko
finances the FSB.
- That's a state security operation.
- But... but Putin?
Well, whoever finances it
and runs the state security apparatus,
it's not the sport minister.
Officials are essentially saying,
"There may be some problems,
but we are trying
and have already taken steps
to address those problems."
And all of the officials
are essentially rejecting the idea
that there's still a major problem.
Honey, hi.
I am here, far away and in the darkness.
You see them all?
Wearing fancy suits, ties,
making speeches on TV...
It's all a farce.
Of course
I was very disappointed
when laboratory was closed.
Now reading this IC report,
I am just watching with another's eyes.
I know that I could change the past,
telling the truth.
But would you like telling the truth,
you will be annihilated.
George Orwell,
I was reading the first in 1989.
I was 30.
Before that time, in Soviet Union,
the book 1984,
it was strictly, strictly prohibited.
For me, it was totally shocking.
Especially "ignorance is strength."
This is the most powerful thing.
It was my weapon.
It gave me definitions,
it gave me coordinates
how you can apply to your life.
It's like a road map.
"'There are three stages
in your reintegration, ' said O'Brien.
'There is learning,
there is understanding,
and there is acceptance.
It's time for you
to enter upon the first stage.'"
I was thinking that we'd start...
I ask you questions,
and you answer "yes" or "no."
Does Russia have a systematic, statewide
doping system in place
to cheat the Olympics?
Yes.
Were you the mastermind
of a statewide system
that cheated the Olympics?
Of course. Yes.
Russia won a total of 73 medals
in the 2008 Beijing Olympics.
How many of those athletes were dirty?
Thirty.
Russia won 81 total medals in London.
How many of those were dirty?
Oh, even more.
50% is for sure. Let it be 50%.
They were earned using special program.
State-sponsored, of course.
Was Putin aware of the existence
of a Russian doping system?
Yes. Aware of my name.
He took me from the prison
for such special affair.
- From prison?
- Yes.
To redeem.
Okay, let's back up one sec here.
My concern is that it's something
they would use to discredit you.
Oh, of course.
So, the first criminal investigation
against you,
when was it and what happened?
Oh, it's not easy to say how it happened.
Before 2008, China was
the biggest producer of anabolics.
It was produced in a pharmaceutical,
well-equipped,
good manufacturing practice.
No contamination, high qualities.
And all these anabolics are coming
to Europe, to the United States.
It's the same like in Russia.
Of course, at that time in Russia,
as the head of laboratory,
I was a part of system.
There are three or four
top-level witch doctors,
like Portugalov.
Portugalov was the famous anabolic coach
of Russian national team.
It was Soviet time. He was before me.
Portugalov is conveyor of athletes.
He has his own protocols,
and he really had great success.
And then they became Olympic champions.
The problem began in 2008.
Jacques Rogge,
the president of the Olympics,
told government of China,
"You are Olympic country,
but you are producing anabolics in bulk.
You cannot do like this anymore. Stop it."
They stop it. Officially.
But who is supplying steroids
to national team?
Before, there was not any concern.
You buy stanozolol, it's stanozolol.
But Portugalov was so confident,
offering and providing things
which were not proven or tested.
They have impurities
which could be detectable.
"Oh," Portugalov say. "What to do?
I spent so much money for this.
Maybe you could advise to do?"
What advice? Drop it to the trash.
Now, in Moscow laboratory,
we had the best sensitivity
and detection limits.
I'm very proud that I created the test
for long term metabolites,
which caused the detection window
to enlarge from two or three weeks
to six months.
That's why Portugalov suddenly had
so many positives.
All people on the national team,
they came to ask
where to get these steroids.
I knew one source.
Suddenly, I was coordinating
the whole steroid program.
So you were
cutting out Portugalov?
Yes, but what I was doing,
I was saving national team
from purchasing dirty steroids.
Eventually, I don't know
whether it was by purpose,
I fight with Portugalov.
Then I became enemy.
Criminal narcotic police came to my home,
they took my computer,
and they said,
"Then we arrest you on Monday."
I was in such depression
and my will was paralyzed.
And I decided to escape, I don't know how.
I took some knife from...
very, very sharp...
from my wife's kitchen.
I drank whiskey, I sit to the bath.
And...
And... it was...
It goes so smooth.
Then, in the water,
I see how blood is doing like this.
It wasn't very strong, the lock.
My wife opened door.
My heart was seared.
It was very good surgeon.
And since I was considered
to be suicide...
I was sent to a psychiatric clinic.
After seeing that I am depressed,
they started to give me such crazy drugs.
I was totally out of reality.
And then again, something happened.
The criminal police,
they sentence me
to another psychiatric clinic...
which is for those who are sadist,
who are totally
worst-of-the-worst criminals.
They respected me very much.
I was called "professor."
But I get better, better, better.
The most funny thing,
they allowed me to use computer,
so I was working in psychiatric clinic
like a head of laboratory director,
advising the whole Russian national team.
That time,
I received, from Olympic Committee,
an invitation to London,
2012 Olympic Games, being the director.
Russian ministry was little bit uncertain
that I'm criminal in full.
But WADA said,
"If not Rodchenkov, we don't see
in Russia any other candidate than him.
If you don't send him to London,
we send to London another director."
You can imagine how important
information from London laboratory is
for national team.
I had information, what testing
this London laboratory is doing,
to understand where we are
and how much is danger.
Without this, all Russian doping situation
will be collapsed.
Thanks to God, Mutko understood this.
I received a call
from the Moscow investigators.
"Grigory...
your case is dropped."
Who took care of it?
Who got the charges dropped?
Putin. Of course.
It's my redemption. Success in Sochi
instead of being in prison.
We are two workers,
Kamaev and Rodchenkov,
with a mission in mind...
This is not a mission.
This is a revolution.
- This is an anti-WADA strategy.
- Of course! Of course!
The former head of Russia's
anti-doping agency RUSADA
has unexpectedly died.
Nikita Kamaev's death comes just
two months after he resigned his post,
which is, obviously, following
the doping scandal that has rocked Russia
and the rest of the world in athletics.
No, no, no.
I have to see.
We're told by RUSADA,
which is the doping agency
he was formerly the head of,
that he appears to have had
a massive heart attack.
Of course.
Bryan?
I'm here.
You know, my friend?
My friend...
died.
I show you.
He's got no previous history
of heart problems.
It means, "Grigory, Nikita died."
He just died.
And so, it's an enormous shock.
He's my friend
since school time,
and he never complained about his heart
or any health problem, and...
He had a young wife.
They dreamed about children.
I was talking to him day before.
This is...
Still, I cannot understand.
It cannot be like this.
He wrote book.
It's dangerous to write book in Russia.
I don't know.
We gotta figure this out, because...
Of course, of course.
Do you think that they would...
Bryan, we are playing the most danger game
in the history of sport.
WADA, ready to pay everything
for me and for you to disappear.
Because we destroy not only their future,
we destroy their past.
You know, there is very bad man
still not mentioned.
Deputy Minister Mutko.
He could kill everybody.
He's a KGB man.
He's very dangerous.
He has no moral at all. No, no.
"Oh, Nikita is writing book?
Fifty-two. Oh, he's tired.
He's desperate.
Oh, please, prepare obituary
for the next week."
Can you imagine? I can imagine easily.
We should be very much careful.
Who were you reporting to?
Yuri Nagornykh, vice minister.
He was practically involved
in everyday routine.
- So you would report to Yuri?
- Yes.
- Yuri would report to Mutko?
- And Mutko reported to Putin?
- To Putin, yes.
You know, there is no rest
if you are paranoid.
It was around 12:30,
one o'clock at night?
Or two. I don't know.
They were just hanging around, so...
- Somebody in the courtyard?
- Yes.
Two strong men knocked my door
and appeared from darkness.
They asked me to let them in,
and they came here.
And we were talking about sport,
about many relevant or auxiliary things.
They knew about death of Nikita Kamaev.
About, first of all,
my boss, Minister Mutko.
It was inspection and...
Exhausts my nerves...
They finally gave me subpoena.
United States district court.
You see, it's for me.
"To Grigory Rodchenkov."
You're commanded to appear
in front of the grand jury.
He had been approached
by two FBI agents.
They want him to go to New York
and appear in a grand jury
and provide his information.
It triggered a whole series of decisions
that had to be made.
I've checked out these two guys,
and both of these guys
are not your everyday agent.
But why did they come to him?
They want him for something else
that they're doing.
They didn't come to him for himself.
They're trying to make a case,
and they found out he was in LA.
His boss, Mutko, was actually the guy.
How was he able to survive?
Because he's Putin's best friend.
He's the head of the sports ministry.
Just what sort of, uh... crime...
like, example, I could be done against
or under US legislature?
The United States Justice Department loves
to charge broad conspiracies.
That's their favorite charging instrument.
That you conspired
with Mutko and others to...
What is the conspiracy?
It was conspiracy since 1980.
Let's reconsider Moscow Olympic Games,
and then reconsider situation
in United States in 1984.
That's right.
They're looking for him to plea
to what's called a cooperation agreement.
What happens is, he cooperates,
and at the end of the day,
the judge generally
wouldn't incarcerate him, most likely.
First of all,
we don't know whether that's...
what the bureau's interested in
at this point.
If we turn down,
they could indict him.
- You gotta be shitting me.
- We can talk to these guys.
The most important thing
is he is not sent back to Russia,
where he would certainly be assassinated.
We've been discussing with Grigory
whether or not he should go public
in some way
prior to the Olympics.
Prior to the Olympics.
What you're saying is
if he's established
as a cooperating witness,
he may not be able to do that.
That's right. That's right.
Which is a downside.
But once Grigory's public,
I think he's in much less danger.
Because if the Russians do anything
to hurt him,
it makes them look very guilty.
Except they'll just say
he had a heart attack, like they did...
Grigory, look at me.
Is it in your best interest
to break the story?
Uh...
You mean to disclose? We have to disclose.
Please enter
your participant ID. Thank you.
I strongly suggest
they stay only with list of 36 athletes.
Okay.
But they're about to publish.
They're asking us how they can verify
the authenticity of the Sochi list.
Yes, this is most important.
It's authentic document.
It was in Sochi on my table.
And if you go behind this list,
there is creation date.
And this list came
from the ministry?
Of course, of course.
So, Rebecca, you have the file.
So under properties of the file,
you can see it was created
Tuesday, January 21st, from the ministry.
Oh, my God! You're unrecognizable!
Not recognizable at all.
Psychological, looking in mirror,
it's not me.
The New York Times is breaking tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?
- Tomorrow.
Oh, I need... I need...
Intravenous injections
- to relax. Tomorrow?
- Tomorrow.
- Why not?
- Okay, so here's what's happening.
Have you spoke
to the Department of Justice yet?
I told them,
and they reacted
like I expected they would.
They're upset.
- Right.
- So...
They wanted to know,
did he provide any documents to them?
He provided lists
of doped athletes.
He provided an FSB file
of how the testing was arranged at Sochi.
Yeah, unfortunately,
they're gonna terminate the whole...
Now that he turned over documents,
they're gonna cancel.
And they're just gonna prosecute him.
"It's time for you
to enter upon the second stage."
The International Olympic Committee
has the honor of announcing
that the 22nd Olympic Winter Games in 2014
are awarded to the city of Sochi.
That's future for everything.
That's future for my country! For Russia!
Millions of citizens of Russia are united
by the Olympic dream.
Our national pledge to you is,
the choice of Sochi is the best choice.
There is a top-level decision.
You know who I mean.
And big boss, Vladimir Putin, saying,
"We have to show the best result in Sochi.
We must show the others who we are."
- Hurrah!
Hurrah!
We could make team clean
before Sochi. One month.
But it was decided
to use PEDs during Sochi.
Through the competition
so they could be at their very top level?
Right, right.
Vladimir Putin.
So instead of using the science,
the science that you developed
to get around the system,
you abandoned the science?
Yes.
The most important "yes."
Forget about this.
Ladies and gentlemen,
let me declare the 126th session
of the International Olympic Committee
open.
Thank you.
Opening ceremony was
the most heartbreaking day...
in sports history.
- Hi, Bryan.
- The story just broke.
What do you mean?
Is it published or not?
Yes, published.
Published! The story is published!
According
to The New York Times, Rodchenkov...
Okay.
This is the photo of bottles.
Those bottles were given
from Nikita Kamaev.
"Grigory Rodchenkov,
who ran the laboratory
that handled testing
for thousands of Olympians,
said he developed a three-drug cocktail
of banned substances
that he mixed with liquor and provided
to dozens of Russian athletes,
helping to facilitate
one of the most elaborate
and successful doping ploys
in sport history."
Join and support
our fight for fair play.
The athletes deserve it.
And to you, my fellow Olympic athletes,
I say, respect the rules,
play fair, be clean.
In 2014, in Sochi,
did Russia swap out dirty urine
for clean urine?
Always.
The information contained
in this little bottle
helps keep sport
on the level playing field.
That's why we created ADAMS,
the free Anti-Doping Administration
and Management System from WADA.
All operating under a level of security
typically used by financial institutions.
In effect,
becoming the centralized clearing house
for all anti-doping information.
ADAMS. Everyone should play true.
Walk us through
the collection process.
The sample is provided
in front of a doping control officer.
It's in this container.
It's divided into two.
The A sample and the B sample.
These are the...
- Bottles.
- They're called the Bereg-Kits?
Yes. It's one particular company
in Switzerland that makes them.
It's called
the Berlinger bottle,
and the Berlinger bottle is
state of the art.
It's sealed very tight
with a vice-like device.
A collector is right there, watching.
And then it goes to the lab.
It's in the lab that the B bottles are
pulled aside and put in the freezer.
The analytical work is done
on the A sample.
The way we collect the sample,
the trustability of the sample,
the fact that we've got
an A and a B sample
is a very, very, uh, safe system.
The caps on the bottles,
they're designed in such a way that
they need to be destroyed to be taken off.
In the lab, they have a device
that cracks open the A sample.
It's the only way you can get it off.
If an A sample tests positive,
then the B gets analyzed.
The B has to confirm the A.
That's this enormous protection.
From Nagornykh,
in preparation to Sochi,
it was strict order to develop procedure
how we can have new bottles,
new caps or open cap.
And this FSB officer,
he was responsible for the day
when I gave closed Bereg-Kit,
and after half an hour,
I receive it opened.
And the...
cap and the bottle are the same.
And I can...
A little bit rinse
and then pour and close.
Like Bereg-Kit.
It's unbelievable how they could do this.
This was named Operation Sochi Resultat.
In Russian, "Resultat" means
"to achieve positive results."
So, you need clean urines?
I need clean urines
for each candidate.
For every single Russian athlete
under the state-sponsored doping,
you had clean samples
of their urine being held?
Yes.
If an athlete needed
to be swapped, you could swap 'em.
Yes.
But in Sochi, because of the Olympics,
I am under double control.
Both from IOC, WADA and I don't know who.
Level of security is stunning.
It's unbelievable.
There was a delegation
of foreign scientists
who were embedded in the laboratory.
So, if there were substitutions,
manipulations,
these people would've been
in the front line to observe this.
In Sochi, laboratory was like this.
It was our entrance,
but from this behind,
where we have a fire exit,
there is another building.
It was a KGB building.
And bank of clean urines were kept here.
Coming into the final two heats
of the four-man bobsleigh,
Pilot Alexander Zubkov
and brakeman Alexey Voevoda...
Gold to Russia,
making their pilot the oldest man ever
to win the four-man bobsleigh.
So how many FSB officers
were working at Sochi?
Hundred.
Throughout the day, our KGB officer
brought the clean urines
of all our athletes selected for testing
to our secret operational room
in the laboratory.
Meanwhile, all the urines collected
from the athletes during the day
were transported to the Olympic village
and held until 1:00 or 2:00 a.m.
Then I received a call.
"Grigory, I will be delivering the samples
in 15 minutes."
Before samples arrived,
it gave me time to make sure
that there were no WADA or IOC observers
left snooping around the laboratory.
Once samples were checked in,
the operation entered
the most dangerous phase.
When the A and B bottles
were split on to two different carts,
my assistant wheeled the B bottles
into a storage room
and slipped the Russian athletes'
B bottles into his lab coat.
This is highly illegal,
but we need to replace these dirty urines.
Then he wheeled the cart
with the A bottles
into the aliquoting room,
as per procedure.
'Cause it's supposed to be opened.
For all A samples, yes.
To escape all the video recording,
aliquoting room was like this.
And our room, we had the hole in it.
So we take this little bit...
- How you say this thing? It's...
- Uh...
Like this, if you have something...
You take this table out,
and there is a... like a...
like a power outlet blocked
without any, uh... socket.
- Okay, right, right.
- But then you take it out.
So it looks like it's a power outlet
without a socket, but it's not.
- It's not. It's a hole.
- It's a hole.
You're taking both samples
through this hole,
and A samples, we immediately...
pour away and clean.
But the B sample...
B samples are taken
by KGB and... whew!
In the darkness,
people coming from the trash/fire exit.
Then, after two hours, they came back
with B bottles opened to swap.
Because, of course,
you have in advance clean urine.
So, B samples are finished
with the urine swapping.
Taken by KGB and...
Because the B samples are taken
by the IOC and held in long-term storage.
Yes.
If WADA or the IOC retest
those samples, would they be clean?
Reanalysis will return negative.
Because, you know,
we are top-level cheaters.
To over-cheat us,
you should be much such experienced.
But how it comes, such experience?
If there were
evidence brought forward
that showed that a country or WADA lab
had found a way
to break into the collection bottles,
what do you think that would say
about the entire testing system?
What it would say is that corruption
has gone to the depths of...
that part of the process,
which would be most disturbing.
It would be, uh...
obviously a very serious, serious act
of manipulation from that lab.
It would be done. It wouldn't work.
If that can be done successfully,
then the testing system is over.
Does WADA have the ability
to catch drug cheats today?
No.
Because of this whole steroid program,
I pulled off 13 gold medals.
It's unbelievable.
Never before.
Everything was made clean,
and Putin was very much happy.
Russia came out on top
of the medals board,
winning 33 overall,
including an Olympic high of 13 gold.
But immediately after,
he started war against Ukraine.
Before the Olympics,
his popularity rating in Russia
had been falling steadily for years.
But when the games began, this.
I felt my personal guilt
for such event.
Would Russia had less medals,
Putin would be not such aggressive.
What you're about to hear
is not lifted from a Tom Clancy novel,
nor is it borrowed from
the elegant prose of John Le Carré
or adapted from Robert Ludlum's work.
But if the protagonist is to be believed,
this drama is the ultimate handiwork
of Vladimir Putin
and the intelligence successors
to the KGB.
LA may be a lot safer than Mother Russia,
given the recent...
- Bryan!
- Yeah?
Article is incredible. It's so very good.
I am shocked. I'm reading twice.
You know, Russia even cannot breathe.
They still even don't respond.
- Of course, there it is, midnight, but...
- Let me stop you.
- I just spoke to our lawyer.
- What happened?
They're not returning any
of his calls.
I am arrested?
We don't know yet.
We're in a holding pattern.
I am sitting locked in my home.
I'm a little bit afraid.
Let me get this done,
and I'll come by, okay?
Putin will kill me.
- Rodchenkov...
- allegations...
Dozens of Sochi medal winners
were part of a secret...
Nine, one, seven.
Okay.
He has since fled Russia
because he said he feared for his life.
Russia's sports minister
has dismissed the claims as nonsense,
adding they were a continuation
of the attack on Russian sport,
which was backed up
by the deputy sports minister.
So that this is clear
for everyone...
there has never been
and there is not any doping program.
Vladimir Putin calls
the claims "the slander of a turncoat."
We're meeting
with a white-collar attorney
who has handled a lot of criminal cases.
What happened
with his other lawyer?
His other lawyer,
they have a Moscow office.
It appears that the firm got cold feet due
to a conflict of interest, they said.
Thomas Bach,
who heads the IOC, said,
"If this is true,
it is an unimaginable level
of criminality."
The IOC
calling the report "very worrying."
"We ask
the World Anti-Doping Agency
to investigate immediately."
The Justice Department
is opening an investigation
into Russian government officials,
athletes, coaches
and anti-doping authorities.
This letter was sent by WADA.
"Dear Grigory, in light of your recent
declarations to The New York Times,
we would like to meet to better understand
the basis of your allegations
and your proposed way forward.
Sincerely, David Howman
and Olivier Niggli."
I'm talking tomorrow to another lawyer.
So...
He seems credible, but of course,
it's his word against Russia.
There were older questions
regarding Rodchenkov's mental health
in all this,
as four years ago,
after a failed suicide attempt,
he was placed into a mental institution,
the diagnosis described
as the first stages of schizophrenia.
What to do with my wife
and children? What they will know?
Or I just disappear for them?
They'll go crazy.
Bryan, this is David and Olivier.
We want this meeting to go ahead.
Can you call us back?
I'm not ready to answer.
We need something lucky,
like it's Alice in Wonderland,
to rabbit's hole, to sit here.
- I know.
- To wait until it ends.
I know. That's why I wanna...
We're trying to get this...
To make it right.
But lawyer is trustful?
- He is a big one.
- He's a big one.
- Yeah, top of the top of the top.
- Yes.
We are digging deeper into his identity.
We've obtained
some of his exclusive documents.
Grigory Rodchenkov
and American movie director Bryan Fogel,
they talked many times
via e-mail and wrote...
The FBI are following him closely,
Grigory Rodchenkov himself mentioned
to his sister in a recent Skype call.
Grish,
just sit tight. Don't be too impulsive.
No, of course
I will not do anything...
Of course. Absolutely.
Without the protection
of the FBI.
I refuse to make any
comments on this. I'm very sorry.
I'm sure you have very intelligent people
who can explain all this.
Honey, I already
spoke to the children. They're fine.
Grisha,
now it's another problem.
I'm worried about you.
I'll take care of this.
Just hold on.
This is what I'm worried about.
They're turning us into the monster now.
Or trying to.
It's okay.
We'll get through this.
What do you want
to come of all this?
"To the future or to the past,
to a time when thought is free...
when truth exists
and what is done cannot be undone."
What everyone
is interested in is the evidence he has,
both in terms of the documents
on his computer
and the cell phone
that he was using at the time.
Two people connected
with the Russian doping program are dead
under circumstances
that seem highly suspect.
One of the first things
that I learned from authorities
when I came onto the case
was that the Russian government
has the resources and the will.
So we've had to develop
a very multi-stage protocol
to minimize the chances our conversations
will be intercepted.
The main concern
is that they would be able,
through those communications,
to try to triangulate his location,
and if they have agents
in the United States, then to do him harm.
We're 84 days away
till the Summer Games
in Rio de Janeiro in Brazil.
Until now, there's
only been hard evidence about athletics,
but this is pointing the finger
at a whole range of sports.
As you know, there's a Department
of Justice investigation going.
Grigory's been advised by his lawyer
he should not be here
for security reasons.
I worked with Grigory
over about six months
to compile a record
of what happened in Russia.
This is the spreadsheet
of every single athlete
that was on the state-mandated protocol.
What every single athlete was taking
in London,
including their sample numbers
and collection.
When Christiane goes back
and tests these samples correctly,
she will basically find them all positive.
And we have all their protocols
before the London Games.
We have the same for Beijing.
And this outlines
how Russia was collecting
thousands and thousands
of clean samples for swapping.
No, no, this we saw,
but we want to ask question
as well as how it was done,
understanding...
So, sodium chloride is added to the sample
to increase specific gravity.
Many of these samples are gonna have
a hundred times the sodium content
that should be in somebody's urine.
Let me make sure I understand.
They were taking the B
to be opened secretly?
Yes.
You said it was removed
after the Paralympic Games.
Does it mean that it happened
also for the Paralympic Games?
Yes, yes.
Both the Olympic and the Paralympic Games,
they swapped urine.
Vancouver was really the impetus
for the urine swapping operation.
They only won a handful of medals,
and to see to it that
that didn't happen again at Sochi.
We'll find that out when...
In terms of time-sensitive,
London is more sensitive,
in the sense that
these athletes are going
to the next Rio Games,
not the winter ones.
This is Sochi. This is London.
This is Beijing.
This goes all the way back to 1968.
There never was anti-doping in Russia.
Period. Ever.
Across all summer sports?
Every sport.
He's sorry?
- Who's that?
- Grigory.
I don't want to get into that.
Do you think, as a scientist,
I am happy to have been in Sochi?
And to everything...
We gave credibility to the lab.
Do you think that I feel good today?
Do you think that the athletes
who were cheated feel good?
As angry as you guys might be,
I think the one thing...
Grigory risked his life,
and is risking his life, to do this.
He left his wife behind,
he left his children behind,
he left all of his belongings behind,
all of his financial security behind.
We're here to get everything out.
Okay.
"Dear Mr. Fogel
and Dr. Rodchenkov,
the IOC has full confidence
in the authority
of Professor Richard McLaren
and respects his judgment
to ensure a comprehensive inquiry.
We will act swiftly
to take the necessary measures.
Sincerely yours, Thomas Bach. President."
Transferring you to Richard McLaren.
You speak of them as being
orders. Are they actually orders?
Nagornykh is ordering Grigory?
Or ordering the lab?
Does it matter?
Yes, Nagornykh is ordering Grigory.
There's e-mails, like,
explicitly about soccer players.
There's e-mails explicitly of,
you know, of weightlifters.
And that essentially were...
Of rowers, of swimmers...
where Grigory had found the positive.
Then if they are
concerned about it,
they find the right profile in the bank,
and pick that one out of the bank,
and they run the analysis on that one?
You got it.
I see.
If this all can be proved,
it's quite mind-blowing.
- The sooner I have it, the better.
- Okay.
It's important
to a lot of people around the world.
- We do it now?
- Yes.
Russian athletes could not credibly
return to international competition
without undermining the confidence
of their competitors and the public.
They are the pride and joy
of Russian sport.
But track and field stars,
like pole-vaulter Yelena Isinbayeva,
won't be going for gold
at next month's Rio Olympics,
despite having friends in high places.
This is truly important to us, because...
Today, our track and field team
finds itself in a dire situation.
We have been banned from the Olympics
very aggressively,
without any evidence or proof.
Rodchenkov,
director of the Moscow WADA lab,
was forced to resign from his position
even though, when you think about it,
he was a brilliant doctor.
So he's fired, and then somehow
ends up in the United States,
where he subsequently took his story
to The New York Times.
Not exactly the smallest paper on Earth.
He gets there,
he turns over all this information.
Finally, he stated
that the entire doping program
was in fact part of a state-run system.
Whatever he claims,
he is confusing himself
with the government.
You see, all of his claims against
the government, he did himself.
It was a solo act.
So the swapping,
the destruction of samples,
this was all just a farce?
Again, I just don't see
how this is possible. How could it be?
Please let me repeat,
these allegations are not facts,
just rumors and speculations.
Welcome
to the McLaren Independent Commission
news conference here in Toronto.
In May, Professor McLaren was mandated
by the World Anti-Doping Agency
with respect to the allegations made
by the former director
of the WADA-accredited Moscow laboratory,
Dr. Grigory Rodchenkov.
The investigation has established
the findings set out in the report
beyond a reasonable doubt.
Our experts were to determine
if samples had scratches and marks
on the inside of the bottle caps,
representative of a tool used
to open the cap.
Of the set of samples suspected
of being swapped...
we were able to confirm...
100% had evidence of tampering.
We've conducted cyber
and forensic analysis,
secured data from hard drives,
and reviewed thousands of pages
of documents.
The Moscow laboratory operated for
the protection of doped Russian athletes
within a state-directed, fail-safe system.
Ministry of Sport,
Deputy Minister of Sport Yuri Nagornykh,
RUSADA, that's the anti-doping agency
in Russia,
and the former director
of the Moscow testing laboratory
were all involved in this operation
with the active participation
and assistance
of the Russian Federal Security Service,
formerly known as the KGB.
The FSB, who had access to the Sochi lab
under the guise
of the building maintenance contractor,
can be identified in the evidence we have.
Alex Mihailovich, RT.
Rodchenkov himself is a person who's
under investigation in Russia currently.
He took off from Russia.
He seems to be a character
that you really can't rely on,
and a lot of this relies on Rodchenkov.
Does this compromise your work?
He is a person in this investigation,
but not the only person
in this investigation.
I can say without a doubt,
Dr. Rodchenkov is telling the truth
and was a truthful witness.
I was able to corroborate that
because of all the scientific
and forensic information.
My team can demonstrate the existence
of this system beyond a reasonable doubt.
It was clear
from Richard McLaren's report
that was contained
in our independent commission,
it's proven that offenses were committed.
So, I don't think anybody can accuse us
of sitting back and doing nothing.
President Putin condemned the findings,
saying the world is seeing
a dangerous recurrence
of politics interfering in sport.
Russia's government says
any decision which collectively punishes
its competitors is unacceptable.
Richard Conway, BBC News.
I'm gonna be rolling your hands
like that.
Let me do all of the work.
It makes it easier for everybody.
What were you all doing today?
We were worrying all day.
But today,
I was paying for everything, bills, etc.
Nika, we will get through this.
Oh, you have new glasses!
Not that new.
I have some sad news to tell you.
Yes?
I am going
into the witness protection program.
- You are?
- Mm-hmm.
Why?
Because the current situation is unclear.
- So, this is serious?
- Yes.
For a while?
I was thinking of you yesterday.
Well, visa is just one thing, but...
You are my bride
and keeper of the family and the dogs.
Grigory, I was worrying all day,
and on top of that, trying to reach you.
Don't tell anyone anything.
Who would I even tell?
I don't see much of anyone these days.
Maybe they'll pay off some officials
to sit in prison for some time?
As a formality.
I have to get going.
- Veronika?
- Yes?
You wrote down the lawyer's contact
information and have everything?
You know what I'm talking about?
Of course I understand.
It's just... This is all so sad.
Whatever packing
you need to do and getting dressed...
Okay. Okay.
So, do we know
what, uh, you're gonna be able to...
I still don't know
how it will be organized.
"Protection" means protection
that you don't know how it's organized.
What do you foresee at this point?
I will start writing book.
Oh, we are on the first floor.
Where is the exit?
I wonder when I'm going to see you again.
Don't worry. I'll be back.
Bryan,
you are medium-sized monster!
Remember me.
We have decided today
that Russian athletes can compete in Rio.
The International Sports
Federations
will carry out individual analysis,
taking into account...
Anti-doping officials are fuming.
The IOC going against the World
Anti-Doping Agency recommendations...
Olympic champion.
Vlasov had won gold again.
"Winston sank his arms
to his sides
and slowly refilled his lungs with air.
His mind slid away into
the labyrinthine world of doublethink.
To know and not to know,
to be conscious of complete truthfulness
while telling carefully constructed lies."
Thomas Bach.
"To repudiate morality
while laying claim to it.
To forget whatever
it was necessary to forget..."
Join and support
our fight for fair play.
Respect the rules, play fair, be clean.
"Then to draw it back
into memory again
at the moment when it was needed..."
This decision is about justice.
Justice has to be independent
from politics.
Hurrah!
"And then promptly
to forget it again."
Fails a drug test,
is stripped of the gold medal...
"and above all, to apply
the same process to the process itself."
Trying to make sure
your testimony's clear.
How many times do I have to say it?
I've never taken drugs. How clear is that?
Okay. I think it's clear.
"And if all others
accepted the lie,
then the lie passed into history
and became truth."
We've never had
a doping program in Russia.
This is just impossible, unthinkable.
We would never do something like that.
I don't even recall the name
of that citizen who defected,
the one who ran
the Russian anti-doping lab.
"Even to understand the word 'doublethink'
involves the use of doublethink."
We are now able to put
the findings of the first report
into sharper and clearer focus.
I can confirm, for years,
that spectators have been deceived.
The desire to win medals
superseded their collective moral
and ethical compass, and Olympic values...
I was doing
in parallel two things
which canceled out each other
in being fully contradictory.
Doping and anti-doping.
It was pure, exact doublethink.
I was like a slave.
Slavery was my freedom...
till the end.
So...
truth.