Saroo.
Saroo!
Come on, come on!
Get up!
Come on, quickly!
Hold it properly, Saroo, catch!
Get down!
Guddu! The guards!
Hey, boy, get down!
Go! Get down, boy!
Saroo
I'm here!
We will get a lot of money today
We've got a lot of coal!
Show me!
Ohhh, so much!
You kept telling me how little I am
but see how clever I am?
That's right, you are!
You jumped from so high!
What a leap!
Yes, great heights!
Give them some milk, two packets
Guddu, I want some jalebis!
One day I will buy you some jalebis
We'll buy the whole shop!
Ha, alright
- Which way should I go now?
- Left, left!
- Which way now?
- Right, right
Do you want to drink some milk?
I got some milk!
It's magic
Tell me now
how did you get the milk?
Be honest
Guddu? My Saroo?
No
Okay, Shekila, I have to work now
Who's going to look after Shekila?
My Saroo?
Come, eat
Sleep... sleep
How long will you be away for?
You did a really good job today
I want to come too
- How many days?
- I'm going for a week
- Who's going to look after Shekila?
- Kallu will be here
- You're too small to lift bales
- I can lift anything
Guddu!
Can I come too?
You're too small, you can't do this
I can lift anything
Saroo, I've told you
it's night work, not for kids
Go, go, you're too small
Saroo, leave it
I can lift this
Okay, fine
Hey, Guddu!
Hey! How are you, Shankar?
- Saroo, come on, wake up now!
- I want to sleep
- Saroo, wake up!
- Saroo
- I want to sleep
- Saroo, wake up
- Don't annoy me, I am sleeping
It's my fault, I brought you here
You're too young for the night work
It's so late
you will never be able to work
Saroo, Saroo...
Saroo, I'm going
to find out about work, okay?
And then I'll come back
You wait here, don't go anywhere
Guddu?
Guddu!
Just bring back a hundred jalebis
You want jalebis?
- Bring me two thousand jalebis!
- Jalebis?
Just wait there, don't go anywhere
Guddu?
Guddu!
Help me!
Guddu! Guddu!
Someone save me!
Help me!
Help!
Guddu!
Mum, I love you very much
Guddu, I miss you very much
The train on platform two
is a decommissioned train
It is not taking passengers
Save me!
Someone help me!
Get me out of here!
Save me...
Get me out of here! Save me!
Save me! Save me!
Open!
Guddu!
Mum!
Ganestalay?
I want to go home, Ganestalay
Ganestalay? I want to go home
I don't understand! Speak Bengali!
I don't understand you
Move! What's the matter?
You don't understand Bengali?
Ganestalay?
Don't walk on that
you're going to fall off
- Do you understand Hindi?
- Yes
- Where are you going?
- I have to go home, I am lost
- Did you come from this way or that w
- I don't know which way
Then how will you go?
- What's your name?
- Saroo
My name is Noor
You're hungry?
Come on
Come inside, come on!
Come on!
I have to do all this
make lunch boxes for all the men
you have to feed your stomach, you kno
Everybody has to work
I help my mum to carry rocks
Your mum carries rocks?
What is this?
Just drink
Leave some for me!
And now a bit of soap
There is a man and he is called Rama
he's a very good man
He helps everyone
he will help you too
He's coming tomorrow morning
Is he going to help me
look for my mum?
He's going to help you
look for your mum
Close your eyes go to sleep
Sleep
Oh, my baby
Were you sleeping?
I wonder what worlds you've travelled
- Are you Rama?
- Yes, but not the God
Come and lie down
Come closer
Do you know? I've come
to meet you from really far away
and I want to take you
to a really nice place
Are you going to take me to Mum?
And from there we're going to try
and look for your mum
I'll be back tonight
and then we'll search
Get up!
Come closer
Say "thank you"
Thank you.
Thank you
You've done well
He's exactly what they're
looking for come closer
What happened? You didn't drink?
You don't like it?
Why are you down?
Drink this
Come closer..
Saroo
Saroo!
Good boy!
Go pick up the small ones
Good boy
Good boy! Good boy!
Good boy!
Who's my good boy? Who is it?
I'm sorry, Mum
So I came out of the cafe
and started talking to him
I realized he doesn't speak
a word of Bengali
He only speaks Hindi
I asked him where he was from?
He replied with only
one word "Ganestalay"
I've never heard of it
Ganestalay
Okay, which district
is Ganestalay in?
Which district is Ganestalay in?
- What is your mother's name?
- Mum
LOST
- What's your name?
- Amita
This is a very bad place
Does anybody ever leave here?
I've seen it
- What are you going to do once you le
- I'm going to buy a watch
Did you write it?
Hey, Shonedeep!
What are you doing?
Stop!
- Stop! Stop right now!
- Shonedeep!
Why are you being so naughty?
Shonedeep!
Come with me, I'm going
to give you a good beating!
You won't get away with this!
Hey! Shonedeep! Come on, come on!
Shonedeep! Come on!
Look this way, look this way
It's me, it's okay, I'll take him
Bring him back before morning
All the stars came out
in search of the moon
The ill-fated came out
on the streets
The stars came out
in search of the moon
They came out in search of the thief
The stars came out
Yes, Saroo, my name
is Mrs. Sood, come sit here
It's my job to make sure that
there isn't a single kid here
who should be somewhere else
That's why I'm here
People don't like me here
Look at this
We have been asking around
about you for a long time
We have published it
in the newspaper
In all the newspapers in Calcutta
15 million people read this paper
that's a lot of people
But we haven't
had a single reply
My home is really far
Not one reply
- What about Mum?
- No
not even Mum
Guddu?
Saroo...
We have found a family over in Austral
who want to look after you
Do you know where Australia is?
Would you like to see them?
Come, I'll show you
Come sit here
Look, look at this, this is John
and this is Sue
This...
This is their home
They live in Tasmania
A small island
and everyone there is really nice
They are such nice people!
Aren't they?
Keep this with you
and keep it safe, ok?
Saroo...
Son, you can't stay here
Did you really look for my mum?
Looked everywhere
You'll have a nice home
Australia is a great place
Does everybody have a napkin?
- This is called a "serviette"
- Serviette
Lay it down on your lap like this
so that food doesn't fall on your clot
So it doesn't ruin them
I'm going to teach you how
to eat using cutlery
I will ask you, and you will tell me
in English what each thing is called
What do you call this?
Fork.
Fork. Yes good.
- What do you call this?
- Nice
Knife.
Good.
And this?
Spoon.
Okay, Manisha
you tell me, what is this?
Try to remember
Salt.
Very good.
Payper!
- Pepper.
Okay, okay.
HOBART, AUSTRALIA
Thank you.
Saroo.
This is your mum and dad
Say hello
Hello, I'm Swarmina.
Oh hello. I'm John, this is Sue.
Hello there.
Hello. Here this is for you.
Good on the plane?
Eh, good?
Sue...
- This is...
- Mummy and...
Dad.
And we're so happy to meet you.
A boat.
Amazing.
Gently... gently...
This is where you live.
Down there, that's the living room.
Television.
Do you know what a television is?
Pictures.
Water.
You can open it.
Do you want me to cut it up for him?
Payper!
What was it?
Yes, pepper.
That's right and...
Sauce!
Sauce?
- Salt.
Very good.
Hi.
So, you've come a long way,
haven't you? Hmm?
Little one.
I'm sure it hasn't been easy.
One day you will tell me all about it.
You'll tell me everything.
Who you are, everything.
I'll always listen.
Always.
Stay, yeah yeah...
Yeah, that's... that's it.
- Go easy on me, yeah?
- Yeah.
Okay mate.
- Mum... Daddy...
- Pay attention.
Here he comes! Come on mate!
She's out!
Oh my gosh!
How did you do this to me?
All right.
Dad, mum, Saroo...
Mantosh.
Yes.
Yeah.
Hello again!
Aw, Saroo, my goodness, look at you!
Hi.
Oh my gosh, we've been so excited!
This is Mantosh.
Hi.
Hey Man...
This is Saroo. I'm Sue...
This is Saroo, your brother.
- And John...
- Hello mate!
Show, show Mantosh what you've done.
He did a picture, Yeah...
- It's been a long flight?
- Yes, Yes, Yes.
You must be hungry.
We're going to get something to eat.
Would you... like to join us?
Oh alright, Ok that would be nice.
Stop, stop, stop, stop...
No no no, It's alright.
I know it's Okay.
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it! Stop!
- Come on...
- I know I know...
- No no no.
- Hey mate.
- It's okay, Man...
- Just play with your toys.
No, no, no, don't hit mate.
Don't hit yourself. No no no..
Not your head.. Not your head.
- Come on
- You're right, you're right...
It's okay.
Come on, it's okay Man.
Look, there's a boat.
It's better now.
I'm okay.
Hey!
I'm all right.
This one.
- We're gonna miss you.
- Yeah.
It's only Melbourne.
Who is across the water?
Saroo...
Our beautiful boy!
May this bring you
all that you could wish for.
Yeah, and then some.
Thanks mum. Thanks dad.
From the moment you
came into our lives...
- Mum...
- No no no, let me finish.
From the moment you
came into our lives...
You were all that
we could have hoped for.
More, more than we hoped for, really.
And, er, more work, that's for sure.
You really embraced every opportunity.
We're very proud of you, son.
Very proud and very excited with this
next chapter in your life.
- To success!
- Excuse me guys?
Are you still waiting on someone?
Or can I take this plate away?
- Yeah, you can take it away.
- No no no, you can leave it.
No, take it.
I'd like to keep it.
Thank you.
You don't really think
he will turn up, do you?
No, just leave it, son.
That's a nice one.
- Yeah it's a good one.
- This one's a local one.
Mantosh?
Yeah...
Sorry, I didn't meet lunch.
What's that course again?
Hotel Management.
So you're going when to do what?
Manage a hotel!
Well... have fun!
Any bills you need to pay?
You can give us a job
when you come back.
Please could you not do
anything while I'm away?
Yeah Yeah...
that's going to make mum
more unhappy than you already do.
Mate...
Why do you think I stay away?
We see ourselves as United Nations
of hospitality schools.
And we'd like to think we teach
a global and balanced perspective.
You're here because
you have a dream.
We're here to help make
that dream a reality.
Yeah and I saw firsthand how
the hospitality industry
can really bring infrastructure to
communities that need it.
But I also saw a lot of problems
that they cause,
which is why community groups need to
be, involved every step of the way,
and they need to be taken seriously.
And?
I guess I want to help facilitate that
and help give them a voice.
Saroo.
I want to run hotels, so I put
all the profits into my pocket.
Well, let me ask and start with
where you are from? Shall we?
So, born in Australia?
Yeah No, er...
Calcutta.
I've got family in Calcutta.
My cousins are quite...
Which part?
I'm adopted. I'm not really Indian.
But you like cricket though, right?
Ah, you like cricket...
You go for the Aussies or the Indians?
Only the Aussies, mate!
This is going to be interesting.
Okay, Saroo...
Why did you choose this course?
What else do you want to
get out of it?
Hi, Hey!
- Welcome.
- Come in. Come in.
Hi!
Hi, how are you?
Do you guys like Indian food?
That's all we have.
- It smells so great.
- I tried to copy from someone...
You've ever done Bollywood dance?
- Oh, just like, one leg.
- Yeah, one leg...
Where I grew up, I say flashlight.
What do you say?
- Lampo de poche.
- Lampo de poche?
- Flashlight
- Lampo de poche.
- Flashlight is er...(Indian word)
What do you say?
Torch.
If you want to eat with your hands,
you need to use the naan,
like a spoon.
- Use a fork.
- No, let him use the naan.
So how do you say taxi?
- Taxi.
It is the same in every language.
Do you want a fork, Saroo?
Yeah!
He's like my father.
- You want another beer?
- Yes please, thank you.
Guddu, I want some jalebi.
Guddu, jalebis
Hello...
You okay?
Saroo?
I'm not from Calcutta.
I'm lost.
Howrah station is enormous,
you must have been freaking out.
I once went through there
on a pilgrimage to Puri,
and I missed my connection twice.
And you didn't speak Bengali?
I didn't even know it was called that.
- How long were you on the train?
- A couple of days.
A couple of days?
Saroo, what was your hometown again?
Ganestlay.
I must have had it wrong
because it doesn't exist.
But there must be something else
that you do remember.
The platform...
I fell asleep on,
there's a big rain tank.
It was only a few stops
from Ganestlay.
There are thousands of
stations with rain tanks.
Okay, it was a long time ago.
Have you heard of this new
program, Google Earth?
It's incredible, you can find
any place from anywhere.
Listen to me, we can find out how
fast passenger trains went back then.
We take that speed, multiply by
the hours that you were on the train.
That's it!
We create a search radius.
And inside there, you will find
the station with the rain tank.
Yeah, but it will take a lifetime
to search all the stations in India.
Did I say all the stations?
Ok, even half the stations..
Really guys,
I don't want to talk about this.
Did your parents
try to find you?
- What?
- They tried to find him.
No I just mean like,
if they tried to find him,
maybe they left like a paper trail.
What paper trail?
- He didn't know his surname.
- My mum couldn't read or write.
What does she do?
A labourer, she carried rocks.
Your mum?
My mom died about four years ago now.
I'm sorry.
My dad is still so angry at her.
Not for getting sick, obviously...
but just for refusing chemo.
But she just knew herself, you know?
She knew what her terms were
and she knew how
she wanted to live, so...
Just couldn't accept that, I guess.
And how do you feel?
I miss her.
And what do you think of
Bharat's search radius idea?
What was that?
Is that your dance?
Is that how you dance?
Oh, God!
Hey.
You can't keep going on like this.
Let me help you.
Let's go for a run.
What?
Lucy!
Come here.
Hold on.
Got a cramp.
You lied! You cheat.
I never show anybody this.
Okay, they're beautiful.
I do enjoy it.
My little hobby.
- Oh wow, look at Mantosh!
- Uh huh.
I'm so glad he's coming tonight.
Cheeky little thing.
Pure energy.
But incredible.
So sweet!
He's been hard to control, but...
very, very smart... and very...
I mean, he could do anything if he just
learned to control that energy.
He could do it, and do it all.
Saroo is very protective of him.
I've been blessed.
Very blessed.
Your mom showed me
all your old little trophies.
Mum, you didn't.
I didn't know you were so athletic.
That's only half of them.
There's plenty more in the garage.
Hey, where you going, mate?
Finishing my smoke.
I can barely get him off...
the couch these days.
- Lucy!
Why can't you just tell them...
what you've been up to?
- Don't!
Tell us.
They will understand and
they will support you.
What? Come on.
Hey, um, dinner!
Better eat it, while it's hot.
- You hungry?
- Yeah.
What?
What have I missed?
Nothing.
- She looks upset.
- She's not upset!
You and I are leaving.
Saroo knows everything.
- He's an expert.
- Uh oh!
He's a manager.
Why are you here?
He's here because
he's your brother.
No, he's not.
- We're different.
- Hey, now now, Saroo!
Saroo...
All right.
It's all right.
Hey hey, no no...
It's all right, It's all right...
Stop!
Don't move.
It's okay.
Nice one, mate.
It's okay mate, It's okay,
just breathe, mate. Just breathe...
I hate what he's done to you.
I'm sorry.
Saroo!
Saroo.
Hey!
Hey...
Kiss me.
- Stop, please.
- Hey!
Look at me.
Look at me!
- Can this wait?
- Where are you?
Can this wait 'til we get home?
- Yah?
- Home?
What home?
You mean, where I'm alone in one room
and you're alone in another room?
Come on.
Stop, Luce. Stop it.
Please.
Saroo!
You need to face reality!
What do you mean? Reality?
You have any idea what it's like
knowing my real brother...
and mother spend everyday
of their lives looking for me?
How every day my real
brother screams my name!
Can you imagine the pain they
must be in for not knowing where I am?
25 years, Luce.
25!
Why didn't you tell me
that's was happening for you?
And we swung about in our...
privileged lives.
It makes me sick.
I have to find home.
They need to know, okay?
I've never stopped you.
I want to help.
I can't do this anymore.
You deserve more.
Don't you do that!
Don't you dare do that!
This is on you, not on me.
Saroo, you there, mate?
It's One Day International (cricket)
tomorrow. You can come over if you like?
I meant to tell you,
I fixed the tiller.
Why don't we take her out?
We can head up the coast?
Hey, Saroo...
Mate, your mum's not, um,
look, we've lost track of Mantosh,
he's missing again.
You know how worried she gets.
We know you quit your job, mate.
Just worried about you, son.
I've been visiting her.
Every night I walk
those streets home.
Home from the dam.
Home from the station.
I know now...
every single step of the way.
And I imagine that I'm...
whispering in her ear...
I'm here, it's alright.
What was she like?
Beautiful.
How was New York?
It's the same.
So, what brings you back?
My funding came through.
It's great!
See...
They know how good you are.
I miss you.
I saw your mom.
She's not doing very well.
I'm worried, it would kill her
if she knew I was searching.
You underestimate her.
She needs you.
No, give me five rupees
then I'll carry them all
Okay, you win, take this
He was carrying a watermelon
and didn't see it coming
What?
What if you do find home
and they're not even there?
And you never stop and keep searching?
And you don't know what happens over time,
things change, and entire worlds change.
I don't have a choice.
Stay.
I can't.
Stay right there
Weren't you supposed
to look after him?
Where were you?
Don't you love him?
John heard Mantosh
is out on the boats.
Doing a lobster run.
He's due back tomorrow.
So he'll be flushed with cash,
back on the hard stuff.
I'm sorry you couldn't have your own kids.
What are you saying?
We...
weren't blank pages, were we?
Like your own would have been.
You weren't just adopting us
but our past as well.
- I feel like, we're killing you.
- I could have had kids.
What?
We chose not to have kids.
We wanted the two of you.
That's what we wanted.
We wanted the two of you in our lives.
That's what we chose.
That's one of the reasons,
I fell in love with your dad.
Because we both felt, as if...
the world has enough people in it.
Have a child, couldn't guarantee
it will make anything better.
But to take a child that's suffering
like you boys were.
Give you a chance in the world.
That's something.
I bet you never imagined
it being this hard.
It's not a matter of hard.
It's not a mat...
There's only one path for me.
And, that's how I think.
That's how this happened because...
When I was 12,
I had a vision.
Some people would say,
it was a breakdown. But it...
My dad was an alcoholic.
You know that, and he was like
he wasn't a good man.
He was out of control when I was...
I was standing at the back of the house.
I was looking out across this field.
And I just wanted the
earth to swallow me up.
And I...
I felt an electric current,
it was like a shock,
like a jolt through my whole body.
And then I saw...
A brown skinned child
across that field.
And he was standing beside me.
And it was right there and I could
feel it so strongly.
And for the first time in my
life I felt something good...
I felt good.
And I knew it was guiding me.
And I knew that
I was going to be fine.
It was, as if, that moment I could
see my future, right there!
Because I always thought that
I could keep this family together.
And now...
Now I don't know.
Where...
- Mum...
- What's happening? I don't understand.
You don't talk to me any more.
I need you, Saroo.
Mantosh!
Sorry for what I said at dinner.
Ganesh Talai...
Ganesh Talai.
Ganestlay!
Mum
I found home!
What?
Please wait for me.
I'm here.
So this is where you've been.
I don't want you to feel,
I was ungrateful.
There wasn't a day,
I didn't want to tell you.
Saroo.
I really hope she's there.
She needs to see
how beautiful you are!
Hey
Hi, I used to live here.
I... used to...
Can I help?
That's me. I'm Saroo.
I used to live here.
- You lived here?
- Yes I used to live here.
I'm looking for Guddu,
Kallu, Shekila.
My mother.
Come.
Come where?
Come with me.
Just come.
Saroo!
Mum.
Mum?
Saroo?
Saroo...
Saroo!
Oh, how I looked for you!
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Yes, the watermelon.
Watermelon
Tarabuja!
Yes, Tarabuja!
Watermelon...
Guddu?
And Guddu?
Where is Guddu?
Where is he?
Guddu is no more.
He is with God.
Shekila.
- Shekila
Shekila?
- Shekila?
- He's your brother!
She's so big!
It's me, Saroo.
Beautiful.
Hi, mum.
I know you will be sound asleep.
I just want to say that I'm safe.
I'm safe and the questions
have been answered.
There are no more dead-ends.
I found my mother, and...
she thanks you both for raising me.
She understands that
you are my family.
She's... happy,
just knowing I'm alive.
I found her, but that doesn't change
who you are.
I love you mum...
so much.
And you, Dad.
And Mantosh.
C'mon!
Let's go!
Come on!
Saroo!
Let's go!
Walk faster!
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going!