MAN 1: We get the wheels,we get la feria,
we keep moving on.No messing around.
You mess those wheels upthis time, Chong,
I'm gonna have your ass.
Move!
MAN 2: Right there, homes.MAN 3: There's nobody, homes.
MAN 1:Where's your party, boy?
Turn down the radio.
You inviting the cops, too,or what?
MAN 2: I want el cromó.
MAN 1: Gonna get some green
for this shit right here,homes.
(GROANS)
Fuck.
(MEN CONTINUESPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
MAN 1: Hey.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
Uh, guys?
Those are chrome-plated lugs.You're gonna strip them.
MAN 1: Look at this guy, eh?
The plating flakes off.
Yeah?
This is a lease.No one's gonna pay to ride...
(GUNSHOT)
(MAN LAUGHING)
(MEN SPEAKING SPANISH)
(GROANING)
Shit.
MAN 3: Come on, man.
Uh, guys, guys.
MAN 1: What the fuck?
Guys, seriously,you don't wanna do this.
MAN 1: Take him out.
(ALL GRUNTING)
MAN 1: Fuck him up!
(MAN SPEAKING SPANISH)
No! Not the car!
MAN 1: Get that puto!
Fuck him up, man!
Fuck him up!
Get him!
Hit that fool!
(YELLING)
Motherfucker!
(CHOKING)
(YELLS)
(MAN SPEAKING SPANISH)
- (GRUNTS)- (GLASS SHATTERS)
(PANTING)
Shit.
Fuck.
- (BULLETS CLATTERING)- (GRUNTING)
(SPITS)
CLYDE: (ON RADIO)Everyone's asleep, Burt.
Sleepwalking.Between the ice caps,
the pornographers,poisoned water, mutants...
it's all connected.
BURT: Hey, Clyde. It's 2029.
Why are we stilltalking about mutants?
Hey, it's me. I'm in the car.
Yeah, it was a good trip.
Killed it up and downthe fence.
BOYS: (CHANTING)USA! USA! USA!
USA! USA! USA! USA!
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
GABRIELA: Wolverine.
I knew it was you.
- Oh, fuck.- Please!
I'm in trouble!
You're the only onethat could help!
(GABRIELA SPEAKING SPANISH)
Get the fuck away from me!
(GABRIELA CONTINUESSPEAKING SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH) Please!
Logan!
Who was that?
I don't know, some crazy lady.Don't worry.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(COUGHING)
(DOOR OPENING)
As I live and breathe,the Wolverine.
And he's a junkie now.
Who the fuck are you?
You know, you got somebuckshot in your door.
I heard you was in Phoenix.
But then, last night,some friends of mine
in Texas HP called...
and told me they found
three dead cholosin a pullout on 54.
Not unusual, I know.
Except one was missing a hand,another one a leg.
So they was thinking...
it was either an escaped tigeror Freddy Krueger.
But neither one of themcan drive...
one being fictional,the other one extinct.
And since the wheel lugsthey found
belonged to a '24 Chrysler...
and, well...
this is a '24 Chrysler.
She found you yet?
Gabriela?
See...
I'm not looking for you,Wolvie.
Well, not really.I'm looking for someone
who's looking for you.
She took something of minewhen I wasn't looking.
Something for whichI am responsible.
Mexican lady.
Has her sights on you now.
Doesn't ring any bells?
I don't know any Gabriela,so get the fuck out of my car.
Oh.
You know...
I knowwhat you're hiding, amigo.
The old cue ballsouth of the border.
What do you want?
A little co-operation.
I'm a fan, by the way.
Fuck, fuck!
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENTSOVER PA)
LOGAN: No, Mr. Esperanza, no.
I know I said June,but I need the boat now.
Why would that meanthe price go up?
(COUGHS) Listen to me.
I know you wanted 70...
Okay, what if I couldput together
$45,000 cash right now?
Hello? Hello?
Shit.
Hey, Sam.
Morning.
(COUGHS)
CHARLES: "I know that virtueto be in you, Brutus.
"As well as I do knowyour outward favor.
"Well, honor is the subjectof my story."
He's having a bad day.
LOGAN: They're all bad days.
He needed these six hours ago.
This is not enough, you know.
Won't see us through the week.
I'm working on it.
Your turn.
I've had a rough night.
Poor you.
In other news,he told me last night
he's communicatingwith someone.
He's not talking to anybody.
Don't be so sure.
He's got all these details.
I thought that tank wassupposed to act as a barrier.
- It's got them cracks in it.- Just please stop.
Bottom left.
You're not listening.
He's been asking questionsagain about why we're here.
I think he's trying toread my mind.
That's what these are for.
(GROANS)
CHARLES:Eating his curds and whey
Then came a big spiderWhich sat down beside her
And frightened Miss Muffet...
(DOOR OPENING)
(SIGHS)
Friends, I havegood news for you today!
It's not about what you do.
It's not about your deeds.
You can'tlive up to God's rules.
He knows that you can't.It's okay, we're imperfect.
Make way, sir.
I said make way!
The new Quesalupafrom Taco Bell!
Get it with chicken!Get it with steak!
And with the cheese bakedright in the shell...
it's the next big thing!
Go now while supplies last.
Who are you?
You know who I am.
You're the manwho puts me to sleep.
We both could use some sleep.
No! No!
(PANTING)
What are you doing to me?
Charles.
Come on, now.(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(HIGH-PITCHED RINGING)
(GRUNTING WEAKLY)
(WHIMPERING)
(RINGING STOPS)
(BOTH GASPING)
(GASPING)
How long have I been here?
(LOGAN COUGHS)
CHARLES: What are these?
LOGAN:You remember what they are.
The shots mellow the seizures.
The pillskeep them from happening.
How about you blow on themto make them safe?
Fuck off, Logan.
So you remember who I am now.
I always know who you are.
It's just sometimesI don't recognize you.
Take the pills.
You leave me alonewith that fucking albino.
He doesn't listen to me.
I know a damn speciationwhen I see one.
A what?
Speciation.New mutant, a young one.
There are forcestrying to kill them.
- Forces?- They want help.
(GRUNTS) Forces, forces.
It's too bad you're notin that business anymore.
They don't want me,they want you.
(SCOFFS)
Oh, yes, that's howfucking stupid they are.
They're waiting for youat the Statue of Liberty.
The Statue of Libertywas a long time ago,
Charles, a long time.
There are no new mutants.Understand?
Hasn't been a new one bornin 25 years. Not anywhere.
You always thought...
we were part of God's plan.
But maybe...
Maybe we were God's mistake.
What a disappointment you are.
When I found you...
you were pursuing a careeras a cage fighter.
A warm capper to a lifeas an assassin.
Hooked on barbiturates.
You were an animal.
But we took you in.
I gave you a family.
And they're gone now.
Logan.
Logan...
What did you do?
Answer me! Why are we here?
No one should live like this.
Drugged in a fucking tank!
- It's for your own good.- No, it's not!
You're waiting for me to die.
(CROSSING BELLS RINGING)
(GRUNTING)
(TRAIN CLACKING)
(DOOR OPENS)
I don't wanna fight...
but there's thingswe need to discuss.
What things?
Well, would it beconsidered nagging...
if I was to repeatmy previous observation...
that the dose is too lowto suppress the seizures?
It's what the guy gave me.
Wasn't in a positionto make demands.
I almost died this morning.
- That seizure was...- It was barely a minute.
It felt a lot longer thana minute. I couldn't breathe.
You're less affected.
You knowhe needs a higher dose.
And I know you got more moneysquirreled away.
That money'sto get us out of here.
No, not us. You and him.
You're savingto buy a Sunseeker.
"Sun" is the keyword.
I hardly see myself coweringbelow decks like Nosferatu.
Do you?
Folding your underpants,and making him spotted dick.
Found this in your pocket.
(SNIFFS) Adamantium.
If you are planningto blow your brains out...
could you wait till you'reout on the high seas?
- I just mopped these floors.- I don't need this shit.
A year ago,you asked me to help you.
And God knows I've tried.
But I can't help you, Logan,not really...
if you're notgoing to talk to me.
I hear you at night.You're not sleeping.
You don't wannatalk about that.
Or the booze you're drinking.
Or the pus you're wiping awayfrom your knuckles.
Or the bloodI wash from your clothes.
Or the fresh woundsin your chest.
The ones that aren't healing.
And I'm pretty sure...
you don't wanna talkabout the fact
that you can't read the labelon that bottle.
It says, "lbuprofen."
(MUG SHATTERS)
That was my favorite mug.
Stay out of my shit.
Something's happening to you,Logan.
On the inside you're sick.I can smell it.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
BRIDESMAID: Best night ever!
(ALL CHEERING)
Hey, driver.
WOMAN: I love you. I love you.
You're such a doll.
Mr. Logan.
Oh, Jesus.
Please. We need a ride.
Not available. Call a cab.
My name is Gabriela Lopez.
I don't wannaknow your name, lady.
There are men after us.
- We need to get out of here.- (LOGAN COUGHS)
Go north, cross to Canada.
Anyone can do that job.
I'll give you $50,000.
How did you find me, huh?
'Cause you are fucking upmy life, lady!
The people after you,they're on my ass now!
Sightings were posted.
- Laura, go inside.- What sightings?
People said someonewho looked like the Wolverine
was in El Paso, driving.
Said he looked old.
(WINDOWPANE SHATTERS)
WOMAN: Hey!
I told youto stop it with that ball!
- Bad girl!- No, please.
- I told you, bad girl!- No, please.
Mamacita 's gonnahave to pay for that.
Stop, please. No.
Shit!
They're gonnahave to pay for damages.
(MUMBLES)
And she has cash.
I've seen it.
You should get your fat assback in your office.
You'll get your money.
Don't let her call anyone,please.
They will find us.They will kill us.
(GABRIELA BREATHING HEAVILY)
I am a nurse.
Was. In Mexico City.
When did that happen?
This morning. Near the border.
I got away from them, but...
...now they know my car.
Look, I gotta go.
No, wait. Please. Here.
Please, wait! Look.
Look. Here, take this.It's $20,000.
Here. Take us to this address.
You can have $30,000 morewhen we get there.
My friends therewill give it to you.
They will be waiting.
They will give you anything.
Where did you get this?
My boyfriend.
He wants to kill meand take her.
And that's your daughter?
Yes.
I knowyou're still good inside.
I know you want to help us.
You don't knowanything about me.
Please!
I promise, there will beno problems if we leave now.
I can't just leaveto North Dakota!
- We have to be there Friday.- Or what?
Or we miss our chanceto cross.
Please.
You have to. Please.
- I like those.- Huh?
They make you look younger.
Charles, listen.
I gotta go awayfor a few days, okay?
I got a long ridefor some good money...
but when I get back,we're gonna get outta here.
We're gonnadrive down to Yelapa.
We're gonnaget ourselves a boat.
And we're gonnago live on the ocean.
Will you be safe there?
Yeah. We'll be safe.
Look what Logan got us,Charles.
Be back in a few days.
(TRAIN CLACKING)
(SIGHS)
Shit.
(SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE)
(LOGAN COUGHING)
- Logan.- Yeah?
What happened?
Did something go wrong?
The job was wrongto begin with.
(SNIFFS)
Logan!
What?
Who does this belong to?
Who's that?
Thought you were supposed tosee shit coming.
I can track mutants.
I'm a glorified truffle pig,not a clairvoyant.
Go insideand keep Charles quiet.
Go inside now!
You need to turn around,asshole.
This is private property.
Yes, it is.
In fact, I believe it belongs
to a multinationalsmelting company...
based in Shanghai.
Where are you keepingthe old man? Hmm?
Is he over there?
Or is he there?
That'd be smart.
I'd like to meet him.
I'm told the HSAclassifies his brain
as a weaponof mass destruction now.
Damn shame,what happened back east.
He's been dead for a year.
I need the girl.
What girl?
The one that goes along withthat ball you're holding.
There's no girl here.
I know you went to the motel.
Yeah, I was called there.
There was no girl.It was just the woman.
Just the woman.Such as she was.
So, you saw Gabriela.
But you didn't call me.That hurts.
You didn't shootthe poor thing, did you?
- No, did you?- I asked you first.
- I don't like guns.- Of course.
I wish you'd called me, Logan.
Like I asked.
See?
You're not the only onethat's been enhanced.
(GIRL SCREAMS)
Logan. Logan!
This is Laura.
Caliban, come!
This is whoI've been telling you about.
This is Laura.
We've been waiting for you.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Come, come here.
It's okay.
Come.
Laura.
It's okay. It's okay.
Come.
Come. It's okay.You can stay here, Laura.
It's safe.
We can look after you here.
Come on.
Looks like ex-military.Bounty hunter, maybe?
Worse.
Is he by himself?
Yeah, not for long.
You get him back in his ride,
take him out to the washand dump him.
What if he wakes upbefore I get there?
Text me where you are.We'll pick you up.
(CHARLES SPEAKING SPANISH)
Yes.
Logan.
- Logan.- Hey. Hey!
You'll get it backafter I figure out
what you and your motherhave got us into.
- No, Logan.- What?
- I think the...- (LAURA STRAINING)
Logan, the woman that you met,that's not her mother.
- So she talks?- We're communicating.
Communicating.
Take these now.
We have to get out of here.It's not safe here anymore.
And you can't have an attackout there, you understand?
Yes, but this is the mutantthat I told you about.
- She needs our help.- She's not a mutant.
- Yes, she is!- What's her gift, Charles?
Eating? Pipe throwing?
(RUMBLING)
It's okay.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(GRUNTING)
Oh, yeah.
Take the gun. Dump the body.
Text mewhen you're on the way back.
You have anything elseyou need?
Food for the kid?
(SPITS)
You're fucked now, mutie.
(RUMBLING)
It's okay.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
CHARLES: Choo-choo.LOGAN: It's not a choo-choo.
It's okay. Sit down.
- We gotta go.- What?
- What's going on? Where?- Stay here.
- Don't move.- Where are we going?
Hey, don't worry.He will be back for you.
Logan, the girl. You've got togo back for the girl.
Logan, what about the girl?
Logan.
Logan, we mustn't forgetabout Laura.
She's not our problem.
Shit!
Ah, shit!
(MEN SPEAKING SPANISH)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MAN SPEAKING SPANISH)
Logan.
Yeah, I'm thinking.
The child.
Logan,we mustn't forget Laura.
- Please be quiet.- Logan.
Huh.
- Charles Xavier.- Where's Caliban?
America's most wantedoctogenarian.
I'm a nonagenarian, actually.
(GRUNTS)
Ah.
Where's Caliban?
Why don't you tell mewhere the girl is first?
Or I could ask Cue Ball.He seems quite friendly.
I told you, she's not here.
Where's Caliban, motherfucker?
Well, I left himin the same ditch
he was gonna leave me in.
- (GROWLING)- (MEN GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
(GUNS COCKING)
(PANTING)
Jesus, Wolverine,
seeing you like thisjust breaks my damn heart.
As soon as I rip it outof your chest, fuck-stick.
(GROANING)
Go get her.
(CRUNCHING)
(DOOR OPENING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(MAN SCREAMING)
(GUNFIRE)
(PANTING)
Laura.
That a girl!
Hey, baby.
Laura...
Laura!
Honey, you wanna staywhere you are.
You wanna seeyour friends, right?
- (SHOUTING IN SPANISH)- Command, stop.
You said alive or dead.
Laura!
Laura.
(GUNS COCKING)
No. No.
Move! Go!
- (GRUNTING)- (SCREAMING)
(YELLING)
- Move! Go!- (ORDERING IN SPANISH)
(GUNS FIRING)
Stop shooting!
She heals! Move! Go!
(MEN CLAMORING)
Holy shit!
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
- (YELLING)- (GROANING)
(MAN SPEAKING SPANISH)
- (YELLS)- (GROANING)
(MEN SHOUTING IN SPANISH)
Gotcha!
- (GROANING)- (YELLING)
- Ah!- (GRUNTS)
Come on, hold her down.
(SCREAMS)
(GROANING)
- (LAURA SCREAMING)- (MEN SPEAKING SPANISH)
(MAN SCREAMING)
(CHOKING)
(COMMANDER ORDERINGIN SPANISH)
(LAURA SCREAMING)
(LOGAN YELLING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
As I told you, Logan,she's a mutant like you.
Hold on!
Very much like you.
- (TIRES SCREECHING)- (GRUNTS)
- (GUNFIRE)- (MEN SHOUTING IN SPANISH)
Laura, are you all right?
- (GLASS SHATTERS)- Ahh!
(SPITS)
Move!
(COMMANDER ORDERINGIN SPANISH)
Hold on!
(ALL GROAN)
Fuck! Come on!
(ENGINE REVVING)
Come on!
(GUNFIRE)
Shit.
(MEN SCREAMING)
(GUNSHOT)
(MAN YELLING)
Fall in! Let's go!
CHARLES: Oh, watch out!
Ah!
- (YELLING)- (MAN SCREAMING)
Sit back.
Bring me the tracker.
You.
Who the hell are you?
Hey! I asked you a question.Who are you?
You know who she is, Logan.
No, I don't.
Does she remind youof anybody?
I read about youwhen I was a kid.
I believe you're thinkingof someone else.
Hmm.
(PANTING)
Now, if I'm not mistaken,you used to work for my team.
You were helping round upall those old mutes.
What changed?
You got religion?
I'm gonna need you to do
one more thingfor the good guys...
and track one morespecial mute for me.
I'm not helping you.
Of course, you'd say that.
But I got a theory thatpeople don't really change.
Beware of the light.
Caliban, I bet that's whatyour mama told you
every day when you was a kid.
(CLICKING TONGUE)
Beware of the light.
(WHIMPERING)
(CALIBAN SCREAMING)
Now, let's not bring outthe worst in each other.
The girl is not worth it,trust me.
She's not a natural fuck-uplike you.
She's a business mistake,a R&D gone bad.
There's liability.
They can't have thingswith patents
running around,hurting people, can they?
We need to get heroff the board
before she hurts anybody else.
Someone you care about, maybe.
- (SKIN SIZZLES)- (GROANING)
So, get to sniffin'.
My name is Gabriela López.
I am a nurse.
And for 10 years, I worked for
Transigen Researchin Mexico City.
Transigen is ownedby an American company.
What I am about to show youis illegal...
in the U.S. And Canada.
(CHILDREN SINGING)
They told us we were partof a pharmaceutical study.
But, of course,that was a lie.
These childrenwere born in Transigen.
They were born here...
and have never left.
They have never seenthe sun or the ocean...
rain or snow...
or any of God's creatures.
They have nobirth certificates...
no names...
besides the oneswe have given them.
They were raised inthe bellies of Mexican girls.
Girls no one can find anymore.
Their fathers aresemillas genéticas...
special seeds in bottles.
(CHILDREN SINGINGIN SPANISH ON VIDEO)
- Birthday? No birth.- DR. RICE: María.
We do not dress them upfor Halloween.
We do not call them "baby"or kiss boo-boos.
Don't think of themas children.
Think of them as things...
with patents and copyrights.
Comprende?
Si, señor.
GABRIELA: They thoughtwe were too poor
and stupid to understand.
We're poor, yes...
but we are not stupid.
TRAINER: Use your powers.
(BOY GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
(RUMBLING)
GABRIELA: This is business.
They are making soldiers.
Killers.
(SIGHS)
These are babiesofmutantes...
(BEEPS)
CHARLES: North Dakota.LOGAN: Mmm.
You took that woman's money.
You said you would takethe child there.
(RATTLING)
What is she?
She's your daughter, Logan.
Alkali has your genetic code.
Not just mine.
Logan...
I don't want to talk about it.
I don't wannahear about it anymore.
- Logan...- Just stop.
I have to pee.
(RATTLING)
Last ride.
(COIN RATTLES)
You're welcome.
CHARLES: Stop it.For God's sake,
I can do this myself!
LOGAN: Yeah, well,you're not doing it.
Just get on with it.
Not with you standing there.
Trust me, I'm not lookin'.
(COUGHS)
(SIGHS)
(CASH REGISTER WHIRRING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
STORE CLERK: Hello.
Hi, there!
You know you gotta payfor that, right?
(CHIPS CRUNCHING)
Hey! Where's yourmommy and daddy, huh?
(SIGHS)
Come on.
That's enough. These, too.
(LAURA GROWLING)
- Shit!- Not okay!
Sorry.
Um, do you sellphone chargers?
Uh...
(LAURA GRUNTING)
Come on. Get in the car.
(VEHICLES PASSING)
- (COUGHING)- (CELLPHONE BUZZING)
GABRIELA: As the childrenbecame older...
Laura. Laura.
...they became more difficult.
They could not be controlled.
(GABRIELA SPEAKING SPANISH)
The company made their bodiesinto weapons.
Tried to teach them to kill.
But they did notwant to fight.
- (GUARD SPEAKING SPANISH)- (BOY YELLING)
A soldier who will not fightis useless.
(SIGHS)
Inside this building...
they are working onsomething new.
Something they think is betterthan the children.
Something they sayis without a soul.
MAN: Would you like to hearmy full lab report, Dr. Rice?
DR. RICE: You can't getgood sushi here.
It's the Mexican equivalentof Denver, Colorado.
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
GABRIELA: They must havebeen successful.
About a week ago, they told usto shut our program down.
(GIRL SCREAMING)
They started puttingthe children to sleep.
(INDISTINCT CLAMORING)
(PIERCE LAUGHING)
We are going to saveas many children as we can.
I read about a place,up north.
A place for mutants.
They call it Eden.
(GABRIELA SPEAKING SPANISH)
(MAN SCREAMING)
GABRIELA:If you are watching this...
it means that I am dead.
I am not sure ifany other children survived.
We were separated.
There is no more money.
That was a lie.
She's not my child.
But I love her.
You may not love her.
But she is your child.
Please. I beg you...
take her to safety.
(SIGHS)
(CARS HONKING)
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYINGIN DISTANCE)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Is this wherewe're hiding out?
LOGAN: We're not hiding out.
We're gonna geta couple of hours' sleep...
clean up,get some new clothes,
get a new rideand get outta here.
WOMAN: (ON SPEAKER)Harrah's Hotel and Casino
welcomes you to Oklahoma City.
Please keep rightfor valet parking.
LOGAN: Hey.
The fun never stopsat Harrah's Hotel and Casino.
Hey, keep it out front,all right?
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Come on, let's go.
(PEOPLE EX CLAIMING)
(MACHINES RINGING)
Hey, Laura.
Let's go.
We need clothes.
FEMALE VOICE: Going up.
No, no, stop. Not a toy.
- Uh, no, no, sorry, chair.- What? Okay.
- Push up again.- Thank you.
FEMALE VOICE: Going up.
Come here. Stand there.Just stand there.
Logan, it's yours.
What?
I'm not gonna wear it now.
In the room. We'll getchanged in the room.
You're a low-down,lying Yankee.
Prove it.
(GUNSHOT)
(HORSES NEIGHING ON TV)
This is a veryfamous picture, Laura.
It's almost 100 years old.
(LOGAN COUGHING HEAVILY)
(SINGING ON TV)In life, in death, oh, Lord
Abide with me
I first saw this picture
at the Essoldo Cinemain my hometown...
when I was your age.
ALL: Who art in heavenHallowed be thy name
Thy kingdom come,thy will be done
Shit.
SHANE: (ON TV) I've heardthat you're a low-down,
Yankee liar.
WILSON: Prove it.
(GUNSHOTS)
You read thesein your spare time?
Oh, yeah, Charles,we got ourselves an X-Men fan.
You do knowthey're all bullshit, right?
Maybe a quarter of ithappened, and not like this.
In the real world, people die.
And no self-promoting asshole
in a fucking leotardcan stop it.
This is ice creamfor bed-wetters.
Logan...
Her nurse has been feeding hersome grade-A bullshit.
I don't thinkLaura needs reminding
of life's impermanence.
Didn't you say something aboutfinding us a new ride?
Two more pills in one hour.
Give 'em to him.
BOY: (ON TV) Why, Shane?
A man has to bewhat he is, Joey.
Can't break the mold.
I tried itand it didn't work for me.
Joey, there's no livingwith a killing.
There's no going backfrom one.
Right or wrong, it's a brand.
A brand sticks.
Now you run on hometo your mother,
and tell hereverything's all right.
And there aren't any more gunsin the valley.
STORE CLERK: Who are you guys?
More cops? 'Cause I told
the other guyseverything that I...
(MAN SCREAMING)
MAN: Get up!In your cage, tracker.
You did your job.
LOGAN: Fellas.
Shit.
Knock yourselves out.
WOMAN: I'll tell you what.Eight grand...
I'll have her freshly paintedfor you, new tires...
mounted, balanced,and complete paperwork.
I'll give you 10 as-is,
if you can forgetthe paperwork.
Well, you still neednew tires, man, they're bald.
How long will that take?
An hour.
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS)
Jesus.
You gotta befucking kidding me.
(HORN HONKING)
(COUGHING)
Sir, are the keys in... Sir!
You have the keys in it? Sir!
Shit!
(PEOPLE CHATTERING LOUDLY)
(HIGH-PITCHED RINGING)
- (RUMBLING)- (GROANING)
Charles. Charles!
Argh!
(GASPING)
(GROANING)
AUTOMATED VOICE: Going up.
(GRUNTING)
(LAURA GRUNTING)
(STRAINING)
(CLATTERING)
(GRUNTS)
(WHIMPERING)
(PANTING)
(MAN GROANING)
(YELLING)
(CAR ALARMS BLARING)
Oh, shit!
You all right?
We gotta get outta here.
(WOMAN SOBBING)
CHARLES: I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
(PEOPLE GROANING)
(EXHALES)
NEWSCASTER: Emergencypersonnel are still on scene
at Harrah's Casino Hotelin Oklahoma City...
where at least 400 guestswere stricken
with temporary paralysisyesterday.
Many are noting a similarity
to the Westchester incidentover a year ago...
that left over 600 injured...
and took the livesof seven mutants,
including severalof the X-Men.
Knock it off.
(DOOR LOCK CLICKING)
I said, knock it off!
She's a child, Logan.
And, point of fact,she's your...
How long has it beensince you took your meds?
(EXHALES)
Tell me,how long has it been?
I don't know!
Two days.
You sawwhat happened yesterday.
If that shithad gone on any longer,
everyone in that casino...
I did what I had to doto save Laura.
You didn't do anything.
You just freaked outand had a fucking seizure!
I guess you prefer mepharmaceutically castrated,
rambling on like a lunatic.
So much easier for you.
Easier? Jesus!
There is nothing easyabout you, Charles, nothing!
Yes, yes, please belike the rest of the world...
blaming someone elsefor your boring shit.
I know, Pop, I'm sucha giant disappointment.
You honestly deriveno sense of purpose...
from what we're doing?
Okay, what are we doing? Hmm?
There is a young mutantsitting in our car.
Yeah, I see that.
And where we're taking her,there are others.
Does that mean nothing to you?
Yeah, means nothing to me.
Especially sinceNurse Gabriela...
made all that Eden shit upwith fucking comic books.
What are you talking about?
Give those to him, will you?
Take out two pillsand give them to him.
- Logan! Logan!- Give 'em to him.
Now!
I wanna see it.
(EX CLAIMS)
PIERCE: Dr. Rice.It's under control...
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Motherfucking auto-trucks.
Language, Logan.
And you're screamingat a machine.
Oh, what? She can gut a manwith her feet,
she can't heara few naughty words, huh?
CHARLES:She can learn to be better.
You mean, better than me?
Actually, yes.
And, by the way,Laura's foot claws...
are the obvious resultof her gender, you know.
LOGAN: Is that a fact?
In a pride of lions,the female...
is both hunter and caregiver.
LOGAN: Good to know.
She uses her front clawsfor hunting...
and the back clawsdefensively.
LOGAN: Oh, yeah?
Thus, ensuring their survival.
- (COUGHS)- (HORN HONKS)
Hey, hey!
(HORSES NEIGHING)
CHARLES: We should help them.
No, we have to keep going.Someone will come along.
Someone has come along.
FEMALE AUTOMATED VOICE:Alert. Alert.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
(SHUSHING)
Hey, uh, you need a hand?
(TRUCK STARTING)
Ready? Go!
Ah. Good, got it.
Come on, let's get home.
Laura!
Thank you so muchfor your help.
- I'm Kathryn.- James.
This is my son, Nate.
- Hi.- Hey.
That's your daughter?
Yeah, that's Laura,and that's my dad...
Chuck.
Come on, Laura, let's go.
Well, can we showour appreciation
and treat the three of youto a decent meal?
We don't live far from here.
- Uh, no, thanks.- That would be lovely!
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
My name is Dr. Rice.
But you can call me Zanderif you like.
My colleague tells me
you've beensomewhat resistant.
He believes you've been
dispensingdelayed information...
to allow your friendsto stay one step ahead.
I'm offering youthe possibility
of redemption, Caliban.
To protect the world,and in the process,
save your friends.
The girl is a rathersmall price to pay for that.
Unlike you, she's impure.
She wasn't made by nature.
She's a mistake of my own.
I did what I could
and they burned meand beat me.
Your colleagues are savages.
(CHUCKLES) I agree.
The Reaverswere very ineffective.
But I'm bringingnew tools to bear.
But I still need someone
to point usin the right direction.
No, I can't help you.
- (PANTING)- Breathe, breathe.
Now, what does he have?The old man.
Alzheimer's? ALS?
A degenerative brain disease
in the world's mostdangerous brain?
What a combo.
(HORSE NEIGHING)
KATHRYN: Be nice.Now, you know we got company.
CHARLES: That's wonderful.
KATHRYN:Everybody, have a seat.
WILL: Nate, sit up.
James, why don't you sitat the end of the table?
KATHRYN: You wanna say grace?Say grace, baby.
Uh, thank you, God,for this food...
and for our new friends,the Howletts.
Mmm. They came to our aid.
- Amen.- Amen.
WILL: Here we go.Here you go, Charles.
Thank you, sir.
LOGAN: Mmm-hmm.
Oh, there's plenty moreif she wants.
She's fine. Thank you.
CHARLES: This is delicious.
KATHRYN: Oh, thank you.CHARLES: It's so good.
Where are you all headed?
- Uh... Oregon.- South Dakota.
Um...
Well, Oregonand then South Dakota.
Vacation?
Uh... Yes.
Uh, long overdue.
We're city folk.
Always wanted to takea road trip, see the country.
Um...And meet the people in it.
KATHRYN: That sounds lovely.
Been trying to get Will here
to take a vacationfor years now.
Oh. If we go traipsingall over the country,
who's gonna take careof this place?
KATHRYN:Exactly. I say, let it go.
And live off what?
The Lord will provide.
WILL: I'm still waiting forthe Lord to provide me
- with a new thresher.- (LAUGHS)
KATHRYN: All the same,I'd love to travel someday.
And I bet you will.
- I could drop out of school.- Okay, let's not go that far.
I mean, I'll do it.
KATHRYN: No. No.NATE: Why not?
You wanna travel,I wanna travel.
KATHRYN: Son. Son.
WILL: That sounds goodto you, right?
This is the perfect plan.
Why would you want to do that,Nate?
Careful, you're speaking toa man who ran a school...
for a lot of years.Right, Charles?
(STAMMERS) Yes, it was a...
It was a special needs school.Um...
Uh-huh.That's a good description.
He was there, too.
Oh, yeah, no. Um...
- I got kicked out a few times.- (LAUGHS)
I wish I could sayyou were a good pupil,
but the words would choke me.
(ALL LAUGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERAND LAUGHTER)
(HORSE NEIGHING)
Ma'am, I can't thank youenough for this.
Uh, it was great.
But we have a long driveahead of us, so...
But you need to rest,don't you?
LOGAN: Yeah, we'll finda motel somewhere.
The nearest oneis two hours from here
and it's not even that nice.
We have a perfectly fineroom upstairs
for your fatherand your daughter and
you can sleep in the livingroom on the convertible.
Kathryn, it's very,very nice of you,
but we really should go.
We can leaveearly in the morning.
Break of dawn, as it were.
(LOGAN STAMMERS)
Okay, why don't we wash up,Pop?
Okay.
Sit.
KATHRYN: Um, sweetie,you want some dessert?
Two days on the road,
only one meal,and hardly any sleep.
She's 11, I'm fucking 90.
Well, that's 101 reasonsto keep moving.
I'm not a box of avocados,Logan.
LOGAN: And then what?We stay the night, then what?
Then we take herto her friends in Eden.
And then we buy the Sunseeker.
Take the pills.
(WATER SPURTING)
WILL: Oh, shit!
(PIPES CREAKING)
- What's going on?- Nate!
Go fill up the tubbefore we lose pressure.
Honey, check the sink.
KATHRYN:They shut it off again.
They are just not going tolet this thing go.
Well, you might as wellhandle it now.
It can wait till the morning.We just had rain last night.
KATHRYN:We got three houseguests
and a sink full of dishes.
All right, all right.
The pump stationthat supplies us
is a mileand a half from here.
Sometimes it gets itselfshut off.
- By assholes.- WILL: Hey!
No.
My son is happyto go with you.
No, no, no, that's fine.
The men that do this,sometimes they can be...
- I can go.- No, you got homework.
All right, I'll go.
Just, uh,let me get my dad settled.
(STRAINING) All right.
WILL: I'm just saying, I don'tcare what the lawyer says.
KATHRYN: But it's dangerous.
WILL: I'm not gonnahurt our chances.
(LOGAN PANTING)
Want TV? There's TV here.
I'm fine.
Okay. Get some rest.
You know, Logan...
this is what life looks like.
A home,people who love each other.
Safe place.
You shouldtake a moment and feel it.
Yeah. It's great.
Logan. Logan!
You still have time.
Charles, the world is notthe same as it was.
We're taking a risk hangingaround here, you know that.
And where we're going, Eden...
it doesn't exist.
Her nurse got itfrom a comic book.
You understand? It's not real.
It is for Laura.
Get some rest.
Canewood Beverage bought upeverything out here,
except for us.
When we wouldn't sell,they tried eminent domain...
then screwing with our water.
Couple of months ago,somebody poisoned our dogs.
LOGAN: So, out on the highwaytoday, those trucks...
WILL: (SIGHS)Who knows. Maybe.
Hey, look at 'em.
Look like dinosaurswith their 20-ton bodies
and tiny little brains...
shucking their cloned-upsuper corn.
You knowit tastes like shit, too.
Why do people eat it?
They don't. They drink it.Corn syrup.
It's in those drinksthat everyone's having...
to stay awake, cheer up,feel strong, sexy, whatever.
Used to be a time whena bad day was just a bad day.
LOGAN: Mine still are.
(MUSIC PLAYING FAINTLYTHROUGH EARPHONES)
Those are forbreakaway roping.
Those are for barrel racing...
and right hereis for pole bending.
They're all second,third place.
I'm not too good at it,but my dad makes me.
Do you want to listen?
(MUSIC CONTINUESTHROUGH EARPHONES)
Do you like it?
Um, here,you can take it for tonight...
and I'll get it back from youin the morning.
(WILL GRUNTS)
(GATE SQUEAKING)
(WATER SPRAYING)
Looks like we're gonnabe here a while.
(MUSIC PLAYINGTHROUGH EARPHONES)
(WILL GRUNTS)
Should hold it.
Yeah.
Till next time.
(PANTING) Thanks.
Hey, so, uh,how long has your girl
- been like that?- Huh?
Mute.
Uh, since the beginning.
Mmm.
Well, in a lot of ways,I envy you.
They get to be Nate's age,
with the nonsense thatcomes out of their mouths...
Makes you wonderthe whole point of it all.
Shit.
Don't worry.
We won't need it.
Stay here.
Evening, Mr. Munson.
What brings y'all this way?
Why don't you ask your boys?
Mr. Munson,
you understand you'retrespassing right now, right?
I have an easement withthe previous owner
of your property.
Huh. Bullshit.
"Previous" beingthe operative word.
Who's this?
Just a guy telling you
to get backin your nice truck.
Go play Okie dickheadsomewhere else.
Hey, Carl...
it looks like Mr. Munsonhired some muscle.
Looks that way.
He's a friend of mine.
A friend with a big mouth.
I hear that a lot.
JACKSON: Then you probablyhear this, too.
(GUN COCKS)
More than I'd like.
Then you know the drill.
I'mma count to three...
and you're gonnastart walking away.
I got rights to this water.
- One.- I have a lawyer now.
Two.
(GROANS)
- Three.- Ah. Ah.
- (SPITS)- You all right, boss?
(GRUNTS)
You know the drill.
JACKSON:Pick up my goddamn hat.
Get the hell out of here.
- You okay, boss?- Fuck off.
Go!
(JACKSON GROANS)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(COUGHING)
(CONTINUES COUGHING)
You've had training.
Some.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(CLOCK TICKING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
CHARLES:Hey, don't wake her yet.
Let her sleep another hour.
(SIGHS)
You know, Logan...
this was, without a doubt...
the most perfect nightI've had in a very long time.
(VOICE CRACKING)But I don't deserve it.
Do I?
I did something.
Something unspeakable.
I've rememberedwhat happened in Westchester.
This is not the first timeI've hurt people.
Until today, I didn't know.
You wouldn't tell me.
So we just kept onrunning away from it.
I think I finallyunderstand you.
Logan...
(GASPS)
(GROWLS)
- (LAURA SCREAMS)- (GRUNTS)
- (CONTINUES SCREAMING)- (GROANING)
(NATE GRUNTS)
- (CLAWS STABBING)- (NATE GROANING)
He's fantastic.
You said you only neededthe girl!
I told you I was forcedto bring a new tool to bear.
Your friends had every chance.
And so did you.
KATHRYN: Nate?
Put her down.
(GUN COCKS)
(COUGHING)
Honey.
KATHRYN:Stay down there, Will!
(HORSES NEIGHING)
Stop!
- (GUNSHOT)- (KATHRYN SHOUTS)
- (LAURA SCREAMING)- WILL: Kathryn!
- (CONTINUES SCREAMING)- WILL: Kathryn!
Kathryn!
- (GROANS)- (SCREAMING)
(LAURA CONTINUES SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
(LAURA SOBBING)
(LAURA SHRIEKS)
(SCREAMING)
Charles!
(LAURA CONTINUES SCREAMING)
Hold this.
It wasn't me. It wasn't me.
(LAURA SCREAMING)
DR. RICE: Here he comes.
DRIVER:I could pick him up,
meet him halfway.
No, no, no.Let them come to us.
We struggled with the X-23s.
We assumed,because they were children...
we could raise themwithout a conscience.
But you can't nurture rage.
You must simply design it...
from scratch.
(LAURA SCREAMING)
Who the fuck is that?
Will Munson!
- (PANTING)- (CHARLES GROANING)
Just hold on, Charles.
JACKSON: Munson, God damn it,come out here!
- (PANTING)- (CHARLES GROANING FEEBLY)
JACKSON: Munson!
Come out here now!
Come out here now, Munson.
There's that asshole.
Hello, asshole.
Listen, I'm willingto let bygones be bygones.
I don't know whatMunson's paying you...
but Canewood can start you outat five G.
A week, that is.
You best staywhere you are, pal.
I'm the law out here.
- (GRUNTS)- No, no, no.
What in high...
What? Oh, shit!
Shoot him!
(MEN SCREAMING)
We need to intervene.
Well, he only listensto you, Doctor.
(MEN SCREAMING)
DR. RICE: 24!
Get back here!
Stop! Stop now!
Hold this down,right now, tight!
(GROANING)
(CHARLES STAMMERING)
- Our boat.- What?
The Sunseeker.
No.
- (MEN SCREAMING AND GRUNTING)- (LAURA SHRIEKING)
Come!
24!
Need some help out here!
I guess we're gonna have totake care of this now.
DR. RICE: Pierce!PIERCE: Give me that.
DR. RICE: Get your lily-facedass out here!
(GRUNTING)
DR. RICE: Listen to me!
What the fuckdo you think you're doing?
PIERCE: All right, we gotta goaround that truck
and flank them farmers.
Follow my lead.
Bring extra ammo,take these clips.
Come!
Now!
Pick her up.
(GASPING)
(SHRIEKING)
Beware the light.
(PIERCE SCREAMS)
(PANTING)
- (LAURA CONTINUES SHRIEKING)- (LOGAN GRUNTING)
- (SCREAMING)- (GRUNTING)
What the hell are you?
(BOTH YELLING)
(STRAINING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(YELLING)
(PANTING)
(X-24 GRUNTING AND STRAINING)
(CONTINUES GRUNTING)
(LOGAN COUGHING)
(GUN COCKS)
(PANTING)
(GUN CLICKS)
(LAURA SHRIEKING)
(CONTINUES SHRIEKING)
(PANTING)
(COUGHING)
(SCREAMING)
Sit down.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(LAURA CONTINUES SHRIEKING)
(SHRIEKING)
Hold still.
(PANTING)
MAN 1: Get him on the truck.
MAN 2: Yeah.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Go.
(GRUNTING)
It's all right,it's all right.
It's all right.You did fine, 24.
You're healing. Just breathe.
You're a newborn,by any measure.
Just breathe.
Your body has work to do.
Hemostasis, angiogenesis,epithelialization...
stromal cell proliferation.
(GASPS)
This will help you heal.
Make you stronger.
(COUGHING)
(CONTINUES COUGHING)
(PANTING)
LOGAN: Well...
It's got water, and...
(SIGHS)
(VOICE BREAKING)It's got water.
- (EXHALES SHARPLY)- (SHOVEL CLANGS)
Fuck this. Fuck this.
(ENGINE STARTING)
- (YELLING) God!- (STEERING WHEEL THUDDING)
(GRUNTING)
Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck!
Shit!
(DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE)
- LOGAN: Fuck! Fuck!- (METAL CLANGING)
(YELLING) Fuck!
Motherfucking...
(SCREAMING)
Shit!
Fuck! Fuck!
(JINGLING)
(COUGHING)
DOCTOR: Welcome back.
I was starting to thinkI was gonna have to tell...
that nice little girlout in the waiting room...
her daddy's gone.
(SIGHS)
I'd always hoped...
that I'd get the chanceto meet someone like you.
There's so few of you left.
Nice to meet you, too, Doc.
(GROANING) But I reallygot to get on my way.
No, no, don't do that.
What you need is rest,and treatment.
You need to check yourselfin somewhere.
- I'll be fine.- No, you're not!
I mean, I knowthat you're different...
but that doesn'tchange the fact
that something inside youis poisoning you.
You got to check yourselfinto a hospital.
Find out what it is!
I know what it is.
Please, mister, if you don'twant to go to a hospital,
maybe I can help you.
Maybe I can run some tests.
Look, Doc. You seemlike a nice guy, all right?
You wanna save a life,save your own.
Forget we were here.
(COUGHS) Let's go.
(CONTINUES COUGHING)
Hey!
You can't just take shit,you know.
(KEYS JINGLING)
I don't knowhow you got me here...
but thank you.
De nada.
Yeah.
You can talk?
What the fuck?
Why in the fuck...
What's all this bullshit been
for the last2,000 fucking miles?
(YELLING IN SPANISH)
What? Shut up.
Shut the fuck up!
Jonah, Gideon,Rebecca, Delilah, Rictor.
What? Who's that?
Who is that?
Jonah, Gideon,Rebecca, Delilah, and Rictor.
North Dakota.
What?
North Dakota, por favor.
Shit, okay. Look...
No. Por favor.
This place. Okay?
Your nurse,
she read too many stories,you understand?
Too many stories!
(COUGHING)
(CONTINUES SPEAKING SPANISH)
I've seen it!I've seen it, okay?
This all here...
None of this...No existo, okay?
You understand me?
- This Eden does not exist. No!- Sí! Eden!
It's a fantasy, kid. See that?
Those are the namesof the people
who just made this...(COUGHING)
They made this whole thing up.
Okay? This whole...
It happened once,
and they just turned itinto a big, fucking lie!
- (CONTINUES SPEAKING SPANISH)- That's all this is. No!
Fuck.
(COUGHING) No.
I know, I understand.
This is a long way.
You understand?
I am not taking youto North Dakota.
I am fucked up.And I cannot get you there.
It is a two-day drive.And I am not taking you...
- (SPEAKING SPANISH)- Don't fucking hit me!
Don't hit me!
Jonah, Gideon...
- Stop saying those names....Rebecca...
Delilah, Rictor.
Right now.Stop saying those names.
- Stop it! Stop!- Jonah, Gideon, Rebecca...
Fuck it. Fine, fine.
- (KEYS JINGLING)- You wanna go?
I'll take you there.
See for yourself.
Let's go tofucking fantasyland.
(ENGINE STARTS)
MAJOR: We understandthe importance
of containment, Dr. Rice.
But you can't leavea war zone behind
like you did in Juárez.
Well, try to remind yourselves
that these are alllittle killing machines.
Machines who would've happilydisemboweled your family.
Not all.
I was told you wantthese assets off-board,
dead or alive.
Are you changing my brief?
No.
All right, then.
Save tissue from this one.
He's a good trackerand had a high IQ.
Here you go.
Hey.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Hmm?
LAURA: (IN ENGLISH)Let me drive.
(SCOFFS)
Absolutely not.
Quit looking at me.
(CONTINUES SPEAKING SPANISH)
No comprende.
(IN ENGLISH) You are dying.
You want to die.
Charles told me.
What else did he tell you?
To not let you.
Hey, hey, hey!
Rest.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(BIRD SCREECHING)
(GROANS)
(LAURA SHOUTING IN SPANISH)
(WHISTLES)
(CONTINUESSHOUTING IN SPANISH)
(THUDS)
(COUGHING)
RICTOR: Keep it steady.
(LOGAN CONTINUES COUGHING)
RICTOR: Swing him toward me.
Yeah.
Easy. Easy
(WATER DRIPPING)
Is this good, Rictor?
No, not so much. Less.
(BLOWING)
Hey!
(COUGHING)
Where am I?
Hey, what is it?
Where did you get that?
RICTOR: Where we came from.
They gave it to us
when we would fight.It makes you stronger.
It makes you crazy,is what it does.
It'll kill you.
No, not if you use itin small doses.
It's helping you heal.
Where's Laura?
BOBBY:She's asleep down there.
Do you want me to wake her up?
No.
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
(LOGAN GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(YELLS)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
You had a nightmare.
Do you have nightmares?
Sí.
(IN ENGLISH) People hurt me.
Mine are different.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH) I hurt people.
(IN ENGLISH)You know what it is.
It's made out of Adamantium.
It's what they putinside of us.
That's why it can kill us.
Probably what iskilling me now.
Anyway...
I got this a long time ago...
and I kept it as a reminderof what I am.
Now I keep it to, uh...
Actually, uh...
I was thinking ofshooting myself with it.
Like Charles said.
I've hurt people, too.
You're gonna have to learnhow to live with that.
(GROANS)
They were bad people.
All the same.
(WOOD CREAKING)
(SCISSORS CLIPPING)
- (LOGAN MUMBLES)- (CHILDREN GIGGLE)
(CHILDREN GIGGLING)
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
(COUGHING)
Not funny. That is not funny!
Hey! Hey, pal.
How long have I been out?
How long have I beenin that bed?
Two days.
You've been sitting herefor two days?
Hey, go inside and telleveryone to get packing.
You can't do that.You can't just stay here.
We had to wait.It was the plan.
And everyone had till todayto find their way here.
If you keep waiting,
Alkali will find youand they will kill you all.
You need to get out!
We're leaving tomorrowbefore dawn.
We're gonna cross the border.
It's a safe haven.
Same coordinates?
WOMAN: (ON RADIO)Yes, between noon and 5:00.
Satellites are blind then.
- Your asylum approved.- Copy.
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
RICTOR:Swing it to your right, Laura.
A little more. Yeah.
You see the woods?
Sí.
It's an eight mile hikethrough there.
And you see that pass?
LAURA: Mm-hmm.
RICTOR: That's the border.
That's where we will be safe.
Come inside.
Laura told meall that you did for her.
She was lucky to have you.
Take it. She says it's yours.
That's why you did it, right?
Yeah, well...
Look, I don't need it.You do, okay?
RICTOR: (CHUCKLES)Suit yourself.
(GIGGLING AND CHATTERING)
Your friends, they seem nice.
Kind of reminds me...
Hey, hey, what's going on?
Huh?
You're with your pals.You made it.
Where will you go?
Nearest bar, for starters.
Hey, I got you here.That's all I signed up for.
I even gave back the money.
Such a nice man.
Hey, I never asked for this!
All right?Charles never asked for this.
Caliban never asked for this.
And they are six feetunder the ground!
Now, I don't know what Charlesput in your head...
but I am not whatever it isyou think I am, okay?
I only met you,like, a week ago.
You got your Rebecca,your Delilah...
your blah, blah, blah,whatever.
Everything you asked for,you've got it!
And it is better this way.
Because I suck at this.
Bad shit happens to peopleI care about.
You understand me?
Then I'll be fine.
(CHILDREN CHATTINGINDISTINCTLY)
(DRONES BUZZING)
(CHILDREN YELLING)
RICTOR: Run!Towards the mountains! Run!
(PANTING)
(CHILDREN YELLING)
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
(WHIMPERING)
GIRL: Run, Bobby, run!
Ah!
(CHILDREN SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(MAN YELLING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(CHILDREN CONTINUE SCREAMING)
DR. RICE: Go! Go!
Move faster!
We need to reach thembefore they get to the border.
(GIRL GRUNTING)
(MEN YELLING)
(LAURA SCREAMING)
(LOGAN YELLING)
- (GRUNTING)- (REAVERS GROANING)
(YELLING)
MAN: Move out!
Let's go, let's go!
RICTOR: Run! Run!
Corre, Jonah! Run!
(GUNSHOT)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
I want you to breathe.
It's just a flesh wound, baby.
(GRUNTING)
REAVER: There she is.
We got her.
Back it up! Contain her.
(LOGAN YELLS)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(LAURA YELLING)
(LAURA SCREAMING)
- (GUNFIRE)- (GRUNTS)
Get behind me!
(LOGAN GRUNTING)
(LAURA SCREAMING)
(BOTH YELLING)
(PANTING)
You took all the medicine.
It's wearing off.
(GASPING)
(PANTING)
Go to your friends.
Go.
Laura?
You'll know when.
(COUGHS)
Nine o'clock.
That green juiceis wearin' off, huh?
You know, for an old mute,it's kind of a short high.
Be hard tokeep them claws out, soon.
- Waste this dick, Logan!- (GRUNTS)
Please stop, Mr. Howlett.
I'm gonna haveto tell these men
to fire on these children.
You don't want that.
You can see the effects ofthe serum are wearing off.
You will not survivefurther wounds.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Zander Rice.
I believe you knew my fatheron the Weapon X Program.
Yeah. He's the assholewho put this poison in me.
Yes, he was one of them.
I thinkI might have killed him.
I think you're right.
Why don't youshow some respect, mutie?
You're lookin' at the manwho wiped out your kind.
My friend Donald overstates.
He makes it sound more brutalthan intended.
The goal wasnot to end mutant kind...
but to control it.
I realized
we needn't stop perfectingwhat we eat and drink.
That we could usethose products
to perfect ourselves.
To distribute gene therapy
discreetlythrough everything...
from sweet drinksto breakfast cereals.
And it worked.
Random mutancywent the way of polio.
We embarkedon our next endeavor.
Growing mutants of your own.
- Precisely.- Dangerous times, James.
You can't...
- (DR. RICE SPLUTTERING)- Argh!
- Argh!- (REAVER YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
(GRUNTING)
Showtime, boy!
(YELLING)
(GROWLING)
- (BOTH GRUNTING)- (SLASHING)
(YELLING)
(GROANING)
Get up, boy. Get up, boy!
He did that. Get up!
(SCREAMS)
Laura! No!
Laura!
(YELLS IN PAIN)
(GROANING)
(BOTH YELLING)
Please.
(GRUNTING)
(BLOWING)
(RICTOR GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
Ah!
Go.
(LOGAN COUGHING)
Let's go.
Go.
Go, go, go!
Go! Get out of here! Go!
(METAL STRAINING)
Go. Go, go, go!
- Go, go!- (YELLS)
Go!
Run!
No!
- (SCREAMING)- LAURA: No!
(GROANING WEAKLY)
(SCREAMING)
No, no. No.
- (YELLS)- (METAL CLANGING)
(GROANING)
(LAURA SOBBING)
Take your friends, and run.
No.
Run. They'll keepcoming and coming.
Listen, you don't haveto fight anymore.
Go, go.
(WHISPERS)Don't be what they made you.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Laura... Laura...
Daddy.
So, this iswhat it feels like.
(CRYING) No!
No!
Daddy.
Dad.
(SOBBING)
"A man has to bewhat he is, Joey.
"Can't break the mold.
"There's no livingwith a killing.
"There's no going back.
"Right or wrong, it's a brand.
"A brand that sticks.
"Now you run on hometo your mother.
"You tell hereverything's all right.
"There are no more gunsin the valley."
Let's go. We gotta move.
There's a man goin' 'roundtakin'names
And he decides who to freeand who to blame
Everybody won't be treatedall the same
There'll be a golden ladderreaching down
When the man comes around
The hairs on your armwill stand up
At the terror in each sipand in each sup
For you partakeof that last offered cup
Or disappearinto the potter's ground
When the man comes around
Hear the trumpetshear the pipers
One hundred millionangels singing
Multitudes are marchingto the big kettle drum
Voices callin', voices cryin'
Some are bornan'some are dyin'
It's Alpha 's and Omega 'skingdom come
And the whirlwindis in the thorn tree
The virgins are alltrimming their wicks
The whirlwindis in the thorn tree
It's hard for theeto kick against the pricks
Till Armageddonno Shalam, no Shalom
Then the father henwill call his chickens home
The wise men will bow downbefore the throne
And at his feet they'll casttheir golden crown
When the man comes around
Whoever is unjustlet him be unjust still
Whoever is righteouslet him be righteous still
Whoever is filthylet him be filthy still
Listen to the wordslong written down
When the man comes around
Hear the trumpetshear the pipers
One hundred millionangels singin'
Multitudes are marchin'to the big kettle drum
Voices callin', voices cryin'
Some are bornan'some are dyin'
It's Alpha and Omega 'skingdom come
And the whirlwindis in the thorn tree
The virgins are alltrimming their wicks
The whirlwindis in the thorn tree
It's hard for theeto kick against the pricks
In measured hundredweightand penny pound
When the man comes around