I know we haven't been
together that long,
but these last ten months
have just been the happiest of my life.
You're not only the person I love,
you're also my best friend,
and I want to spend
the rest of my life with you.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
Seriously.
Do you think that sounds good?
- No! - Really? 'Cause I think
that kinda sums up--
- No!
- Oh? Oh, sorry. Sorry.
Sometimes these catheters
can pinch a little bit.
Well, thanks for listening.
I really appreciate it.
You've got a real gentle
touch there, Doctor.
She won't be able to say no.
Actually, I'm a nurse.
Doctor'll be right in.
- Good luck, Greg.
- Thanks, Kim. - Good luck, buddy.
Okay, it's time
for our problem of the week.
I want you to pick out
your problem--
a problem that's been
bothering you all week--
With your eyes still closed,
I want you to picture
that problem in your mind.
Pretend that it's right there
in front of you.
Not only are you my best friend,
but you're also the person
I wanna spend the rest of my life with.
I love you.
Will you... marry me?
Now I want you to scare your problems away.
I want you to say boo.
All right, you guys are great.
Very good. I will see you guys
after lunch, all right?
Hey, Pam, isn't that
your special friend outside?
Yeah, I think so.
Why don't you go
talk to him?
- You think I should?
- Yeah.
Come here.
- Hi, sweetie.
- How you doin'?
- What's going on?
- I was in the neighborhood, got off work early.
Thought maybe you wanted
to get a bite to eat.
Oh, that's very sweet.
What a nice surprise.
Oh, shoot, I forgot
to change my shoes.
You don't have to change.
I can't resist a man in nurse's shoes.
I know, but I got sneakers
in my backpack.
- It'll just take a second.
- Okay.
honey--
Pam, I love you.
I love you too.
Come on, sweetie.
I got a half hour before I have to be back,
so you wanna go have lunch?
- What are you doing?
- Um, nothing.
I just love you so much.
These last ten months
have been the happiest of my life.
Yeah, they've been amazing.
What's going on?
Nothing. I just-- I just--
I just feel like we're so close.
You're my best friend, and you're also
the woman that I love, and--
Are you okay, sweetie?
You're acting so weird.
I'm fine. I just got a crick in my neck.
I was doing C.P.R....
...on a 300-pound crack addict
this morning. - Oh, my goodness!
Do you want me to massage
your neck or something?
- No, no, no, I'm fine, I'm good.
- A back rub? Are you sure?
Honey, look, your kids--
they're trying to tell you something.
- What? Hold on.
- Look!
- Oh, it's my sister. Hello? Hi!
- I'm engaged!
You're engaged! That's wonderful.
Congratulations!
Oh, my God, you're getting
married in two weeks. That's a little soon.
Wow, Mom and Dad really don't know
Bob very well. Dad was okay with this?
Well, Bob asked Dad.
Wow, that was very thoughtful of him.
I can't believe he knew
to ask Dad's permission.
I'm just here with Greg.
He's gonna take me out for lunch. He's okay.
Okay, yeah, I know you gotta go.
I love you.
Okay, talk to you soon.
Bye.
-So what's going on? What?
Debbie's marrying that guy?
- Yeah, in two weeks.
Dr. Bob of Denver.
Isn't that great?
Yeah, yeah, that's--
Didn't they just meet like a few months ago?
Well, yeah, but, you know, he asked her,
and she said yes.
He asked my dad. He said yes.
Then he asked Debbie.
Huh? Yeah, I overheard that.
So, what, like he had to ask his permission?
No, no, he didn't have to.
Bob just understood that Dad appreciates
that kind of thing.
Anyway, Deb said
Dad's crazy about him.
Evidently, Bob bought him, like, the
perfect gift that just won him over.
Really? Huh?
A gift?
Are you sure it's okay
to X-ray this?
Yeah, it's not gonna mutate
or anything.
- Uh, sir, that's not gonna fit.
- Wait. Hang on a second.
The bag's too big, guy.
You gotta check it.
Over here.
Raise your arms, sir.
I've got an engagement ring
for my girlfriend in the bag.
I can't open it here. Don't you think
I can just carry it on?
Hey, pal, if it ain't fittin' through the
frame, you ain't carryin' it on the plane.
- 531 -- New York La Guardia.
Check it. - Wait, wait!
- Excuse me! - Don't worry.
It'll be waitin' for you on the other side.
Baby, hurry
Don't make me worry
Welcome to New York's
La Guardia Airport.
Excuse me. Hi.
You lost my bag, and there's a
two-carat diamond ring inside it.
I didn't lose
your anything, sir.
But put your local address on this form,
and we'll ship it when it surfaces.
And what if it doesn't? Am I supposed
to spend the entire weekend...
with just the clothes
on my back?
It's a great gift. I just thought you
were gonna get them champagne.
Trust me. I think your dad is gonna
be very psyched about this gift.
Well, don't forget
he's retired, though.
The guy was in the rare-flower
business for 30 years. I think
he still maintains an interest.
- You make it sound like
they're really hard to please.
- No, not at all!
He's the sweetest man
in the whole world. Just relax!
He's gonna love you.
I promise.
As much as he loves Dr. Bob?
Take it easy on the sarcasm.
Humor is entirely wasted on my parents.
What, are they Amish?
Okay, no jokes.
- What are you doing?
- What?
I told you my dad sees smoking
as a sign of weakness.
Okay, all right,
I'll leave 'em in the car.
No, no, no, no, he'll check there.
Oh, gosh.
Yeah, the roof is probably
a better idea.
...we're not living together.
- I thought you said you told him.
- Well--
- I missed you so much, Pamcake.
- I missed you too, Flapjack.
Short stack, short stack,
coming up.
Where's my "wittle" girl?
- Mommy! Mom!
- You look so beautiful.
So do you. Look at you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Mom, Dad, this is Greg.
- Hi, Greg. I'm Pam's father, Jack Byrnes.
- Great to finally meet you.
- Good meeting you. - And I'm Dina.
Welcome to Oyster Bay.
What are you driving there,
a Ford?
Oh, yeah, it's a Taurus.
We were gonna get a mid-size,
but I figure, hey, we pull down decent bucks.
Might as well go all out,
pop for the full-size.
Sure. Interesting color.
You pick it?
Oh, no, the guy at the counter.
Why?
Well, they say
geniuses pick green.
- But you didn't pick it.
- Jack!
Oh, yucky.
What smells of old sour milk?
- Oh, poor Greg got spit up on by a baby.
- He didn't.
Yeah, he did, Ma, at the lost luggage
counter. The airline lost his bag.
They didn't!
- Yeah.
- Yeah, they did.
- What about you, honey?
- Oh, no, no, no. I carried on.
That's my girl.
It'll turn up, I'm sure.
And anyway, Greg, meanwhile,
anything you need, just ask.
- That's right. Mi casa es su casa.
- Oh, thanks, Jack. You too.
- This is so nice.
- We like it.
Beautiful.
Oh, now, Greg, you have
a very unique last name.
Um, we were curious,
how do you pronounce it?
Oh, just like it's spelled.
F-O-C-K-E-R.
Focker.
Hmm, Focker. Hmm.
- Oh, I'll get it, honey.
- Oh, thanks, Mom.
- Oh, there he is. There's our little guy.
-Jinxy, come here, boy.
Come here, baby. Come to Daddy, Jinxy.
Come on. Come on, Jinxy.
Come here.
Come to Daddy.
Come on.
Taught him that in one week.
This is Pam's cat, Jinxy.
Jinxy, say hello to Greg.
- Hi, Jinx. - Wave to Greg.
- Hello, Jinx.
Attaboy.
That took me another week.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Pam, I didn't know you had a cat.
Yeah, I left him here
when I moved to Chicago.
Your daddy's
found his new best friend.
You won't believe it.
He even taught him to use the potty.
- He did? Dad, that's kinda weird, isn't it?
- What's so weird about it?
- Now we don't have to smell
kitty litter all the time. - That's right.
That's incredible. How did you teach
the cat to use the toilet?
Oh, that was easy, Greg. I just designed
a litter box to put inside the toilet,
and then once he got used to it,
I took it away.
- Yeah, makes sense.
- But I don't think he likes it.
I mean, every chance he gets,
he tries to dig, squat and bury.
I had to move all my
potted plants off the floor.
Plus, you got another guy
around the house to leave the seat up.
He can't lift the seat, Greg.
- He lacks the strength
and the opposable thumbs. - Yeah.
Ah, right. Opposable--
I didn't think about that.
Jinx is strictly a house cat.
Can't let him outside because he
lacks outdoor survival skills.
One of those things,
isn't it, sweetheart?
I don't think Greg will be playing
with Jinxy too much. He hates cats.
Pam, I don't hate cats.
I don't-- I don't hate cats.
I just happen to be more of a dog lover.
Yeah, yeah. I am too.
- Well, that's okay if you hate cats, Greg.
- No!
- I don't. I don't hate cats at all.
- That's okay.
Just be honest about it.
There's some things I hate.
I-- I'm being honest.
Really? Like what?
Honey, why don't we let
the kids freshen up, huh?
Greg, you come with me.
We'll get you something to wear
from Jack's closet, okay?
- Yeah?
- I'm so happy you're home, sweetheart.
Oh! Me too, Dad.
Hey, listen, be nice to this one, okay?
I kinda like him.
- Okay, I'll try.
- Thank you.
- Shirt fit okay, Greg?
- Oh, fantastic. Thanks, Jack.
Good.
Tom Collins coming up.
- You know, I wish you hadn't
told your parents I hate cats.
- But you do hate cats.
Yeah, but you didn't have to
tell them right when we met.
I know. I'm sorry.
It just kinda slipped out.
- Get your red-hot papooses.
- My goodness, what is that?
Oh, that's just a little something from me.
Go ahead. Open it up.
Oh. Look, honey,
Greg brought us a present.
Oh, isn't that nice?
Oh, look at this.
It's a flower pot
with the dirt in it.
Actually, the real gift is
what's planted in the soil.
The bulb
of a Jerusalem tulip.
Which I was told is one of the rarest
and most beautiful flowers in existence.
Oh, right, right,
the Jerusalem--
From the "Jerusales tulipesias" genus.
Yes, yes.
Anyway, yeah,
the guy said with regular watering,
it should bloom in about 6 months, so--
Oh, we'll look forward
to that, Greg.
So, Greg, how's your job?
Um, good, Pam.
Thanks for asking.
I, uh, I recently
got transferred to triage.
Oh, is that better than a nurse?
No, Mom, triage is
a unit of the E.R.
- It's where all the top nurses work.
- Well--
No, they do.
Not many men in your profession, though,
are there, Greg?
No, Jack, not traditionally.
Oh, Pam, honey, did you know
that your father started his own business?
Really?
Dad, that's great.
Yes, I thought with my knowledge
and experience,
why should I allow
retirement to stop me?
- I really admire that.
- Yeah.
So what is it?
What's the new venture?
Let me ask you a question, Greg.
Let's just say
you have kids...
and you wanna get out of the house,
spend a night on the town.
So, you hire a baby-sitter,
someone you think you can trust.
References, work experience--
it all checks out fine.
But then how do you
really know for certain...
that your loved ones are safe
with this stranger?
I mean, can you ever really trust another
human being, Greg?
Sure, I think so.
No, the answer is you cannot.
Let me show you something.
Take a look at this, Greg.
What's this look like to you?
This looks like
a teddy bear.
Smile, you're on "Nanny Camera."
I've seen these things
advertised on TV.
Oh, no, not like this, you haven't.
Take a look.
Oh, my gosh.
Hi!
- Where's the other camera?
- Right here in this decorative artifact.
- Wow, that's great.
- Our cameras are motion-activated,
so they begin taping as soon as
they sense any movement.
We can hide 'em in anything.
We hide 'em in mirrors, lamps,
televisions, you name it.
So no matter where you go,
we'll be watching you.
So, Jack, couldn't this
maybe be construed as illegal?
You know, invasion of privacy?
Trust me, Greg, when you
start having little Fockers running around,
you'll understand the need
for this level of protection.
Impressive, isn't it?
Quite.
- Oh, I'll get that.
- I'll get it. I'll get it.
Honey, I'll get it.
Any problem
with the documents?
Okay. I'll meet you at the
Oyster Bay Drugstore in about 20 minutes.
Now you gotta be more careful
when you call here.
If anybody else answers,
just use a Southern accent...
and ask for
the vegetarian special, okay?
Oh, that wasn't the airline, was it?
Nope, wrong number.
We're all out of Collins mix,
so I'm gonna make a run for the store.
That's funny.
I thought I just bought some.
You know how that stuff-- it just goes,
so I'll be back in a jiff.
Well, why doesn't Greg
go with you?
Sweetie, you'll need something
in case your suitcase doesn't show up.
- Oh, I'm sure it'll show up.
- Yeah.
You don't wanna take a chance.
You don't have a toothbrush.
Go on, sweetie.
- Yeah.
- Okay, unless you want some privacy.
Why would I need privacy?
No, I didn't think you would.
- Okay, let's head out.
- Oh, good.
Bye.
Have fun, you guys.
Pam, he seems wonderful.
- He is. We have the best time together.
- Good.
Now, have you two been
- Mother!
- Oh, thinking about anything permanent.
Oh, I don't know.
I mean, we haven't really discussed it,
but I definitely
have a feeling this is it.
Dad seems to like him.
Don't you think?
Absolutely.
Big day, Saturday.
Yes.
This car is--
You got-- What do you use?
Unleaded? Regular unleaded?
Premium.
Hey, you know, Jack,
now that we have a second to talk,
I just want you to know
how much Pam means to me.
I know-- I know that we haven't been
together that long,
but the time that we have spent together
has been really incredible.
Greg, how come
you don't like cats?
I don't not like cats.
I- just--
I just prefer dogs.
I mean, I'm just more of a dog kind of,
you know--
Come home, wagging their little tails,
happy to see you kind of--
You need that assurance?
You prefer an emotionally shallow animal?
You see, Greg,
when you yell at a dog,
his tail will go between
his legs and cover his genitals,
his ears will go down.
A dog is very easy to break,
but cats make you work for their affection.
They don't sell out the way dogs do.
You like Peter, Paul and Mary?
Yes, I do. I'm a big fan.
Puff the magic dragon
Dragon
Lived by the sea
- Great song.
- Yeah, one of my favorites.
Who would've thought it wasn't really
about a dragon, huh?
What do you mean?
You know,
the whole drug thing.
No, I don't know.
Why don't you tell me?
Some people think that...
to "puff the magic dragon"
means to--
They're really, uh--
to smoke-- to smoke--
a marijuana cigarette.
Well, Puff's just the name
of the boy's magical dragon.
Right.
- Are you a pothead, Focker?
- No! No.
What?
No, no, no, no, Jack.
No, I'm-- I'm not-- I--
I pass on grass all the time.
- I mean, not all the time.
- Yes or no?
No. Yes. No.
Hey, Greg, I'll meet you back out front
in about... 12 to 15 minutes.
Hey.
How you doing?
Do you have any of those
nicotine patches?
No. We have the gum.
- Great.
- You chew it.
Thank you. Yes, okay.
And what's your most expensive
bottle of champagne?
Mumm's.
It's on sale for 13.95.
Really? That's it?
You don't have, like,
a nice, like, 80 or $100 bottle
of something?
You can get
a whole bunch of Mumm's.
- Focker.
- Hey, Jack. Ready to go?
I've been ready, yeah.
They ran out of Collins mix.
- You been waiting here long?
- No, I was just reading up about...
...pumps.
- Pumps?
Yes. Breast pumps.
I grew up on a farm.
Get your hot buns,
hot patooties.
Wow, Dina,
everything looks fabulous.
It's such a treat for me to have
a home-cooked meal like this.
Dinner at my house usually
consisted of everybody in the kitchen...
fighting over containers
of Chinese food.
You poor thing. What, there wasn't
enough food to go around?
No, there was.
We just never really sat down
like a family like this.
Greg, would you like
to say grace?
Oh, uh, well,
Greg's Jewish, Dad. You know that.
You're telling me Jews don't pray, honey?
Unless you have some objection.
No, no, no, no,
I'd love to.
Pam, come on,
it's not like I'm a rabbi or something.
I said grace
at many a dinner table.
Oh dear God,
thank You.
You are such a good God to us,
a kind and gentle...
and accommodating God.
And we thank You, Osweet,
sweet Lord of hosts...
for the...
smorgasbord...
You have so aptly lain
at our table this day...
and each day... by day.
Day by day by day.
Oh dear Lord,
three things we pray.
To love Thee more dearly,
to see Thee more clearly,
to follow Thee
more nearly...
day by day...
by day.
Amen.
Oh, Greg, that was lovely.
Thank you, Greg.
That was interesting too.
Oh, that's a-- that's a lovely vase.
That's great.
Let me guess, Jack.
Is that one of your secret cameras too?
Greg, that's an urn which holds
the remains of Jack's mother.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
That's all right.
You didn't know, Greg.
- I'm--
- That's our Gran-gran.
We like to think of her
as watching over us as we eat.
Love you, Ma.
Miss you.
Miss you every day.
Oh, honey, why don't you
read Greg your poem?
Oh, no, he doesn't want
to hear that.
What? No!
What-What-What poem?
You see,
when Jack had to retire...
...for health reasons--
- That's a bunch of malarky.
Honey, I'm fine.
The doctor thought it would be
therapeutic if he...
sort of expressed his emotions
in an artistic way.
Honey, you wrote the most beautiful poem
about your mother.
Please, we really
wanna hear it.
- Poem, poem.
- Please!
Oh, all right.
It's a work in progress.
I'm still not happy with it.
As soon as it's ready,
then I am going to glaze it
onto a plate...
...and put it next to the urn.
- Nice.
It's very special.
"My Mother"
by Jack Byrnes.
"You gave me life,
you gave me milk,
'you gave me courage.
"Your name was Angela,
the angel from heaven,
"but you were also an angel of God,
and He needed you too.
"Selfishly I tried
to keep you here...
"while the cancer
ate away your organs...
"like an unstoppable
rebel force.
"But I couldn't save you,
and I shall see your face...
"nevermore, nevermore,
"nevermore,
until we meet...
in heaven."
Daddy, that's beautiful.
It always gets me.
Amazing. So-So--
So much love, yet also
so much information.
It takes a lot out of him.
- Greg, would you like some yams?
- Thank you. Oh, yeah.
You must've had vegetables fresher
than that, growing up on a farm, Greg.
Dad, Greg grew up in Detroit.
He told me he grew up on a farm.
- Do they have many farms in Detroit?
- No, Dina, no, not a lot.
In fact, Jack,
I should clarify this.
I didn't actually grow up...
on a farm per se.
The house we grew up in
was originally erected...
in the early Dutch farm,
colonial style.
So that, plus we had
a lot of pets--
- Which one did you milk then?
- Dad!
Honey, he said he pumped milk.
What have you ever milked?
A cat.
A cat?
- I milked a cat once.
You wanna hear a story? - Sure.
My sister had a cat, and the cat birthed
a litter of kittens.
Must've been 30 of them,
and there was this one little runt...
this little sweet little...
little-engine-that-could runt...
who wanted to get up there
and couldn't really get access
to the-- to the--
to the teat.
Teat?
Dad.
What have you.
I went in and just simply,
you know, just--
into a little saucer,
then took the saucer and fed it to
Geppetto-- that's what I named him.
I had-- I had no idea
you could milk a cat.
Oh, yeah, you can milk
anything with nipples.
I have nipples, Greg.
Could you milk me?
Okay, could we change
the subject perhaps?
- Champagne, champagne.
- Yes.
- I thought maybe we could
celebrate with a little bubbly.
- That'd be great.
Good idea.
Yum!
"I have nipples.
Can you milk me?"
Well, in a funny way,
you've already seen Deb's ring.
That's true.
Would anybody care for a bottle
of Oyster Bay Drug and Sundries
finest champagne?
That is so sweet of you, Greg.
Isn't that a nice gesture?
- That's very nice.
- How could I have seen Debbie's ring, Mom?
Well, when I gave Bob
the okay to propose to Deb,
I put him in touch
with my diamond guy,
and he picked out the same design
Kevin gave you.
- Kevin, your old boyfriend?
- Thanks, Dad.
Well, yeah,
Kevin was Pam's fiance.
Oh, my God.
- Oh!
-Jinxy, no!
Greg, sweetie,
how you doing?
Oh, just fine, considering I desecrated
your grandma's remains,
found out you were engaged
and had your father ask me to milk him.
At least back then he was
still talking to me.
- I can't believe you didn't
tell me you were that close.
- Who, Daddy and me?
No, Kevin and you.
Do we have to know everything
about each other's pasts?
You never told me about
your cat-milking days in Motown.
That was
a long time ago, Pam.
Yeah, okay, well,
so was this.
Kevin's and my connection
was more physical than anything else.
Physical? Like what?
Like you worked out together?
No, no, it was nothing, nothing.
It was a stupid sexual thing.
I'm gonna go throw up now.
Greg, listen.
Kevin and I were only engaged
for a month before I realized
that I'd made a mistake, okay?
I gave back the ring,
I moved to Chicago,
and I met and fell in love with you, okay,
so can we please drop this?
- Good. - I just feel like this
is not going well at all.
- I feel like your dad hates me.
- He doesn't hate you, sweetie.
Come on. Just give him
a chance, all right?
Maybe he's nervous too, huh?
I thought he would love my gift,
you know, being this big flower guy,
but it's like he didn't
even show the slightest bit of interest.
Listen to me.
Forget the gift.
You are the most adorable,
loving, sweetest man in the whole world,
and I love you.
And very soon my parents
are gonna see that...
and grow to love you too, okay?
Speaking of growing
to love you--
- Honey, it's late.
- I know it's late.
But Mr. Winky is still
on Chicago time,
and we both know there's only one way
to make Mr. Winky go away.
And there it is.
What's with the robe?
It's Pam's. My pajamas are in the suitcase
with everything else.
- Hey, I'll lend you a pair of Jack's.
Okay, honey? - Sure.
- You don't have to do that,
- Oh, no, no, no.
No, that's fine.
We have to.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Look, Greg, I just wanna say, don't worry
about what happened tonight.
Oh, thanks, Jack.
Still, I feel horrible. I mean--
Well, it was
a horrible thing.
But let's just put all that behind us
and enjoy our weekend together.
Okay. Okay.
Thank you, Daddy.
- Oh, thank you.
- Thanks, Mom.
- These'll do just fine.
- Good night.
Night-night.
Good night, sweetie.
See you in the morning.
- Have a nice sleep.
- Okay, you too.
Oh, no, no, no, Greg, we made up
the pullout for you down in the den.
Oh, okay, 'cause Pam said
I should sleep in Debbie's room.
Well, Debbie'll be
sleeping here tomorrow.
This way, you'll have more privacy,
you'll have your own bathroom.
Just try not to flush the toilet.
It's always a little quirky.
- Okay.
- Oh, one more thing.
I'm a realist. I understand it's
the 21st century,
and you've probably had
premarital relations with my daughter.
But under our roof, it's my way
or the Long Island Expressway.
- Is that understood?
- Of course, yeah.
Good. Keep your snake
in its cage for 72 hours.
Okay.
Welcome to Atlantic American Airways'
Lost Luggage Department.
At Atlantic American Airways,
customer satisfaction always comes first.
We are experiencing
heavy call volume.
Your call is very important to us.
It will be answered in approximately 27 minutes.
Please press "1" if you'd like
to talk to a representative
We are closed for the night.
Please call back--
Sorry.
I don't know what it is,
but there's just something
about him that's a little off.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Jack, you know we've been
through this...
with every boyfriend Pam has had
since, what, middle school.
I think Greg--
he's a lovely young man.
And, honey, Pam thinks
he might be the one.
She said that?
She said those exact words?
I didn't tape record it, Jack,
but that's the impression.
What kind of a family doesn't have time
to sit down for dinner?
- Fugitives.
- Please try to enjoy the weekend, honey.
- Both our daughters are in love.
- That's what I'm worried about.
- Oh, geez, I just realized something.
- What?
Pam's middle name.
Martha.
Pamela Martha Focker.
"Operation Ko Samui"?
Looking for something,
Greg?
Jesus, Jack, you scared me.
I heard a noise, so I came down
to see if everything was okay.
Everything's fine. I just-- I'm sorry.
I saw a light on, and I kinda stumbled in.
- I didn't realize--
- That's okay. See anything interesting?
No, not at all.
I mean, I mean--
I mean, this is great, though.
I love this-- what you-- it's a cozy little nook.
I noticed you were looking
at that when I came in.
- Yeah. - It's an antique
polygraph machine.
Is that what that is?
I've seen these before,
but I never saw one
actually up close.
You know what?
Why don't you try that on?
Oh, that's okay.
Oh, come on. We'll have some fun.
I'll show you how it works.
I shouldn't.
- Why should you be afraid?
You have nothing to hide. - No, I know.
- I know you know, so there
shouldn't be any problem.
- No, there's no problem.
- So, try it on.
- Okay.
I'll help you.
Don't worry.
You'll enjoy this.
All right.
Looks complicated.
Now these aren't 100% accurate, right?
- They're--
You'd be surprised how accurate they are.
They can tell fairly easily
if someone's lying or not.
Now I'm gonna ask you
some questions,
and all you have to do
is answer "yes" or "no."
- Okay.
- All right.
Let's give it a whirl.
Did you fly on an airplane today?
- Yes, I did.
- No peeking.
- Did we eat pot roast
for dinner tonight? - Yes.
Was it under-cooked?
No, it was rare.
It was a little rare
for my taste.
- But I wouldn't--
- I'm just kidding, I'm just--
Relax. Relax.
The needles are jumping.
Have you ever watched
pornographic videos?
- I mean, well, I don't--
- Yes or no?
What's the matter?
You can't sleep?
No, no, I'm just going over some
of my answers from the polygraph
test your dad gave me.
- Oh, no, he didn't.
- Yeah, he did.
Well, did you lie to him?
No! I mean--
Well, he asked me if
we were living together,
and--
What'd you tell him?
Nothing.
Your mother walked in...
and yanked the little thingies
off before I had to answer.
Is this how you'd react
if I told you he shoved bamboo
shoots up my fingernails?
Or does he hook all your boyfriends up
to his little machine?
Well, he doesn't need a machine.
He's a human lie detector.
- What? - Greg, my father was never
in the rare flower business.
That was just his cover.
He was in the C.I.A.
for 34 years.
How could you not tell me this?
I wanted to, honey,
but it was strictly...
on a need-to-know basis.
So, what? He's in the C.I.A.?
He was a spy? He is a spy?
No, he was more like
a psychological profiler.
They used him to interrogate
suspected double agents in the company.
Oh, that's great.
Yeah.
I was scared of your dad
back when I thought he was a florist.
It's wonderful to know that I've actually got
a C.I.A. spy-hunter on my ass.
Would you stop?
You're doing great, okay?
This is a lot to take in, honey.
I'm sorry.
- It's just weird.
- Oh, I know, but you're doing fine.
I promise.
- Mm, no, no!
- W-What's wrong, sweetie?
I forgot. I'm not supposed to let
the snake out of my cage.
Your what?
I told your dad I wouldn't touch you
for 72 hours.
Okay, I'm not in junior high
anymore, so-- No, no, no.
Seriously. I want to try
to respect his rules, okay?
Okay. Fine.
Uh, why don't you go ahead
and get some sleep,
and I'll see you in the morning.
- Morning, Greg.
- Good morning.
Pam told me she let you in
on a little secret of mine last night.
Yes, she did.
Well, as long as you can keep your
mouth shut for the rest of your life,
you're in no immediate danger.
I won't tell.
I'm just being humorous.
Huh. That was funny.
But the fact is, Greg, with the knowledge
you've been given,
you are now on the inside
of what I like to call...
"the Byrnes family
circle of trust."
I keep nothing from you,
you keep nothing from me...
and round and round we go.
Okay.
Understood.
Okay, good. Come on. Let's go inside
and have breakfast.
Jinxy cat, Jinxy cat
where are you
I love you
Jinxy. Jinxy.
Not at the table,
honey, please.
- Attaboy!
- Hey, hey, look who's up!
- Hi, sweetie.
- You must be Greg.
- Hello. - Oh, look, somebody had a visit
from the hair fairy.
- Oh, yes.
- Nice 'do, nice 'do.
I'll do the intros.
Greg, this is my sister, Debbie.
- Hi. - Nice to meet you.
Oh, the bride to be.
- Congratulations.
- And her fiancée, Dr. Bob.
You can call me
Bob... M.D.
- These are his parents, Linda Banks,
- Hi. How are you?
- Nice to meet you.
...and the world-famous plastic surgeon...
Dr. Larry.
Whoa, now, cut that out.
You know, Greg's
in medicine, too, Larry.
- Oh, really? What field?
- Nursing.
That's good.
No, really.
What field?
Nursing.
Hey, why don't I get you
a chair, Greg?
Thank you.
Thanks.
So, you didn't want
to go for the M.D.?
No, I actually thought
about becoming a doctor,
but I decided it wasn't for me.
Just as well.
Boards are killer.
Actually Greg aced
his MCATs.
- You serious?
- No, I did okay.
Oh, he did more than okay.
Trust me.
Why did you take the test
if you weren't planning
on going to med school?
Well, I wanted to keep
my options open,
but in the end,
nursing was a better fit for me.
It gives you the freedom to work
in several different areas of medicine.
Plus, I can focus
100% on patient care,
as opposed to being a doctor where
you have to deal with the bureaucracy.
- Wasn't your friend Andy
supposed to be here by now?
- Oh, my God!
I thought Deb told you.
Dr. Andy threw out his back.
He can't make the wedding.
Oh, damn. Now I have to reconfigure
the whole procession.
Bob, why doesn't Greg
stand in for Andy, be the usher?
- Oh! No, Pam, no. - That'll be fine.
Bob, Greg'll be your second usher.
- Good. - Uh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, okay, sure.
Good. Let's all finish up
and get ready to go...
...because we have a pre-activity
briefing in about 32 minutes.
- Thirty-two minutes!
You know what? In that case,
I'd better get upstairs...
and pay a little visit
to the shower fairy.
Dina, thank you so much
for breakfast.
Hey, you okay?
Why didn't you wake me up?
- Because I thought you'd like to sleep late.
- Not when I'm a guest.
- It's okay. Don't worry about it.
- No, it's not okay.
Tell that to Dr. Torquemada in there
with the Grand Inquisition.
Go take a shower, get dressed
and come back down.
- Get dressed in what?
- Borrow some more of Dad's clothes.
- No, I don't-- Come on.
- Why not, honey?
I just-- No, I don't feel comfortable
wearing your dad's underwear.
Okay, well, go wake up Denny
and borrow some of his.
You want me to go wake up
your brother who I never met...
and ask if I could have
some of his clothes?
Okay, all right. Where's Denny's room?
Top of the stairs, turn right.
Hello?
What the hell you doing in here?
I'm-- I'm Greg,
Pam's friend.
What? Were you just
sniffing my boxers, dude?
No, dude, no. No, no, she said
I could come up here,
...maybe borrow some clothes from you.
- Do me a favor. Close the door.
- Okay.
- Quick.
- Tell anybody I wasn't here?
- No, they think you're asleep.
- Yeah, so, it's all good.
- You scared me.
Dad keeps you guys under
a pretty close watch, huh?
No, it's not that bad. Your little Pamcake's
got it a lot worse than I do.
- Oh! You need some clothes.
- Yes, that would be-- that would be great.
- Glad to hook you up.
- Cool. - All right?
Like what you done
with the crib.
Oh, Lil' Kim.
She's phat.
P-H phat.
Yeah, I think these ought a do it.
All right, here you go, chief.
- All right!
- Enjoy!
- Thanks a lot, Denny.
- No problem.
Oh, and don't worry
about the little covert op, all right?
- I'll keep it on the lowdown.
- Down low.
No doubt.
People, people, come get
your revised itineraries.
Larry, Linda,
Debbie, Bob, honey.
Now, I'm gonna activate the alarm.
It'll go off in T minus 16 seconds.
- I don't think I need a jacket.
- It's cold out, honey.
Hold on.
Here, take Denny's jacket.
Hey, Denny, I'm lending Greg
your jacket, okay? Whatever.
Let's go.
Denny, how's the tux fit?
- Dad, uh--
- What's that?
I-It's a sculpture
I found in Greg's jacket.
This isn't a sculpture, Denny.
This is a device for smoking marijuana.
Really?
Not mine.
It's not.
Oh, hey, Jack.
How you doing?
I like the top hat.
Complements you.
Can I talk to you
for a minute?
Sit down.
Did I not clearly explain
the circle of trust to you, Greg?
Mm, yeah, I think I got it.
Then is there something
you wanna tell me?
I don't think so.
Didn't we have a discussion yesterday
in the car about this?
Oh, yes!
You mean-- Yes!
You mean me and Pam.
Yes, I would love to talk to you about that.
We're not talking about Pam.
We're talking about you.
See, if I can't trust you,
Greg, then I have no choice...
but to put you right back
outside the circle.
And once you're out, you're out.
There's no coming back.
Mm, well, I would definitely like
to stay inside the circle.
Well, then, tell me the truth.
Jack, I don't know
what we're talking about.
All right, now look, Focker,
I'm a patient man.
That's what 19 months in a
Vietnamese prison camp will do to you.
But I will be watching you,
studying your every move.
And if I find that you are trying
to corrupt my firstborn child,
I will bring you down, baby.
I will bring you down
to Chinatown.
Where are we? I thought
we were going to Kevin's house.
We are, sweetie.
This is Kevin's new house.
- Oh, this is a crazy house.
- Not bad, huh, Dad?
Maybe he uses marijuana for medicinal purposes.
People do that nowadays.
Honey, this kid has been lying to us
from the moment we met him.
Hey, you. Get in some
quality time with the boys?
Uh-huh, yeah, it was fun.
Listen, I hope this lunch
isn't too weird for you.
Why would "B.B.Q
at Best Man's" be weird?
Oh, my God, Greg.
I was sure I told you.
Kevin is Bob's best man.
This is his place.
- Kevin, your ex-fianc?
- Welcome, everybody.
I don't understand.
How does he know Bob?
Well, they-- they went
to lacrosse camp together,
and Kevin was the one
who introduced Bob to Debbie.
Lacrosse camp?
I was really lucky
I was able to salvage this wood...
from an old seamen's chapel
in Nantucket.
Kevin, the house is amazing.
This is where
Maybe you should have
gotten married here.
All right, the sun is out,
the grill is hot and the pool is luke.
If I can interest you
in a swim and a little B.B.Q, just follow me.
All right, Kevo.
Right on schedule.
- Bring it on.
- Wow. It must cost a fortune...
Wait till you see
the rest of the house.
-You okay, sweetie?
- Yeah.
I'm really sorry.
I don't know why I thought you knew.
It-- It's not
a big deal.
If I can handle a weekend
without sex and cigarettes,
I think I can handle an afternoon
with your ex-fiancée?
Okay. Thank you.
Now, for the floor that you're walking on,
I chose this Bolivian wormwood.
I think it works well in here. I have the
Viking range here and the twin Sub-Z's.
- Yeah, they open up right there.
- Oh, I get it. Like hidden.
- Yeah, kind of blend in.
- Great.
Are you a homeowner, Greg?
No, no, I rent.
So, things are going real, real well
for you, aren't they, eh, Kevo?
Gosh, things have been going
so great lately.
I got in early on some
wireless I.P.O.s, and the stuff
just skyrocketed from there.
What about you, Greg?
What line of work are you in?
- I'm in health care. - Yeah, so you know
what I'm talking about.
There are a lot of Benjamins to be
made now with biotech stuff.
I don't have to tell you that.
How's your portfolio?
I'd say strong...
to quite strong.
You gotta strike
while the iron's hot.
Now's the time.
- Greg's a male nurse.
- That's right. Thank you, Jack.
Well, that's great.
That's great to give something
back like that. I'd love to
find time to do volunteer work.
Just the other day I saw
this golden retriever that--
He had like a gimp,
and he couldn't really--
It made me feel terrible.
I wish there was something I could do.
Yeah, well, I get paid, but also it feels,
you know, good too.
So it's kind of
an everybody wins.
What are you-- You're like
a Wall Street trader?
- An investment guy?
- No. I mean, I'm willing
to be painted with that brush.
Yes, that's my day job.
We have time?
We got time, don't we, Jack?
I want to show you what I'm really
interested in. Come on. Let's go.
Wow! It looks like
somebody got an "A" in wood shop.
Yeah, it's always been kind of a hobby.
I whittled that out of beech wood.
It's beautiful.
- So what got you into, uh, "carpentering"?
- Carpentry?
I guess I'd have to say Jesus.
He was a carpenter, and I
just figured if you're gonna
follow in someone's footsteps,
who better than Christ?
Greg's Jewish.
- Are you?
- Yeah.
Well, so was J.C.
Wow.
You're in good company.
Well, I'm gonna head
to the pool,
but why don't you show Greg and Pam
the gift?
- Wow, he made a gift.
-Greg.
I put a fresh coat
of lacquer on this this morning,
so bear with me
with the fumes.
- Isn't that something?
- That's incredible.
- Thank you.
- Roses. Deb's favorite.
- Yes, right. - It's beautiful.
The little holes are for candles.
Exactly. And then later,
they'll collect rainfall.
- They make a tiny birdbath.
- That's great.
It's beautiful.
What is it?
It's an altar.
Or you might call it a "ho-puh".
Isn't that sweet?
I'm gonna take it over
to the Byrneses',
and tomorrow Robert and Debra
will meet beneath it to become man and wife.
And later,
when they purchase a home,
maybe it will
grace their garden.
Well, that's my sappy,
romantic idea.
Must have taken forever to build.
No, not too bad.
About 70 hours.
Which isn't bad, considering I carved it all
by hand from one piece of wood.
Hey, Kevo.
12:15. Time to start
the barbecue, big guy.
Okay, Mr. B.
I better get back to playing host.
Okay, you guys,
grab your suits, and I'll
meet you down at the pool.
- I think I'm gonna take
a pass on the swimming.
- Oh, no, you can't.
I don't even have a suit with me.
The airline lost my bag and--
- Pamcake, let's go. Mom's got your suit here.
- Coming, Dad.
You better get going.
Gosh, she's great.
Congratulations, man.
Thank you. And, by the way, she just
had the nicest things to say about you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Gosh. Yeah, we had
some good times together.
Boy, she is a tomcat.
So, let me hook you up
with some trunks, Gregger.
- I'm not gonna swim.
- No, come on. I'm not taking no for an answer.
Cold buffet is on the left,
wine and champagne on the right.
Comin' through here.
Yeah, that'd be gre--
Hey, there he is!
Get out here.
G-Man, we got salmon, we got swordfish.
What's it gonna be?
Ah-- How 'bout a little of both, K-Dog?
I'm pretty hungry.
I think they call that
"the munchies."
Let's go. Hit the ball, Kev!
Show 'em what you got!
Come on, team.
He's got nothing.
- Service.
- Come on, Greg.
Nice serve, pal.
Oh, Greg! Come on!
- Whoo! Nice shot, Maverick!
- Sweet setup, Iceman.
- Nice one, Nurse.
- Glenn, Glenn, Glenn.
You gotta rush the net on defense.
Don't be afraid of the ball.
- It's Greg.
- Huddle up, team.
Greg, not Glenn.
Greg is afraid of the ball.
- Come on. This is unacceptable.
- He's gotta go for the ball.
- Here's what we gotta do.
- Let's go! We're gettin' cold in here.
- We're gettin' creamed.
- If Florence Nightingale
over here would play defense.
- Larry, I missed one shot.
- It was a big shot.
Larry, keep floatin' where
you are. You're doin' great.
Denny, take the deep shots.
Greg, nobody's expecting
much out of you.
- If I set you up with the ball,
can you jump up and spike it? - No.
Yeah. I'd have to be
pretty high, but yeah.
I bet you would, Panama Red.
- All right, everybody, look sharp. Break!
- Let's play some ball.
All right, here we go.
Let's go.
Come on.
Greg!
Set!
You gotta spike those, Focker!
You gotta spike those!
- Look how Bob did that. Nice play, Bob.
- Thanks, Jack.
Fire it up there, Focker!
Let's do it!
- Way to go, Deb!
- Greg!
Honey! God!
- What the hell's the matter with you?
- It's only a game, Focker!
Oh, honey! I'm coming!
Get some ice.
- My eye! Oh, my eye!
- Focker!
Pam, help your sister, please.
I'm sorry, Deb.
Deb, you can totally see Voit
backwards on your forehead.
- Denny, get outta here!
- You the bandleader? - Yes, sir.
Go over the song selection
with Bob. Bob? Bob!
- Yeah, Jack.
- Are you a Mr. Focker?
- Yes.
- Okay. Sign here, please.
Hey, your suitcase.
You go through it, make sure it's all there?
- Yeah, it's fine. - Good.
- What's up?
I just wanna make sure you're okay
since hitting the spike heard 'round the world.
- Oh, yeah. I'm really sorry about that.
- It's okay.
I don't know
what got into me, Iceman.
- "Iceman"? - I'm sorry. Is that a
special thing between you and Kev...
- Stop it.
- Stop what, Iceman?
Top Gun was a very popular movie
when Kevin and I dated.
- All right? That's it.
- Hey, Iceman.
Do you want to be Maverick?
Is that what this is all about?
- I can't be Maverick. Kevin's Maverick.
- He used to be,
but we can change that.
- Um, can he be Goose?
- No, because Goose dies in the end.
Very sad.
- Honey, I don't really--
- Greg, shut up.
- Jesus, Dad, you ever think of knocking?
- Not in my own den.
- What are you two doing in here?
- I'd say rounding in 2nd base.
- This is Greg's room, Dad.
- Not anymore. We're gonna
use it for storage.
Greg will stay
in Debbie's room, and she'll
bunk up with you tonight.
Fine.
Come on, Greg.
- Okay. I'll be right up.
- I'll meet you upstairs.
Oh, good.
They found your suitcase.
Hey, Jack, I don't quite know
what happened back at the tux shop,
but if I've given you
the wrong impression regarding
Pam in any way, I'm sorry.
Okay? I have nothing but the best
intentions with Pam, and I-I just--
Actually, there's something
in the suitcase here that
I'm planning on giving her...
that I think, um,
symbolizes...
the level
of my commitment, uh, to her.
And I wouldn't feel right
asking her to wear it...
without her father's permission.
Jack?
Did you flush
this toilet?
Maybe. You know what?
Maybe Jinx flushed it.
I saw little Jinxy
come in last night,
and he took a little squat
and relieved himself.
Jinx knows not to use that toilet,
and even if he did, he'd never flush it.
- What does it matter?
- The matter, Greg, R.N.,
is that when this toilet
is flushed, it runs,
and when you have a septic tank
that's nearly full and a toilet
that's been running all night,
then you could have
a hell of a problem.
Mr. Byrnes?
This is not part
of my job description.
Nice stench.
You're really on a roll there, bud.
Bite me, Denny!
In 20 hours, I'm having a wedding here,
so I need my cesspool pumped now!
- Not tomorrow. Now!
- Dad, what's going on?
- Oh, my God!
- What's that smell?
That smell, Bob,
is our shit.
Focker flushed the toilet in the den,
so the septic tank is overflowing.
Jack, I told you.
It wasn't me. It was Jinx.
Focker, I'm not gonna tell you again!
Jinx cannot flush the toilet.
He's a cat, for Christ sakes!
The animal doesn't
even have thumbs, Focker.
- Hey, look at this!
- Kevo!
Over by the tree, right?
No. No, no, no.
Not on the lawn!
Stay where you are.
What the heck?
I got my mojo workin'
Just won't work on you
I know that's what I said I wanted,
'cause that's what I wanted.
It is a black
Samsonite suitcase.
What I'm saying is, do you
think it's possible that
the Samsonite people,
in some crazy little scheme
to actually turn a profit,
made more than one?
- I don't think so.
- You don't?
- I am going to need your
baggage claim number again.
- Jinx, stop.
- I know I signed for it.
- I'm looking at your signature
right here, Mr. Focker.
- Do me a favor. Could I talk
to your supervisor? - Excuse me?
- What's your name?
- Joy.
- Okay, let me talk to your supervisor.
- My supervisor is on a break.
When he gets back, have him give me
a call right away.
- It's a very important bag.
- I'm sure it is--
- Don't ask me what it's for.
I need you to do this thing.
Please, I'm in a time situation here,
so just do it. I'll hold on.
- So the name's "Greg Focker"?
- I don't know. Greg or Gregory.
Run both names.
Jinx.
Come on. No. Jinx.
Come here. Jinxy.
Jinx. Oh, shit.
Greg didn't ace his med
school boards. He never
even took the goddamn MCATs.
Oh, Jack, that's what you
had your sources check out?
What this poor boy did
on some test scores?
I bet he doesn't even have
a real nursing degree.
A lot of these hospital workers
are just pill poppers looking
for easy access to ludes.
We already know that he's been
puffin' the magic dragon.
I knew the little crack
was lying.
Jinxy. Come here.
Come here, little Jinxy.
Jinxy cat, Jinxy cat
I won't hurt you.
The fact is,
Greg lied to you.
- He did not lie to me, Dad.
- He lied to you when I thought
you should know the truth.
I love you too much
to see you get hurt.
I don't care what your information says, Dad.
Greg took the MCATs. Okay?
No! Oh!
Oh, my God!
All right, everybody.
All right, stand back.
Stay back. Stay back.
Oh, Jack! Oh, God!
We've got a fire! Somebody call 911
right away! Hurry up!
Jinxy! Jinxy!
We checked every yard,
every car on the street.
Nobody's seen him.
He's not up in any
of the trees, Jack.
We checked all the bedrooms.
Jinx isn't up here.
Yeah, none of the neighbors
have seen him either.
You tried to milk him, didn't you,
you sick son of a bitch!
Dad, stop it.
That's enough.
Honey, please calm down.
How can I calm down...
if we're 15 minutes away
from the wedding rehearsal
and the ring bearer's missing?
- Whoa. What do you mean, "the ring bearer"?
- Your daddy didn't tell you?
He taught Jinx to walk down the aisle
with this little pillow.
Oh, no.
No, you didn't, Dad.
Yeah, yeah. You put this around
the neck, and these ribbons are for the rings.
That's adorable, Jack.
Oh, for Chris sakes!
- That's great, Dad.
- Yeah, but now we have
to postpone the rehearsal.
Bob, you ride with me.
Larry, you come with your car.
We're gonna canvass the neighborhood.
Dee, ask O'Boyle to wait.
If we're not back in an hour, we'll
reschedule the rehearsal for the morning.
- Jack! - No! We cannot cancel the
rehearsal for some stupid cat!
Stupid cat? How could you say that?
That cat's been like a brother to you!
We're supposed to let him wander
the streets without food, water or toilet?
- D-Dad, Greg'll find him.
- What?
- Yeah, what?
- Oh, that's wonderful.
Fine. Fine. Okay.
Denny?
- Denny? Denny? Denny!
- Dad, I'm right here.
Okay. You're gonna fill in
as the ring bearer for now.
- No. I'm not wearin' that
stupid pillow thing on my head.
- Oh, yes, you damn well will!
Jinx! Jinx!
Here, Jinx.
You just go and wander the streets
without food, water or toilet? Fucker!
Actually, you may be in luck.
They brought in a Himalayan a little while ago.
There he is.
Holyshit, that's Jinx.
- Jinxy!
- Uh, no, let me see that photo again.
You gotta picture him without
that stupid Santa cap.
- Come on, Jinxy. Jinxy!
- Uh, no.
You see, in the picture,
your cat has an all-black tail.
And this one has a white tip.
No, I'm sorry
about that, chief.
- Looks just like him.
- Almost.
Except for that tail.
Dearly beloved--
we are gathered here
on this beautiful day...
to join Dr. Robert Banks--
Dearly beloved, we are gathered here
on this beautiful day...
to join Dr. Robert Banks
and Debra Byrnes in holy matrimony.
This is a special day--
He found him!
Yea!
It's him!
I gotta see this.
- Look, Dad, it's Jinx.
- Oh, my little baby!
- We found you. We found you.
- Greg, thank you so much.
- Where did you find him?
- Gave us a little scare, huh?
For once in my life
I got someone who needs me
To Greg.
Hooray!
- Honey, where is Greg, anyway?
- He's in the restroom.
Yes, I tried there. I've tried every shelter
on the north shore, okay?
He's a brown-and-black Himalayan
with an all-black tail.
Mr. Jinx. Yeah, okay.
You go check. I'll call you back.
It's the man of the hour.
Sorry, folks. Had to pay a little visit
to the urinal fairy.
Greg, nice work
with the cat today.
Aw, thanks, Jack.
I'm just glad I could help out.
We never did get to finish
that little "convo" back at the den.
So, when you have a minute, there is
still something I'd like to talk to you about.
We'll get right to it as soon as
we get back. You have my word.
I'm gonna hold you to that.
Circle of trust.
Guess who's back in
the circle of trust.
Pull the string
and I'll wink at you
I'm your puppet
Oh, poor Kevin looks lonely.
Maybe I should ask him to dance.
What do you think?
Sure. I bet he could, uh, whittle a
private little dance floor for the two of you.
I'm serious.
I saw some beech wood outside.
He's very handy.
He's an extremely handy
and crafty craftsman.
I shouldn't paint him
with that brush, but--
Come on. Seriously. Seriously.
Part of you wishes you ended up with him.
Yes, he's very talented,
but it would've
never worked out.
Why not?
I was never in love with Kevin.
I'm in love with you.
- That's a good explanation.
- Think so?
Thought you'd like that.
- I do.
- I'm glad.
No, Jinx. Mr. Jinx.
I called you like half an hour ago.
Okay, I already--
I already described it. Airline.
Messages.
It's brown...
with a little bit
of black trim.
Yes.
Please enter
your four-digit code.
Jack, hi.
It's Hank MacAtee from next door.
You'll never guess who wandered
over here this afternoon. Mr. Jinx.
Yeah, he's not wearing his collar,
but, uh, I'm sure it's Jinxy.
Thought you might be worried, so just
give me a jingle when you guys get home,
and I'll bring
the little rascal over.
Okay, well, if you could just keep checking,
please, and I'll call you back later. Thanks.
Any luck?
No, they're still looking.
Hey, Jack,
this is a great party.
I guess sometimes these things sort
of come together in their own kooky sort of way.
Yeah, it's kind of like
the way you found Jinxy.
- You found him at that animal shelter, huh?
- Uh-huh. Yeah, right.
- Well, the important thing
is he's home now. - Yes.
Yeah. You know, there's something about
that ball of fur...
that just puts
a big smile on my face.
Yeah. You haven't seen any of
his latest tricks, have you?
Well, when we get back,
I'll show you.
We don't have to do it tonight.
He's had a long day. He's probably tired.
No, I think he'd like
to show you tonight.
Why don't you give me
the key and let me drive?
Hey, Larry. You know what?
Why don't I drive?
Be my guest, Focker.
- Hey, sweetie, what are you doing?
- Larry said I could drive.
- Let's go. Hurry, hurry.
- All right. Bye, guys.
- See you.
- Thanks for driving.
Drives a little better
than your Taurus, huh, Greg?
Come on. Get in the car, honey.
Let's go. Hurry up.
Whoa, Nellie!
Everybody comfortable
back there?
You're a real wild man
at that wheel there.
You got your seat belts on back there?
Get your seat belts on.
Oh, Jesus, Focker!
Focker, take it easy.
Benz drives like a dream, Larry.
Oh, there's Jack.
Hey, Jackie.
Wanna play, Pops?
Let's play.
Okay, now, Greg? Greg?
Is everything okay, honey?
Yeah, just trying
to make good time.
What the heck
is the matter with you?
All right. We're gonna be home.
We're gonna get home.
It's not the autobahn.
Come on, Greg!
- Maybe you should drive after all, honey.
- We're okay.
All right.
Oh, no.
No, please.
- Yes!
- Jack just turned.
You were supposed
to make that left at the light,
Focker.
I think I'm gonna be sick.
Where does he think he's going?
- Home, home, home.
- What a fun ride.
Who gave him the keys?
- Okay, we're out.
- Yeah, we've had enough excitement.
I wonder if he has a license.
Yeah, a license to kill.
Come on, everybody.
Hey, nice driving, Mario!
You're a lunatic!
Come on, Linda!
It was the cat!
Goddamn you!
Dad, Dad-- Dad! Dad!
Calm down!
- Where's the cat?
- Cat got out! Cat got out, Jack!
You spray-painted his tail...
to make him look like Jinxy,
didn't you, Focker?
Greg, what's he talking about?
Hank MacAtee called me a couple of
hours ago and told me he found Jinxy.
He took his collar
and put it on an impostor.
Then he spray-painted his tail,
and then he tried to beat us back here...
so that he could
get rid of the evidence.
Please tell me
that's not true, Greg.
It was just a temporary solution
until I could find the real Jinx.
How could you do
something like that?
- I'm sorry.
- What are you going to tell me next?
That you set Kevin's
altar on fire?
Oh, my God.
Well, it wasn't intentional.
I was chasing Jinx up onto the roof.
I had a smoke, and I think
I might have lit something that--
I don't know what happened. He put so
much goddamn lacquer on that thing.
It was an accident
waiting to happen.
This is very disappointing, Greg.
Get out of my house, Focker,
and take your friend with you.
So you lied to me
about everything, huh, Greg?
You lied about the cat,
about the fire, about the MCATs.
I didn't lie about the MCATs. Come on, Pam.
Don't you see what's happening here?
- Your dad has totally turned you against me.
- I didn't turn her against you.
You did that to yourself.
Jack, please. You didn't like me from
the second I walked in here.
I'm a very
accepting person, Focker.
All I ask for is honesty.
Oh, honesty?
You wanna talk about
truth and honesty, Jack?
Okay, let's talk
a little truth and honesty.
Let's talk a little
"Operation Ko Samui," Jack.
What's he talking about, Dad?
Yeah, that's weird, 'cause I thought there
weren't any secrets...
inside the circle of trust, Jack.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- You don't? Huh?
What's the matter?
Cat got your tongue?
Hey, Pam, guess what.
Daddy's planning a little
covert operation in Thailand
for the day after the wedding.
You are?
Round and round we go, Jack. Hey.
I bet everybody would love
to hear about your rendezvous...
in the parking lot of the Oyster Bay
Drug and Sundry.
You know what I'm talking about.
Where the guy gave you
the passports and the documents.
Or how about
your little phone call in Thai?
- Jack can't talk Thai.
- Oh, no, Dina.
Jack can talk Thai.
Jack talk Thai very well.
I'm sorry, Pam,
but your dad is not retired.
He's still very much
in the C.I.A.
- Daddy. What--
- He's right.
He's right.
My cover's blown.
I-I-I am planning...
a secret operation
the day after the wedding.
- What?
- A surprise honeymoon for Deb and Bob.
You stupid son of a bitch!
You just blew it!
What?
Ko Samui is an island
off the coast of Thailand!
That guy I was meeting in the parking lot
is Thor Svenson, my travel agent.
He was giving me their visas.
Wow, Thailand. Thanks a lot, J.B.
That's something.
Don't mention it.
I just, um--
You know, if this nursing
thing doesn't work out, Focker,
I'd say you definitely
have a career in espionage.
Thanks, Greg.
Well, I guess I'm gonna go
to the airport now.
I guess you're gonna stay here.
Pam, I--
- Gaylord M. Focker?
- Gaylord? Gaylord?
Yeah, that's me.
- I thought your name was Greg.
- It is.
That's not what it says
on the form. I know.
It's my legal name. Nobody's called me
by it since I was in third grade.
Whatever.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
So your name's Gay Focker?
- Denny.
- I'm sorry. It's just it's not...
You're in luck.
There is room.
And without a Saturday stay-over,
that fare difference will be...
$1,137.11.
- Would you want me to book you the seat?
- Okay. All right.
Did you want to check
any bags today?
We should be all right
with only one usher, don't you think?
I'm not so sure, Jack.
Thought you might like to see this.
- How did you get this?
- Oh, I have my sources too.
I called Gaylord,
a.k.a. Greg's parents in Detroit.
They saved his SAT scores too,
in case you're interested.
Oh, honey. It--
That doesn't matter if he
did well on some test.
What does that prove?
Look at this place!
He almost destroyed the wedding
because he lied!
I love you Daddy,
but you can be
a real jerk sometimes.
So what if he took the MCATs?
He's still not good enough for Pam.
Who is, Jack?
Nobody has ever been
good enough for your Pam.
I mean, do you realize that you
never even warmed up to Kevin
until she broke up with him?
Maybe it's time you think about
what Pam wants.
Greg, it's me.
I'm sure you're in
the air by now,
so I guess you'll just
get this when you get home.
Listen, I am so sorry.
I acted like a complete idiot,
and I hope that you
can forgive me.
I mean, I-I don't care about
the fire or the cat or--
I mean, I can't believe you
actually spray-painted a cat.
That's actually really gross,
but th-the point is that--
that I understand
why you did it, and--
and I love you.
I want you to know that I really--
I really, really love you, and, uh--
When you get this,
will you please call me?
Okay. Bye.
Marty, listen, I need
a commercial flight I.D. scan.
Interstate from New York
La Guardia to Chicago.
Four-hour sweeps,
backwards and forwards.
Last name: Foxtrot, Oscar,
Charlie, Kilo, Echo, Romeo.
First name: Golf,
Alpha, Yankee, Lima--
Gaylord Focker on Atlantic American
flight 27, departs 2:35.
- 2:35? - Affirmative.
Twenty-three minutes. Thanks.
Enjoy your flight.
Thanks.
Hello.
Oh, I'm sorry. We're only boarding
rows nine and above right now.
You'll have to wait.
Well, I'm in row eight.
Please step aside, sir.
It's just one row.
Don't you think it's okay if I--
We'll call your row
momentarily.
Step aside, sir.
Thank you for waiting. We'd like to
continue boarding the aircraft now.
We're now boarding all rows,
please. All remaining rows.
Mm, hello.
Enjoy your flight.
Excuse me.
Okay, where's the fire, huh?
- I'm sorry, sir. You're gonna have
to check that. - I got it.
- No, I'm sorry. That bag won't fit.
- No, I'm not-- Hey.
- I'm not checking my bag, okay?
- There's no need to raise your voice, sir.
I'm not raising my voice.
This would be raising my voice to you, okay?
I don't want to check my bag. By the way,
your airline, you suck at checking bags.
Because I already did that once,
and you lost it,
and then I had everything
screwed up very badly for me.
- Okay?
- I can assure you that your bag...
will be placed safely below deck
with the other luggage.
Oh, yeah? How do you know my bag
will be safe below with the other luggage?
Are you physically gonna
take my bag beneath the plane?
Are you gonna go with the guys
with the earmuffs and put it in there?
- No.
- No? Okay. Then shut your pie hole...
and listen to me
when I say that I am finished...
with the checking-of-the-bags
conversation!
Sir, we have a policy on this airline
that if a bag is this large, we--
Get your grubby little paws
off of my bag, okay?
It's not like I have a bomb in here.
It's not like I want to blow up the plane.
- Sir!
- I wanna stow my bag according
to your safety regulations.
- Sir, sir--
- If you would take a second...
and take the little sticks out of your head
and clean out your ears,
maybe you would see that
I'm a person who has feelings,
and all I have to do
is do what I wanna do!
All I wanna do is hold onto my bag
and not listen to you!
The only way that I would ever let go of
my bag would be if you came over here now...
and tried to pry it
from my dead, lifeless fingers.
Okay? If you can get it from my kung fu
grip, then you can have it.
Okay? Otherwise, step off, bitch.
Get off of me!
- You got him?
- Yeah.
- Hey. Hey! You can't leave
your vehicle unattended. - Tow it.
I've got a plane full of people
saying you threatened that stewardess.
I was not threatening her.
I was trying to get my bag
into the overhead storage thing.
You were acting like a maniac,
and you threatened her with a bomb!
- I said I didn't have a bomb!
- You said "bomb."
- I said, "It's not like I have a bomb."
- You said "bomb" on an airplane.
- What's wrong with saying
"bomb" on an airplane?
- You can't say "bomb."
Bomb, bomb, bomb, bomb,
bomb, bomb, bomb, bomb, bomb!
You gonna arrest me?
- You assaulted an airline employee--
- What if I was a bombardier?
- I got enough to put you away
for a few years!
- Bomb, bomb, bomb, bomb, bomb!
Norm. Take five.
We got a specialist here.
Bye, Norm.
Oh, shit.
How'd you get here?
I'm everywhere, Focker.
I didn't do anything, Jack.
- Yeah, I know.
- Well, then tell these guys
that I'm not a terrorist.
Listen, Focker. I'm not gonna tell anybody
anything until you answer some questions.
Unless you want to spend the next
couple of years of your life in prison,
you better goddamn well
tell me the truth. No more lies.
You understand?
No more lies.
- Did you do this?
- Just answer the questions.
- Did you have me taken off of that airplane?
- Just answer the question.
Put your hands
over there. That's it.
You're sick, you know that?
Is your name Gaylord Focker?
Yes or no?
- Yes.
- Are you a male nurse?
- Are you a pothead?
- No.
- Have you ever smoked pot?
Yes.
Did you spray-paint the tail
of a cat to pass him off as Mr. Jinx?
Yes.
Did you do that because you desperately
were seeking my approval?
- Yes.
- Because you love my daughter Pam?
- Do you wanna marry her?
Do you want to marry her?
I did, until I met you.
What does that mean?
I love your daughter, Jack.
I love her more than anything.
But frankly, sir, I'm a little terrified
of being your son-in-law.
This whole weekend
has given me a lot of doubts...
about whether or not
I could even survive in your family.
I think you've got
some serious issues.
If I lighten up, would you
consider marrying my daughter?
Would you lighten up a lot?
- Yeah.
- Yes or no?
- Yes.
- Would you let me and Pam...
live our lives and not
interfere all the time?
I promise not interfere
in your lives all the time.
Will you stop making fun of me
for being a nurse?
Could you at least try, maybe,
to consider another profession?
- Jack, yes or no?
- Ever?
- No!
- Okay, yes.
Would you let me and Pam
sleep in the same room?
Don't push it, Focker.
You're in a real mess.
If you married my daughter,
would you support her...
in the way that she
deserves to be supported?
- Yes.
- Would you be honest and faithful to her?
Yes.
Will you devote yourself entirely to her
for the rest of your life?
Of course.
Gaylord Focker,
will you be my son-in-law?
Greg?
I thought you were
going back to Chicago?
Yeah, well, we had
a little plane trouble.
Plus, your dad
caught up with me at the airport.
No. Don't worry.
It's okay. We worked out
a lot of our issues.
You and my dad worked out
a lot of your issues?
Yeah. First he gave me his little human
lie detector thing, but I passed.
Good.
Yeah, and...
then he proposed.
Are you feeling all right?
Listen. This weekend was a nightmare.
I had this whole
elaborate plan, and then...
somewhere between
giving your sister a black eye...
and setting the house on fire,
it kind of went off track.
I just-- I love you.
I love you so much.
I think he's about to do it, Jack.
Come on, honey.
Give 'em some privacy.
...and I think
if we can get through...
what we got through in the last 48 hours,
we could get through anything.
I think so too.
- And, Greg, I don't--
- Wait. Hang on a second.
Mr. Jinx?
That's a ring.
I like to think of it
as a little circle of trust.
Pam?
- Will you marry me?
- Yes.
Yes.
Attaboy, Greg!
That "circle of trust" thing?
That's mine.
Well, looks like we got
another wedding to plan.
- Yep. Just gotta do one more thing.
- What's that?
Meet his parents.
- Jack--
- Honey, relax. I'm sure they're wonderful,
Good night, Jack.
I mean, they'd have to be, right,
to name their son Gaylord Focker.
Do you, Debra Byrnes,
take Robert Banks...
to be your lawfully
wedded husband?
Yes. I mean, I do.
I now pronounce you
man and wife.
Let's just see if you really can
flush the toilet, Jinxy.
I knew it.
Shit!
- I knew it.
- Damn it!
That's my future son-in-law.
What do you think?
Hello, Jack.
Oh, look at that.
Nice Jack. Hi.
What's that, Jack?
What?
You're a big, bad C.I.A. man, huh?
Did they teach you that in the C.I.A.?
They teach you that?
Oh, yeah.
What's that, Jack?
What? Yeah, you thought Puff was just
the name of the boy's magical dragon?
Not too quick
on the uptake, huh, Jack?
Why don't you ask Denny who's puffin'
the magic dragon? Not onto that one, huh?
Surprising for a big
C.I.A. pulse detector.
Ooh. Hey, hey, check my pulse
on this question, Jack.
Do I think you're a psycho?
Yes.
What? Oh, you like my little gift?
What?
The Jerusalem what?
What? I can't hear you.
Jerusalem toodle-oo-poosey, poosley-loo?
What? What?
Oh, you don't now shit about flowers.
What's that?
You want me to what?