Subtitles by explosiveskull
Thank you.
So, how does it feel
being back after how many years?
A long time.
I am Minister of Justice Buresova.
- How do you do, Mrs. Horakova?
- How do you do?
I'm glad to meet you.
Please.
Can I see them first?
We're hoping to hand them to you
in front of the cameras.
A symbolic gesture, if you will.
Thank you.
A bit a late delivery, isn't it?
What should I tell them?
I'm sorry, but I need to read it first.
I have recently read somewhere
that a letter is like a ray of light
from a distant star.
Its light comes to us and shines on us,
it shows us the way in the darkness
even though the source is often long gone
and it doesn't exist anymore.
I will be embracing you
and kissing you with my words
even though the hand
that has written them will be long gone.
My only little girl Jana,
God blessed my life as a woman with you.
Apart from your father's magic love,
you were the greatest gift
I received from fate.
The President
is expecting you, Mrs. Horakova.
- He's actually seeing me, Bohu.
- Yes and the little part of me.
He was interested in my work.
He was interested in my thoughts
about the women's movement.
So he wants you in politics.
Hitler
deranged, twisted.
Twisted.
Deranged.
Hitler torted
Distort twisted.
Hitler's
Distorted?
Our union with Germany
is a perfect example of success.
- Success?
- Yeah.
It is a downright horrible example.
It is not a union.
It is an occupation!
Hysterical woman.
Is every woman with an opinion
hysterical to you?
Czechoslovakia is hardly
an interest to anyone.
Czechoslovakian economy
is one of the largest in the world
and I am sure Herr Hitler is preparing to
occupy us. For that very reason.
Jew!
Protestant as if it matters.
I think it's time for us to go.
Yes.
At which point
would any of you say, "Enough!?"
Must Hitler reach Paris or London
for you to take threat seriously?
Gentlemen
France and Britain
are throwing us to the wolves.
They have only concerned
about their own interests.
And they don't realize
they're simply sheep of a different flock.
The wolf never stops eating.
Is anyone home?
- Boo!
- I had no idea you were there.
I have something for you
from London and Paris.
Help, help.
It was pretty stiff.
Try it on.
It's beautiful.
These trips
are getting longer and longer.
I've always wanted to go to Paris.
- What if a piece of Paris came to you?
- Thank you.
Pepik will take you one day.
Just as your wife took you?
Come on. Help me in the kitchen.
How was the trip?
Well, they were
as agreeable as my own daughter.
It will get better with Jana.
With the others, I am not so sure.
This is a good place.
When?
As soon as we can.
Bohu, I want to do it.
A list of those
willing to help with the resistance.
Of course.
I will carry it.
Are you sure senator Plaminkova?
This was not a good idea.
You have a family.
- No.
- I should do it with myself.
No, no, no. Because we are a family,
they are much less likely to search us.
Are you sure about this?
Don't worry, we will be fine.
How do you know?
I should carry the list.
Why?
If anything happens,
they are not likely search a woman.
Everyone's name is on little list,
the whole resistance.
I will get rid of it quickly.
Jana.
Family Horak?
Mrs. Horakova?
Yes.
For the love
of God, it's just cough candy!
Too much candy is bad for her teeth.
Enough!
Now when you get home
be sure to share some with Aunt Vera.
You understand?
We are taking you in for questioning.
Where are you taking him?
Come and eat, Jana.
How long?
Pappa how am I supposed to know?
- They refused to say.
- I cannot believe this.
I told her it was dangerous and not to go.
Not now, Jana, you'll spoil your ape
- How could she?
- Not now.
I will clean the living room.
You were very brave.
They'll be home soon. I'm sure of it.
Get out!
Out. Over here.
- Faster.
- Hana Kaufmann!
Come here.
You are the transport from Pankrac prison?
- Yes.
- When were you imprisoned?
- Two years ago.
- What year?
1940.
- Name?
- Milada Horakova.
- It says here you are a doctor.
- Of Jurisprudence.
Good.
You will work in a medical room.
I never thought I would see you again.
Milada. What's the latest from outside?
I have no idea.
I was in prison for two years.
I'm lucky to even be here.
I am waiting a new trial.
They sentenced me to death.
- What?
- But I'm waiting a new trial.
I should have never
let you take that list ever.
They never found it.
Why did they arrest you?
Because they could.
You will be released tomorrow.
But is she well enough?
She will be fine for transport.
Transport?
You ask too many questions.
- Did you like it?
- Yes, I did.
- Do up the last button.
- Oh, you sound like mom.
Someone needs to.
Tell her I have grown a whole bunch
for her for when she comes back.
I will.
We have to rush to a train.
Bye.
Sweetheart!
From your husband.
I heard the few days ago
that they transferred you
on the other side of our camp.
I hope you will receive my message
and this ring
that I made out of a bread for you.
I love you. Bohu.
Transport!
Faster.
That is factually incorrect.
I was in charge of
organising social welfare.
I agree. However, such activity
can be hardly considered a conspiracy.
And may I remind you that the prosecution
failed to provide any evidence.
I commute
your death sentence to eight years
to be served in Aichach.
- Your love will carry me through.
- You are with me always.
Miladka.
Jana!
Mamma!
Bohu?
He is here.
The doctor will be here tomorrow.
Bohu
- Mamma?
- What is it?
Is Daddy going to die?
We will to pray for him,
and he will heal.
Why is he sick and you are not?
Sometimes it's hard to explain things.
But he is sick because of you.
Why would you say that?
They arrested him because of you.
Who told you that?
Auntie.
One day, I will explain everything.
But not tonight.
Here.
Your father made this for me in the camp.
Now try to rest.
She has grown up so much.
Thank you.
You have done a great deal for my family.
Jana is brave.
She could have ended up
in a concentration camp with you.
But she didn't, right?
Jana made the cake.
Taste very good.
She's very confused.
They arrested us because of me?
Why would you say that to her?
I told you it was not safe!
Had everyone stood by, we would be
still living in the Third Reich.
OK.
Let's eat the cake.
It's really good.
What if he dies?
We have to hope.
All these people we knew
are gone.
I don't understand
I don't know.
But I am glad that you came back.
Sometimes we find out later
why things happen as they do.
I am sorry.
I shouldn't have told Jana those things.
I was wrong.
When you are better,
we will move to the country,
build the house.
Sorry.
I'm... I'm thirsty.
Our people do appreciate very highly
the presence of the American Army
on Czechoslovak's soil
and will strengthen
in the future this friendship
which was so happily established
with a great American democracy
through the benefits of our peace.
This is it.
I will miss having you home.
You will enjoy your space with Bohu.
And it's time me and Pepik
started on our own.
So it's true!
- Welcome back.
- You look well.
You lie even better.
Same office, same desk.
Milada, we need you.
My family needs me.
They went through enough.
You know there's no "they"
if the communists gain control.
That's a big "if".
The President asked about you.
How is Bohuslav?
- He's doing well.
- It's great.
- How was Jan?
- He is still the foreign minister.
Maybe president one day.
He lacks the fortitude
of his father to become one.
I prefer to be direct these days.
Why are you here?
We all would be better off if we had
more people like you on our side.
Your flattery won't get you much,
I am afraid.
- Milada.
- Lida.
- It is so good to see you.
- Good to see you.
MILADA HORAKOVA RECEIVES
LEGION OF HONOR IN FRANCE
The Legion of Honor
was awarded to Milada Horakova
by general de Gaulle.
What sorts of concessions?
Military cooperation,
sharing of the Carpathian-Russia region.
Sharing?
The communists are growing stronger.
People are feeling vulnerable,
we need to form a united front.
Then let's unite in calling things exactly
what they are. Coercion and annexation.
Precisely.
That is why we need
your run for Parliament.
Many politicians oppose
what you call equal protection.
They say it is but a simple feminist
ideology, a sort of special privilege.
That is because most politicians
are men governing only for other men.
These need a signature
from the mayor's office.
Are you considering
running for Parliament?
Yes.
And why now?
Well
When I was a little girl,
I had a brother and a sister
who died from Scarlet fever.
I had no power to help.
As a member of Parliament
I can help all my brothers and sisters.
Yeah.
- When are you coming back?
- In three days.
- Thank you for your time.
- I'm sorry.
I am a big admirer of your work.
I am divorced and my husband
refuses to help financially.
If only someone were in a more influential
position to promote the laws you advocate.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Sorry.
- Bye.
Congratulations. I heard Initiative 99
is progressing through the legislature.
Although I'm not sure it's going to be
popular with the Right Wing.
The Right Wing will appreciate
their own pensions when they retire.
- Sorry, I must go.
- You will be fine.
I'm coming, late, but coming.
This law will guarantee
that all survivors of the war,
widows, orphans,
and our wounded heroes,
will never have to suffer
the existential insecurities,
once they rejoin society.
- Impressive first showing as an MP.
- Thank you.
Comrade Horakova.
Ah, Prime Minister Gottwald,
congratulations.
And Mrs. Horakova. Still.
Quite an impassioned plea.
One that I will make certain
my fellow party members hear.
We communists
have a lot of the same values.
Isn't it reassuring, then,
we can share our common goals
while maintaining
our unique party perspectives.
Now if you will excuse me.
Don't worry. It will be fine.
- Hello.
- I will speak to you later then.
Mrs. Horakova? Anezka Spurna.
I just joined
the Council of Czechoslovak Women.
Of course, yes. Pleasure.
I want to continue the work
Senator Plaminkova started.
Do you know what happened to her?
Yes. There isn't a day
I don't think about her.
Yes, yes, she was a great woman.
Yes, well I look forward to work with you
at the Women's council.
Isn't it just lovely
to return some sense of normalcy
after the horrors we've all seen.
Some of us, of course, more than others.
How fortunate we all are
that the Soviets liberated us.
Actually, our camp was freed
by American soldiers, not Soviet.
Well, it's a shame, the Americans
weren't able to come as far as Prague.
They had an agreement
to liberate Prague together
but Stalin barged in days earlier.
Then we should applaud
our true liberators' eagerness.
- It was lovely to meet you finally.
- You as far.
She had the nerve to try
to recruit me, right there.
Such propaganda.
She is only one person.
But it is not, there are many and they
are going especially for the young ones.
Alois was right.
Those who want democracy
need all the help they can get.
Why does it always have to be you?
You have always supported me,
I cannot do this without you.
You know I will support you
as long as I can.
I'll not put us in danger.
I promise.
How did we go from
wanting them out of our country
to seeking asylum in theirs?
Are people blind?
People are told what they want to hear.
And so they will believe it.
And they will continue to believe it
until it is too late.
So that's Gottwald keeping us safe.
- From what?
- From our freedom, apparently.
I can and I will speak up.
I am still a Member of Parliament.
If it doesn't work?
Then we will find
other ways to voice our dissent.
I am returning
from the presidential castle
where the President has accepted the
resignation of the democratic ministers.
Today, we Communists celebrate this,
the Victorious February!
What is it?
Anezka
Why are you here?
Surely it would be easier for us all
to unite with one voice.
It's not too late for you.
This attempt of Communist scheme
to unite, as you say, with one voice,
seems to have created a deafening silence.
What you call a deafening silence,
I believe is actually the sound of peace.
But people like you insist on disrupting
that tranquility with your falsehoods,
and I cannot
for the life of me understand why.
If you do not
and will not support Communism,
then you are a threat to this country.
And this is what you call democracy.
The choice remains yours, of course.
But if I don't oblige
then there will be consequences.
Am I right?
You have a wonderful family.
You should think of them.
It is time for you to go.
It is no longer safe, I know.
See you in the morning.
I'll be ready.
What?
What is wrong?
The Communist...
it is the Nazis all over again.
What do we do?
How about just leaving?
I am considering resigning.
Good.
Resign, and then we go.
We are giving up our mandates to fight.
What sort of fight
it would be if I run away?
Fight for Jana.
For once, put her first.
I am.
But I want to believe
that evil will be punished.
I want to force myself to believe
that the world will be as it should be.
But if we are not free,
then Jana is not free
and I cannot bear the thought of it.
He was to leave for London this morning.
I spoke to him right before.
Be careful.
Who did it?
Russians most likely.
Do we have proof? Some evidence?
Everything was cleaned up
by the time the police showed up.
They say he jumped from that window?
No. From that window.
And yet he landed here.
Yes.
There's a reason for me to stay.
There are still people in need
from social services.
I can help them get funds, documents.
It's a lost battle, Milada.
You should know when to leave.
No.
Tell whomever needs to escape the country
to come to my office and say they are
they are case 45.
If they don't hesitate to kill
the foreign minister of sovereign nation,
they will go further.
Case 45.
Our democracy
was a sacred institution to be cherished,
protected.
I fear we no longer have those values.
And thus with the heaviest of heart
I hereby resign
in protest.
So, when are you going to arrest me?
Now?
So what do you suggest?
She is still popular with the public.
We need her on our side.
I have tried everything.
Try harder.
I think it is time to leave Prague.
Come in.
I am case number 45.
Right.
Lida
This needs to go downstairs.
Please, come in.
When are you crossing?
Hopefully by Friday.
Thank you.
Thank you for everything.
Good luck.
Hello. Welcome.
Hello.
I have been fired.
They took over the radio.
When you get to the safe house,
you must ask where is the blacksmith.
This will be enough for your family.
If they catch you,
please destroy the list, OK?
Be safe.
Thank you.
We should cross today.
We have time.
No, no we can't trust anyone.
We can trust our informant.
- I will be fine.
- Are you sure?
I will catch a tram.
Goodbye.
I was never a good wife
...more of a lover.
But...
...never a good wife.
I often sin against
the goodness of your heart.
I neglect you.
I always rely on your being there.
Will you ever forgive me?
I think it is time to leave.
Thank you, Lida, thank you.
- Alois.
- Milada.
We have been friends for many years.
- I hope you trust me.
- Of course.
Have you been speaking to Communists?
You know, I talk to everyone.
Have you accepted the position within?
Milada, I will go
where I can best serve the people.
So you have.
I did not.
Not yet.
What do they have on you?
- My family.
- I have a family too.
But your parents are not German.
Thank you.
Gottwald is the head of government
approximately 300 are in urgent need to
escape or at high risk of prosecution.
The Communists
have overtaken the government.
Annette, this is the latest
intelligence from Czechoslovakia.
I'll quickly finish up everything at work,
and will meet you and Jana at two.
Yes, I will do it.
- Maruska.
- Good afternoon.
Thank you.
What?
What is the problem?
Keys.
Sit down.
- Who are you?
- Police.
Come on.
Sit down.
Sit down!
I have worked for Mrs. Horakova
for over ten years.
- What people? Their names?
- I am just a help.
I was never introduced.
I must get your mom.
I will come back for you.
Sugar?
They don't drink tea.
Mrs. Horakova's guests
never asked for tea.
That's all
- Hello?
- It's me.
Veruska.
I thought the three of you
might want to come for dinner tonight.
No talk of politics. Just family.
Oh Vera I have to go.
I have visitors.
On what legal grounds
am I being arrested?
State your name and date of birth.
Milada Horakova, born Kralova.
December 25, 1901.
When did you first engage
in political activities?
I have the right to know
why I am being held.
You don't have any rights.
Presumption of innocence,
and according to Law 1523 Paragraph 4B,
I have the right to know
what I am being arrested for.
Where is my husband and my daughter?
First, tell me.
Then we can discuss your family.
Do you have children?
No, no, no.
I am the one asking the questions!
Hello, Mrs. Horakova.
Do you remember me?
I did an interview with you.
It was a long time ago.
This is your bed.
If you ended up here,
no one is safe.
You need to find something on her.
I spent the last four months
interrogating her.
If there was anything,
we would have found it.
- Be creative.
- How?
Let's give her one hour of
interrupted sleep and then continue.
But she's been up for two days now.
Still not working.
So what?
Go in.
The case has no substance.
I have no evidence to build on,
no clues, no witnesses.
I don't understand
which one of them is the one to go after.
Her?
And?
She needs to learn this.
You can leave now.
I don't know how to approach this.
We trust you'll find the way.
Beautiful wife and very young daughter.
Bring another one!
Milada, I am sorry. They forced me.
Quiet!
Leave us.
- But we're family.
- I cannot help you.
Even the Nazis allowed us to visit her.
I don't understand.
We broke them all but her.
- We will do this differently.
- How?
Her family.
Let me do this.
I am a woman.
Fine.
Thanks.
Stay still.
Water?
Vera.
Have you seen Milada?
How is she?
It's no longer safe for you here.
You have to leave.
Not without Jana.
They are watching her.
No, no.
Once you are in Germany,
you will get her through the Red Cross.
You had a bad dream.
It all will be fine.
I was with my daughter
in the most beautiful place.
Tell Jana I will get her.
- Promise her.
- I will.
You need to go.
That's irrelevant!
You cooperated with Western Imperialists
to destabilize the elected government!
An opposition does not destabilize
a legitimate government.
Here.
I have aided and cooperated
with Western Imperialist
in destabilizing democratically
elected communist government!
Your last chance.
Sign it.
We will do this differently.
Interrogation!
Still claiming innocence, right?
Think about your family.
You can see them so soon
if you just confess.
Haven't they suffered enough?
If I were you,
I would sign.
It's good to have principles,
but you still have a daughter,
husband.
One last time.
Sign it.
Your daughter is with your sister.
And my husband?
I have aided and cooperated
with Western Imperialist powers
in destabilizing the democratically
elected communist government.
I confess to leading
a traitors' resistance movement
against the democratically
elected Communist government,
with the intention of aiding
Western Imperialists
to undermine our national integrity.
It is correct.
You see, you realized
how wrong you were in the end.
Now just make sure
it sounds like you believe it.
Confess to leading
a traitors' resistance movement
against the democratically
elected Communist government.
Make sure they are well cleaned up
and fed before the trial.
Against the Communist government.
It's so tragic.
We're working to build this country,
and they want to destroy it.
I hope they all hang.
Traitor!
State your name.
- Frana Zeminova.
- Zavis Kalandra.
- Josef Nestaval.
- Milada Horakova.
Are you aware of the charges against you?
I am.
- I am.
- Yes, I am.
- Yes.
- Do you plead guilty to these crimes?
Confess to leading
a traitors' resistance movement
I am.
Against the democratically
elected Communist government
I am guilty of all I have confessed to.
However, I do not believe
they constituted any wrong doing.
Mrs. Horakova, as a defendant
you are trying to excuse
acts of treason and conspiracy.
Only according to one's conscience.
You conspired against
everyday people of this country,
factory workers, children, mothers.
It is a farce trial.
Are you sure?
Nothing but theater.
She thinks it's a farce trial.
Nothing but theater, she said.
When asleep, she started calling Jana.
She woke up at approximately 10PM.
That's enough.
Take her out.
I remain faithful to my convictions.
Freedom.
Equality.
Democracy.
Compassion.
No one in this country
should be imprisoned or made to die
for their beliefs.
Comrade, I did not ask you
for a dictionary.
The ordinary worker
wants hear honest answers,
not evasive, bourgeois jargon.
rs. Horakova, tell us clearly if you are
guilty of conspiring in an illegal way
against our people
and the democratic Czechoslovakia?
Yes, I am guilty of that.
Now, that is a clear statement.
Mrs. Horakova, you claim that you are
guilty of treason and conspiracy,
but only under the current law,
were treason and conspiracy
legal under the old law?
Not in the way you interpret it.
Thank you, I need no
further response from this defendant.
And we found those enemies of the people.
We were able to find them,
and we brought them here to trial.
The accused Milada Horakova
was organizing adverse groups
to destroy our country!
These terrorists
were planning the Third World War
with the Western Imperialist
to destroy us all.
But we are smarter than them.
We found them
and brought them to justice.
Your honor, I ask for the harshest
punishment for all of them.
The execution
is scheduled for the 27th of June.
If you ask the court for clemency,
they may commute your sentence to life.
I have done nothing wrong.
- What is this?
- Clemency requests.
I plead with you
not to carry out the death sentences
on Milada Horakova and company, STOP,
they were victims of Nazism and suffered
in the concentration camps, STOP,
I am deeply convinced
they deserve to live.
Signed Professor Albert Einstein.
Eleanor Roosevelt.
Winston Churchill.
Jean-Paul Sartre.
Who?
From her father and daughter.
Hello?
Yes.
I see.
Thank you.
Clemency was denied.
Don't tell her about the baby.
It is good to see you.
No physical contact with the prisoner.
How is father?
Holding up.
I agree it is better
that you asked him not to come.
I am not sure how he would
I wish I knew what happened to Bohuslav.
They will not tell me.
Mamma, you haven't done anything,
why are they doing this?
Auntie will explain it to you in time.
Aunt Vera is pregnant.
That is wonderful, Vera.
You will make a great mother, Vera.
I still remember the day you were born.
Mother was so sick
that father had to run and get a doctor
and then he placed you in my arms,
when I held you
you were my first daughter.
So much have changed.
And just now I am so sorry
I will never be able to repay you.
She will be able to stay with us.
We are all a family.
I will take a good care of them.
Thank you.
Mamma.
When you think of me,
know that I am always always with you.
Can I hold my daughter, one last time?
No physical contact is allowed.
It's time for you to leave.
I embrace you and kiss you from here.
I will always be with you.
Always.
Why did it come to this?
Would you have done anything differently?
I have always done
what I believed to be right.
I am scared.
Any last words?
I fall.
I lost this battle.
I leave honorably.
I love this country.
I love her people.
I leave without hatred.
My Jana, providence
planned my life in such a way
that I could not give you my all.
But I felt my calling was to do you good
by seeing that all children can live well.
And so, my little girl,
my hope, my future forgiveness.
Live! Grasp life with both hands!
Until my last breath
I shall pray for your happiness.
I shall always be with you.
Tell us about yourself.
You're now a US citizen?
I am sorry for having left you waiting.
This press conference is not about me,
it's about a woman, my mother,
who left a legacy behind
that we can all look up to.
Your mother was an extraordinary woman.
Yes.
She wanted me to be more like her,
but I could never achieve that.
I think it best,
if we hear her last words here today.
Life is hard,
it does not pamper anyone,
and for every time it strokes you
it gives you ten blows.
Man doesn't live alone in this world;
in that there is great happiness,
but also a tremendous responsibility.
Our obligation is not acting selfishly
but rather merging
with the needs and the goals of others.
Learn to be modest.
You will not be unhappy because of
material things you don't have.
When you come to
consider something just,
be so definite
that you can fight and die for it.
Don't feel sorry for me.
I lived a beautiful life.
I accept my punishment humbly.
My conscience is clear
and I believe and pray
that I shall also pass the test
of the higher court, of God.
Go to the meadows,
the fields and the forests,
there in the smell of
the blooming blossoms
you will find a part of me.
Subtitles by explosiveskull