[TV TURNS ON]
MAN 1 [ON TV]:
- For numenator.
MAN 2:
- Start playing.
MAN 3:
- Be around him lo...
MAN 4:
Ever since Ameri...
WOMAN 1:
We'd like to thank the fo...
MAN 5:
Our cash bail will be out by...
MAN 6: And, you know...
WOMAN 2: Bobo.
MAN 7:
- Behind the mighty.
MAN 8:
- Said to my wife, "Berni..."
MAN 9: Sorry, boy.
MAN 10: They hurt...
- went through the crack.
MAN 11: This ham...
- Our 12th edition...
...of the Psychic Friends Network.
MAN 12:
- Shea Stad...
ANNOUNCER:
You're watching TV Time!
The only network playing lots of old stuff
in nothing but black and white.
Why, it's fun for the whole family.
TV Time! Remember, you're soaking in it.
This Friday on TV Time!
Take the phone off the hook
and the plastic off the couch.
That's right,
it's the Pleasantville marathon.
Twenty-four hours chocked full
of pure family values.
Featuring the warm greeting.
Honey, I'm home.
- Proper nutrition.
- Do you want some more cookies?
And, of course, safe sex.
[KISSING SOUND]
Why, it's a scrapbook of
all your favorite Pleasantville memories.
There's "Trouble at the Barbershop"...
..."Fireman for a Day"...
..."The Big Game"...
...and who could forget
"Bud Gets a Job"?
So join all your favorites:
Mary Sue, Bud, George and Betty...
...and, oh, yes,
Mr. Johnson at the soda shop.
There's more.
If you put your thinking caps on...
...you could win $1000
in our Pleasantville trivia contest...
...plus a free trip
to the Pleasantville of your choice.
Flash back to kinder, gentler times...
...on the Pleasantville marathon,
this Friday, only on TV Time!
Hi.
[CHUCKLES]
I mean, hi.
Look, you probably don't think
I should be asking you this.
I mean, not knowing you well and all.
I mean, you know, I know you.
Everybody knows you.
I just don't know you technically.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Uh...
Anyhow, I don't know
what you're doing this weekend...
...but my mom's leaving town...
...and she's letting me borrow the car,
so, you know...
[BELL RINGS]
Okey-dokey, so just give me a call.
Let me know.
Bye.
For those of you going
to college next year...
...the chance of finding a good job...
...will actually decrease
by the time you graduate.
The available number
of entry-level jobs...
...will drop 31 percent
over the next four years.
Median income for those jobs
will go down as well.
Obviously, my friends,
it's a competitive world...
...and good grades
are your only ticket through.
[BOY BURPS]
In fact, by the year 2000...
- the chance of contracting HIV
from a non-monogamous lifestyle...
...will climb to one in 150.
The odds of dying in an auto accident
are only one in 2500.
This marks a drastic increase...
- from 14 years ago, when ozone depletion
was at just 10 percent of its current level.
By the time you are 30 years old...
...average global temperature
will have risen two and a half degrees...
...causing such
catastrophic consequences...
...as typhoons, floods,
widespread drought, and famine.
Okay, who can tell me what famine is?
GEORGE:
Honey, I'm home.
Hello, darling. How was your day?
Oh, swell. You know, Mr. Connell says
if things keep going the way they are...
...I might be seeing that promotion
sooner than I thought.
Oh, darling, that's wonderful.
I always knew you could do it.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
Hey, pumpkin, what's that smell?
Is that your meat loaf?
"It might be."
It might be.
Oh, pumpkin, you sure know the way
to this man's heart.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
DAVID'S MOM:
No, no. That was not the deal.
No, you have custody
first weekend of every month.
This is the first weekend.
No. I'm not gonna bail you out.
I'm going out of town this weekend.
La Costa.
Barry, if I wanna have a mud bath with my
new boyfriend, that's my business, isn't it?
[RAISES VOLUME]
- Hey, where are those kids?
- Excuse me?
- "Right behind you, Father."
MARY SUE: Right behind you.
Right behind you, Father.
Mother, Father,
Bud has a little surprise for you.
BETTY:
What's that, Bud?
First place in the science fair.
There were lots of swell projects.
I guess mine was just the swellest.
Darling, that's wonderful,
except there's no such word as "swellest."
Well, gee whiz, Mom,
it wasn't the English fair.
[BETTY CHUCKLES]
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
No, that's not the point.
The point is,
you're supposed to see them.
Fine, fine, fine. See them another time.
"What's a mother to do?"
What's a mother to do?
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[BELL RINGS]
HOWARD: Okay, in the very first
Pleasantville episode...
...whose window did Bud break when
he was playing with his father's golf clubs?
Easy. Mr. Jenkins.
What job did Mr. Jenkins have?
Salesman.
What did Bud and Mary Sue name the cat
they found in the gutter?
Scout?
Marmalade.
All right, all right.
Here's one.
Why did their parents come home early
from their weekend at the lake?
Because Bud didn't answer the phone,
and they were worried about him.
Man, you're unbelievable.
You'll win this thing for sure.
When is it on?
Marathon starts at 6:30.
Contest is tomorrow at noon.
Thousand bucks, huh?
And it's on all night?
Well, of course it is, Howard.
That's why they call it a marathon.
GIRL:
Oh, my God, he is, like, so pathetic.
I can't believe you're, like,
related to him.
Only on my parents' side.
Yeah, but you guys are twins and stuff.
You must be from
the cool side of the uterus.
Oh, my God, here they come.
Oh, my God. Don't do anything.
Just don't do anything.
What?
- Hey.
- Saw you at the mall yesterday.
- Yeah, I saw you too.
So you gonna watch
the concert on MTV tonight?
Yeah. You?
Yeah.
My mom's gonna be out of town.
- Cool.
It was so amazing, Daph.
I was like,
"My mom's gonna go out of town."
And he was like,
"Well, maybe we could..."
And I was like, "Yeah, sure."
And he was like, "Cool."
I know. He's so smart.
I don't know. I'm thinking about
that red thing I got at the mall.
It's not slutty.
It's fun.
Well, hello,
he's not coming over to study.
Yeah, I know.
Well, sometimes I'm jealous of you too.
He's not homeless, Howard.
They just don't say where he lives.
[CAR TRUNK OPENS]
Well, it's a silly question.
Because nobody's homeless
in Pleasantville.
Because that's just not what it's like.
[CAR STARTS]
Look, Howard, it's almost 6:30.
I gotta go.
- What are you doing?
Cut it out, David.
Mark Davis is gonna be here in minutes.
Great. The Pleasantville
marathon starts at 6:30.
I don't believe this. He's gonna be here.
Great. You can watch it upstairs.
Upstairs? Upstairs?
It doesn't have any stereo.
DAVID:
Oh, my God.
David, stop stressing.
You can just, like, turn it on normally.
No, I can't. It's a new TV, Jen.
It doesn't work without a remote.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Oh, my God, he's here.
TV repair.
TV repair?
- Yeah. TV busted?
- Yeah.
Well, here I am.
Holy cow, look at that.
Had a little disaster, didn't you, fella?
Well, yeah, sort of.
Well, we'll get you fixed up
in no time.
I know how I'd feel if mine went out.
Almost like losing a friend.
You know, we didn't call any TV repair.
That makes it a lucky day
for both of us, doesn't it?
Do you think you could do this soon?
- It's almost 6:30.
- What's the hurry?
Pleasantville marathon starts at 6:30.
[THUNDER CRASHES]
Pleasantville? Gosh, I love that show.
Watched it for years.
That's not the reason.
I've got a date at 6:30.
Who did Muffin take
to the masquerade ball...
...when her date came down
with the measles?
- Her father.
- That's right.
- And how'd she dress him?
- As Prince Charming.
Nice. Remember the one...
...where Bud lost his cousin when he was
supposed to be watching him?
- Yeah.
- What department store did they go to?
- Mclntyre's.
- McGinty's.
No. Mclntyre's. Remember?
[SINGING]
For the very best in men's attire
Head right down to Mclntyre's
That's right.
Listen...
...why don't you take
this remote instead?
It's got a little more oomph in it.
- Oomph?
- Sure. Big beautiful set like that?
You want something that'll
put you right in the show.
[THUNDER CRASHES]
It's great. We'll take it.
Thank you.
Well, I better get going.
Your show's almost on...
...and it's almost time for your date.
Take care, now.
[CHUCKLING]
MAN [ON TV]:
Whether it's on the track...
...or just driving around the block,
only new Pennzoil with...
For program information, just...
[WHISTLE BLOWING]
[CROWD CHEERING]
GEORGE: Honey, I'm home.
- Great.
- Let me see that.
- No way.
Gee whiz, Mary Sue,
why can't I borrow your radio?
MARY SUE:
I promised Betty Jean she could use it.
Do you mind? This is only
the most important moment of my life.
Forget it, Jen. I've waited a year for this.
Come on, David, just give it to me.
- Forget it!
MARY SUE: No way, Bud.
BUD:
Forget it, Mary Sue.
MARY SUE:
Come on, Bud. It's mine. Give it back.
[JENNIFER SCREAMS]
Oh, my God.
- What happened?
- I'm not sure.
[GEORGE WHISTLING]
Hi, sport. Hi, Muffin.
Better get a move on.
You'll be late for school.
- What did you do?
- I don't know.
[YELPS]
Look at me. I'm pasty.
Psst. Over here.
Told you it was your lucky day.
I bet you thought
I was just a fan or something.
- What happened?
- A miracle.
Every time I thought
I'd found someone...
...they'd turn out to disappoint me.
They'd know all the early episodes...
...but they wouldn't know the later ones.
They'd know all about Muffin...
...but they wouldn't know about Bud.
What the hell is going on?
Shh. Can't talk like that here.
You're in... Well, you know.
BETTY:
Bud, Mary Sue, breakfast is on the table.
We're in Pleasantville?
A dream come true, huh?
Listen, this really isn't funny.
I have a very important date
in five minutes.
You don't have to worry
about that anymore.
- Bitch.
- No!
You have got to get us out of here.
- Why would I do that?
- Because we don't belong.
Oh, sure, you do.
Mclntyre's department store.
Their father dressed as Prince Charming.
That was gorgeous, Bud.
- My name is David.
- Oh, God.
This is a strange way
of showing your appreciation.
Hey, we appreciate it. We really do.
We just wanna go home now.
But you don't know how long
I've been looking for someone like you.
I'm very disappointed.
In fact, I'm starting
to get a little upset.
No, don't get upset.
Well, wouldn't you?
You look for someone for years.
You pour your heart into it.
This is a privilege, you know.
I don't think I better
talk about this now.
Where are you going?
I don't think we should discuss this
until I'm more composed.
Wait a minute.
Maybe in a while
when I'm not so emotional.
Give you a week or two
to change your attitude.
Come back!
[DOOR SLAMS ON TV]
JENNIFER:
A week or two?
BOY [ON TV]:
Think Mom and Da?
WOMAN:
- Being silly.
MAN:
- From day to day.
- Oh, God.
- What's gonna happen?
I don't know. It's not possible.
Is it possible?
BETTY: Bud, Mary Sue,
your breakfast is getting cold.
It can't be possible.
Well, come on, kids.
You're not going off to school
without a hot breakfast inside you.
Forward march.
I just love you in that sweater, Mary Sue.
It's so flattering.
Thanks.
Morning, kids. Better get a move on,
or you'll be late for school.
- I don't believe this.
- Neither do I.
Well, come on, dig in.
I put blueberries in them
just the way you like.
Well, come on, sweetie.
It's getting late.
Actually, I'm not hungry.
[GEORGE AND BETTY LAUGHING]
Nonsense, young lady.
You're gonna start your day off with
a nice big breakfast. Here we go. Sit down.
Here's some pancakes and eggs.
Sausage and some good crisp bacon.
And, of course, a ham steak.
You eat on up,
then it's right off to school.
Hurry, hurry.
JENNIFER:
I'm gonna hurl, David, I swear to God.
DAVID:
Just take deep breaths.
It's all that animal fat.
I can feel it in my pores.
I still don't see why
we're doing this.
We're supposed to be in school.
We're supposed to be at home, David.
- We're supposed to be in color.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- God.
MAN: Hello, Bud.
Hello, Mr. Simpson.
Hear your dad got a new car.
Oh, yeah. A Buick. It's swell.
Great.
Do you know that guy?
Yeah. He owns the hardware store.
You listen to me for just a minute.
I don't know what you've done,
but you better fix it.
- Shh! Shh!
- Fast.
I had a date with Mark,
and I bought new underwear.
We have to just play along for a little while
until that guy shows up again.
- Play along?
- Yes.
I am Bud Parker,
and you are Mary Sue.
No. No. I'm not gonna do it.
If I don't dress like this for Mom...
...l'm not gonna do it for you.
- We have no choice.
We are stuck here
until that guy shows up again.
Why can't we just explain it
to somebody?
To who?
[HORN HONKING]
[SIREN WAILING]
FIREMAN:
Go. Go. Go.
[IN HIGH-PITCHED VOICE]
Here, kitty.
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Oh, God.
We are.
We're, like, stuck in Nerdville.
[CAT MEOWS]
I knew you'd pay a price for this. I knew
you couldn't be so hopelessly geek-ridden...
...for so long without suffering
some really tragic consequences.
But it's just not fair.
I was getting really popular.
And Debbie Russell had transferred
to another school.
And my skin was really great
since March.
Mark Davis was finally starting
to come around.
BOY:
Hello, Mary Sue.
What's all the commotion?
Where's the cat?
Um...
It's...
[CAT MEOWING]
Oh. Right.
I'll see you at school, Mary Sue.
Who's that?
DAVID:
Skip Martin, captain of the basketball team.
Does he like me?
As a matter of fact, he does.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Those are my friends?
Peggy Jane, Lisa Anne, Betty Jean.
Can we do any better?
I don't think so.
[SIGHS]
Okay.
PEGGY JANE: Mary Sue.
JENNIFER: Hi.
Last week, class, we discussed
the geography of Main Street.
This week we're going to be
talking about Elm Street.
Now, can anyone tell me
the difference...
...between Elm Street
and Main Street?
Tommy.
It's not as long?
That's right, Tommy. It's not as long.
Also, it only has houses.
So the geography of Main Street
is different...
...than the geography of Elm Street.
Mary Sue.
Yeah. What's outside of Pleasantville?
I don't understand.
Outside of Pleasantville.
Like, what's at the end of Main Street?
Mary Sue, you should know
the answer to that.
The end of Main Street
is just the beginning again.
[STUDENTS GIGGLING]
[COACH BLOWS WHISTLE]
COACH:
Come on, men, let's go.
That's it, men, keep it up.
Big game tomorrow.
SKIP:
Bud.
Hi, Bud.
Hi, Skip.
- Bud, can I ask you a question?
- Sure.
Well...
...if I was to go up to your sister...
What I mean is,
if I was to go up to Mary Sue...
Oh, my God. Are we in that episode?
- What?
- Oh, I don't believe this.
What's the matter?
You wanna ask her out tonight, and then
you wanna give her your school pin.
Yeah. How'd you know?
Look, Skip, I don't think
it's a real good time for that right now.
What do you mean?
Well, what I mean is...
...Mary Sue's a little different lately.
She won't go out with me?
No, no. Hey. I didn't say that.
It's just that she's...
I don't know what I'd do
if she wouldn't go out with me.
COACH: Come here, guys.
Don't touch it. Stay back.
I'm sure we'll work something out.
[BELL RINGS]
DAVID: I thought you liked him.
- Yeah, but I don't know.
One date, Jen. Please.
That's all I'm asking.
If you don't go out with this guy,
we could throw their universe out of whack.
It's too weird.
This place gives me the creeps.
- Did you know the books are blank?
- What?
I was in the library.
They have covers and nothing inside.
What were you doing in a library?
I got lost. Oh, wait. Look at this.
Know why the firemen
only rescue cats out of trees?
- Nothing burns around here.
- Jen, stop.
They don't even need firemen.
I could really use a cigarette too.
Jen, listen. I will get us out of here.
I really will.
But if we don't play along...
...we can alter their whole existence,
and then we may never get home.
You really think anybody's gonna notice if
I don't have a chocolate malt with this guy?
[GIRLS GIGGLING]
PEGGY JANE:
You won't believe what we heard.
Skip Martin is gonna ask you out.
- And that's not all.
PEGGY JANE: No, that's not all.
He's gonna give you his pin.
[GIGGLING]
JENNIFER:
Are you sure I'm supposed to wear this?
I could kill a guy with these things.
It's in your closet.
I've worn kinky stuff before...
- He won't notice anyway.
- Why not?
They just don't notice
that kind of thing around here.
- So, what's the point?
- Jen, please.
Hello. I've got 3 pounds
of underwire on here.
Just go with the program, huh?
I'm late for work.
Work?
Bud.
Yeah. Yeah. Sorry.
I just had to help my folks...
...and then I couldn't find my hat.
Oh. I didn't know what to do.
What's wrong?
Well, I always
wipe down the counter...
...and then you set out
the napkins and glasses...
...and then I make the French fries, and...
- Yeah.
But you didn't come,
so I just kept on wiping.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, well... Ha, ha.
Um...
You know, if this ever happens again...
...you can make the fries...
...even if I haven't put out
the napkins yet.
Oh.
Thank you.
[ROBERT & JOHNNY'S "DREAM GIRL"
PLAYING ON JUKEBOX]
[ALL SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[ALL GIGGLING]
[BELL DINGS]
- There aren't any cheeseburgers.
- What?
Usually, I put out the burger,
and you finish with the lettuce.
- Okay, listen. Do you have the lettuce?
- Yeah.
- Have you cooked the burgers?
Put on the lettuce,
finish the burger...
...and pretend it was me doing it
the whole time.
Yeah. You can do it, really.
Okay.
I sure am glad you said
you'd come out with me tonight.
Oh, well, gee whiz, Skip.
I sure am glad you asked me.
I don't know if I ever said this
to you before, but, well...
...I think you're just about
the keenest girl in the whole school.
Really, Skip? The keenest?
Oh, yeah.
DAVID:
What can I get you two?
SKIP:
I don't know, Bud.
I guess I'll have my usual:
Cheeseburger and a cherry Coke.
Oh, I don't know, Bud.
I guess I'll have a salad and an Evian water.
Cheeseburger it is.
You see, the whole time
we were in Civics together...
...I really wanted to come over
and sit next to you...
...but you were always sitting between
Lisa Anne and Peggy Jane.
And you always seemed
so smart and everything.
Like that report you did
on our town hall.
Gosh. I didn't know
what I'd talk to you about.
Yeah. Well, sometimes
talking's overrated.
Don't you think?
Huh?
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, right.
So I know I haven't been steady
with anybody or anything...
...but I just don't wanna rush it.
I mean, there's kids
that are holding hands already...
...but I figure there's plenty of time
for that kind of thing later on, don't you?
Yeah. Can you excuse me
for just a second?
[SIGHS]
God.
Oh, God.
[GIGGLING]
- Did he give it to you?
- I bet he gave it to you.
I don't think he knows how.
I bet he's gonna take her
to Lovers' Lane.
I bet he is. I bet he is.
I bet he's even gonna hold her hand.
ALL:
Ohh!
[ALL GIGGLING]
So, anyhow, I really wanted
to sit next to you in Civics, but...
- You wanna get out of here?
- What?
Do you wanna leave?
Do you wanna go somewhere?
But where could we go?
Lovers' Lane?
Yeah, Lovers' Lane. You up for it?
Come on.
Oh, shit.
Jennifer!
Jennifer, stop! Stop!
You can't do this, Jennifer!
He doesn't exist!
You can't do this to someone
who doesn't exist!
[GROANS]
[PAT BOONE'S "MR. BLUE"
PLAYING ON RADIO]
It sure is pretty.
Oh, yeah. Gorgeous.
To be honest, Mary Sue...
...I didn't think you'd wanna come here
until we'd been pinned for a while.
Oh, Skip, you can pin me
anytime you want to.
Or maybe I should just pin you.
That's silly, Mary Sue.
How could you possibly pin me?
[PANTING]
[GROANS]
Bud? Son, what's wrong?
Have you seen Mary Sue?
Why, no. She's still on her date with Skip.
Is something the matter?
No. No. I was just worried about her.
Bud, your sister's getting older now...
...and she'll naturally
be going out with boys.
But she's a fine young woman.
She would never do anything
for us to be concerned about.
Honest.
[JENNIFER AND SKIP MOANING]
[JENNIFER GASPING]
[SKIP GRUNTING]
[JENNIFER GIGGLES]
I think I better go home now, Mary Sue.
Why?
I think I might be ill.
Something's happening to me.
That's supposed to happen.
It is?
Yeah. Trust me.
BETTY:
Do you want some more cookies?
No, thanks. I'm fine.
How about
some marshmallow rice squares?
Those are swell.
No, I'm fine, thank you.
[KNOCKS]
- Now, who could that be?
- I've got it.
- Oh, hi.
- Hi there.
You took off so quick,
I wasn't sure you were okay.
Oh, yeah. No, I'm fine.
I just... I had to get home early.
Bud, you know how when we close up...
...I close the register,
then you lower the blinds...
...and I turn out the lights,
and we both lock the doors?
- Yeah.
- Well, you weren't around this time...
...so I did the whole thing by myself.
Wow.
And not only that,
I didn't even do it in the same order.
First I lowered the blinds,
then I closed the register. And...
Oh, hello, Betty.
Hello, Bill.
Okay, well, that's great.
Thank you for stopping by.
I... You know, I appreciate it.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Well, gee, thanks, Skip.
I sure had a wonderful time.
Me too.
Night.
Hello, Mr. Johnson.
Oh, hello, Mary Sue.
- What did you do to him?
- Nothing.
What do you mean, "nothing"?
That's not nothing.
Why don't you relax, Bud?
We had a nice time.
[YAWNS]
I am really sleepy, and I have to wake up
early in the morning to go to school.
So night.
MAN [ON TV]:
- Pleasure.
Hi. Looks like it's gonna be
another beautiful sunny day.
High 72, low 72,
not a cloud in the sky.
BETTY:
Bud?
[TURNS OFF TV]
It's 8:00 in the morning.
Are you watching television?
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
Oh, no.
[COACH BLOWS WHISTLE]
COACH:
Come on, men. Let's get in positions.
We got a big game next week. Let's go.
Come on.
Oh, my God.
DAVID:
You can't do this, Jennifer. I warned you.
So, what's the big deal?
Oh, okay. They're not good
at basketball anymore.
- My God. What a tragedy.
- You don't understand.
You're messing with
their whole goddamn universe.
Maybe it needs to be messed with.
Did that ever occur to you?
- Hey, M.S. How you doing?
- Cool, P.J. How are you doing?
- Cool. Cool.
- Cool.
"Cool"? What are you doing
to these people? You can't do this.
- If I don't, who will?
- But they're happy like this.
No. David, nobody is happy
in a poodle skirt and a sweater set.
[SIGHS]
You really like this, don't you?
No, it's not like
you think it's funny or dorky.
You, like, really like it.
No. You have it all wrong.
I am mortified to be your sister.
You have no right to do this to them.
Listen to me for just a minute.
These people don't wanna be geeks.
They wanna be attractive.
They have potential.
They just don't know better.
They don't have that potential.
Oh, yeah? Look at that.
TOMMY:
Wow. What happened to your gum?
I gotta go.
I'm gonna meet Skip at the flagpole.
[CROWD CHEERING]
[CHATTERING]
DR. HENDERSON:
Mm-hm.
Hm.
Well, I don't think
it's anything to worry about.
You cut down on greasy foods
and chocolate.
You know, things like that.
It'll probably just clear up on its own.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
DAVID:
Jesus Christ.
[LLOYD PRICE'S "LAWDY MISS CLAWDY"
PLAYING]
Do you think we could have
two cheeseburgers and some cherry Cokes?
I'll be right with you.
Thanks.
Two cheeseburgers,
two cherry Cokes.
MR. JOHNSON:
There aren't any cheeseburgers.
- I thought we talked about this. I thought...
- What's the point, Bud?
You make hamburgers.
That is the point.
No, I know. I know I do.
But it's always the same, you know?
Grill the bun, flip the meat, melt the cheese.
Never changes.
- It never gets any better or worse.
- Okay, just listen for a sec.
The night when I closed by myself
was different.
Oh, forget about that.
Oh, okay.
I really liked it, though.
Come here.
Look.
You can't always like what you do.
Sometimes you just gotta do it
because it's your job.
And even if you don't like it,
you just gotta do it anyway.
- Why?
- So they can have their hamburgers.
- Oh.
- I'm sorry.
You know what I really like?
- What's that?
- Christmastime.
See, every year, on December 3rd...
...I get to paint Christmas decorations
on the window...
...and every year I get to paint
a different thing.
Here, I'll show you.
[MR. JOHNSON CHUCKLES]
Wow. That's pretty good.
Thanks. But this morning
I was thinking...
...and I realized that
I look forward to it all year.
I thought, "That seems awfully silly.
It seems like an awfully long time
to be waiting for just one moment."
Don't you think?
Well, don't you?
I think that you should try not
to think about that anymore.
Okay.
I'll try that, then.
- Morning, Jim.
- How are you?
Awfully nice.
Have they ever lost before?
Basketball? No, they sure haven't.
It just feels wrong, that's all.
Maybe that's where
they get that saying:
"Can't win them all."
That's a good point, Ralph.
They do have that saying.
But they do win them all.
They've always won them all.
Oh, Mr. Mayor. Here. Here. Go ahead.
Oh, don't be silly, Roy.
I couldn't possibly take your spot.
What I wanna know is,
if they've never lost before...
...and they've never tied before,
isn't that what you call winning them all?
- He's right. That's what you call it.
BIG BOB: Yeah.
- They have called it that.
- That's true.
He said it would clear up
on its own...
...if she just stayed away
from fried foods and sweets.
[WOMEN CHUCKLE]
Except it's spread to her lips now too.
Oh, I don't know.
MARY:
And you say it was just red?
MARGE:
Well, you know, like real red.
WOMAN:
I know what you mean.
That's like this car that was in front
of Bill Johnson's soda shop.
I was going by it the other day,
and it looked green.
Real green.
MARGE: Have you seen him lately?
I was getting my sewing machine fixed...
...and he was sitting in the window
of his shop just staring.
MARY:
That is strange.
It's your bid, Betty.
- Mary Sue.
- Yeah?
What goes on up at Lovers' Lane?
What do you mean?
Well, you hear these things lately.
Kids spending so much time up there.
Is it holding hands? That kind of thing?
- Yeah.
- Hm.
That and...
What?
It doesn't matter.
No. I wanna know.
Well...
[WHISPERS]
...sex.
Ohh.
What's sex?
- You sure you wanna know this?
- Yes.
Okay.
Well...
You see, Mom...
...when two people really love
each other very, very much...
...and they wanna share that
with each other...
...that's what it's like to have sex.
Are you okay?
Yes.
It's just that...
...your father would never do
anything like that.
Ohh.
Hmm.
Well, you know, Mom...
...there are other ways
to enjoy yourself...
...without Dad.
Ahh.
Sweetie, you coming to bed?
Yeah. I'm just going to take a bath first.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh. Oh. Oh.
Oh.
Oh, my. Oh, my.
WOMAN [ON TV]:
What are you making?
Oh, shit.
Oh, God.
Fire!
Cat?
[SIREN WAILING]
DAVID:
Okay, right here.
All right, stop.
Stop!
Where is it?
Whoa!
Hey, here, grab the nozzle.
- But where's the cat?
- Come on. Just hold on tight.
FIREMAN:
Whoa!
So that's what these things do.
BIG BOB: In honor and in recognition
of your heroism...
...and with great appreciation from
the citizens of Pleasantville...
...I am pleased to present you with
this special commendation...
...from the Pleasantville
Chamber of Commerce.
[APPLAUSE]
MAN:
Attaboy, Bud.
MARGARET:
Bud.
DAVID:
Oh, hi.
- That sure was swell.
- Well, thank you, Margaret.
I baked you some of my oatmeal cookies.
Oh!
Oh, no, no. You baked those for Whitey.
No. I baked them for you.
No. You baked them for Whitey.
- No, you baked them for...
- No. I baked them for you.
Thank you.
Sure.
[PEOPLE WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY]
- Hey.
What's going on?
I'm not sure.
They wanna ask you a question.
- I didn't really know how to handle it, so...
- Okay.
[WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY]
Hi, Bud.
- How you doing?
GIRLS: Hi, Bud.
You wanted to ask me something?
How'd you know about the fire?
What?
How'd you know
how to put it out and all?
Oh.
Well, where I used to live,
that's just what firemen did.
[PEOPLE MURMURING]
And where's that?
Um...
Outside of Pleasantville.
[PEOPLE MURMURING]
Well, what's outside of Pleasantville?
It doesn't matter. It's not important.
What's outside of Pleasantville?
There are some places...
...that the road doesn't go
in a circle.
There are some places
where the road keeps going.
Keeps going?
Yeah. Yeah, it just keeps going.
It all keeps going. Roads and rivers and...
Like the mighty Mississippi?
What?
I thought the books were blank.
They were.
Okay. This was not my fault.
They asked what it was about.
I didn't remember,
because I read it back in 10th grade.
When I told them what I did remember,
that's when the pages filled in.
- The pages filled in?
- Mm-hm.
But only up until the part with the raft,
because that's as far as I read.
Do you know how it ends?
- Yeah, I do.
- So how does it end?
Well, okay.
Let's see. They were running away.
Huck and the slave.
They were going up the river,
trying to get free.
And, in trying to get free...
...they see that
they're sort of free already.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
Hey, what about this one?
Oh, yeah. Yeah. This is great.
This is... This kid Holden Caulfield,
he's a really lonely kid.
He gets kicked out of boarding school.
And then...
Sheesh. Look at them.
Spreading all over the place.
Look at her books.
ROY:
Look at her sweater.
I mean, going up to that lake
all the time is one thing...
...but now they're going
to a library?
What's next?
RALPH:
You're right.
Somebody ought
to do something about that.
Soon.
George, you're probably wondering
why I asked to stop by and see you today.
I'm sure you've noticed
the same things we all have.
Certain changes in the town.
You know what I mean by changes?
Changes.
Yeah, changes.
And I'm not just talking
about big stuff like the fire.
It's the little things.
You hear about Bill Miller?
No. What?
Wife wants him
to get one of those new beds.
- One of those big beds?
- Yeah.
Oh, my gosh. What's he gonna do?
I don't know. I mean, it's everywhere.
Bill Anderson's boy
just quit his job at the market.
What do you mean, quit?
Took his apron off in the middle of an order,
said, "I don't feel like it anymore."
Groceries all over the counter. Ha-ha-ha.
Took them three hours
just to sort it out.
- Sheesh.
- Yeah.
Everybody really likes you, George.
- Oh, well...
- No, they do.
Not just because you're a good bowler.
People respect you.
Well, thank you.
It's important for them to see
someone they respect...
...stand up for what's right.
If you love a place,
you can't just sit back...
...and watch this kind of thing
happen, now, can you?
No, of course not.
That is why I want you to be a member
of the Pleasantville Chamber of Commerce.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh!
I hardly know what to say.
[LAUGHING]
It's just like yours.
Well, it is exactly like mine, George.
[BIG BOB LAUGHING]
- Ohh.
- Huh.
Well, you can start by saying yes.
- Yes.
- And by getting me...
...one of those swell pineapple kabobs.
- Well, sure. You bet.
Betty, Bob wants to try
some of your great hors d'oeuvres.
Betty?
Bett?
I'll get her.
Are you okay?
You all right?
What am I going to do?
I can't go out there this way.
How can I go out there this way?
Look at me.
It's okay. It's all right.
GEORGE:
Betty?
Have you got any makeup?
In my handbag.
GEORGE:
Honey, where are you?
Here. Give me your cheek.
Here. Give me the other. There.
That's good. Now lift your chin up.
- Is it working?
- Yes.
Here, look at me.
BETTY:
What?
Does it look okay?
Yeah. It looks just like it did.
And... And they won't be able to tell?
No. No, they won't be able to tell.
GEORGE:
Betty, are you in there?
BETTY:
Coming, sweetie.
- Oh, hi.
- Hi.
Aren't you a little bit early?
I brought you something
from the library.
It's an art book.
Oh, my gosh, Bud.
I just thought, since you like to paint,
it might help to...
Gee whiz.
Who is Titian?
I'm not sure.
It's beautiful, Bud.
What's wrong?
Oh, it's...
I'll never be able to do that.
Well, you just started.
I mean, you can't do it now.
No, no, no. That's not it.
Just where am I gonna see
colors like that?
Must be awful lucky
to see colors like that.
I'll bet they don't know
how lucky they are.
- Hi.
- How are you doing?
- Swell.
Look, you probably don't think
I should be asking you this.
Will you go out with me tonight?
Whoo!
Hi there, Bud.
Hey, Mr. Simpson.
Your lawn looks great.
Yes.
TV REPAIRMAN:
Bud.
David.
Well, come here, young fella.
You know, I've been thinking.
I might've been a little hasty the other day
when you asked to come home.
It just took me by such surprise,
you know? Ha-ha-ha.
So even though
I can't make any promises...
...well, I figured
if you asked me real nice...
...I might just be willing
to talk about it again.
- I can't.
- What?
- Talk about it right now. I mean...
- I'll be honest with you, Bud.
I'm getting a little concerned about
what I'm seeing on some of these reruns.
Reruns?
Like when Margaret Henderson
makes her cookies for Whitey.
- Those are not your cookies, Bud.
- Yes, I know.
I know they are not my cookies...
Those are Whitey's cookies, Bud.
They belong to him.
He eats them,
then he asks her to go to Lovers' Lane...
I would love to talk about this right now,
but I am really in a hurry.
- Bud. Don't touch...
- I can't hear you.
It's really cruddy reception.
We'll talk later.
What's wrong?
Listen...
You're reading.
I can't believe you started
such a dorky fad.
It's D. H...
...Lawrence.
- You ever heard of him?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I read a couple pages.
Seemed kind of sexy.
It is.
Hey, can I ask you a question?
Sure.
- How come I'm still in black and white?
- What?
I've had like 10 times as much sex
as the rest of these girls...
...and I still look like this.
They spend an hour
in the back seat of some car...
...and all of a sudden
they're in Technicolor?
I don't know.
Maybe it's not just the sex.
- Where is it?
- A little bit farther, I think.
DJ [ON RADIO]:
WKPV, the sounds of Pleasantville.
Here's a new one
for all you kids out at Lovers' Lane.
[ETTA JAMES' "AT LAST" PLAYING]
Wow.
- It's amazing, huh?
- Yeah.
We're closed right now.
- Oh, I'm sorry. I...
- Oh, hi.
Hi. I just thought that...
No, no, no. Come on in.
BETTY:
It's beautiful.
Oh. Thanks.
I was just trying to do
one of these still lifes.
Kind of having a tough time.
Oh, I think it looks nice.
Well, here's what
it's supposed to look like.
Oh, my.
Here. Look at this.
- Where did you get this?
- Bud brought it to me.
- My Bud?
- Yeah. Here's my favorite.
What do you think?
Isn't it great
how she's resting like that?
She's crying.
No, she's not.
BETTY:
Yes, she is.
- Wait. It's all right.
- No. No. I've gotta go.
Let me see.
It's beautiful.
You shouldn't cover that up.
Here. Let me... I just... Let me just...
So, what's it like?
- What?
- Out there.
Well, it's...
It's louder...
...and scarier, I guess.
And it's a lot more dangerous.
Sounds fantastic.
The other night,
some kids came up here to go swimming...
...and they took off
all their clothes.
Do you want some berries?
Huh?
MARGARET:
Some berries. I picked them myself.
- Really?
- Mm-hm.
Yeah, there's lots of stuff.
Like what?
Um...
Here. I'll show you.
Here.
Go ahead. Try it.
[CLATTERING]
SKIP:
Mary Sue.
What are you doing?
It's 6:30.
So?
We were gonna...
You know.
Oh. I can't.
- Why not?
- I'm busy.
- With what?
- I'm studying.
MAN 1: Evening.
MAN 2: Evening.
MAN 3: Evening.
MAN 4: Evening.
MAN 5:
Evening.
- George.
- Evening, Norm.
Huh.
Honey, I'm home.
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[THUNDER CRASHING]
- What was that?
- I don't know.
What is that?
What's going on?
It's rain.
- Real rain?
- Yeah.
You don't have rain either?
Well, of course you don't. Hey, it's okay.
Here, come on.
[ALL MURMURING]
WILL:
What's going on?
Rain.
It's okay. It's fine.
Nothing to be scared of.
Here, I'll show you.
It's just rain. It's okay.
It's fine. Come on out.
You see? Look.
You see?
Come on. Come on.
GIRL:
It's cold.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Cool.
Honey, I'm home.
Where's my dinner?
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
[LAUGHING]
George?
[MEN WHISPERING]
What happened?
Are you all right?
What is it?
Rain.
Real rain?
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
Oh, my God.
Are you all right?
I came home like I always do...
...and I went in the front door...
...and I took off my coat...
...and I put down my briefcase...
...and I said, "Honey, I'm home."
Only there was no one there.
[MEN MURMURING]
No wife.
No lights.
- No dinner.
ROY: No dinner?
I went to the oven.
I thought maybe she had made
one of those TV dinners.
- Yeah, sure.
- She hadn't.
She was gone.
I looked and looked and looked.
It's gonna be fine, George.
You're with us now.
What are we gonna do, Bob?
Well, we're safe for now.
Thank goodness we're in a bowling alley.
But if George here
doesn't get his dinner...
...any one of us could be next.
It could be you, Gus.
Or you, Roy.
Or even you, Ralph.
That is real rain out there, gentlemen.
This isn't some little virus
that'll clear up on its own.
Something is happening to our town.
And I think we can all see
where it's coming from.
Roy.
Why don't you show them
what you showed me before?
But, Bob...
It's okay, Roy. Come on up here.
I know, Roy.
[ALL GASP]
Thanks.
He asked her what she was doing.
She said, "Nothing."
She was just thinking.
My friends, this isn't about
George's dinner.
It's not about Roy's shirt.
It's a question of values.
It's a question of whether
we wanna hold on to those values...
...that made this place great.
So a time has come to make a decision.
Are we in this thing alone...
...or are we in it together?
Together.
- Together.
MEN [CHANTING]:
Together. Together.
Together. Together. Together.
[THUNDER CRASHING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
BETTY: I told you where I was.
GEORGE: All night?
BETTY: I got caught in the storm.
You were gone all night too.
Look...
Let's just forget about it.
We'll just go to the meeting.
No. I told you, George,
I am not going to that meeting.
- Sure, you are.
- No, I'm not.
Look at me, George.
Look at my face.
That meeting's not for me.
- You'll put on some makeup.
- I don't wanna put on some makeup.
It goes away. It'll go away.
I don't want it to go away.
Now, you listen to me.
You're coming to this meeting.
You're going to put on some makeup.
You're going to be home
at 6:00 every night...
...and you're going to have dinner
ready on this table.
No, I'm not, sweetie.
I made you a meat loaf.
Just put it in the oven
and turn this little knob up to 350.
If you put the pie in
40 minutes later...
...it'll be hot in time for dessert.
Um...
I made a couple of lunches
for you for tomorrow...
...and put them in brown paper bags.
I'm going to go now.
Where are you gonna go?
Betty, don't go out there like that.
They'll see you.
Betty, come back here.
It's beautiful. Can I open it?
Sure.
[MARGARET GIGGLES]
Where'd you get it?
It was a prop from the school play.
Thank you.
[CAR APPROACHING]
Hello, Bud. Hello, Margaret.
Whitey.
Hey, Bud, why aren't you
at the town meeting right now?
No reason. How come you're not?
Oh.
We're supposed to go around
and let everyone know about it.
I thought maybe it was because
you were too busy...
...entertaining your colored girlfriend.
[PETE LAUGHS]
Hey, why don't you guys
get the hell out of here?
All right. We'll do that.
You know, Margaret,
you can come over...
...and make those oatmeal cookies for me
anytime you want to.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[CROWD CLAMORING]
BIG BOB:
People.
- People.
- Roy Campbell's got a blue front door.
- It's always been blue.
- People.
People, please.
Please.
I think we all know
what's been going on here.
Up until now...
...everything around here
has always been, well, pleasant.
[CROWD MURMURS]
Recently, certain things
have become unpleasant.
MAN: Hear, hear.
- Now, it seems to me...
...that the first thing
we have to do...
...is to separate out the things
that are pleasant...
...from the things that are unpleasant.
[CROWD MURMURING]
[BELL TOLLING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[BIKE CRASHES]
WOMAN 1: That's Betty Parker.
WOMAN 2: That is an outrage.
[CROWD MURMURING]
TV REPAIRMAN:
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Get in here. Now.
You think this is a toy?
You think it's your own little
goddamn coloring book?
- Look, it just sort of happened.
- A deluge doesn't just happen.
Bolts of lightning don't just happen.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Oh, no? Let me show you something.
Go on, try it.
TV REPAIRMAN: Boom! Right there.
What do you call that, huh?
You know, you don't deserve this place.
You don't deserve to live in this paradise.
- Where's the remote control I gave you?
- Why?
Because you're coming home,
you little twerp...
...and I'm gonna put this place
back the way it was.
- I can't let you do that.
- What?
I'm sorry.
I'm not gonna let you do that.
Just give me the damn remote. Ow.
- I'm gonna go now.
- You're not going anywhere.
You're gonna get that remote
and come home...
...and we're gonna make
everybody happy again.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Hey. Where you going in such a hurry?
Now, that's not real friendly.
BOY 1: Let's see if she looks like her picture.
BOY 2: She's real pretty.
Yeah, you wanna be friendly, don't you?
Why don't you show us
what's under that nice blue dress?
WHITEY:
Yeah, come on.
[BOYS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
PETE: Hey, where you going?
There's nowhere to go over there.
[BOYS LAUGHING]
You know, that is a lovely shade of blue.
Don't you think that's
a lovely shade of blue?
[WHITEY GRUNTS]
DAVID:
Get out of here!
Go on! Go! Get out of here!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
What?
[CROWD SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[CROWD CHEERING]
It's okay. He's not in there.
Hey. Hey. It's okay. It's okay. All right?
I'm gonna get you out of here, all right?
Are you okay?
[WHOOPING]
MAN:
Keep them coming.
- No!
- No, Mary Sue. It's better this way.
This is the only book I've ever
read in my whole life...
...and you're not gonna put it
on that fire.
Just give me the book.
[SKIP GRUNTS]
Mary Sue.
DAVID:
Jennifer.
It's me.
Let's go inside.
[GLASS CLINKS]
[FOOTSTEPS]
Hello?
Just thought I'd try to tidy it up a bit.
Oh, it's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
Once we sweep it up,
it'll be all right again.
Yeah. Yeah.
He's right. Let's...
Here. Help me with this, will you?
Good. Put this up in here.
[CROWD CLAMORING]
BIG BOB:
People.
[CLEARS THROAT]
This is not the answer, people.
No matter how upset we may get...
...or how frustrated we may be...
...we're not gonna solve our problems
out in the street.
It's just the wrong way to do it.
We have to find a code of conduct...
...that we can all agree to live by.
Now, I asked George and Ralph here
to sketch out a few ideas...
...and I think they've done a terrific job.
Now, if we can all agree to these,
we can take a vote...
...and I think we can start off
in the right direction.
[CROWD MURMURING]
"One: All public disruption
and acts of vandalism...
...are to cease immediately.
Two: All citizens of Pleasantville...
...are to treat each other
in a courteous and pleasant manner."
"Courteous and pleasant manner."
Well, that's not too bad.
"Three: The area commonly known
as Lovers' Lane...
...as well as the public library...
...shall be closed until further notice.
[MURMURING]
Four: The only permissible recorded music
shall be the following:
Johnny Mathis, Perry Como,
Jack Jones...
...the marches of John Philip Sousa,
or 'The Star-Spangled Banner.'
In no event
shall any music be tolerated...
...that is not of a temperate
or pleasant nature.
[MURMURING]
Five: There shall be
no public sale of umbrellas...
...or preparation for inclement weather
of any kind.
Six: No bed frame
or mattress may be sold...
...measuring more than 38 inches wide.
Seven: The only permissible
paint colors...
...shall be black, white, or gray...
...despite the recent availability
of certain alternatives.
Eight: All elementary
and high-school curriculum...
...shall teach the non-changeist
view of history...
...emphasizing continuity
over alteration."
Wow.
Hey. This thing still works.
[BUDDY HOLLY'S "RAVE ON" PLAYING]
Turn that off.
You're not allowed to do that now.
Sure, you are.
[SONG PLAYING]
DAVID:
Oh, this is good.
Just do it?
Don't worry.
We'll get you a new one.
I don't know what I'd do
if I couldn't paint anymore, Bud.
Maybe I have an idea.
WOMAN 1:
Disgusting. It scares me.
[CROWD MURMURING]
WOMAN 2:
You should be ashamed of yourselves.
WOMAN 3:
This is disgusting.
[CROWD SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[KIDS WHISPERING]
LISA ANNE:
When are they gonna let them out?
POLICE CHIEF DAN:
Hey, what are you kids doing out there?
There's someone to see you, Bud.
- Oh, hi.
GEORGE: Hi.
Is this a bad time?
No. No, it's fine. Come on in.
- I brought you something.
- Thank you.
- Cocktail olives.
- Everything else was frozen.
- I didn't know how to...
- I appreciate it.
- You know, your mom went out.
- Went out?
Yeah. She went out for a little while.
When?
Three days ago.
Jeez, everything is so cockeyed.
I didn't even know it was Tuesday.
Tuesday we play bridge
with the Jenkins.
There was no bridge. It's...
Can I have one of those?
Sure. Yeah. You hungry?
[GEORGE CHUCKLES]
Mrs. Benson was making
meat loaf next door.
I almost climbed in her kitchen window.
What happened?
One minute, everything's fine.
The next...
What went wrong?
Nothing went wrong. People change.
People change?
Yeah, people change.
Can they change back?
I don't know. I think it's harder.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Not fair, you know?
- You get used to one thing, and then...
- I know. It's not.
BIG BOB:
Bud Parker, William Johnson...
...you are charged with the desecration
of a public building...
...and the use
of prohibited paint colors...
...in violation of
the Pleasantville code of conduct...
...and laws of common decency.
Do you admit that on the night
of May 1 st...
...you did willfully apply the following
forbidden paint colors...
...to the north wall
of the Pleasantville police station:
Red, pink, vermilion, puce, chartreuse...
...umber, blue, aqua, oxblood,
green, peach, crimson...
...yellow, olive, and magenta?
Yeah, I do. Where's our lawyer?
I think we wanna keep these proceedings
as pleasant as possible.
I don't think a lawyer
will be necessary.
[CROWD CHUCKLING]
Do you further admit
that this unnatural depiction...
...occurred in full public view
where it was accessible to...
...and in plain sight
of minor children?
It was accessible to everyone.
Let the record show
that the defendants have answered...
...in the affirmative to all charges.
Do you have anything
to say in your defense?
- Yeah, I do...
- Bill?
I didn't mean to hurt anybody.
Maybe if I painted
something different.
Or maybe I could use
less colors or something.
Or, you know, certain colors.
Or maybe I could...
You could pick out
the colors beforehand...
...and then they wouldn't
bother anybody.
- I've got something to say.
- Very well.
You don't have a right to do this.
[CROWD MURMURING]
I mean...
...I know you want it
to stay pleasant around here...
...but there are so many things...
...that are so much better.
Like silly or sexy...
...or dangerous or brief.
And every one of those things
is in you all the time...
...if you just have the guts
to look for them.
[GAVEL POUNDS]
- Enough.
- I thought I was allowed to defend myself.
- You're not allowed to lie.
- I'm not lying.
You see those faces up there?
They're no different than you are.
They just happen to see something
inside themselves...
[GAVEL POUNDS]
- I said, that's enough.
- I'll show you. Dad?
Yeah, Bud?
It's okay, Dad. Just listen for a sec.
I know you miss her.
I mean, you told me you did.
But maybe it's not just the cooking...
...or the cleaning that you miss.
Maybe it's something else.
Maybe you can't even describe it.
Maybe you only know it
when it's gone.
Maybe it's like there's a whole piece
of you that's missing too.
Look at her, Dad.
Doesn't she look pretty like that?
Doesn't she look just as beautiful...
...as the first time you met her?
You really want her back
the way she was?
Doesn't she look wonderful?
Now, don't you wish
you could tell her that?
[CROWD GASPING]
BIG BOB:
You're out of order.
DAVID:
Why am I out of order?
BIG BOB: I'm not gonna let you turn
this courtroom into a circus.
I don't think it's a circus,
and I don't think they do either.
[CROWD GASPS]
[GAVEL POUNDS]
- This behavior must stop at once.
- But see? That's just the point.
It can't stop at once,
because it's in you...
...and you can't stop something
that's inside you.
It is not inside me.
- Oh, sure, it is.
- No, it is not.
What do you wanna do to me
right now?
Come on. Everyone is turning colors.
Kids are making out in the street.
No one is getting their dinner.
Hell, you could have a flood.
Pretty soon, the women
could be going to work...
...while the men stayed at home
and cooked.
- That is not going to happen.
- But it could.
No, it could not!
[CROWD MURMURING]
Bud.
[CROWD LAUGHING]
Hey, look at this.
MARGARET:
Bud.
JENNIFER:
Uch.
- What an image.
- Oh, shut up.
BETTY:
Bud.
[LAUGHS]
DAVID: You sure you don't
wanna come home?
Yeah. I gotta do this
for a little while.
Besides, you think
I even have a chance...
...of getting into college back there?
Honestly?
- Do you have your admissions letter?
- Yeah. It's right here.
I did the slut thing, David.
Got kind of old.
I'll come back
and check on you soon.
Okay.
[BUS APPROACHING]
You turned into a pretty cool guy.
How'd that happen?
I don't know.
[JENNIFER CHUCKLES]
- I'll see you.
- Okay.
Bye.
MARGARET:
Just don't forget about me.
Even if you never come back.
I just don't want you
to forget about me.
I couldn't do that.
- Here.
- Oh, what's this?
Lots of stuff.
A meat loaf sandwich and...
BETTY:
And a hard-boiled egg.
And some marshmallow rice squares.
Hello.
There's some fried chicken in there too.
Don't skip dinner just because
you're not here anymore.
- I won't. I thought that you weren't gonna...
- Oh, I had to come say goodbye.
Just wear this on the trip...
...in case it gets cold.
It's a pretty short trip.
Still.
Oh, Bud.
I am just so proud of you.
Thanks.
I know.
I love you too.
Well...
I... I guess you'd better stand back.
["PLEASANTVILLE" THEME SONG
PLAYING ON TV]
ANNOUNCER [ON TV]: That concludes
the first hour of the Pleasantville marathon.
Don't forget, we'll be going all night long
until noon tomorr...
[WOMAN SOBBING]
DAVID'S MOM:
Hi.
I thought you went out of town.
Came back.
What's wrong?
[GROANS]
I don't know.
Everything's just so fucked up.
I got halfway there and thought,
"What am I doing?"
He's nine years younger than I am.
Doesn't make me feel younger.
Makes me feel older.
When your father was here,
I used to think this was it.
This is the way
it was always gonna be.
I had the right house. I had the right car.
I had the right life.
There is no right house.
There is no right car.
God, my face must be a mess.
It looks great.
Honey, that's really sweet of you,
but I'm sure it does not look great.
Sure, it does.
Come here.
I'm 40 years old.
I mean, it's not supposed to be like this.
It's not supposed to be anything.
Hold still.
How'd you get so smart
all of a sudden?
I had a good day.
So, what's gonna happen now?
I don't know.
Do you know
what's going to happen now?
No. I don't.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
I guess I don't either.