EMT 1:
All right, people,
let's move! Let's go!
EMT 2:
Let's go, everybody!
We need some help!
Some help here!
Get in here, get in here!
She's close!
Vitals are down
to nothing.
Here you go. Come on.
Let me get in here.
You got her?
We're clear.
MAN: I got it.
All right, lift her up
on three. One, two, three.
EMT 2: Let's move!
EMT 1: Let's go! Let's go!
We need some room!
Clear it out, clear it out!
Let's make a hole! Come on!
Get a sterile pack!
NURSE: Right down
the hallway, please!
Let's go! In here!
(THUNDERCLAP)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Anna didn't make it, Greg.
(SIGHS)
We tried everything.
The trauma was
just too much.
The baby?
The baby, I'm concerned,
might have some abnormalities.
Outwardly, we can
already tell that the child
has no pigmentation.
It's called albinism.
It's strictly genetic.
That's, that's... Well,
that's pale skin, right?
And pale eyes
that are usually
more light-sensitive.
I want to see him.
Greg, you have to remember
that an unborn child
experiences everything
that the mother experiences.
You take me to him.
You show me.
(BABY CRYING)
(GURGLING)
DOCTOR: We'll do everything
we can for him, Greg.
You know that.
GREG: What are you
doing to him?
DOCTOR:
We're measuring
his brain waves.
(CRYING CONTINUES)
You don't have
to do this now.
(CRYING CONTINUES)
(RAPID BEEPING)
(CRYING)
That's not my son.
(BABY CRYING)
(LOUD BEEPING)
(CRYING CONTINUES)
That's not my son.
Come on, Greg,
let's go.
(CRYING)
That's not my son.
You don't need this.
For Christ's sake, let's go.
(CONTINUES CRYING)
(CRYING ECHOES)
Not good, Sheriff.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
Jessie.
JESSIE: Doug.
Thanks for making
the drive.
Are we still
in Wheaton County?
Barely.
Did I ruin your Sunday?
Well, I guess if somebody
was going to have to,
I'm glad it was you.
Doug,
I can hear him again.
He's movin' around
down there.
Tell me you didn't
try to talk to him.
You bet your ass
I didn't.
Good.
Miss Caldwell.
They said a boy, right?
I'm guessing
that's what it is.
The old man here
died last night.
The neighbors
found him this morning.
We figure
the kid's his grandson.
So where is he?
He won't come up
from the cellar.
He didn't report
his grandfather's
death either.
We already know
he died of natural causes.
Doug, what am I
doing here?
The neighbors say
he may be retarded.
One of them says deformed.
You know,
physically handicapped.
I don't know.
I couldn't for the life of me
think of who else to call.
He's scared enough,
and I thought
maybe you could
come down and talk him
out of there without us having
to go down and drag him out.
Jessie, the neighbors
talk about him
like he's some
kind of a phantom.
I haven't met one yet that
ever had a good look at him.
What are you
telling me, Doug?
That the old folks may have
kept him down there,
like some kind
of a family secret.
I don't know.
Boy?
I brought somebody
to talk to you.
Hello?
Hey, my name is Jessie.
Are you okay down here?
You think we could
turn a light on?
Hey, if you're afraid,
you don't need to be.
Not with me.
BOY: (SOFTLY)
I'm not afraid.
What's your name?
Powder.
Is that a name or a nickname?
He was getting coffee
and he fell.
He just... He just
fell over and died.
I tried to help him.
I tried. He...
DOUG: We know that.
Son, I told you,
you're not in any trouble.
I'm sorry.
I just want to see you.
Why?
Come on.
Nobody's gonna hurt you.
It's all right.
Give me your hand.
Come on.
What's your real name, son?
Jeremy Reed.
You've been down here
all night, Jeremy.
JESSIE:
You must be starved.
Could you get us
something to eat?
Anything. Sheriff?
We'll be all right.
Be right back.
Why didn't you tell anyone
when you knew he was dead?
Why didn't you
call the police?
Grandpa said
there would be a day
when he would die,
like grandma died,
and that people would come
and see me
and try and take me away.
Get back there.
Keep an ear,
but don't go down.
Yes, sir.
Lucy, this is Barnum.
LUCY:  Go ahead, Sheriff.
I'm here.
We're still out at the Reeds'.
We got something out here
nobody's gonna believe.
You don't live
down here?
Mmm.
I do most of the work
around the place.
At least until the sun
gets too high.
Then the sunglasses
don't even help.
Did you know they make
contact lenses now
that can protect your eyes
from the sun all the time?
I read about them,
but Grandpa said
they cost too much.
When's the last time
you were in school?
I've never been to school.
I read about it though.
But you said you
read all these books?
Have you read
this book?
Well, I know college kids
who couldn't wade
through this one.
Pick a page.
Two hundred and sixteen.
"Where lies the final harbor,
whence we unmoor no more.
"In what rapt ether
sails the world of which
the weariest will never weary?
"Where is the foundling's
father hidden?
"Our souls are like those
orphans whose unwedded mothers
die in bearing them.
"And the secret of our
paternity lies in their grave,
"and we must there
to learn it."
You know the whole book?
I know 'em all.
Go clear 'em back.
All right, everybody,
let's move back.
And I mean back beyond
the vehicles. Let's go!
It's all right.
You don't have to be afraid.
You're afraid.
You're afraid for me.
(ONLOOKERS CHATTERING)
(SIRENS BLARING)
(SIRENS STOP)
Why don't you
get in here?
I'll take that.
(STARTS ENGINE)
HARLEY: You ever see so
many goddamn lightning rods
on one house?
I just got off the horn
with the coroner.
He said that old boy died
of natural causes, but there
was evidence of fibrillation.
His body was juiced
with electricity.
That old man was laying
dead there all night.
You think the paramedics
showed up this morning
and tried paddles on him?
Are you telling me the kid
electrocuted the old man?
What do you think,
he's Dr. Frankenstein?
I'm just sayin' that that's
more than an albino, Doug.
That is spooky.
I never thought we'd
find a man too white
for you there, Harley.
(DOG BARKING)
(WINDOW OPENING AND CLOSING)
(BOYS CHATTERING)
Down! Set!
Hut!
JESSIE:
Don't let 'em fool you.
They spend most their time
tryin' to look tough.
You get to know 'em,
you find out they're
mostly scared and lonely,
just like everybody else.
(BOYS CONTINUE CHATTERING)
Hut!
(BOYS STOP CHATTERING)
What the hell is that?
You need to see him, Aaron,
to know what I'm saying.
You need to see him sitting
out in the hall right now,
'cause I'm telling you,
I've never seen
anything like him.
That's exactly what I mean.
Because of the way he's lived.
Uh, he doesn't seem
to know what things are.
I mean, things you and I
take for granted,
common, everyday objects,
simple ideas...
I just don't think
he's ever been
exposed to them.
I mean, he's about the most
well-read teenage kid
you could ever meet,
but in other ways...
(WHISPERS)
I think he's a lot
like a little child.
(BOYS MURMURING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(BOYS LAUGHING)
(CHATTERING STOPS)
Why you look like that?
You look like some
kind of vampire from
outer space or something.
They kick you out
of cancer camp?
You got some kind
of disease?
Don't look at me, man.
Did you hear what I said?
I don't like your eyes.
(SCATTERED LAUGHING)
What's a new guy gotta do
the first day he gets here?
He's gotta do the due.
New guy, first day,
first meal.
He's gotta wear his spoon.
(BOYS LAUGHING)
You ever wear your spoon?
Well, you got two choices.
You can either wear it
on the end of your nose...
Why don't you show, Mitch?
(BOYS LAUGHING)
Now, you can wear it
like that,
or you can
wear it the other way,
which is up your ass.
You choose.
What are
you doin'?
(BOYS GASPING)
(BOYS QUIET)
(RUSTLING)
(RUSTLING CONTINUES)
(CLATTERS)
Poppa.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
You see Steven?
He stayed
three hours.
Did her more good
than them painkillers.
She was hurtin' all day
till he got here.
(SIGHS)
He brought her that, too.
What happened out
at the Reed farm today?
I'm here, angel.
Something about
a retarded boy they got
up at the state home now.
How the hell
did you hear about that?
I guess I don't have
to tell you what I
think about that.
I'd love it if you didn't.
The last thing
we need up there
is another mental
defective along with
all that other trash.
(SOFTLY)
Here you go.
I don't know what he is,
but retarded he's not.
Well, aside from the absence
of any and all body hair,
which is a condition
not too uniquely uncommon,
bottom line,
he's a very healthy
young man.
In fact, with all that
farm work, I'd say you're
in damn fine shape.
And the optometrist
said his contact lenses
will be here
the end of the week?
They'll be
callin' him Ol' Blue Eyes
in time
for the county fair.
You guys are comin', right?
Uh, you'll see
a few of us there.
Hey, Doc,
thanks for comin' out.
It's my pleasure.
Good day, Mr. Jeremy Reed.
Jeremy, listen, uh,
I want you to
think about something.
We attend school in town
at Wheaton High.
You certainly wouldn't
be at an intellectual
disadvantage there,
and I know most
of the teachers, so...
Anyway, um,
all I'm saying is,
if you'd like to attend
school one day next week,
I can arrange it.
Will my contacts be ready
by Monday?
(STUDENTS CHATTERING)
BOY: Hey, hey, guys...
(CHATTERING STOPS)
(SOFTLY)
Molecules.
When we speed up the course
of molecules, we get...
(TAPPING FEET)
...energy.
And, um, since we
are all basically
just a mass of molecules,
what does our brain send out
to all the other parts
of the body?
Lindsey?
Um, impulses.
Yeah.
Electric impulses.
Jeremy, turn your head
and look at Lindsey.
(STUDENTS SNICKERING)
Yes. That's lovely.
That's very good.
You've just
relayed electricity.
Your brain sent out
an electric impulse
down to your neck muscles
and, uh, what, what
turned your head,
besides the obvious?
What your, what your muscles
used to turn your head?
(SNAPPING FINGERS)
It's energy. Energy.
Always relaying,
always transforming
and never-ending.
Now, looky here.
This is a, uh,
a Jacob's Ladder.
It's a science fair toy,
and it's, uh, built to show us
how electricity travels.
Okay?
Can we get the, uh, shutters?
Watch this.
STUDENTS: Ooh!
Hey, cut it out.
Cut it out.
RIPLEY: Ooh, look at this.
Blinding, isn't it?
Now, who can tell me
why electricity travels?
Uh, boredom?
(STUDENTS LAUGHING)
Huh, he tickles me.
No. No, potential.
Potential.
One side
of this thing is positive,
while the other side
has a strong negative pull.
And, uh,
that's all the potential that
electricity needs to travel.
That's right.
That's pretty good.
Don't I bring you good,
entertaining things?
But you get the idea that it
does... You know, it travels
and just keeps going.
Did you ever...
What's your experience
with electricity?
Did you ever, you know,
run your feet over a carpet
like that and touch somebody?
What happens?
Static electricity?
That's right, that's right.
Now, where does it go
when you touch somebody?
(PEN SPINNING)
It just goes out.
So... So, so electricity,
like energy, uh,
just, um, uh, recycles.
(BUZZING LOUDLY)
It flows in a cycle
that doesn't end.
It, uh...
(BUZZING INTENSIFIES)
Are you all right?
Mr. Ripley?
(BUZZING INTENSIFIES)
Are you okay?
(STUDENTS GASPING)
(GASPING CONTINUES)
(GASPS)
HARLEY: The local news
and those Channel 5
people are outside.
So is Jimmy Hobbs
from the newspaper.
Tell them to go home.
Oh, come on, Doug.
They ain't goin' anywhere
till somebody goes out there
and talks to 'em.
Tell them there's no
fatalities, no sex scandal.
That will
get rid of them fast.
God damn it, Doug,
I sound like a moron
if I say more than
five words to those people,
and you know it.
Well, if the shoe fits.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON PA)
DUANE:
But I can't do it.
I've got no authorization
to do anything.
I can't let you
go anywhere...
DOUG: Hi, Doc.
Here we go, here we go.
Doug, Doug,
tell Duane that it's
okay for me to see that kid.
Thank you.
Donald, you're just
the man I wanted to see.
I got 20 different kids
telling me
20 different stories.
Right. Uh, if I hadn't
seen it myself,
I'd say it was impossible.
It was a model.
For God sakes, it picked him
right out of his seat.
What did?
Hold it! Hold it, Doug.
The kid doesn't have
a scratch on him.
Heart rate's
a little irregular,
but nothing to indicate
the kind of electrical shock
you're talking about.
Right, right!
And he's got a hole, uh,
burned in his shirt
the size
of a bowling ball.
(SIGHS) Something's
happened here.
Something's happened here.
I'm telling you,
with everything we know
about science,
about the makeup
of the human body,
what happened in that
classroom is impossible!
That kid attracted
an arc of electricity
from 30 feet away.
And not just
from the Jacob's Ladder.
I mean, after a second,
it was like it was
comin' at him out
of the whole... Building.
You want to know why
there isn't a hair on him?
DOUG: Why?
Because he is electrolysis.
It can't grow on him.
NURSE: Doc Roth?
Yes?
Can I see you
for a minute?
Excuse me.
NURSE: Excuse me.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON PA)
Drink that in.
DOUG: I will.
Nobody saw him
leave his room,
but his clothes
are gone too.
Find him.
He can't have gotten far.
Lucy, come in.
(DOG BARKING)
(SOFTLY) Hey.
(GROWLING)
Zack! Zachary!
Zack, come here.
Come here, boy.
(BARKING)
(GROWLING)
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Watch out. He bites.
The family before us
made him
pretty mean, so...
Wow, I can't believe
I'm looking at you.
Are you okay?
I didn't mean
to scare anybody.
The whole thing was pretty
embarrassing really.
Embarrassing?
You're kidding, right?
(LAUGHS)
My grandma used to
say I have an
electric personality.
(LAUGHS)
Well, that was
some light show.
I mean, people will
be talking about that
to their grandkids'
grandkids around here.
I don't mean to stare,
but I had a bet
with a friend
that you have
blue-gray eyes.
She says
they're blue-green.
Looks like she's right.
Well, actually...
You're both wrong.
Oh.
Sorry.
No, no, that's okay.
Just kind of took me
by surprise, that's all.
(SIGHS)
Oh, well.
(ZACK BARKS)
LINDSEY: You must feel
like you've got two heads,
the way everybody
looks at you around here,
huh?
Have you ever listened
to people from the inside?
Listened so close,
you can hear their thoughts
and all their memories?
Hear 'em think from places
that they don't even know
they think from?
What, are you saying
you can do that?
Are you sure you're okay?
(NERVOUS LAUGH)
Do you know how to get
to the interstate?
Yeah, it's, um...
If you follow the train
tracks, you'll see
the Redmond water tower.
Then, if you go across
the trestle, you'll see it.
But you're really okay?
I'm okay.
You better hurry.
They catch boys running
away from Central,
I hear they get solitary.
Hey!
Stay away from those
electrical outlets, okay?
(SOFTLY)
Bye.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say you were headed
for the highway.
Don't make me
come out there, boy.
Now, you're about to make me
a whole lot meaner.
Trust me, son,
you don't want
to make me mad.
Afraid.
I don't make you mad,
I make you afraid.
What was that?
I said that
you're afraid of me.
Duncan,
get on back.
I can handle this.
I'm all right.
I can see that.
Then let me go home.
I don't want to go back
to that hospital.
We'll call the doc.
If he says okay, I'll take
you back to Central.
Central's not my home.
DOUG:
I'm trying to tell you
as nice as I know how.
Now either you come with me
without a fuss, or we're gonna
have ourselves a problem.
You want me to cuff him?
(ENGINE STARTS)
Lucy, this is one.
We got him.
I'm coming back
to the office.
LUCY:  Doug.
You got a problem
with hospitals in general?
I don't like 'em.
Well, you can put me
on that list.
Worst day I can remember
was in a hospital.
(DOOR OPENS)
What day was that?
The day I was born.
Let me get this straight,
Jeremy.
You said that you've never
been tested for IQ before.
Is that right?
And your grandmother
tutored you.
Did she ever say
anything about it?
She said I was
a fast learner.
(LAUGHS)
Yeah.
Well, I think
that's about to fall
into the no-shit category.
(SIGHS)
Jeremy Reed, this is
Dr. Aaron Stipler with
the State Board of Education.
Jeremy.
JESSIE: These men and
women are here
because the results of
your diagnostics came back
with a few surprises.
Please, sit down.
(SIGHS)
Miss Caldwell says
you're a very unique
young man, Jeremy.
Hmm.
She also tells me
that, um,
reading and your grandparents
are the only ways you've
experienced the world.
Is that true?
What about a radio
or, um, a TV set?
Surely you've watched some
television at some point?
He probably couldn't.
Didn't your grandparents
have a TV set, Jeremy?
I could never
watch television.
Are you saying
you weren't allowed?
Here,
it probably just makes...
No.
Oh!
I'm saying I could
never watch television.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
That was... That was my fault.
I, uh... I was just trying
to make them understand.
What the good doctor hasn't
let you in on yet is that
your test shows
that you're a genius.
STIPLER: Please!
Your IQ scored right
off the charts, Jeremy.
There isn't even
a classification for you,
it was so high.
All of your tests indicate
that you have
the most advanced intellect
in the history of humankind.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
If you thought I was
that advanced,
would you ask me
if I understood?
(CHUCKLES)
Jeremy, these people are
in a position to help you.
Can they send me home?
Can they
send me back?
No.
I'm sorry. They can't.
The fact is, the...
The farm's in probate.
Do you know
what that means?
"Of or pertaining to probate
or a court of probate,
exempli gratia,
"the official proving
of a will as
authentic or genuine."
Or it can also mean
the official,
certified copy of
a will so proved.
Right.
Well, it seems that
the bank owns most of it.
I'm sorry.
(CLEARING THROAT) Well,
back to the matter at hand.
I have a few more questions
I have to ask you, Jeremy.
You're not here
to ask me questions.
You're here to find out
how I cheated.
That's the only way
you can make sense of it.
That's what you need
to believe.
But I don't need you to
believe in me, Dr. Stipler.
And I'm not interested
in any of your tests.
I'm not interested in you,
or anything else here.
I'm interested in going home!
What the hell
is going on here?
What you already know.
I'm not like other people.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SIGHS)
(BOYS CHATTERING)
(CHATTERING CONTINUES)
(STRUMMING GUITAR)
What the hell is that thing
doing up here anyway?
Jessie told me you didn't
want to come up here.
I don't want to be
anywhere that's not home.
Jessie's trying so hard
to help you, kiddo.
If you're as smart as they
say you are, you know she's
about the best friend you got.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
The storm's
over Poho County.
We'll be lucky
to get a drop.
When a thunderstorm comes up,
I can feel it inside.
And when lightning comes down,
I can feel it
wanting to come to me.
Grandma said it was God.
She said
the white fire was God.
Do you believe
in God, Sheriff?
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
That it was God who
took my mother?
Anna!
Hey.
Took your mother? Your
grandfolks told you that?
I remember it.
(LEAVES RUSTLING)
Hello, John, Mitch.
What the hell are you
doing out this far?
What are you?
You're supposed to be
at the lake, skinny-dipping
with the rest of the faggots.
(COCKS RIFLE)
You afraid you're gonna
get a little color on that
marshmallow ass of yours?
Look, man, you'd
better get out of here.
Oh, Johnny!
How about it, huh?
What are you doin', man?
I could do you right now.
Right now, man.
One less freak
in the freak show.
Come on, man!
It might go off!
Why don't you go suck
your old man off some more?
How about it, huh?
You gonna show us
one of your little tricks?
Come on, John!
It's...
(GUNSHOT)
(BOYS WHOOPING)
Let's go!
Yeah!
BOY 1: All right!
BOY 2: Look at it!
Look at it! Look at it!
Oh, man!
(PANTING)
A good hunter
don't hunt for the kill.
hunts for the hunt.
Now, that's a perfect hit
right there.
That's a perfect shot.
That's a clean kill
right through the heart.
Y'all see that?
Now, what she's doing now...
It's just her nerves dyin'.
Suffering's minimal
when you know
what you're doin'.
What the hell
are you doing
out here?
Now, listen to me.
You didn't
see any of this,
you hear?
Now you just
back out of here, boy.
Now, now,
stay away from it.
It ain't dead yet,
stupid.
Well, what the hell's
with you, man?
Oh, let's get this moron
out of here before
he gets himself kicked.
(GASPING)
BOYS: What's he doin'?
What's he doin'?
MITCH: What do you think
you're doin', man?
(GASPING)
Hey, come on!
Harley?
Let Harley go!
(GASPING)
BOY 1: Oh, my God!
Cut it out, man!
BOY 2: Stop, man!
Somebody do something!
Say something, man!
BOY 1: Are you okay?
BOY 2: Somebody
make him stop.
MITCH: It doesn't matter
what you do,
just make him stop!
Somebody make him stop!
Come on! Come on, man!
(GASPING)
BOY 1: Harley!
He's giving him
a heart attack
or something!
Let him go!
(HARLEY SCREAMING)
BOY 1: Harley!
BOY 2: Harley!
Do something, John!
Let him go, you freak!
BOY: He's gonna have
a heart attack.
JOHN: Let him go.
Now. Let him go.
Do it!
Put the goddamn
gun down, John.
Do it!
(HARLEY GASPING)
(GUN FIRES)
(HARLEY SCREAMING)
BOYS: Harley!
Harley!
Harley, calm down!
Are you okay?
Harley?
(WHIMPERING)
(CRYING)
(CONTINUES CRYING)
(PANTING)
Break it up, guys.
Come on. Okay.
DOUG: I left camp
for less than an hour.
When I get back,
one of my deputies is being
hauled down the mountain
in an ambulance.
The boys tell me
that you gave him
some sort of an attack.
It was like a seizure.
Is that right?
No.
Then what did happen?
Why won't you tell anyone?
I let him see.
I opened him up,
and I let him see.
He just couldn't see
what he was doing,
so I helped him.
(RADIO DISTORTING)
LUCY:  Sheriff...
You better start
leveling with me.
Go ahead.
(RADIO DISTORTION CONTINUES)
It's Maxine, Doug.
She just called.
I'm on my way.
I gotta go.
I need you
to think real hard
about telling me
what happened.
Thanks, Jess.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Jeremy, please.
I want to go home.
Do you understand that?
Look,
whatever happened up there,
whatever you saw...
I saw that
I don't like what you do!
Any of you!
Jeremy...
No!
You pretend
to be my friend,
the way you
pretend everything!
A friend
doesn't lock you up!
(GASPS)
A friend doesn't take you
away from your home...
(GASPS)
...and say that
it's for your own good!
How long do you really think
I'll let you keep me here?
(PANTING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
She's all right.
I got nervous
when I couldn't find you,
so I called the doc.
(SIGHS)
Harley just got admitted
over at County.
Give a call over there,
will you, Maxine?
Find out how he's doing.
Listen, this is like
having your heart
torn out every day.
Doug, there's
no explanation
why your wife
should still be
alive right now.
DOUG:
Give me the short one,
will you, Doc?
DUANE:
She can't like seeing
this strain on you,
which may be why
she's hanging on through
the worst pain of her life.
(SIGHS)
It's just gonna make it
that much easier
if we get her
back to County.
This is where
she wants to be, Duane.
She told me
when she still could.
She keeps holding on.
I just don't know why.
DUANE:
And you won't.
Doug, she's past
communicating.
You can't get
inside of her head.
(SIGHS)
And if you could,
she'd probably tell you,
"Let me go."
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
RIPLEY: Knock, knock.
Mind if I come in?
(SIGHS)
Hey, you, you
did something to me.
Um...
You know,
I didn't figure it out
until enough people
looked at me like I was crazy
or told me to act my age,
but you, uh, uh, zapped me
or I, uh, zapped myself
when I touched you.
But I've been...
I've been running
around on this high
like I was 18 again.
I've had more ideas
and more, more focus
and better sex
than I've had in 10 years.
Do you believe me?
Well... Why shouldn't you?
You know if what I say
is bullshit, don't you?
So you know when I say
I'm just here to talk
that, uh, that I mean it.
Uh, say, did you...
Did you read any,
uh, Einstein?
No? Oh, well...
Oh, I think you'd like him.
Um, he said he believed
in life after death.
Only because energy can
never cease to exist.
That it relays,
it transforms,
but it doesn't stop ever.
Uh, and he said that if
we ever got to the point
where we could
use all our brain,
uh, that we'd be
pure energy
and that we wouldn't
even need bodies.
Now, um, what would you
say to the possibility
that because something
happened to you,
uh, something
that never does
or isn't supposed to,
that you are, are closer
to that energy level
than any one body
has ever been?
I'd say, "So what?"
So what?
Jeremy, you know,
your life up till now
has been
that farmhouse and, uh,
and the 12 acres of earth.
You know, you've kind
of lived in books.
But I think you're
starting to find out now
that the misery
that you read about
is real.
The tragedy is, is real
in all those stories,
Jeremy.
Did you think
that it wasn't?
I mean, my God,
that deer hunt...
You think that's
the dark side of man?
Killing for pleasure?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry,
but you haven't begun
to see what we do.
We're... Jesus,
we're stumbling around
in a very dark age,
basically just trying
not to kill each other.
So it hurts me
when you say,
"So what?"
Because you are not
just different, Jeremy.
I think that you have
a mind that, uh,
that we won't
evolve to for like, uh,
thousands of years.
You're maybe
the man of the future
right here and now.
I don't know.
And I'm not
here to hurt you.
Jeremy, I want
to be a friend.
(SIGHS)
I want
to talk with you.
Well...
I mean,
did you ever have
a friend?
I don't need
a friend.
Really?
Gee, I thought
you were a genius.
You know
what I say is true.
Are you telling me
you, like, never shook
anybody's hand before?
Ah, how do you do?
Hmm?
Now we've been
properly introduced.
Want to see a trick?
(CHUCKLES)
(GASPS)
Hmm.
Wow.
They were afraid
to touch me after a while.
My grandma and grandpa,
they...
They got really scared.
What? To touch you?
Jeremy,
that's not right.
No way.
That's not right.
(KNOCKING)
Doug.
You've done a little
spring cleaning?
What the hell are you
doing here, Doug?
A couple of my deputies
told me that Harley Duncan
got rid of
every goddamn gun
in his house.
Said he dropped out
of the marksman tourney
over in Butte, too.
The one he wins
every year.
I just ain't huntin'
no more, Doug.
Is that
some kind of crime?
I just got lots
of other stuff to do.
You gonna
stop carrying one
on the job?
If you can't
pick it up and use it,
that's a liability.
I want you
to level with me.
I already know you snuck off
hunting with the boys,
which is the last damn thing
you should have done.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
(SIGHS)
And I popped this pretty doe,
just up at Little Lake.
Let me tell you
something, Doug.
You ever tell anybody
I said this,
I'm moving out of town.
That... Kid?
He lays his hand on the deer
while it's still shakin',
and then he touches me
at the same time.
Now, I can't
figure out why,
till my heart starts poundin'
and I'm shakin',
and I'm feelin' myself
hurt and scared shitless,
slippin' away
in the goddamn dark.
That's the worst thing
I ever felt.
It's like I could feel
that animal dyin'.
(SCOFFS)
It's like I was
the goddamn thing.
Aw, come on, Harley.
Doug, I swear.
Now...
I just can't do it anymore.
I can't look at something
down the barrel of a gun
without thinking about it.
I've tried it.
I'm telling you,
that thing ain't normal.
he took whatever was
in that goddamn deer,
and he put it
right into me.
(DOOR CREAKING OPEN)
DOUG:
I'm sorry, son.
Uh...
Jessie said
it may be okay
for you
to come with me.
(CAR APPROACHING)
(TURNS OFF ENGINE)
I don't know
what it is you do.
I'm not even sure
I believe you can do it.
But if you can,
I need your help.
(SIGHS)
MAXINE:
Doug Barnum,
don't you do this.
That boy
should not be
in this house!
(SHUSHING)
Go to bed, Maxine.
If you heard
the stories I've heard,
you wouldn't want him
in this house!
Go on, go on.
Go back to bed.
I'm telling you,
that boy should not be here.
Go to bed, Maxine.
(SIGHS)
She knows you're here.
DOUG:
Talk to me, woman.
Tell me what
I can do for you, Emma.
She can't go,
not until she knows
you're gonna
get through this.
She says the both of you.
You and Steven.
Steven?
What the hell
do you want me to do?
What should I do?
Throw my arms around him?
JEREMY: She wants you
to remember the snow
when Steven was younger.
And it was snowing.
You were all
playing in it.
A snowball fight.
And she lost her...
Ring.
You lost
your wedding ring.
You looked
down at your hand,
and it was gone.
We all looked.
Me and Steven,
we dug through the snow
all afternoon.
He came back
from school every day,
digging through the snow
banks, thinking he'd find it.
JEREMY:
She cried that you both
loved her so much.
The way each of you
looked so hard for it.
(SIGHS)
I remember that.
I do.
JEREMY:
The silver box.
The silver box on the table.
Oh, no, Mama.
No.
(GASPS) Oh, no.
(SOBS)
JEREMY: He found it
at the old house.
In a garden he was tilling.
He said he knew right away
what it was,
and that it was time
to come home.
She says she believes
in miracles now...
And that you should, too.
She thinks I'm an angel
come to take her home.
And to bring you and Steven
together again.
Remind you how much you're
still in each other's hearts.
(GASPS)
Everything about each other
we don't like.
You know that.
He loves you more than
any man in the whole world.
And she won't go,
she won't leave this place,
this room, or this world,
until you know
that you still have a son.
She'd like to feel
the ring on her finger.
You can hear.
(SNIFFLING)
Oh, it's all right.
(CRYING)
Angel, it's all right.
(SIGHS)
Good-bye,
Emma, sweetie.
(CAR APPROACHING)
Hurry!
What?
He's got him
up there right now!
What? What is...
He's got him up there
with your mama!
(PANTING)
Papa.
(CRYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
LINDSEY:
Why don't we just
tell them all to stop,
and they can just
take a picture
or something?
Jeremy,
are you okay?
They're wondering
if I killed her.
Don't tell me you're
seeing inside them again.
What are people like
on the inside?
Inside most people
there's a feeling
of being separate.
Separated from everything.
And?
And they're not.
They're part of absolutely
everyone and everything.
Everything?
I'm part of this tree?
Part of Zack
barking over fences?
You're telling me
that I'm part of some
fisherman in Italy
on some ocean
I've never even heard of?
Of some guy
sitting on death row.
I'm part of him,
too?
You don't believe me.
It's hard to believe that,
all of that.
Well, that's because
you have this spot
that you can't see past.
My grams and gramps
had it.
A spot where
they were taught
they were disconnected
from everything.
So that's what they'd see
if they could?
That they're connected?
And how beautiful
they really are.
And that there's
no need to hide or lie.
And that it's possible
to talk to someone
without any lies.
With no sarcasms,
no deceptions,
no exaggerations,
or any of the things
that people use
to confuse the truth.
I don't know a single person
who does that.
Hold out your hand.
Put your fingers up.
Wow.
Is that your heartbeat?
And yours.
Wow, this feels strange.
You're afraid someone
will see us holding hands.
You're really nervous
talking to me.
You don't think
you're pretty enough.
You feel alone.
You feel so alone.
Sometimes you just want
to break out of yourself.
Your father.
Your father hurt you
a long time ago.
You're so sad.
He made you so sad.
He thought you were,
you were ugly and...
And he kept
saying you, you weren't...
I'm so sorry.
Do you?
Do I what?
Do you think I'm ugly?
I don't know what
I think when I look at you.
But sometimes I think,
I think you're the most
beautiful face I've ever seen.
What?
What in the name of God
do you think you're doing?
You having a good time
with my daughter?
Wonderful.
It's a good school...
You think
this is funny?
Funny man, huh?
Dad!
You think this
is funny, huh, lover boy?
Would you stop?
Now, I asked
you a question,
and I want
an answer.
Would you please...
You think it's funny?
Dad, he wasn't
doing anything!
KELLOWAY: Answer me!
Mr. Kelloway.
Let him go.
I said, "Let him go."
Dick Kelloway, you take
your hands off him now!
I thought your boys had
rules about fraternizing.
I said now.
Keep your state trash
away from my daughter.
Christ, you know
nothing happened.
Is that
your expert opinion?
You keep
that thing on a leash,
or I'll slap a lawsuit
on that state zoo
that will shut it down
so fast it will make
your head spin.
I am so sorry.
Powder.
(SIGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(BOYS WHOOPING)
(BOY LAUGHING)
(SNEAKERS SQUEAKING)
BOYS: Yeah!
(CHATTERING CONTINUES)
(BOY WHOOPING)
BOY: Oh!
Too bad,
it's mine!
Watch your pick!
Run it! Run it!
Run it!
(BOYS LAUGHING)
(DOOR SLAMMING)
JOHN: Why don't you
take a picture, man?
Hey, Skye!
Does this look
like a genius to you?
Peeping tom faggot, maybe.
You were gettin'
an eyeful of him,
weren't you, light bulb?
You want to see what
a real man looks like?
Huh?
You think you
can take me,
freak show, go for it.
In the meantime...
I keep the hat.
When you think you're
man enough to get it back,
you take your best shot.
You think you're
man enough to get it back?
You take your best shot,
tough stuff.
What did you say?
I'd beat you to shit before
you got this old hat back.
That's what
he said to you
when he was drunk.
You were 12 years old,
and he took
your father's hat.
It's the only thing your
real father ever left behind.
Your stepdad, John.
That's what he said to you.
"You think you're
man enough to get it back?
"Then take your best shot,
tough stuff."
And then he beat you bloody
that night when you tried.
Hey, fuck you!
You had marks so dark,
you were embarrassed
to suit up for gym.
I ought to kill you
right now, man.
I ought to
slit your throat
and spit down it
while I'm doing it.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Well, what do you know.
Boogeyman's afraid
of lightning.
What's the matter,
freak show?
MITCH: Leave him alone,
Johnny! Jesus Christ!
He's scared to death!
Bullshit, Mitch!
He got a free show.
Now we get one.
(LAUGHING)
Now that is white!
Look at that.
You're as bald as a baby.
He needs some color.
Doesn't he need
some color?
You definitely need
some color, buddy.
(GASPING)
JOHN: Go get him.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Do it!
Now you got
some color.
That's enough, John.
There's not
much fight in you,
is there, freak show?
(THUNDER CLAPPING)
You really
think you can
be like us?
Is that what
you think,
freak show?
Hey.
Hey, what the hell?
(ALL LAUGHING)
Holy shit.
ZANE: Look at this. Look.
What's going on here?
(BOYS LAUGHING)
Ah! Ah! Ow! Ow!
SKYE: What's going on?
Oh!
What's going on?
What the...
(ALL SCREAMING)
Jesus!
His heart stopped beating!
You son of a bitch!
Zane!
No, no, no, no!
Don't touch him, man!
What the hell are you?
Don't touch him!
MITCH: Come on, you assholes!
Go and get
some help now!
Do it!
Hey, what the hell do you
think you're doing?
You got to be kidding me.
Come on!
Just get away
from him, man!
(ELECTRICITY JOLTING)
Stop it, man!
Come on!
He's gone!
(COUGHING)
Go get help,
you idiots! Do it!
(COUGHING CONTINUES)
Now!
(GASPING)
Come on, man!
You gotta get outta here!
Let him go, John!
Listen! Listen!
I can get you out of here!
I've done it before!
(STATIC ON RADIO)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Jeremy?
Oh.
They took everything?
Jeremy, listen to me.
We can track it all down.
We'll find every book.
Why don't you look
at me and say something?
(SIGHING)
Jeremy, listen.
From the first moment
I saw you down here,
scared in the dark,
I had this feeling that...
That you would change
everything I knew.
And maybe
this is not
the right place
for someone
as beautiful as you.
But if you come with me,
I promise you we'll
find a place that is.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Let's go.
(CAR DOOR CLOSING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(SIGHING)
Donald.
Just let him come on down,
Miss Caldwell.
We don't want
no trouble from you.
What the hell
you doin', Jess?
The right thing.
(SIGHING)
And if you don't see that,
then why don't you
just turn your head
and please, please,
just look the other way.
I don't know how
to do that, Jess.
Of course you do, Doug.
Christ's sake, just, uh,
you know, turn your head.
Just like that.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Let's do it.
He can't be out
in this weather.
Where the hell are
you gonna take him?
Let's have a talk.
Come here. Come on.
Why don't you hit
the road, Harley?
Do what?
I said get the hell
out of here.
I'm not gonna
let this happen, Doug.
You're breakin'
the goddamn law.
Lucy, this is Harley...
I said go away.
LUCY:  Go ahead, Harley.
(RADIO SHATTERING)
You're out of your goddamn,
motherfrickin' minds,
you know that?
All of ya!
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Lucy. Lucy, this is Harley.
I need some help
out here at the Reed place.
A couple of units
would be good.
Jeremy?
Powder? Hey!
DOUG: If you're gonna go,
you better go now.
Jeremy?
She didn't go someplace.
Your wife.
What?
I felt her go.
Not away.
Just out.
Everywhere.
(CHUCKLING)
"It's become
appallingly clear
"that our technology
has surpassed our humanity."
Albert Einstein.
I look at you and I,
I think that someday
our humanity might actually
surpass our technology.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(GASPS)
Hey! God!
JESSIE: Powder!
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(ALL GASP)
(ALL GASPING)
(PANTING)
(SOBBING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)