[Music]
so
um
[Music]
so
lydia kitty
[Music]
my dear mr bennett have you heard never
field park is let it last
do you not want to know who has taken it
but as you wish to tell me my dear
i doubt i have any choice in the matter
lucky kitty what have i told you about
listening at the door
never mind that this is mr moore right
from the north
and how can that possibly affect them oh
mr bennett how can you be so tiresome
you know he must marry one of them
so that is his desire and settling here
you must go and visit him at once
good heavens people
for we may not visit if you do not as
you well know mr bennett
listening at once
there's no need i already have
oh mr bennett how can you tease me so
have you no compassion for my poor
nerves oh you mistake me my dear
i have the highest respect for them
they've been my constant companions
here's trundles
is he amiable who is he handsome
he's sure to handsomely 5 000 a year it
would not matter if you had warts and
delirium who's got wars i will give my
hearty consent to his marrying whichever
the girls he chooses
so will he come to the ball tomorrow
i believe
[Music]
well then i'll do a wedding for a week
sorry
uh
[Applause]
love every man in the room does not end
the evening in love with you that i am
no judgement
one of these days lizzy someone will
catch your eye and then you'll have to
watch your tongue
[Music]
how good of you to come so which of the
painted peacocks is on mr bing well he's
on the right and on the left is his
sister
and the person with the quizzical brow
that is his good friend
mr darcy it's a miserable person
miserably may be
but poor human certainly is not tell me
ten
thousand a year and he owns her daughter
the miserable half
[Music]
so
immediately
mr bingley my eldest daughter you know
mrs bennett miss jane bennett elizabeth
and miss mary bennett it is a pleasure
i have two others but they're already
dancing i'm delighted to meet your
acquaintance
and may i introduce mr darcy of family
and derbyshire
[Applause]
very much the library at netherfield
i've heard is one of the finest in the
country
yes fills me with guilt not a very good
readings yeah
birthing out of doors i mean i can read
of course
and i'm not suggesting you can't read
out of doors of course um
i wish i read more but there always
seems to be so many other things to do
yes that's exactly what i meant
you will never ever ever believe what
we're about to tell you what tummy
quickly
i'm going to take the beard
oh look james dancing with mr bingley
[Music]
are you dance mr garcia
mr darcy i've never seen so many pretty
girls in my life
you are dancing with the only housing
girl in the room she is the most
beautiful creature i have ever beheld
but her sister elizabeth is very
agreeable fairly tolerable
i dare say not handsome enough to tempt
me
you better return to your partner and
enjoy her smiles you're wasting your
time with me
count your blessings lizzy if he likes
you you'd have to talk to him
precisely as it is i wouldn't
dance with him for all of derbyshire
then learn the miserable harm
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
your friend miss lucas is the most
amazing young woman oh yes i adore her
it is a british is not more handsome
but lizzy will never admit that she's
plain
of course it's my jane who is considered
the beauty of my heart
she was only 15 there was a gentleman so
much in love with her but i was
sure he would make her an offer however
he did write her some very pretty verses
and that put paid to it
i wonder if he first discovered the
power of poetry and driving away laughs
i thought the poetry was the food of
love of a fine doubt love it may
but if it is only a vague inclination
i'm convinced one poor sonnet will kill
its stone dead so what do you recommend
to encourage affection dancing
even if one's partner is barely
tolerable
[Music]
[Applause]
mr bingley is just what a young man
ought to be
sensible could you hand some
which is why i will end up an old maid
do you really believe you like music
jane he danced with you most of the
night and stared at you for the rest of
it
but i give you leave to like him you'd
like many as cheap at a person now
you're a great deal to act to like
people in general you know
all the world is good and agreeable in
your eyes not his friend
oh i still can't believe what he said
about you mr darcy
i'd more easily forgive his vanity had
he not wounded mine
but no matter i doubt we should never
speak again
[Music]
oh
and then he danced the third with miss
lucas we were all there now
poor thing it is a shame she's not more
handsome there's a spinster in the
making and no mistake
the fourth with him is king of little
standing and the fifth
again with jane he had any compassion
for me he would have sprained his ankle
in the first
set oh mr penny the way you carry on
anyone would think our girls look
forward to a grand inheritance
when you die mr bennett which may in
fact be very soon our girl could be left
without a roof over their head nor a
penny to their life hey mama please it's
ten in the morning
a letter addressed to miss bennett mom
from netherfield wall
praise the lord we are safe negotiations
oh happy day
it is from caroline bingley she has
invited me to dine with her
her brother will be dining out dining
out
can i take the carriage where let me see
that it's too far to walk my mom
accountable of him dining out into my
carriage for jane
certainly not go on horseback
horseback
oh she'll have to stay the night exactly
as i predicted
good grief woman your skills in the art
matchmaker positively occult
though i don't think mama you can
reasonably take credit for making it
rain
my kind friends will not hear of me
returning home until i am better but do
not be alarmed accepting a sore throat a
fever and a headache there is nothing
much wrong with me
this is ridiculous well if jane does die
it'd be a comfort to know it was in
pursuit of mr bingham
people do not die of cold
with the shame of having such a mother
i must get another one
[Music]
apparently lady barthurst is
redecorating her ballroom in the french
style
a little unpatriotic don't you think
miss elizabeth bent
good lord miss elizabeth did you walk
here
i did
i'm so sorry how is my sister she's
upstairs
thank you
my goodness did you see her hem six
inches deep in mud
she looked positively medieval i feel
such a terrible imposition they're being
so kind to me
don't worry i don't know who is more
pleased at your being here mama or mr
bingley
thank you for turning to my sister so
diligently she is in far better comfort
here than she would have been at home
it's a pleasure no i mean it's
sorry not a pleasure that she's ill of
course not it's a pleasure that she's
here
being ill
not going to be famous our pigs tackled
back
not related to the rounded pig of norris
now that bigger it's all going according
to plan
he's half in love with her already who
is blasting mr bingley
and he doesn't mind a bit that she
hasn't a penny so he has more than
enough for the two of them
oh we need them
[Applause]
you write uncommonly fast mr darcy
you're mistaken i write rather slowly
how many letters you must have occasion
to write
mr darcy letters of business too how
odious i should think them it is
fortunate then that they fall to my lot
instead of yours
do tell your sister that i longed to see
her i've already told her once by your
desire i do dote on her i was quite in
raptures at her beautiful little design
for a table
perhaps you will give me leave to defer
your raptures till i write again
present i have no room enough to do them
justice well i think it's amazing you
young ladies have the patience to be so
accomplished what do you mean charles
you all paint tables and play the piano
and
embroider cushions i never heard of a
young lady but people say she is
accomplished
the word is indeed applied too liberally
i cannot boast of knowing more than
half a dozen women in all my
acquaintances that are truly
accomplished nor
are i to be sure goodness you must
comprehend a great deal than the idea
i do absolutely she must have a thorough
knowledge of music
singing drawing dancing and the modern
languages to deserve the word
and something in her air and manner of
walking
and of course she must improve her mind
by extensive reading
i'm no longer surprised that you're
knowing only six accomplished women i
rather wander out you're knowing any
are you so severe on your own sex i
never saw such a woman
she would certainly be a fearsome thing
to behold
[Laughter]
mr elizabeth let us take a turn about
the room
it's refreshing is it not after sitting
so long in one attitude
it is a small kind of accomplishment i
suppose
will you not join us mr darcy you can
only have two
motives caroline and i would interfere
with either what can he mean
my first way of disappointing him will
be to ask him nothing about it
but do tell us mr darcy
either you are in each other's
confidence and you have
secret affairs to discuss or you are
conscious that your figures
appear to the greatest advantage by
walking
if the first i should get in your way if
the second
i can admire you much better from here
shocking how shall we punish him for
such a speech
you could always laugh at him oh no mr
darcy is not to be teased
are you too proud mr darcy and would you
consider pride a fault or a virtue that
i couldn't say
because we're doing our best to find
fault in you maybe it's that i find it
hard to forgive the follies and vices of
others
or their offences against me my good
opinion once lost is lost forever
dear i cannot tease you about that
what a shame for ideally love to laugh a
family trait i think
a mrs bennett a miss bennett a miss
bennett and
miss bennett sir oh for heaven's sake
are we to receive every bennett in the
country
what an excellent room you have sir
such expensive furnishings
oh i do hope you intend to stay here mr
bingley absolutely i
find the country very diverting don't
you agree darcy
i find it perfectly adequate even if
society is a little less varied than in
town
less varied not at all we dine with four
and twenty families
of all shapes and sizes so william lucas
for instance
is a very agreeable man and a good deal
less
self-important than some people half his
rank
mr bingley is it true that you have
promised to hold a ball here at another
field a ball
um it would be an excellent way to meet
new friends you could invite the militia
they're excellent oh do you hold the
ball kitty
when your sister is recovered you shall
name the day i think a ball is a
perfectly irrational way to gain new
acquaintance
it would be better if conversation
instead of dancing with the order of the
day
indeed much more rational but rather
less like a ball
thank you mary what a fine
imposing place it is to be sure is it
not my dears
there's no house to equal it in the
county
mr darcy miss bennett there she is
mr bingley i don't know how to thank you
you're welcome anytime you feel the
least bit poorly
thank you for your stimulating company
it has been most instructor
not at all pleasure is all mine
mr darcy mr
my idea you've ordered a good dinner
today
i have reason to expect an addition to
our family party
his name is mr collins he's the dreaded
cousin who's to inherit
indeed everything apparently even my
piano store belongs to mr collins
when he may turn us out of the house as
soon as he peases but why
because the estate passes directly to
him and not to us for the females
mr collins at your service
what a superbly featured room and what
excellent boiled potatoes
many years since i've had such an
exemplary vegetable
to which of my fair cousins should i
complement the excellence of the cooking
mr collins we are perfectly able to keep
a cook
excellent i'm very pleased the estate
can afford such a living
i'm honored to have as my patroness lady
catherine de berg
you've heard of her i presume my
small rectory abuts her estate
rosings park and she often contends to
drive by my humble dwelling
in her little fatem and ponies
does she have any family one daughter
the heiress of rosian's and very
extensive property
i've often observed lady catherine that
her daughter
seemed born to be a duchess before she
has all
the superior graces of elevated rank
these are the kind of little delicate
compliments which are always acceptable
to the ladies in which i conceive myself
particularly bound to pay how happy for
you mr collins
to possess the talent for flattering
with such delicacy
these pleasing attentions proceed from
the impulse of the moment
or are they the result of previous study
he arrives chiefly from what is passing
at the time
and though i do sometimes amuse myself
with arranging such little elegant
compliments
i always wish to give them as unstudied
an air
as possible oh believe me no one would
suspect your manners to be rehearsed
after dinner i thought i might read to
you all for an hour or two
i have with me four dices sermons which
speak very eloquently on all matters
moral
are you familiar with four dice's
sermons miss bennett
mrs bennett you do know that i've been
bestowed by the good grace of lady
catherine de berg
a parsonage of no mean size i have
become aware of the facts
well it is my vowed hope that soon i may
find a mistress for it
and i have to inform you that the eldest
miss bennett
has captured my special attention
oh mr collins unfortunately
it is incumbent upon me to hint that the
eldest
miss bennett is very soon to be engaged
engaged but miss lizzie next to her in
both age and beauty would make anyone an
excellent partner no not you agree
mr collins indeed
indeed very agreeable alternative
[Applause]
[Music]
mr collins the sort of man who makes you
despair of the entire sex
yours i believe oh mr
wickham how perfect you are i picked up
my handkerchief too did you drop yours
on purpose lizzie mister
was a left-handed and enchanted
lieutenant what are you up to lydia we
just happened to be looking for some
ribbon
white with a ball should we all look for
some ribbon together
good afternoon mr james good afternoon
i shan't even browse i can't be trusted
i have
very poor taste in ribbons only a man
truly confident himself would admit to
that
no it's true and buckles when it comes
to buckles
i'm lost dear oh dear you must be the
shame of the regiment what laughingstock
what do your superiors do with you
ignore me i'm of next to no importance
so it's easily done
lizzy lend me some money you already owe
me a fortune lady
allow me to oblige oh no mr wickham
please
i was just on my way to your house mr
bingley how do you like my ribbons for
your bowl
very beautiful she is look at her she's
blooming
oh lydia be sure to invite mr wickham
he's a credit to his profession you
can't invite people to other people's
balls
of course you must come mr wickham if
you'll excuse me ladies enjoy the day
do you plan to go to the netherfield
ball then mr whitman
perhaps how long has mr darcy been a
guest there
about a month hmm forgive me but
you acquainted with him with mr darcy
indeed i've been connected with his
family since infancy
you may well be surprised miss elizabeth
especially given our cold greeting this
afternoon
well i hope that your plans in favor of
meritan will not be affected by your
relations with the gentleman oh no it is
not for me to be driven away
if he wishes to avoid seeing me he must
go
not i i must ask mr wickham
what is the manner of your disapproval
of mr darcy
my father managed his estate
we grew up together darcy and i
his father treated me like a second son
loved me like a son
we were both with him the day he died
with his last breath his father
bequeathed me directory
in his estate he knew i had my heart set
on joining the church
but darcy ignored his wishes and gave
the living to another man
but why jealousy
his father
will he love me better and does he
couldn't stand it
how cruel so now i'm a poor foot soldier
too lowly even to be noticed
breathe in i can't anymore you're
hurting
[Music]
betsy
i still think there must have been a
misunderstanding oh jane do you never
think ill of anybody well how could mr
darcy do such a thing
i'll discover the truth from mr bingley
at the ball this evening if it is not
true let mr darcy contradict it himself
till he does i hit never to encounter
him poor unfortunate mr wickham
on the contrary wickham is twice the man
darcy is and let us hope a rather more
willing dancer
[Music]
what an immense pleasure it is to see
you again mr being me this is bennett
miss bingley charming
i'm so pleased you're here so am i
and how are you miss elizabeth
are you looking for someone no no not at
all i
was just admiring the general splendor
it is breathtaking mr bingley
good
did you see how it does
always doing what's best for her
[Music]
[Applause]
charlotte lizzy have you seen mr wickham
no
perhaps he's through here
lizzy mr wickham is not here apparently
he has been detained
detained where he must be here
there mr collins
perhaps you will do me the honor
oh i did not think you danced mr collins
i do not think it incompatible with the
office of encouragement to indulge in
such an
innocent diversion in fact several
people with her leadership included have
complimented me on my
likeness of foot
[Music]
apparently you're mr wickham has been
called on some business to town
[Music]
to be sure dancing is a little
consequence to me but it doesn't
it does have the opportunity to lavish
[Music]
to lavish upon one's path oh my informer
tells me that you want to be less
you'd be less delighted to be engaged
were it not for the
were it not for the presence of
netherfield of a certain gentleman which
is my primary object to be the gentleman
barely wants the name
it's my intention if i may be so bold
to remain close to you throughout the
[Music]
evening
may i have the next dance miss elizabeth
did i just agree to dance with mr darcy
i dare say you will find him very angry
about this he
should be most inconvenient since i want
to lose him for all eternity
[Music]
i love this dance indeed most
invigorating
does your turn to say something mr darcy
i talked about the dance now you want to
remark on the size of the room or the
number of couples
i'm perfectly happy to oblige please
advise me of what you would like most to
hear
that reply will do for present
perhaps by and by i may observe that
private rules are much pleasanter than
public ones
and now we may remain silent
you talk as a ruler while dancing
no no i prefer to be unsociable in
taciturn
makes it all so much more enjoyable
don't you think
tell me do you and your sisters very
often walk to marathon
yes we often walk to marathon
it's a great opportunity to meet new
people
but when you met us we just had the
pleasure of forming a new acquaintance
mr wickham is blessed with such happy
manners he is sure of making friends
whether he's capable of retaining them
as less said he's been so unfortunate
to lose your friendship
and i dare say that is an irreversible
event it is
why do you ask such a question to make
out your character mr dawson what have
you discovered
very little i hear such different
accounts of you as puzzle me exceedingly
i hope to afford you more clarity in the
[Music]
future
[Applause]
is that mr darcy apparently i believe so
i must make myself known to him
immediately he's the nephew of my
esteemed patronus lately catherine
mr collins you will consider it an
impertinence
mr darcy mr darcy
mr darcy
good evening what interesting relatives
do you have miss elizabeth
you've enlightened us long enough and
the other young ladies
since it was a child and then she died
they have a beautiful grave
because caroline's a much better rider
than i of course
we fully expect a most advantageous
marriage
[Music]
[Applause]
clearly my family are having a
competition to see who can expose
themselves to the most ridicule
well at least bingley has not noticed no
i think he likes her very much but does
she like him
there are a few of us who are secure
enough to be really in love with that
proper encouragement
mainly likes her enormously but might
not do more if she does not help him on
but she's just shy and modest
if you cannot perceive her regard he is
a fool we are all fools in love
he does not know her character as we do
she should move fast to snap him up
there is plenty of time
for us to get to know them after matches
i can't help the feeling that at any
point this evening someone's going to
produce a piglet
[Music]
forgive me
i've been back
[Music]
[Applause]
such a good time in my life
charles you cannot be serious
[Music]
we'll be having a wedding here at
netherfield in less than three months if
you ask me mr bennett
mr bennett
[Music]
[Applause]
mary please
[Music]
thank you mr hill
hmm
mrs bennett i was hoping if it would not
trouble you that i might solicit a
private audience with miss elizabeth in
the course of the morning
oh yes certainly lizzie will be very
happy indeed everyone
out mr collins would like a private
audience with your sister wait please i
beg you mr collins can have nothing to
say to me that anybody need not hear no
not since lizzy i desire you will stay
where you are
everyone else to the drawing room mr
bennett
now
jane jane
[Music]
hmm
dear mr elizabeth i'm sure my attentions
have been too marked to be mistaken
almost as soon as i entered the house i
singled you out as the companion of my
future life
but before i am run away with my
feelings perhaps
i may state my reasons for marrying
firstly that it is the duty of a
clergyman to set the example of
matrimony in his parish
secondly that i am convinced it will add
greatly to my happiness
and thirdly that it is at the urging of
my esteemed patroness lady catherine
that i select a wife my object in coming
to longborn was to choose
such a one from among mr bennett's
daughters for
i am to inherit the estate and
such an alliance will surely
suit everyone
and now nothing remains but for me to
assure you in the most animated language
of the violence of my affection mr
collins
and that no reproach on the subject of
fortune will cross my lips once we're
married
you are too hasty sir you forget that i
have given no answer i must add that
lady catherine will thoroughly approve
when i speak to her of your modesty
economy and other amiable qualities
sir i am honored by your proposal but i
regret that i must decline it
i know ladies don't seek to seem
too easy mr collins i am perfectly
serious
you could not make me happy and i'm
convinced i'm the last woman in the
world who could make you happy
i've let myself constantly your refusal
is merely a natural delicacy
besides you should take into account
that despite your manifold attractions
it's by no means certain that another
offer of marriage may ever be made to
you
mr collins so i must conclude that you
simply seek to increase my love by
suspense
sir according to the usual practice of
elegant females sir
i am not the sort of female to torment a
respectable man
please understand me i cannot accept you
a strong foolish child
don't worry mr collins we'll have this
before he comes out with immediately
you must come and make lizzie marry mr
collins
mr collins has proposed to lizzy but she
vow she will not have him
and now the danger is mr collins may not
have lizzie
what am i to do well come and talk to
her
now
[Music]
[Applause]
tell her you insist upon them marrying
papa please
you will have this house i can't marry
you save your sister's from destitute i
can't
go back now and say you've changed your
mind no
think of your family you cannot make me
mr bennett say something
so your mother insists
on you marrying mr collins yes i shall
never see her again
from this day onward you must be a
stranger to one of your parents we'll
maintain you when your father is dead
your mother will never see you again if
you do not marry mr collins
and i will never see you again if you do
mr bennett
ungrateful child i shall never speak to
you again
not that i take that pleasure in talking
people who suffer as i do from nervous
complaints because my pleasure is
talking to anybody
jane
what's the matter
[Music]
i don't understand what we're taking
from netherfield
why would he not know when he was to
return read it i don't mind
mr darcy is impatient to see his sister
and we are scarce with his ego to meet
her again
i really do not think georgiana darcy
has her equal for beauty elegance and
accomplishment
so much so i must hope to hear after
call her my sister is that not clear
enough caroline sees that her brother is
in love with you
and has taken him off to persuade him
otherwise but i know her to be incapable
of willfully deceiving anyone
it's far more likely that he does not
love me and never he loves you jane do
not give up
go to our aunt and uncles in london let
it be known you are there and i am sure
he will come to you
give my love to my sister and try not to
be a burden dear
aung a girl likes to be crossed in love
now and then
it gives her something to think of and a
sort of
distinction amongst her companion i'm
sure that will cheer her up for her well
it's your turn now lizzy
you've turned down collins you're free
to go off and be
sheltered yourself what about mr wickham
and he's a pleasant fellow and he do the
job credibly
father and you have an affectionate
mother
who would make the most of it
charlotte my dear izzy i've come here to
tell you the news
mr collins and i are engaged
engaged yes
to be married yes of course lizzy what
other kind of engaged is there
oh for heaven's sake lizzie don't look
at me like that
there is no earthly reason why i
shouldn't be as happy with him as any
other
but he's ridiculous oh hush not all of
us can afford to be romantic
i've been offered a comfortable home and
protection
there's a lot to be thankful for i'm 27
years old
i've no money and no prospects i'm
already a burden to my parents
and i'm frightened so don't judge me
lizzy
don't you dare judge me
[Music]
so
dear charlotte thank you for your letter
i'm so glad the house furniture and
roads are all to your taste and that
lady catherine's behavior is friendly
and obliging
what with your departure jane's to
london and the militia to the north with
the colourful mr wickham
i must confess the view from where i sit
has been rather gray
as for the favor you ask it is no favor
at all
i would be happy to visit you at your
earliest convenience
[Music]
[Laughter]
my wife encourages me to spend as much
time in the garden as possible for the
sake of my health
my dear i think our guest is tired after
her journey i found many improvements of
course i intend to throw out a bow and
plant a lime walk oh yes i flatter
myself that
any young lady would be happy to be the
mistress of such a house
we shan't be disturbed here this parlor
is for my own
particular use
oh lizzy it's such a pleasure to run my
own home
charlotte come here what's happened
has the pig escaped again oh it's lady
catherine
come and see lizzy great news
great news we've received an invitation
to visit roses this evening from lady
catherine de berg how wonderful
do not make yourself uneasy my dear
cousin about your apparel just put on
whatever you've brought that's best
lady catherine's never been a verse to
the truly humble
one of the most extraordinary sites in
all of europe is it not
that blazing alone costs upwards of
twenty thousand pounds
come along go along
[Music]
mr berg
uh
so you are elizabeth burnett i am your
lady shep
hmm this is my daughter
it's very kind of uterus
[Music]
mr darcy
what are you doing here
mr darcy i had no idea we had the honor
miss elizabeth i'm a guest here
you know my nephew yes mom i
had the pleasure of meeting your nephew
and hertfordshire
colonel fitzwilliam how'd you do
mr collins you can't sit next to your
wife
move over there
i trust your family is in good health
miss elizabeth
my eldest sister is currently in london
perhaps you happen to see her there
i haven't been fortunate enough play the
piano forte miss bennett
a little mom and very poorly oh
you draw no not at all
your sisters do they draw not one
it's very strange i suppose you had no
opportunity
your mother should have taken you to
town every spring for the benefit of the
masters i'm sure my mother wouldn't have
minded but my father hates town
has your governance left you we never
had a governess
no governors five daughters brought up
at home without a governess i never
heard such a thing
your mother must have been quite a slave
to your education not at all lady
catherine
your younger sisters are they out in
society yes ma'am all
or would all five out at once oh that's
very odd
and you only the second the younger ones
out before the elders are married
your youngest sisters must be very young
yes my youngest is not 16.
but i think it would be very hard on
younger sisters not to have their share
of amusement because the elder is still
unmarried
it would hardly encourage sisterly
affection
upon my word you give your opinion very
decidedly for so younger person
pray what is your age with three younger
sisters grown up your leadership can
hardly expect me to own to it
come miss bennett and play for us
no i beg you for music is my delight
in fact there are few people in england
who have more true enjoyment of music
than myself
or better natural taste if i had ever
learned
i should have been a great proficient
so dan if her health would have allowed
her
lady catherine i'm not afflicted with
false modesty when i say i play poorly
come come lizzy
her leadership demands it
how does georgiana get along darcy
she plays very well i hope she practices
no excellence can be acquired without
constant practice i've told mrs collins
this
though you have no instrument of your
own you're very welcome to come to
rosings
and play on the piano forte in the
housekeeper's room thank you
you'll be in nobody's way in that part
of the house
you mean to frighten me mr darcy by
coming in all your state to hear me
but i won't be alarmed even if your
sister does play so well i am well
enough acquainted with you miss
elizabeth to know that i cannot allow
you even should i wish it
what was my friend like in hertfordshire
[Music]
you really care to know prepare yourself
for something very dreadful
the first time i saw him at the assembly
he danced with nobody at all
even though gentlemen were scarce and
there was more than one young lady
sitting down without a partner i knew
nobody be on my own party oh and nobody
can be introduced in a ballroom but
william
i need you
i do not have the talent of conversing
easily with people i have never met
before
perhaps you should take your aunt's
advice and practice
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah jane
mr darcy
please do be seated
i'm afraid mr and mrs collins have gone
on business to the village
this is a charming house i believe my
aunt did a great deal to it when mr
collins first arrived
i believe so
she could not have bestowed her kindness
on a more grateful subject
so i call for some tea no thank you
good day thanks elizabeth it's been a
pleasure
what enough have you done to promise to
darcy
i have no idea
every mind must have some counsellor to
whom it may
apply for consolation in distress there
are many conveniences which others can
supply and which we cannot procure for
ourselves
i have now principally in view those
objects which are only to be obtained
through intercourse
forgive me through the intercourse of
friendship or civility
on such occasions the proud man steps
forth to meet you not with the
cordiality of affection
but with the suspicion the one who
reckon noiters an enemy
who is ready
everyone appears to be at his disposal
nobody doesn't marry and secure a
lasting convenience of that kind
which makes you want to be a lucky woman
cry really
darcy
he recently came to the rescue of one of
his friends just in time what happened
he saved the man from an improved
marriage
there were apparently strong objections
to the lady
what kind of objections i lack a fortune
i think it was a family that was
considered unsuitable
so he separated them i believe so i know
nothing else
[Music]
[Applause]
mr elizabeth i have struggled in vain
and i can bear it no longer
these past months have been a torment i
came to roses with a single object of
seeing you i had to see
i thought against my better judgment my
family's expectation the inferiority of
your birth my rank and circumstance all
these things that i'm willing to put
them aside and ask you
to end my agony i don't understand i
love you
most hardly
please do me the honor of accepting my
hand
sir i i appreciate the struggle you have
been through and i am very sorry to have
caused you pain
believe me it was unconsciously done
is this your time yes sir are you
are you laughing at me no are you
rejecting me i'm sure that the feelings
which is you've told me have hindered
your regard will help you in overcoming
it
might i ask why would so little endeavor
civility i must repulse and i might as
well inquire why would so evident in
design of insulting me you chose to tell
me that you like me against your better
judgment me
if i was uncivil then that is some
excuse but i have other reasons you know
i have
what reasons just think of anything
might tempt me to accept a man who was
ruined perhaps forever the happiness of
her most beloved sister
you deny it mr darcy that you separated
a young couple who loved each other
exposing your friend to the center of
the world for caprice and my sister
to its derision for disappointed hopes
and involving them both in misery of the
acute his car
i do not deny it how could you do it
because i believed your sister
indifferently
indifferent i watched them most
carefully and realized his attachment
was deeper than her that's because she's
shy
bingley too is modest and was persuaded
she didn't feel strongly because you
suggested it i did it for his own
my sister hardy shows her true feelings
to me
i suppose you suspect his his fortune
had something
i wouldn't be your sister the dishonor
though it was suggested what was
it was made perfectly clear that in
advantageous marriage did my sister give
that impression no
no no there was however i have to admit
the matter of your family i want of
connection
mr bingley didn't seem to because
himself about that how sir it was the
lack of propriety showed by your mother
your three younger sisters even on the
case of your father
[Music]
you and your sister i must exclude this
and what about mr wickham
mr wickham what excuse can you give you
your behavior towards him you take an
eager interest in that gentleman he told
me of his misfortune
oh your sister's fortunes have been very
great indeed you ruin his chances and
let you treat him with sarcasm
so this is your opinion of me thank you
for explaining so fully
perhaps these offenses might have been
overlooked had not your pride been hurt
by my honesty and admitting scruples
about our relationship
could you expect me to rejoice in the
inferiority of your circumstances
and those are the words of a gentleman
from the first moment i met you your
arrogance and conceit your selfish
disdain for the feelings of others
made me realize that you were the last
man in the world i could ever be
prevailed upon to marry
forgive me madam for taking up so much
of your time
[Music]
so
uh
[Music]
so
i came to leave you this
i shall not renew the sentiments which
was so disgusting to you
but if i may i will address the two
offences you've laid against me
my father loved mr wickham as a son
in consequence he left him a generous
living but upon my father's death mr
wickham announced he had no intention of
taking orders
he demanded the value of the living
which he was given and which he gambled
away within weeks
he then wrote demanding more money which
i refused
after which he served all acquaintance
he came back to see us last summer at
which point he declared passionate love
for my sister whom he tried to persuade
to elope with him
she is to inherit 30 000 pounds
when it was made clear he would never
receive a penny of that inheritance he
disappeared
i will not attempt to convey the depth
of georgiana's despair
she was 15 years old
as to the other matter that of your
sister and mr bingley
though the motives which governed me
mater you appear insufficient
they were in the service of a friend
is he
are you all right i hardly know
listen how fortunate you have arrived
your aunt and uncle are here to deliver
jane from london
how is jane i was in the drawing room
i'm quite over him lizzy if you passed
me in the street i'd hardly notice
london is so diverting it's true
there's so much to entertain
what news is from kent
nothing
at least not much to entertain
oh kitty stop making such a fuss
i probably can't afford it some better
company
just
has been invited to go to brighton with
the forces you could see bathing would
set me up very nicely sit down with the
officers every night
please papar don't let her go lily will
never be easy until she's exposed
herself in some public place or other
and we can never expect her to do it
with so little inconveniences under the
present circumstances
if you dear father do not take the
trouble to check her she will be fixed
forever as the silliest and most
determined flirt who ever made her
family ridiculous
and kitty will follow as she always does
lizzy we shall have
no peace until she goes
is that really all you care about
what kind of fosters a sense of a man
you will keep her out of any real
mischief
and she's far too poor to be an object
to pray to anyone
father it's dangerous i am certain
the officers will find women better if
there were
let us hope in fact that her stay in
brighton
would teach her her own insignificance
generation hard to grow any worse if she
does
you'd be obliged to lock her up for the
rest of her life
lizzie dear you'd be welcome to
accompany us
the peak district is not brighton and
officers are very thin on the ground
which may influence your decision
come to the peak district with us lizzie
and get some fresh air
the glories of nature what are men
compared to rocks and mountains
believe me men are either eaten up with
arrogance or stupidity
if they are amiable they're so easily
led they have no minds of their own
whatsoever
oh take care my love that save us
strongly of bitterness
i saw mr darcy when i was at rosie's
why did you not tell me
did he mention mr bingley
no
no he did not
[Music]
oh one of men compared to rocks and
mountains
or carriages that work
where exactly are we i think we're quite
close to pemberley
mr darcy's home that's the fellow
very well stocked lake have a hankering
to see it oh no let's not
what he's so i'd rather not he's so
he's so so what you're so rich
my heavens listen to snob you are
objecting to poor mr darcy because of
his wealth
the poor man can't help it he won't be
there anyway
these great men are never at home
so
oh
[Music]
keep up
is
[Music]
just
this is he mr darcy
a handsome face
lizzy is it a true likeness
does the young lady know mr darcy
only a little do you not think him a
handsome man miss
yes
yes i dare say he is
is she at home
[Music]
do
um
mr elizabeth
i thought you're in london no
no i'm not no
i can go some business with my students
uncle and are you having a
pleasant trip very pleasant
tomorrow we go to my clock tomorrow
are you staying at lambton yes at the
rosen crown
yes
i'm so sorry to intrude they said that
the house was open for visitors i had
no idea
may i see you back to the village
i'm very fond of walking yes
yes i know
bye mr darcy
this way song
we've just met mr darcy you didn't tell
us that you'd seen him
he's asked us to dine with him tomorrow
he was very civil
was he not very similar not at all how
you'd painted him
to dine with her there's something
pleasant about his mouth when he speaks
you don't mind delaying our journey
another day do you he particularly wants
you to meet his sister
miss elizabeth
my sister is georgiana my brother has
told me so much about you
i feel it for your friends already oh
thank you
what a beautiful piano forte my brother
gave it to me
he shouldn't have yes i should oh very
well then
easily persuaded is she not your
unfortunate brother once had to put up
with my playing for a whole evening
but he says you play so well then he has
purged himself most profoundly
no i said played quite well oh quite
well is not very well
i'm satisfied
mr gardner are you fond of fishing oh
very much so
can i persuade you to accompany me to
the lake this afternoon it's very well
stocked and its occupants left in peace
for far too long i would be delighted
do you play duets miss elizabeth only
when forced
brother you must force her
splendid fishing good company what a
capital fellow
thank you so much
jane
it's the most dreadful news
lydia has run away
with mr wickham they have gone from
right into lord knows where she has no
money no
no connections i feel she's lost forever
this is my fault if only i'd exposed
wiccan when i should no
no this is my fault
i might have prevented all this mini by
being open with my sisters
has anything been done to recover her
my father has gone to london but i know
very well that nothing can be done
we have not the smallest hope would i
could help you
so i think it is too late
this is grave indeed i will leave you
goodbye
i'm afraid we must go at once i will
join mr bennett and find lydia before
she ruins the family forever
[Music]
now why did the foresters let her out of
their sight
i always said they were unfit to take
charge of her
and now she's ruined you're all ruined
i will take you now with a fallen sister
poor mr bennett will now have to fight
the perfidious wiggum
and then be killed he hasn't found him
yet and then mr collins will
turn us out before he is cold in his
grave do not be so alarmed mama
our uncle has gone to london and is
helping in search lydia must know what
this must be doing to my nurse
there's such fluttering spasms all over
me
my baby lydia my baby
how could she do such a thing to her
you can't do that don't baby kitty
give it to me no it's dressed for par
it's an uncle's writing
let me catch my breath it's an uncle's
writing
you just found them they're married wait
i can't think i'll just give it to me
they've been married they will be if
your father will settle a hundred pounds
a year now that is wicca's condition 100
you will agree to this father son agree
god knows how much your uncle must have
laid on that
wretched man what do you mean father no
man it is census but marry lydia under
so slight of temptation is a hundred a
year
your uncle must have been very generous
you can get a large sun who becomes a
fool if he accepts less than ten
thousand ten thousand
heaven
ring the bell kitty i must put on my
things and tell lady lucas
oh to see her face and tell the servants
they will have a bowl of punch
we should thank our uncle mama and so we
should help he's far richer than us and
has no children
a daughter mary is that really all you
think about
when you have five daughters lizzy tell
me what else will occupy your thoughts
and then perhaps you will understand
you don't know what he's like
we passed sarah's sims in her carriage
so i took off my glove and let my hand
just rest so she might see the ring
and i bowed and smiled like
i'm sure
that is the place to get husbands i hope
you have half my good luck
lydia i want to hear every little detail
did he appear
[Music]
we travel there next week can i come and
stay with you
that is out of the question
well monday morning came and i was in
such a fast i don't want to hear
there's my old preaching and talking
away as if she was reading us
um she was horrid unpleasant can't you
understand why
hmm but i didn't hear a word because i
was thinking of my dear wicker
i want to know whether he'd been married
in his blue coat the northern england i
believe there's
some spectacular scene away from the
church or business and i thought
who is to be our best man if he doesn't
come back lucky he did come back would
have had to ask mr darcy but i don't
think he'd like mr darcy
mr darcy was at your wedding he was the
one that discovered us
he paid for the wedding wickham's
commission
everything but don't tell anyone he told
me not to tell
him mr darcy stop it
mr darcy's almighty is he
[Music]
write to me often my dear married women
never have much time for writing
no i dare say you won't when i married
your father there didn't seem to be
enough hours in the day
my sisters may write to me but they'll
have nothing else to do
nothing so bad is parting with one's
children
one seems so full
[Music]
bye
did you hear the news mr bingley is
returning to netherfield
mrs nichols is ordering a hunch of pork
she expects him tomorrow
tomorrow not
i care about him mr being leaves nothing
to us i'm sure i never want to see him
again now
we shall mention a word about it is it
quite certain he's coming
yes madam i believe he's alone his
sister remains in town
why he thinks we should be interested i
have no idea come along girls
let's go home at once mary tell
mr bennett the appearance of the man i
won't eat there show his face
it's all right lizzy i'm i'm just glad
he comes alone because then we shall see
less of him
not that i'm afraid of myself but i
dread other people's remarks oh i'm
sorry
oh
[Music]
oh my goodness everybody behave
naturally
and whatever you do do not appear
overbearing look there's someone with
them huh
mama mr what's his name the pompous one
from before mr darcy
the very insolence of it what's he think
of coming here
mary put that away at once find some
useful employment
oh my lord i should have a seizure i'm
sure
mary sit down at once mary
mr darcy and mr benjamin
very glad we are to see you mr bingley
there's been a great many changes since
you went away
miss lucas is married and settled
and one of my own daughters too you will
have seen it in the papers though
it was not put in as it ought to have
been very short
nothing about her family yes yes i did
hear of it i i offer my congratulations
but it is very hard to have my lydia
taken away from me
mr wickham has been transferred to
newcastle wherever that is
do you hope to stay long in the country
mr bingley just a few weeks
for the shooting oh when you've killed
all your own birds mr bingley i beg you
will come here and shoot as many as you
please
thank you mr bennett we'll be vastly
happy to oblige you
and we'll save all the best of the
copies for you excellent
are you well mr darcy quite well
thank you i hope that the weather stays
fine for your sport
i return to town tomorrow so soon
my jane looks well does she not
does indeed
well we must be going i think
darcy it's been very pleasant to see you
all again
miss elizabeth it's bennett you must
come again
for when you were in town last winter
you promised to have a family dinner
with us
i've not forgot you see at least three
courses
excuse me
most extraordinary
[Music]
we're gonna walk in and she was gonna
say sit down
so i feel
[Music]
oh it's a disaster isn't it um
um miss bennett
mr bigly it's good
i'm glad that's over at least now we can
meet us in different acquaintances
oh yes no you cannot think me so weak as
to be in danger now
i think you are in great danger of
making him as much in love with you as
ever
i'm sorry though that he came with mr
darcy
let's say that why ever not
i've been so blind
what do you mean look it's him he's back
he's come again
i know this is all very untoward but i
would like to request the privilege of
speaking to miss bennett
alone
everybody to the kitchen immediately
i accept you jane dear of course
oh mr bingley it is so good to see you
again
so soon
first i'm just i'm just telling you i've
been the most unmitigated and
comprehensive ass
quiet
yes a thousand times
thank the yes for that i thought it
would never happen
[Music]
so
i am confident they will do well
together
their tempers are much alike
they will be cheated assiduously by
their servants
and be so generous with the rest
who will always exceed their income
their income here's 5 000 a year
[Music]
i knew she could not be so beautiful for
nothing
hmm
[Music]
she only can address herself effectually
to the heart and the feelings of others
whose mind glows with the warmth of
sensibility
and whose arguments result from
conviction she must feel the influence
of those passions
and emotions which she wishes to inspire
an assumed character
i love you
can you die of happiness
do you know he was totally ignorant of
my being in town in the spring
how did he account for he thought me
different
unfathomable loadout poisoned by his
pernicious sister
bravo i think that's the most
unforgiving speech you've ever made
oh lizzy if i could but see you so happy
if there was such another man for you
perhaps mr collins has a cousin
catherine
the rest of your offspring i presume
all but one the youngest has been lately
married your ladyship
and my eldest was proposed to only this
afternoon
you have a very small garden madam could
i offer you a cup of tea perhaps
absolutely not i need to speak to miss
elizabeth bennett alone
as a matter of urgency
you can be at no loss miss bennett to
understand why i am here
indeed you are mistaken i cannot account
for this honor at all miss bennett i
warn you
i am not to be trifled with a report of
the most alarming nature has reached me
that you intend to be united with my
nephew
mr darcy i know this to be a scandalous
falsehood
though not wishing to injure him by
supposing it possible i instantly set
off to make my sentiments known
if you believed it to be impossible i
wonder you took the trouble of coming so
far to hear it contradicted miss bennett
your coming will be rather a
confirmation
surely if indeed such a reporting if
do you then pretend to be ignorant of it
has it not been industriously circulated
by yourself i have never heard of it
and can you declare there is no
foundation for it do not pretend to
possess equal frankness with your
ladyship
you may ask a question which i may
choose not to answer this is not to be
born
has my nephew made you an offer of
marriage your ladyship has declared it
to be impossible let me be understood
mr darcy is engaged to my daughter now
what have you to say
only this if that is the case you can
have no reason to suppose he would make
an offer to me you
selfish girl this union has been planned
since their infancy
do you think it can be prevented by a
young woman of inferior birth
whose own sister's elopement resulted in
a scandalously
patched up marriage only achieved at the
expense of your uncle
heaven and earth are the shades of
pemberley to be thus polluted
now tell me once and for all are you
engaged to
i him not
and will you promise never to enter into
such an engagement i will not and i
certainly never shall
you have insulted me in every possible
way and can now have nothing further to
say
just ask you to leave immediately
good night
i have never been thus treated in my
entire life
lizzie what on earth is going on it's
understanding
is it one thing you're lying
uh
so
[Music]
uh
so
[Music]
[Applause]
i couldn't sleep my aunt
yes she was here how can i ever make
amends for such baby
after what you have done for lydia and i
suspect for jane also it is i who should
be making amends
you must know surely you must know it
was all for you
you are too generous to travel with me
i believe you spoke with my aunt last
night and has taught me to hope
as i'd scarcely allowed myself before
if your feelings are still what they
were last april tell me so at once
my affections and wishes have not
changed
but one word from you will silence me
forever
if however your feelings have changed
i would have to tell you you have
bewitched me body and soul
and i love and love i love you
i never wish to be parted from you from
this day
well then
your hands are cold
so
[Music]
shut the door please elizabeth
they say are you out of your senses
i thought you hated the man no papa
rich to be sure if he would have more
fine carriages than jane
but would that make you happy have you
no other objection than your belief in
my indifference
we all know him to be a proud unpleasant
sort of fellow
but this would be nothing if you really
liked him i do like him
i love him
he's not proud i was wrong i was
entirely wrong about him
you don't know how if i told you what he
was really like
what he's done what has he done
she doesn't like him i thought she
didn't like him so did i say did we all
i must have been wrong will be the first
time will it
good lord
i must pay him back no
you mustn't tell anyone he wouldn't want
it
we misjudged him for party more than
anyone in
in every way not just in this matter
i've been nonsensical
he's been a fool about about jane
about so many other things but
then so have i
he and i are
he and i are so similar
we've been so stubborn
you really do love him don't you
very much
i cannot believe that anyone can deserve
you
but it seems i am overruled
so i heartily
give my consent
i could not have parted with mind is he
to anyone that's worthy
if any young men come from area kitty
for heaven's sake send them in
i'm quite at my leisure
[Music]
how are you this evening my dear very
well
only i wish you would not call me my
dear why because it's what my father
always calls my mother when he's crossed
about something what endearments am i
allowed
well let me think lizzy for every day
my pearl for sundays and
goddess divine but only on very special
occasions
and what shall i call you when i'm cross
mrs darcy no
no you may only call me mrs darcy
when you are completely and perfectly
and
incandescently happy
but how are you this evening mrs darcy
[Music]
this is
this is darcy
[Music]
you