It is the headquarters of
the world's most famous spy organisation,
the legendary home of
Agent 007... James Bond.
This is MI6, otherwise
known as Her Majesty's Secret Service.
Now, with unprecedented access to the major players
in British espionage...
It's exciting and the
adrenaline is pumping round.
...we reveal the truth behind
the covert operations,
the secret missions
and the double-agents.
We expose the dangerous
secret world
of real-life spies.
There are far more spies
in London now
than there were during the Cold War.
London, a cosmopolitan metropolis
of 8 million inhabitants.
And home to the world-renowned
British Secret Service.
For decades,
cunning games of espionage
have been played out
on the city's streets.
Assassinations...
treason... and betrayal.
London has always been a
crossroads, a global city.
You've always had lots of
exiles and dissidents here.
That means it's a real
meeting place for spies...
British spies, spies from
other countries trying to recruit people,
trying to run operations.
I think it's meant that London is
one of the great spy cities in the world.
Entering the high-stakes
world of spying,
we learn what's really
going on in the shadows.
From the highest echelons
of MI6...
The best form of defence
against plots and attacks
is to know about it in advance.
It was all about
collecting intelligence
and recruiting
and running sources.
...to field operatives who
risked their lives...
At my peak, I was operating
under about 14 or 15 different aliases.
...unsung heroes of Britain's
most secret code-breaking station...
We broke a message
that said 'Today's the day minus three.'
...the KGB double agents
who fought the Cold War.
The Secret Intelligence
Service exists to defend
and protect the security
and interests of the United Kingdom.
It's known by its
World War One designation
as Military Intelligence Section 6...
or MI6.
This green and cream building
behind me is the headquarters of MI6.
That's the Secret
Intelligence Service,
Britain's foreign
intelligence service,
the equivalent of the CIA.
Within intelligence circles,
the building is known as VX,
after its location at Vauxhall Cross on the banks
of the River Thames.
It became even more identifiable to millions of
cinema fans around the globe
when it was famously blown up
in the Bond movie, Skyfall.
It is probably the most
famous secret service building in the world
thanks to the James Bond films.
The fictional world of 007
may be glamorous and entertaining
but the reality of life in
MI6 is far more serious.
Someone who knows this dark
world better than most is Sir John Scarlett.
For 38 years, he was one
of MI6's top operatives,
rising to Chief of the Service in 2004.
MI6 is essentially an
information gathering agency.
It collects intelligence.
That is its job and it is
very good at it.
During his five-year tenure
as Chief,
Sir John authorised many dangerous and daring
intelligence operations.
There's not much I can share but I think,
like many of my colleagues,
over a long period of time,
I've quite often been
in situations where it's exciting,
and the best way of describing it is,
the adrenaline, you know,
is pumping round.
To preserve secrecy and security,
MI6 never acknowledges
its missions or spies.
But one spy has outed himself
and talked...
former undercover MI6 officer
and now author, Matthew Dunn.
The majority of what I did
was recruiting foreign spies,
typically nationals who
were placed in positions
that gave them access to secrets
and targeting senior echelons
within rogue states.
That was the core of my work.
In MI6-speak, those passing
on secret intelligence are called agents,
while men such as Dunn,
who run the agents, are called officers.
Both are commonly
referred to as spies.
Dunn typically met his agents
in the bars and rooms of London's top hotels,
glossy surroundings
that are far more dangerous
than they seem to the average tourist.
The biggest concern a case officer has when attending a
covert meeting with an agent
is fear that he is being
followed by a hostile surveillance team.
In order to address that,
the officer will walk a anti-surveillance route.
Officers will establish
what's called a theme,
and in this case, I'm walking
down Jermyn Street
and my theme is shirt shopping.
If a team's following me,
they will think I am shirt shopping.
If an officer spots the same
face more than once on his anti-surveillance route,
this is called a double-sighting.
This person may well be
enemy surveillance,
in which case, the officer
has to abort the meeting.
I've often felt when
operating that there was a threat to me,
that I could be snatched or
the person you're with could be snatched.
And that threat
could include death.
Today MI6 has over 3,200
officers operating across the globe.
They run covert operations,
infiltrate terrorist organisations
and foil international plots.
They need to extract
information from the most sensitive of sources.
One of the core strengths of MI6
is our agent-running skills
and that is world renowned.
Other agencies...
the CIA, European agencies,
do recognise that our agent-handling abilities
are second to none.
MI6 will use any tool in its arsenal,
including blackmail and bribery,
to persuade foreign agents
to betray their country
and hand over top secret
information.
This is what happens
in this sort of business.
That was a great skill.
You have to talent spot
people in the first place,
you have to spot them,
see their potential
and then bring them under control.
These skills have been
perfected over the agency's 100-year history.
Britain's Secret Service was
founded on 1st October, 1909,
to gather intelligence about the growing
military threat from imperial Germany.
Tensions were rising in Europe
and people feared German spies
were infiltrating Britain.
The Daily Mail told its readers
to refuse to be served
by German waiters:
'If your waiter says he's Swiss,
demand to see his passport.'
MI6's first headquarters were
near the corridors of power in Whitehall.
But few in government knew
the agency even existed.
Where we are now is where
the earliest headquarters of MI6 is,
and that's up in that tower.
2 Whitehall Court
was the foreign section
of the Secret Service Bureau.
It's where Mansfield Cumming
set up his early headquarters
and throughout the First World War,
that's where what
we now call MI6 was based.
Mansfield Cumming was the
first Chief of the Service.
He was a naval officer who
would go on spying missions
wearing rather bizarre disguises.
His office was a laboratory
of strange gadgets and devices.
He was very innovative,
he was one of the first
people in Britain to take his pilot's license.
He had a special license
plate for his Rolls Royce
which allowed him to drive
up and down London streets
at any speed he wanted to
without being stopped by the police.
He was a real character.
His staffing and interview
methods were uniquely gruesome.
He had a wooden leg.
And when he was recruiting
new officers,
he would frequently
take his pen knife
and stab it into this wooden leg.
he was just the right man
to work for Britain's Secret Service.
Cumming knew that good agents
were the most important tool
in the spying game.
From the very beginning, he
understood it was all about
collecting intelligence
and recruiting and running sources.
From the very beginning,
that's what he did.
It was just in the bloodstream.
Cumming disguised his
organisation's true activity
by pretending it was an
import/export business called Rasen, Falcon & Co.
To this day,
MI6 uses fake companies
as a cover for
its clandestine operations abroad.
Cumming also created other traditions
still maintained
by his MI6 successors.
He brought with him the naval
tradition of the captain
writing his log in green ink.
Even now, the Chief of MI6
still writes in green ink,
because Cumming did.
His most famous legacy,
however, is his signature.
Cumming was given
the title of C as a cover,
it was simply the first letter of his name.
It's obviously where M
in James Bond comes from
and even now, the Chief of
MI6, as he's now called,
signs his letter with a C.
Signing yourself as C is a
reminder that we have a continuing tradition.
Everything leads to
everything else.
There's been no break.
That's what's exceptional.
In 1918, Cumming recruited
his most brilliant agent,
the infamous Sidney Reilly,
Ace of Spies.
Reilly, who could speak
seven languages fluently,
was utterly fearless,
a hardened gambler and
a famous seducer of women.
In some ways he was the
perfect spy because he was a bit of conman.
And he was able to persuade
people to do things,
just like any conman, that
they wouldn't normally do.
So he is a great collector
of intelligence
and he has these daring operations.
Reilly's adventures are
straight out of the pages of a novel.
In France, he poses as
a priest to win Britain important oil concessions.
In the Far East, he steals
Russian naval plans to sell to the highest bidder.
He was operating as a film agent
and as a Greek businessman,
changing his identity
at various stages.
After his death, the Evening Standard Newspaper
serialises his memoirs.
He is at once immortalised
as a master of deception.
He was the Ace of Spies.
He was brilliant.
In 1926, MI6 moves
to new headquarters
opposite St James's Park
underground station in London.
It grows quickly into
a sophisticated organisation,
collecting intelligence,
running agents
and mounting
covert operations overseas.
Within 15 years, it has
a spy network stretching across the globe.
It won't be long before the
organisation's capabilities
are tested to their limits.
'The German foe begins its
ruthless march of conquest.'
On 1st September, 1939,
Germany invades Poland.
Europe is at war.
Now more than ever, Britain's
Secret Service needs to know
what its enemy is up to.
Europe's freedom depends on it.
One of MI6's new recruits
is Mavis Batey,
a 19-year-old student
studying German literature.
Little does she know
what lies in store.
I was told that I was wanted
at a place in the country.
They wouldn't
tell you where you were going
but they told you to go
to Euston station
and you would be met with a ticket.
I thought I was going
to be Mata Hari,
I was going to be a spy,
I was terribly excited.
Mavis's mystery destination
is Bletchley Park,
an old manor house hidden
50 miles north of London.
It's the home of a top
secret department within MI6
that is decrypting enemy
coded communications.
Mavis's boss, chief
cryptographer Dilly Knox,
is an eccentric chain-smoking
classics scholar.
He was sitting,
smoke all round him
and he just looked up and said,
'We're breaking machines.
Have you got a pencil?'
And that was my introduction
to breaking Enigma.
In 1939, Enigma is the
world's most secure encryption machine
and the Germans are using it to encode all
their war communications.
The machine uses a clever
combination of interchangeable rotors,
moving rings and switchable plugs
to scramble its messages.
The Germans believe its codes
to be unbreakable.
The number of ways the
operator could set this up
was roughly 158.9 million
million million.
The daily setting
was known as the key
and the setting changed
every day at midnight Greenwich Mean Time.
Breaking the Enigma codes
will be key to winning
the war.
Mathematicians may be an
obvious choice for the work
but the unsung heroes of
Bletchley were a unique group of young women.
There was one actress,
one who'd been to a drama school,
and of all things,
a speech therapist.
And they were all people who
knew patterns of language
and picking it apart.
Armed with only pencils,
paper and bits of card,
it takes the code breakers
five months of ceaseless work
to decipher their first
Enigma message.
Mavis's big moment
would come a year later
during a critical period of the war.
The British learn the enemy are planning
a surprise attack
on the Allied fleet
in the Mediterranean.
But they don't know
when it's coming.
Then, on 25th March, 1941,
Mavis decodes
an extraordinary message.
We broke a message that said,
'Today's the day minus three'.
We then knew
what they were planning.
Everyone was so excited about that.
Forewarned of the impending offensive,
the British call in backup
and turn the tables on the enemy.
Thousands of lives are saved
thanks to Mavis and her colleagues.
Well, we were very good at it,
I suppose, very cunning.
Because it was largely
a strange mixture
of logic and guesswork
by which you broke things.
So we were all a bit dotty afterwards
and very good at Scrabble, of course.
Churchill considered the
code breakers' work so vital to the war effort
that he famously called them
'the geese that laid the golden egg'.
It is extremely unusual to
get such comprehensive...
in fact unprecedented,
in my experience...
to get such comprehensive
coverage of your opponent,
especially in a war,
both at the operational level and also at the level
of their top-level thinking
and strategic intentions.
As the number of enemy
communications increases,
Bletchley Park lacks
the money and manpower
to decipher all of them.
The only people in a position
to help are the Americans.
So in February, 1941,
a secret delegation from
the USA is invited to Bletchley Park
for an historic meeting.
Britain reveals its most
guarded wartime secret,
the cracking of the Enigma codes.
But it has an ulterior motive:
to draw the US into the war.
By bringing the Americans
across, by confiding in them
about breaking the German codes,
you try to make them
partners in the effort,
even though the Americans
are not formally in the war.
You try to give the idea
that somehow
we are both in this together
against Hitler.
This is the first time
that any two nations
have agreed to share such
vital secret intelligence.
It's the beginning of what
will become known as 'the special relationship'.
At that particular time,
we had no formal treaty
alliance between us.
There wasn't the history
of co-operation which subsequently developed
and if you're looking for a
sort of single symbolic event
which captures that rather
remarkable situation,
then it is here we were,
prepared to talk to each other
about the most secret things
that we were doing.
The relationship gradually
deepens as the two allies work together.
Eventually American code breakers
are even stationed alongside
the British at Bletchley.
The Americans were absolutely fascinated
because when they came
and saw us with these things in jam jars,
they just couldn't believe
what we were doing.
One of them said,
'My goodness, if they were the Pentagon,
there'd be rows and rows
of shiny files
and nothing in them,
and you do everything in
these goddamn shoeboxes.'
The methods might be basic
but the Americans are still
impressed by the Brits' ingenuity.
They recognise how well MI6 coordinates
all its various sections
from its London headquarters.
Everything from cryptography
to counter-espionage is under this central control.
The US has nothing like it.
In the words of Henry Stimson,
who was the Secretary of Defence in the US,
'Gentlemen don't read each other's mail'.
So the Americans didn't see
the need for a peacetime intelligence service.
In 1942, the Office of Strategic Services,
America's very first
centralised intelligence organisation,
is set up at Rockefeller
Center in New York City.
Heading the agency is former
army colonel William Donovan.
Because he was an anglophile,
he said, 'We'll structure it
the way the British have set up MI6.
We'll set it up for intelligence, analysis
and also covert operations.'
British brains to guide
American brawn.
The British let the Americans
use their espionage network
and covert listening
stations across Europe.
The Americans are rapidly
trying to catch up with the British.
So we have the development
of a special relationship of structures
but we also have the development of a special
relationship of people,
people who get to know
each other during the war
and who,
after the war ends in 1945,
continue to be in contact
with each other.
By 1947, the OSS is reformed
as the world-renowned CIA.
American co-operation with
British Intelligence continues to grow closer.
That initial move
lies at the very heart
of the quite unique defence
and security relationship
that the United Kingdom has
had with the United States
ever since 1941.
In these early days of the war,
Churchill sees that he'll need to fight dirty to stand
any chance of winning.
MI6 runs secret sabotage
missions abroad
from a small unit that is aptly named
'the Destruction department'.
In July, 1940, they join forces
with government propaganda
and research departments
to create the
Special Operations Executive.
Its mission is to sabotage
the German Army
and set Europe ablaze.
To do this, it adopts the
guerrilla warfare tactics
used so successfully by the IRA.
This secret army has its beginnings
in the most unlikely
of elegant and refined surroundings.
Author Gill Bennett has
documented official government history
for more than 30 years.
Well, this is
the St. Ermin's hotel,
which has definitely strong
intelligence connections
particularly from
the Second World War.
It's only round the corner
from the headquarters
of the Secret Intelligence
Service at the time, SIS,
very near to Whitehall,
very near to Westminster,
and so you could just
go across St James's Park
to wherever Churchill was,
to what are now called
the Cabinet War rooms.
Part of the Special
Operations Executive, SOE,
was formed here,
it had its offices upstairs.
It looks very beautiful
and light and romantic
but it was nevertheless a place
where a lot of clandestine
meetings took place.
Most SOE operatives are
foreigners who have fled occupied Europe.
French, Spaniards,
Danes and Poles
are recruited for
their language skills
and knowledge of occupied territories.
All are united by their desire
to liberate their homeland
from the Germans.
They were often called
a bunch of amateurs.
Actually, a lot of them
were a bunch of amateurs
but it was not a universally
liked part of the intelligence establishment,
even though, of course, in retrospect
it is seen as having had
a major impact.
Like any other MI6 operative,
preparation is key to their survival.
Before being parachuted
into enemy territory,
SOE agents undergo months
of intense commando training.
They would learn how to do self-defence,
silent killing using their bare hands,
and also close combat,
using a variety of weapons.
Machine guns, daggers,
silk escape maps
and even cleverly
disguised suitcase radios
are all part of their spy kit.
This is a Welrod pistol.
This is a silenced weapon,
so it's very, very effective
for assassination
when you need things to be quieter.
It's a very iconic SOE weapon.
Women would be seen out
wearing their hats all of the time.
So take your hat pin,
make it thicker, stronger
and with a very,
very sharp point.
And as long as you know
where you're aiming for,
this dagger is going to
be extremely effective.
SOE used plastic explosive.
This is a very malleable
type of explosive.
A famous SOE weapon is the rat.
Get a desiccated rat,
scoop out its insides,
stuff it with plastic explosive.
A German sentry in a factory
would think nothing of kicking aside a dead rat.
The explosive will blow up
the entire factory.
The SOE are hugely successful.
13,000 agents rally
over a million local resistance fighters
to cause chaos for
the German occupiers.
On the night of D-day itself
in France alone,
there were 960 acts of sabotage
carried out by the French Resistance
against rail networks
and on the roads
to prevent Germans moving
forwards towards Normandy.
After the war,
Ian Fleming is inspired
by the daring exploits of SOE and MI6
and uses them as plot lines
for the elaborate missions
of his master spy James Bond.
The James Bond stories
are uniquely influential
in defining the image
of MI6 and its spies.
They sell the public a world of espionage
that is glamorous and sexy.
Exotic cocktails,
shaken not stirred.
Beautiful women at every turn.
And sharp-suited spies.
Fleming's fictional version
of British espionage is so convincing,
the Egyptian Secret Service
are completely taken in by it.
Actually in the 1950s,
the Egyptians believed
everything that was
in the James bond book
must be based on reality.
The Egyptian Secret Service
had their man in London
buy up copies of every
one of the James Bond books
so they could analyse it
and try and work out
what bits were real
and what bits weren't real.
Even today, MI6 is inextricable
from the Bond mythology.
Much of the public's
knowledge of the Secret Service
comes solely from Fleming's creation.
MI6, which is a secret organisation,
also happens to be one of the most famous
organisations in the world.
But it's the result,
obviously, of the literature.
And that can bring problems,
because people sort of misunderstand
what intelligence work is all about.
I was in service for a long time
and I had plenty of exciting moments...
...but they weren't James Bond moments.
The reality is that espionage work is neither
loud nor high-profile.
For MI6, discretion and secrecy are key.
Unlike James Bond,
I wasn't able
to walk into a swanky bar in a hotel
and announce that
I was Matthew Dunn
and have women
flocking all around me.
We want to work in the shadows.
We don't want the flash-bang
aspect of a James Bond movie.
As an MI6 officer,
Matthew Dunn was trained in
unarmed combat, explosives,
firearms, exfiltration
and a host of other
intelligence techniques.
He's had to use all these skills
at one time or another.
Everything I did was under
what we call alias, assumed identity.
That assumed identity
is not just a name,
it would mean you'd have
a passport, bank details.
You'd have to have in here
a complete background
to that alias identity.
You could be stopped going
through customs just randomly.
So if you're taken
into an interview room
you've got to be able to
convince the person opposite
that you are the person
you say you are.
That can include which schools you went to,
what's your local pub...
you know, small minutiae that
is actually very important.
That's what I did and at peak
I was operating under about 14 or 15
different aliases.
Dunn was recruited from university.
For most of its history,
the British Secret Service
has recruited its spies
from the upper classes.
It's an elitism which would
prove a critical mistake for MI6
and cost the lives of
countless British agents.
It would also severely damage
Britain's special relationship with the US.
In the 1930s and '40s,
exclusive St James's clubs
such as White's,
Brooks's and Boodles
are renowned for their links
with British Intelligence.
Well, this is clubland.
This is what we call clubland.
It's just off Piccadilly,
Buckingham Palace is just over there.
It's the heart of the Establishment at this period
in the early 20th century.
This was the recruiting
ground for MI6.
This was also the high society hangout for
James Bond's creator Ian Fleming.
He incorporated his favourite
clubs and upper class bars
into the 007 stories.
Right, well, this is Boodles.
This is, essentially,
James Bond's club.
In the books,
it's called Blades
but Ian Fleming
was a member of Boodles
and he used Boodles as a backdrop,
if you like,
for the Bond books.
Officers would conduct
secret meetings
behind the closed shutters
of these private clubs.
Even today, members of the
intelligence community use these private spaces.
This is the Reform, this is
one of these hallowed clubs,
places where gentlemen used to gather.
You can imagine people
meeting behind these pillars
or over lunch in the restaurant.
Because they were
from the Establishment,
they were regarded as people
who could be trusted.
They were gentlemen. They
knew what they were doing.
In the 1930s, the KGB realise
that they can take advantage
of the cozy relationship
between the British Secret Service and
the British upper classes.
They begin to recruit Englishmen willing
to betray their country.
If someone said you were
the right kind of person,
a good chap,
then you were in.
There were no more
security checks than that,
no one bothered to look
into your background.
People said,
'He's one of us.'
They were wrong and the Soviet Union
very, very effectively exploited this
by recruiting people and
turning them against the British Establishment.
Cambridge University was one of the KGB's
most successful hunting
grounds for potential British traitors.
And the most famous of all
was Kim Philby.
Kim Philby became converted
to Communism in Cambridge in the early 1930s.
He believed that the choice
the world faced
was between Fascism
on the one hand
or Communism on the other
and he chose Communism.
Philby was instructed by the KGB
to join the British Secret Service
and then to work his way up
into a position of great influence...
all the time passing secrets
to his Russian contacts.
He proved remarkably effective.
He was the liaison with
Washington at the start of the Cold War,
where he was privy to an
enormous range of secrets
of joint operations
that Britain and America
were running against the Soviet Union.
In October, 1949, MI6 and the
CIA send a team into Albania
to try and topple the Communist regime.
The Albanian Army
is waiting for them.
Kim Philby was able to tell
the Soviet Union these operations were going on
and it meant that
the people who were dropped
were effectively rounded up
and, in some cases, executed.
You only have to have
one person like that
on the inside betraying you
and a huge amount of what you do
and your colleagues do
is simply undermined.
So, you know,
it's extremely damaging
and a high vulnerability point
for a service engaged
in this kind of work.
Philby meets his KGB contacts
in the exclusive and rarefied
London suburb of Kensington.
This area of west London is just a mile and a half
from the Soviet Embassy.
The Russians are confident
their meetings
with the traitor Philby
won't be discovered.
They're running rings around MI6.
Around here, one of the most
famous spy sites is Cafe Daquise.
It's a restaurant
where the Cambridge spies
are thought to have come
to eat and to drink.
Near to the cafe is
Holy Trinity Church,
another location that the KGB
use for their dirty work.
So this statue of
St Francis of Assisi
was used as a dead letter
drop by the KGB
during the Cold War.
It's a place where a message
would have been hidden round the back of the statue
which could then have been
picked up by a KGB officer,
so the two people
would never have to meet,
but information could
be exchanged containing secret intelligence.
Another famous dead letter drop
was at Mount Street Park
in Westminster,
yards from the US embassy.
A KGB agent would draw a chalk mark
on a nearby lamppost
to indicate he was leaving
a message in the park.
A second KGB officer would
remove the mark
and head to the park
to collect the message.
The KGB is far more adept,
it's far more cunning,
in some ways.
It's far better at putting
agents inside Britain.
Britain doesn't have
any agents inside the KGB.
It's not able to listen to
their communications in the same way,
so it's effectively blind
and deaf against its enemy.
And that's a real disadvantage.
By the 1950s, Kim Philby
comes under suspicion.
Questions are even asked
in the Houses of Parliament about his loyalty.
He holds a press conference
in which he publicly denies
being a traitor.
It was a very capable performance
by one of the great liars
in British Intelligence.
Philby protests his innocence
for another ten years.
But by 1965,
the weight of evidence
against him is too great
and he finally flees to the Soviet Union.
Instead of receiving the
hero's welcome he expects
for all his hard years of
service to the KGB,
he is met with suspicion.
Stalin actually thought
that they probably
might not be what they seemed.
He actually thought
that the Cambridge spies
were so good they couldn't be true.
In Moscow, Philby finds
himself under virtual house arrest.
The KGB won't employ him.
The disappointment is too
much and he turns to drink.
In 1988,
he dies a broken man.
Philby's betrayal
is an enormous blow
to MI6's relationship
with the United States
because Philby had enjoyed
such an important position
as the MI6 liaison
with the CIA with Washington
that suddenly America
becomes distrustful of MI6.
It thinks to itself, 'Hang
on a sec, how many more traitors might there be?
Should we be sharing as much
information with MI6 as we were in the past?
Are these guys really as good
as we thought they were?'
The British government cover
up the entire Philby fiasco.
As far as the public are concerned,
MI6 and its spies are still
the brilliantly heroic characters
of the James Bond stories...
tuxedoed men armed with guns
and clever gadgets.
The glamorous exploits
might be fictional
but the spy gadgets are a reality.
MI6 has a whole department
that's dedicated to producing
ingenious gadgets, in many cases.
For example I was given a briefcase
that if I flicked
the switches one way,
it would turn on
a concealed recorder.
But the ingenuity of MI6 is nothing compared to the
deadly gadgets of the KGB.
On 7th Sept, 1978,
London witnesses
the use of a lethal device
in a plot that is
stranger than fiction.
Georgi Markov was an
ambitious writer in Bulgaria
who became dissatisfied
with the Bulgarian regime
in spite of having been
at its topmost level.
He went hunting with
the Communist dictator Todor Zhivkov,
but defected and came to London.
...in line with the
corrupt nature of the Party and the regime...
Markov was riling the
Communist leadership in Bulgaria
with his deeply critical
writings and broadcasts.
We have seen how personality vanishes...
For the Bulgarian regime,
Georgi Markov was probably
their number one public enemy.
It's just another
routine day for Markov
as he makes his way to work
across Waterloo Bridge in London.
But within a few hours,
he begins to fell unwell.
The following day,
he is admitted to hospital
suffering massive organ failure.
His doctors have no explanation.
Markov, though, is certain
he has been poisoned.
I went in and saw him.
His words were,
'They're out to get me.
I've been poisoned by the KGB,
there's nothing you can do
about it, I'm going to die.'
Dr Riley is chief medical
officer on call at the time.
His colleagues think Markov
is paranoid and crazy.
Only Dr Riley believes
his fantastic claims.
He just was so convincing
and he seemed so genuine
that I thought I'd better
take this seriously.
Markov desperately tries
to work out how he's been poisoned.
The only strange thing
he can remember happening
is at a bus stop on the way
to work that morning.
He just told me about how
he was waiting at a bus stop
at the south end of Waterloo Bridge.
And he said that he suddenly
felt like a sharp,
stabbing feeling in the back
of his right thigh.
And he turned around,
to see someone there who'd accidentally prodded
him with an umbrella.
Markov's condition
deteriorates quickly
and within three days,
he is dead.
For the first time,
MI6 fear the worst.
Has a foreign agent carried
out an assassination on British soil?
Had someone been given a
real-life license to kill?
Everything you're doing
overseas as an operative is illegal,
because espionage is illegal.
So the concept of having
a license to kill is irrelevant.
If you kill somebody,
you can't suddenly pull out a license
and that's gonna be fine.
So the reality is,
there's no need to have a license to kill.
License or not, Markov
believes he's been targeted.
And whoever has attacked him
has left a trace.
When I examined him and found
on the back of his thigh
sort of this puncture wound,
I thought, 'Well, perhaps
he has been poisoned.'
Buried inside Markov's leg,
the pathologist discovers
a tiny round pellet
the size of a pinhead.
The microscopic holes drilled
into it are so small,
there's only one possible
toxin powerful enough
to have killed in such a minuscule dose.
Ricin.
You can imagine this is the pellet.
The theory is that the holes
were sealed with something
like gelatine which would
melt at body temperature.
So that once the pellet
is beneath the skin,
the gelatine dissolves
and the toxin leaks out.
The pellet was fired into
Markov's leg by an elaborate mechanism
most probably hidden inside
the umbrella he saw dropped at the bus stop.
You need a lot of knowledge,
a lot of skill and a lot of expertise
to engineer something
like the pellet
containing the ricin
that killed Mr. Markov.
MI6 believe the sophisticated
nature of the pellet and umbrella device
point to a state-ordered assassination...
probably the work of the
Bulgarian Secret Service
with help from the KGB.
Our own Secret Intelligence
Service must have been
extremely embarrassed
as well as concerned
that this sort of attack had been carried
out on Waterloo Bridge
in broad daylight
in the centre of London.
It was an incredible affront.
The Markov murder hits the headlines.
Suddenly MI6 finds its
business splashed across the newspapers.
Its secrets are being laid
bare in full public view.
By the late 1970s,
it seems Britain's Secret Service isn't
very secret anymore.
It was an open secret where
the offices of MI6 were based
at Century house just over
the river in Lambeth.
It was supposed to be secret,
there was no plaque outside saying MI6,
but all the bus conductors
in Lambeth used to say,
'Spies alight here,
spies get off the bus here,'
as a joke because everyone
knew where MI6 was based.
After the disasters
of the early Cold War,
MI6's luck finally changes.
They persuade senior KGB
member, Oleg Gordievsky,
to turn double agent
and leak Russian secrets
to the British.
Gordievsky quickly climbs
the KGB career ladder
and in 1982, he's posted
to a prime position
at the Soviet Embassy in London.
Oleg Gordievsky was recruited
by the British at an important moment
when Britain and America
did not have many spies
who could reveal the inner
thoughts, inner workings
of the KGB leadership and
of the leadership of the Soviet Union as a whole.
The MI6 officer in charge
of handling Gordievsky
is none other than John Scarlett.
He was turned into a really
reliable and effective
and committed agent,
if you like, or double agent.
You can only do it if you
trust the double agent concerned
and by definition, trusting double agents is not
a straightforward business.
But the British become
convinced that Gordievsky is genuine.
During lunch breaks, he slips
out of the Soviet Embassy to meet with Scarlett.
Very occasionally, he is
also able to smuggle out top-secret documents.
Gordievsky is risking
his life meeting Scarlett.
If the KGB catch a traitor,
there is no reprieve.
They will execute him.
Gordievsky's most important moment
is to come in late 1983.
Unknown to the public,
for a brief moment,
the world is on the brink of nuclear war.
Tension was increasing
between the West and the Soviet Union
when Ronald Reagan was
talking about the evil empire
and when the Soviet Union
feared there could be a surprise attack.
NATO forces are preparing
for a Europe-wide exercise
that simulates a nuclear attack.
Everyone from the Joint Chiefs of Staff
to the President is to be involved.
But the Soviet Union thinks
the exercise is merely cover
for the West to launch
a real strike against them.
The world is unwittingly
heading towards nuclear war.
Messages went out
to the KGB station saying,
'You must be on high alert
for the possibility
of the West launching
a strike against us.'
And the Soviet Union actually
raised its state of alert in readiness.
In London, Gordievsky sees
the aggressive messages
from the Russian leadership
and immediately warns MI6.
To pacify Moscow,
the US immediately
scale down the exercise
and remove any involvement
by the President.
The West suddenly realised
just how edgy the situation was
and just how volatile
and dangerous things were.
That really helped
London and Washington
think much more carefully
about how they managed that
period of quite high tension
during the latter part
of the Cold War.
Gordievsky has proved his worth
but in 1985,
his luck runs out.
Though free to return
to his Moscow home,
Gordievsky knows his days are numbered.
He is closely watched
at every turn.
In desperation, he asks MI6
to smuggle him out of the country.
His request goes straight
to Number 10 Downing street
where Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher
authorises MI6 to engineer
a daring escape plan.
The rescue date is set.
On 20th July, 1985,
Gordievsky waits at a pre-arranged spot near
the Soviet-Finnish border.
At precisely 2pm, a car pulls
up on the isolated road.
It is the British Secret Service.
Inside are a man and
two women with a child.
MI6 is hoping a family outing
will provide the perfect cover for the escape.
With Gordievsky in the trunk,
the car speeds towards the border.
The Soviet frontier is heavily guarded.
And Oleg can hear search dogs outside.
If the dogs sniff him out,
he's done for.
The strong smell from the
diapers distracts the dogs
and Gordievsky remains undetected.
Finally,
after two tense hours,
he hears the signal
he has been waiting for.
The car has reached neutral
Finland and safety.
MI6 has repaid Gordievsky's loyalty
and ensured his freedom.
Oleg Antonovich Gordievsky
is a well-known public case
and it is not possible to overstate
the contribution he made to our national
well being and interests.
When the Soviet Union
crumbles after the fall of the Berlin Wall,
it seems like Britain and the
West's game of cat and mouse with Russia is over.
But only 20 years later,
the Russians are back
and playing the spying game
with a vengeance.
On 1st November, 2006,
dissident Alexander Litvinenko
is fatally poisoned
at the Millennium Hotel in London,
when his tea is laced
with Polonium-210,
a radioactive substance.
It's become clear
that some of the old threats
and some of the old dangers remain.
You've seen the resurgence
of some of the concerns
about Russian Intelligence
operating in London,
about Russia recruiting spies,
even, it's thought,
the Russian state
killing dissidents
on the streets of London
in the case of Alexander Litvinenko.
The murder of Litvinenko
wasn't just the KGB executing a troublesome dissident.
It was the start of an entirely new level
of violence
in the world of espionage.
Information came out showing
that Alexander Litvinenko
had actually been a paid agent of MI6,
and he'd then been assassinated,
it's thought, on the orders
of the Russian state,
by the Russian Intelligence Services,
using radioactive polonium.
So, in a way, you can see,
though the Cold War is gone,
the spy games between Britain and Russia
are still going on today.
The Russians have broken
an unwritten rule in the spy game.
They have killed another
country's spy, an MI6 agent.
The KGB may be no more
but the new Russian Intelligence Service
is just as deadly and operating on
the streets of London.
Today, MI6 finds itself
with a wider mission:
preventing cyber attacks
on Government organisations,
stopping the spread of nuclear, chemical
and biological weapons,
as well as fighting terrorism.
It gradually became clear
there was a new problem out there
from international terrorism,
not just a theoretical problem,
actually a physical threat.
At least 20 foreign state are known
to be actively targeting the United Kingdom.
MI6 is needed now more than ever.
My entire experience
up until the present day
is we face situations where
we need to be well informed.
Self-evidently,
the best form of defence
against plots and attacks is
to know about it in advance,
and that is a matter
of good intelligence.
As long as there are people
who want to do Britain harm,
Britain will need a secret service.
As long as there
are threats out there,
whether those threats
are now from cyberspace and terrorists
rather than the Soviet Union,
then we'll need spies to try
and understand those threats,
to get inside them,
to understand what your enemy's intentions are.
Because the United Kingdom is
such a high priority target,
the British Intelligence and Security Services
have a budget in excess
of $3 billion to fight hostile forces.
I largely suspect there are
far more spies in London
and in Europe now than there
were during the Cold War.
London will always be
the perfect place for spies to hide
and pass unseen among
the millions of visitors.
Of course, I would say
this, wouldn't I?
But I genuinely,
honestly cannot envisage a circumstance
where our country will not
need an effective intelligence service.
I've seen the importance
of the service
and the role it plays increase,
rather than the other way around.
The service has continued
to work, day in, day out
since 1st October, 1909.
One operation leads to another operation,
leads to another operation,
that's how it is.