[♪♪♪]
MAN: Mummy got sick.
And it happened just like that.
There's nothing anybody could do.
It isn't fair.
There's no reason.
And if we start asking why, we'll go crazy.
Five minutes in the microwave.
Any one of them.
Five minutes,
and ready to eat.
Do you know how to make juice?
Microwave.
Five minutes.
Here. It's my shrink.
Call him.
Loss of Spouse Support Group.
Chicago Cancer Family Network.
Parents without Partners.
Partners without Parents.
"Hug Yourself,"
"Hug a Friend,"
"Hug a Shrink." Or work.
Work hard, work will save you.
Work is the only thing that will
see you through this.
Don't mind him, he's just a guy
who's lost his wife.
What I think we really need is change.
Good idea. Take a couple
of weeks off, get some sun,
take Jonah fishing.
No, real change.
A new city.
Some place where every time
I go around a corner
I don't think of Maggie.
ROB:
Where are you gonna go?
I was thinking about Seattle.
Eventually, in a few months,
you'll start seeing women.
You'll meet someone.
Right, right. Move on, right,
that's what I'm gonna do.
And then in a few months,
boom, I'll be fine.
I'll just grow a new heart.
Sam, I'm sorry...
She didn't mean that.
I know, I know.
Look, it just doesn't
happen twice.
[JIMMY DURANTE'S
"AS TIME GOES BY" PLAYS]
♪ You must remember this, ♪
♪ A kiss is still a kiss ♪
♪ A sigh is just a sigh ♪
♪ The fundamental things apply ♪
♪ As time goes by ♪
♪ And when two lovers woo ♪
♪ They still say "I love you" ♪
♪ On that you can rely ♪
♪ No matter what the future brings ♪
♪ As time goes by ♪
♪ Moonlight and love songs ♪
♪ Never out of date ♪
♪ Hearts full of passion ♪
♪ Jealousy and hate ♪
♪ Woman needs man ♪
♪ And man must have his mate ♪
♪ That no one can deny ♪
♪ It's still the same old story ♪
♪ A fight for love and glory ♪
♪ A case of do or die ♪
♪ The world ♪
♪ Will always welcome lovers ♪
♪ As time goes by ♪♪
The tall one with red hair is your cousin Irene.
You'll recognise her
by the disappointed
look on her face.
Married to Harold,
who ran off with
the secretary.
Who came back because
Irene threatened to put
the dog to sleep if he didn't.
Your brother Dennis
is professor
at Johns Hopkins.
He's married to, uh, Betsy.
The most competitive woman in the world.
I don't see how I'm gonna remember all this.
Oh, well, Walter, you will!
Your Uncle Milton lost all of his money.
And some other people's.
In a pyramid scheme.
Don't mention the IRS
or the federal prisons system.
Your mother's Barbara, your father's Cliff
My father has electric trains.
Really?
Am I what they had in mind?
Oh, Walter, they're gonna love you!
[GLASS CLINKING]
WOMAN: Everybody,
Annie has an announcement.
Oh... Walter and I are engaged.
[SCREAMING]
Thank you. Thank you.
Mum knew.
Dad, Mum knew.
I don't see a ring, Annie.
Congratulations, Walter.
[SNEEZING]
Bless you. Bless you!
CLIFF: Are you all right?
It's nothing. It's nothing.
Maybe it's the flowers.
BARBARA:
We'll move them.
No, don't touch them!
I feel terrible, sneezing at
a time like this.
This is a very important moment for me.
He's allergic to everything,
don't worry about him.
Bees.
I'm allergic to bees.
Harold is allergic to every type of bee.
We always have to
carry a hypodermic of
adrenalin wherever we go.
If he eats even one tiny piece of a nut...
My head swells up
like a watermelon
and I drop dead.
IRENE:
It's the same with him and bees.
Your mother and I had salmon at our wedding.
I really think
a wedding without
cold salmon is...
I'm not allergic to salmon.
Oh, he's not allergic...
I don't think.
But you never know.
You never know.
Harold wasn't always allergic to bees.
BARBARA: Oh, honey,
what a shame.
We had some champagne.
What did we use it for?
Uncle Milton's parole.
And it was delicious.
It was, wasn't it, Milton?
When are you getting married?
In early June, in the garden.
Oh...
What about Harold and bees?
I'm allergic to bees.
BARBARA:
We'll spray you.
Cold salmon, a lovely
cucumber salad,
strawberries.
I'm afraid I am allergic to strawberries.
Is this all right with you?
Today, I'm consider myself
the luckiest man-man-man
on the face of the earth-earth-earth.
The Lou Gehrig line from...
Remember, Dad, the Lou Gehrig line from, uh...
Pride of the Yankees.
Pride of the Yankees!
Yeah. Yeah.
Baseball. It's baseball.
Historical reference.
I would like to propose a toast.
ALL: Hear, hear.
To my kid sister.
To Walter and my baby.
BARBARA:
To Walter and Annie.
Everyone, please eat before it gets cold.
Here it is. The Historical
Society wanted this
and I never would give it to them.
ANNIE:
Oh, Mum...
BARBARA: I noticed these things
are back in fashion.
ANNIE:
Grandmother's dress.
Oh, honey.
He's a lovely man, Annie.
I know he is wonderful, isn't he?
And he's such a wonderful athlete.
Are his folks nice?
You'll love them.
We're going down
to DC tonight to be with
them Christmas morning.
How did it happen?
It's silly, really.
I mean, I'd seen him at the office.
Obviously I'd seen him.
He's the associate publisher.
And then one day we
both ordered sandwiches
from the same place
and he got my lettuce
and tomato on whole wheat,
which, of course, he was allergic to.
And I got his lettuce and tomato on white.
How amazing.
It is, isn't it?
You make a million decisions that mean nothing
and then one day
you order takeout
that changes your life.
Destiny takes a hand.
Mum, destiny is something we've invented
because we can't stand
the fact that everything
that happens is accidental.
Then how do you explain
that you both ordered exactly
the same sandwich
except for the bread?
How many people in this world
like lettuce and tomato
without something else,
like tuna?
Well, it wasn't a sign.
It was a coincidence.
I was in Atlantic City
with my family,
Cliff was a waiter.
He wasn't even supposed
to work that night.
Suppose he hadn't?
He asked me
to take a midnight walk
on the Steel Pier.
I probably told you this
a million times,
but I don't care.
Then he held my hand.
At one point I looked down
and I couldn't tell which fingers
were his and which were mine.
And I knew.
What?
You know.
Magic. It was magic.
Magic.
I knew we'd be together
forever. And that everything
would be wonderful.
Just the way you feel about Walter.
Walter. It's quite a formal name.
One of the things
I truly knew was that
your father and I
were going to have a wonderful time in
the sack, I believe you call it.
Mum.
Of course it took several
years before everything
worked like clockwork in that department.
So don't be worried if it takes a while.
We already...
Fine, fine. Fiddly-dee. How's it working?
Like clockwork.
Oh, honey...
[ANNIE GASPS]
It's a sign.
You don't believe in signs.
[ANNIE CHUCKLING]
They loved you. I told
you they would love you,
and they loved you.
I love you.
I love you, Walter.
Did anyone ever call you
anything other than Walter?
No.
Not even when you were young?
No, not even when I was young.
You sure you don't want to drive with me?
Oh, how will I get back to Baltimore on Friday?
I forgot the present. Walter,
I left your stepmother's
present inside by accident.
I swear, when we're old and grey
you gonna have to remind me to put my teeth in.
I'll be walking all over
town smacking my gums
together, not even noticing.
I'll wait.
You'll wait? Oh, right.
No, don't wait, Walter.
Really, it's silly, you go ahead.
We're late anyway.
I'll be ten minutes behind you.
["SLEIGH RIDE" PLAYS ON RADIO]
♪ Sleigh bells jingle-ing ♪
♪ Ring ting tingle-ing too ♪
♪ Horses, horses, horses ♪
♪ It's lovely weather ♪
♪ For a sleigh ride together with you ♪
♪ Giddy-up, giddy-up ♪
♪ The snow is falling ♪
♪ And friends are calling "Yoo Hoo" ♪
♪ Friends are calling "Yoo Hoo" ♪
♪ Ding-a-ling-a-ling ♪
♪ Sleigh ride together with you ♪
♪ Horse, horses, horses ♪
♪ Horse, horses ♪♪
[ROGERS' AND DALE EVANS'
"JINGLE BELLS" PLAYS]
♪ Jingle bells, jingle bells ♪
♪ Jingle all the way ♪
♪ Oh, what fun, it is to ride ♪
♪ In a one horse open sleigh, hey ♪
♪ Jingle bells ♪♪
WOMAN 1 [ON RADIO]:
Welcome back to
"You and Your Emotions."
I'm Dr. Marcia Fieldstone,
broadcasting live across America
from the top of the Sears Tower in Chicago.
Tonight we're talking about wishes and dreams.
What's your wish this Christmas Eve?
What's your wish?
My wish is to turn the radio station.
MAN: Subject of this evening's
medical update is:
"You and your spleen."
And your host is...
Not on your life.
WOMAN 2: Coming up,
"Jingle Bells" backwards,
sung by the New Jersey...
FIELDSTONE: Seattle, go ahead.
JONAH: Hello, this is Jonah...
[BEEPING]
FIELDSTONE:
No last names, Jonah.
You sound younger than
our usual callers.
How old are you?
JONAH:
I'm 8.
FIELDSTONE:
Eight? How come you're up so late?
JONAH:
It's not that late in Seattle.
FIELDSTONE:
Oh, of course,
you're absolutely right.
All right, what's your Christmas wish, Jonah?
JONAH: It's not for me, it's for my dad.
I think he needs a new wife.
FIELDSTONE:
You don't like the one he has now?
JONAH:
He doesn't have one now.
That's the problem.
FIELDSTONE:
Where's your mum?
JONAH:
She died.
FIELDSTONE: Oh, I'm so sorry.
Well, who can believe this?
JONAH: I've been pretty sad,
but I think my Dad's worse.
FIELDSTONE:
Have you talked to your dad about it?
JONAH: No.
FIELDSTONE: Why not?
JONAH:
It's like it makes him sadder.
FIELDSTONE:
Aw, I can understand that.
Jonah, is your dad home right now?
JONAH: Yeah.
What's he doing? Is he busy?
JONAH:
Not really, he's out on the deck.
FIELDSTONE:
I'm sure that I can help.
But I'm gonna need you to help me...
Wretched woman! Hang up, Jonah!
JONAH: No way, he'd kill me.
FIELDSTONE:
Trust me, Jonah.
He won't be angry when he realises
how concerned you are about him.
Wanna bet?
JONAH:
But if I get yelled at, I'm never
gonna listen to your show again.
FIELDSTONE:
Okay, fair enough.
JONAH: Dad?
SAM: Yeah.
JONAH: There's someone
on the phone for you.
His name is Sam.
FIELDSTONE: Sam.
If you've just tuned in,
this is Dr. Marcia Fieldstone
and tonight's topic is your wishes and dreams.
I got it.
We're on the line now with someone from Seattle.
Hello.
Hello, Sam, this is Dr. Fieldstone
on Network America.
Okay. What are you selling tonight?
Micro-hibachis or knives?
FIELDSTONE:
No, I'm not selling anything.
I just wanna help.
I want you to know that your son called
and he asked me for some advice
on how you might find a new wife.
Who is this?
Dr. Marcia Fieldstone
of Network America.
And you are on the air.
You called a radio station?
FIELDSTONE: Sam, are you with me?
Yeah. Yes.
Your son feels that
since your wife's death
you've been very, very unhappy.
And he is genuinely worried about you.
Get out here. Get out here.
Come on, now, I'm not
gonna go through this alone.
I think it's very hard for him
to talk to you about all this.
I thought maybe you and I
could talk, it would make Jonah
feel a little better. Sam?
Talk to her, Dad. She's a doctor.
Of what?
Her first name could be Doctor.
Please.
Sam. Sam, it's his Christmas wish.
Okay.
Okay. Good.
FIELDSTONE:
Now, I know this is difficult.
But how long ago did your wife die?
About a year and a half ago.
Aw. Have you had any relationships?
No.
No? Why not?
Uh, Marcia, or Dr. Fieldstone?
Dr. Marcia.
SAM: I don't mean to be rude...
FIELDSTONE:
And I don't want to invade
your privacy...
Sure you do.
SAM: Sure you do.
FIELDSTONE:
Go on, Sam. I'm listening. Sam.
We had a pretty tough time at first.
But we're dealing with it.
And Jonah and I will
get along just fine again,
as soon as I break his radio.
[FIELDSTONE LAUGHING]
FIELDSTONE: I have no doubt that
you're a wonderful father.
You know, you can tell a lot
from a person's voice.
You certainly can.
But something must be missing
if Jonah still feels
that you're under a cloud.
Just a few questions:
Are you sleeping at night?
JONAH:
He doesn't sleep at all.
How do you know that?
I live here, Dad.
Look, it's Christmas.
Maggie, my wife.
She really did it...
I mean, she loved...
She made everything beautiful.
It's just tough this time of year.
Every kid needs a mother.
Could it be that you need someone
just as much as Jonah does?
Yes.
FIELDSTONE: Don't answer that.
Let's get into that right after these messages.
Sam, Jonah, don't go away.
If you've have just tuned in,
we are talking to Sleepless in Seattle.
And we'll be right back
after this break
with your listener response.
What is she talking about?
This is when other people
get to call in and dump
on what you said.
Oh. Oh. Well, this is
really fun. And helpful.
WOMAN:
I bet he's tall
with a cute butt.
WAITRESS 1:
I bet he hasn't bathed
in weeks and he stinks.
Harriet, shut up. Hi, can I help you?
Tea, with the bag out.
You know, maybe I'll just go
up to Seattle, give him
a little gift for New Year's Eve.
WAITRESS 2: Yeah, you go on
out there if you want to.
But don't open his refrigerator.
They don't cover
anything when they
put it in the fridge
they just stick it in
there and leave it
till it walks out by itself.
LORETTA: All I'm saying is
I wouldn't kick this guy
out of my bed for eating crackers.
You know what I'm saying?
Sixty five cents.
FIELDSTONE: Let's take a call
before we get back to Sleepless.
ALL: Ooh!
Tennessee, you are on the air.
WOMAN: Yes, I would just like
to know where I could
get this man's address.
Honey, get in line.
FIELDSTONE:
Next caller, go ahead.
If there was one question
I was allowed to ask...
Oh, go ahead.
People who truly loved once
are far more likely to love again.
Sam, do you think that there is
someone out there you could love
as much as your wife?
Well, Dr. Marcia Fieldstone,
that's hard to imagine.
What are you going to do?
Well, I'm going to get out of bed every morning
and breathe in and out all day long.
And after a while I won't have to remind myself
to get out of bed every morning
and breathe in and out.
And then after a while I won't
have to think about
how I had it great and perfect for a while.
FIELDSTONE:
Sam, tell me what was
so special about your wife.
SAM:
Well, how long is your programme?
Oh, well, it was a million tiny, little things.
When you added them all up,
it just meant we were
supposed to be together.
And I knew it, I knew it
the very first time I touched her.
It was like coming home,
only to no home I'd ever known.
I was just taking her hand
to help her out of a car.
And I knew it.
It was like magic.
Magic.
FIELDSTONE: Well, folks, it's time
to wrap it up. I'm Dr. Marcia
Fieldstone in Chicago.
And to all my listeners,
a magical and merry Christmas.
And to you, Sleepless in Seattle,
we hope you'll call again soon
and let us know how it's going.
SAM:
Oh, you can count on it.
[RAY CHARLES'
"OVER THE RAINBOW" PLAYS]
♪ I know ♪
♪ Somewhere over the rainbow ♪
♪ The blue birds fly ♪
♪ Birds fly ♪
♪ Over the rainbow ♪
♪ Why then, oh why can't I? ♪
MAN: This man sells the greatest
soup you've ever eaten, and he is
the meanest man in America.
I feel very strongly
about this, Becky.
It's not just about soup.
BECKY:
Do it. What else?
New Year's Eve.
Please don't
make me write it.
Listen to this: "Phone service
in the Chicago area was tied up
for two hours Christmas Eve
when some kid calls
a radio show and says that
his dad needs a new wife."
Two thousand women
called the station asking
for the guy's number.
I heard it. This kid
calls up and says,
"My dad needs a wife."
And the shrink practically forces
the guy and says,
"Do you want to talk about it."
And he says,
"No, as a matter of fact, I don't."
And then suddenly
for no reason at all
he start to talk
about how much he loved his wife
and how he just fell in love
with her like he was one
of those cows in Michigan.
What cows in Michigan?
It was on 60 Minutes
over those cows that got
zapped by stray voltage.
No one knows why.
And maybe it was Wisconsin.
But, anyway, I was listening
to him talk about how much
he loved his wife
and suddenly I was crying.
It's like what happens
when I watch those
phone company ads.
I don't have to see
the whole thing,
just the part
where the daughter gives
the mother the refrigerator
with the big red bow.
Yes. The Polaroid commercial,
two 5-year-olds at their
grandfather's birthday party.
They're making the album.
That kills me!
You should write something about this.
About what?
BECKY: Whatever it is.
I tell you what it is: Two thousand
women calling a radio station
for a husband?
There are a lot of desperate
women out there
looking for love.
Especially over a certain age.
You know it's easier to be
killed by a terrorist than
it is to get married over 40.
That is not true.
That statistic is not true.
That's right, it's not true.
But it feels true.
It feels true because it's true.
There is practically
a whole book about how
that statistic is not true.
Calm down, you brought it up.
I did not, Wyatt.
Did you even read that book?
Did anybody read that book all the way through?
Are you two finished?
Fine, now where were we?
If someone's a widower,
why do they say
that he was he "widowed"?
Why don't they say he was "widowered"?
I was just wondering.
BECKY:
What was that about up there?
What was what?
What's with you?
ANNIE:
Nothing's with me.
BECKY:
Something's with you.
What are you saying?
Whatever it is, you can tell me.
Sleepless in Seattle?
That's what she called him
on the show because
he can't sleep.
And now 2000 women
want his number.
The guy could be a crackhead,
a transvestite, a flasher, a junkie,
a chainsaw murderer
or someone really sick, someone like my Rick.
Actually, he sounded nice.
Oh? Oh, really?
Now we're getting down to it.
Please, Becky. I'm madly
in love with Walter. He did
the craziest thing the other night.
What was that?
Oh, it was so funny.
We were hysterical.
What was that?
[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
You know, I was thinking,
I've gotta go to Boston
for the AAB convention, right?
And then I gotta visit
Winston-Hughes about
switching over our computers, but...
Why don't we meet
in New York
for Valentine's Day weekend.
Walter, I'd love to!
We can stay at the Plaza.
Ice skate in Central Park.
Register.
Yeah, for dishes, glasses, silver, everything.
[WALTER GRUNTS]
How about it?
I'll take you to Chinatown for dim sum.
Does it have wheat in it?
I don't think so.
♪ Dim sum, dim sum ♪
♪ Dooby-doo-bop ♪
CROWD:
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six
five, four, three, two, one.
Hey, Jonah, wake up, wake up.
The ball's dropping.
["AULD LANG SYNE" PLAYS ON TV]
It's okay. Ohh. There we go.
Happy New Year.
Kiss Howard.
Good night, Howard.
[NAT KING COLE'S
"STARDUST" PLAYING]
♪ Sometimes I wonder ♪
♪ Why I spend ♪
♪ The lonely nights ♪
♪ Dreaming of a song ♪
♪ The melody ♪
♪ Haunts my reverie ♪
♪ And I am once again with you ♪
♪ When our love was new ♪
♪ And each kiss an inspiration ♪
♪ But that was long ago ♪
♪Now my consolation ♪
♪ Is in the stardust of a song ♪
♪ Beside a garden wall ♪
♪ When stars are bright ♪
♪ You are in my arms ♪
♪ The nightingale ♪
♪ Tells his fairy tale ♪
♪ Of paradise where roses grew ♪♪
MAGGIE: Can I have
half your beer?
Sure, go ahead.
What did I used to say?
"Here's looking at you"?
"Here's mud in your eye."
"Here's to us."
You used to say,
Oh, babe.
I miss you so much it hurts.
What do you wanna do?
Tell him when he gets here.
You want to tell him?
You can tell him?
She's back.
She has another idea.
No, no, no.
I don't need this.
CLAIRE: Sam, I'm so glad you're here.
How are you?
I heard you on the radio.
I told everyone about it.
We already knew.
How did you...?
Grace.
The dispatcher?
Yeah.
All of Seattle knows.
I was brushing my teeth
and, suddenly, there you were.
I just couldn't believe
my ears. I called
my mother in Las Vegas.
I said, "Mother,
turn on the radio.
That's my architect."
You know, it's so nice
when a man can
express his feelings.
It's wonderful.
I wish I could express my feelings.
So, Claire, is there a problem?
I was tossing and turning
last night. You know
what that's like, Sam.
Because I realise
I'm never going
to fit my platters
in that refrigerator we ordered.
And when I give parties,
I always put in platters.
So I thought
I would get the sub-zero
refrigerator instead.
And the only problem...
We have to redo all the cabinets.
We're gonna...
We'll be into this wall.
That's bearing wall.
SAM: That's a delay, Claire, of...
Two, three...
Five, six...
Twelve weeks.
I don't mind.
The important thing is to get it right.
Absolutely.
Your words.
Oh, I've gotta rush.
La décorateur calls.
Bye.
Well, this is fate.
She's divorced, we don't
wanna redo the cabinets,
and you need a wife.
What do they call that,
when everything intersects?
The Bermuda Triangle.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
MAN: And here's another one.
Do you got room
for one more here?
Here you go. Right there.
JONAH: Look at this, Dad.
They're all for you.
Yes, sir. Here you go.
"Sleepless in Seattle,"
c/o Dr. Marcia Fieldstone.
If you're having trouble
sleeping, you might wanna try
drinking a glass of water from the other side.
I thought that was for hiccups.
Does it work for hiccups?
For hiccups, take a spoonful
of sugar, hold it in
your mouth for a minute.
Really?
Thank you.
SAM: What possessed you
to give them our address?
They called and asked for it.
"Dear Sleepless in Seattle
you're the most attractive man
I ever lay ears on." Pfft.
Wait, wait.
They called?
How did they get our number?
Oh, let me guess.
You gave it to them.
You have to give them
your number or they
won't let you on the air.
"Dear Sleepless in Seattle.
I live in Tulsa."
Where's that?
It's in Oklahoma.
You know where Oklahoma is?
Somewhere in the middle.
I'm not even gonna think
about what they're not
teaching you in school.
Yeah, somewhere in the middle.
And, generally speaking
we should rule out
anyone that doesn't
live near here.
She's willing to fly anywhere.
She looks like
my third-grade teacher.
I hated my third-grade teacher.
Wait a minute.
She is my third-grade teacher!
Aren't you gonna read any of these?
No. This is not how it's done.
I'd much rather just see somebody I like
and get a feeling about them,
ask them if they wanna
have a drink.
Or a slice of pizza?
Not dinner.
Not on the first date,
because halfway through dinner,
you could be really sorry.
Whereas, if it's just a drink
if you like them,
you can always
ask them to dinner.
If not, you can say,
"Well, that was great,"
and then you go home.
You see what I mean?
I wonder if it still works this way.
It doesn't. They ask you.
I'm starting to notice that.
If you get a new wife,
I guess you'll have sex
with her, huh?
I certainly hope so.
Will she scratch up your back?
What?
In movies, women always
scratch up the man's back
and screaming.
How do you know this?
Jed's got cable.
Oh, Jed's got...
Hand me that towel behind you.
Thank you.
I need it too.
Here, let me get you.
"Jed's got cable!"
Come on.
[DR. JOHN'S "MAKIN'
WHOOPEE" PLAYS]
♪ Another bride ♪
♪ Another groom ♪
♪ Another sunny honeymoon ♪
♪ Another season, another reason ♪
♪ For makin' whoopee ♪♪
[WALTER SNORING]
[CARLY SIMON'S "IN THE WEE SMALL
HOURS OF THE MORNING" PLAYS]
♪ When the sun is high ♪
♪ In the afternoon sky ♪
♪ You can always find ♪
♪ Something to do ♪
♪ But from dusk till dawn ♪
♪ As the clock ticks on ♪
♪ Something happens to you ♪
♪ In the wee small hours ♪
♪ Of the morning ♪
♪ While the whole wide world ♪
♪ Is fast asleep ♪
♪ You lie awake ♪
♪ And think about the boy ♪
♪ And never ever think ♪
♪ Of counting sheep ♪♪
MAN [OVER RADIO]: Welcome back
to the best of Dr. Marcia Fieldstone
clinical psychologist
and the friend you never had.
Remember Marooned in Miami?
WOMAN 1:
He says he doesn't love me anymore.
FIELDSTONE: Why would you
wanna be with someone
who doesn't love you?
MAN:
Disappointed in Denver.
WOMAN 2: Every time I come
close to orgasm,
he goes to make himself a sandwich.
FIELDSTONE: Why don't you make him
a sandwich beforehand.
MAN:
Sleepless in Seattle.
SAM:
Well, I'm going to get out
of bed every morning.
Breathe in and out all day long.
And then after a while,
I won't have to remind myself
to get out of bed every morning
and breathe in and out.
And then after a while,
I won't have to think about
how I had it great and perfect for a while.
FIELDSTONE: Sam, tell me what was
so special about your wife?
SAM:
Well, how long is your programme?
Oh, well, it was...
Oh, it was a million tiny, little things.
When you added them all up
it just meant that we were
supposed to be together.
And I knew it.
I knew it the first time I touched her.
It was like coming home,
only to no home I'd ever known.
I was just taking her hand,
to help her out of a car.
And I knew it.
It was like
magic.
Well, I think I'm going
crazy, Dennis. I really do.
Are you happily married?
What?
I mean...
Why did you get married?
Was it trumpets and fireworks?
I got married because Betsy
said we had to break up
or get married. So we got married.
But when you first met her, did you believe
that she was the only person
for you, that in some mystical,
cosmic way
it was fated?
Annie,
when you're attracted
to someone, it means
your subconscious
is attracted to their subconscious,
subconsciously.
What we think of as fate
is just two neuroses
knowing they're a perfect match.
I don't even know him.
I'm having all of
these fantasies about
some man I've never even met,
who lives in Seattle!
It rains nine months of the year in Seattle.
I know. I know.
I do not wanna move to Seattle.
But what I really don't wanna do
is end up always wondering
what might've happened
and knowing I could've done
something. What do you think?
It's just cold feet, isn't it?
Everybody panics
before they get married.
I mean, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Yes, you did.
Thank you very much,
Dennis.
I feel so much better
just having blown this off.
Anytime.
Sandy has a girlfriend,
Glenda. She's a weightlifter.
Her neck isn't bigger than her head...
No, I'm not asking you to set me up.
I don't need your help
with that. I wanna know
what it's like out there.
That's what I'm trying to tell you
what women are looking for:
Pecs and a cute butt.
Like, "He has the cutest butt."
Yeah.
Where did I hear that recently?
Everywhere.
You can't even turn on the news
without hearing some babe
thought some guy's butt was cute.
Who the first woman to
say this was, I don't know,
but somehow it caught on.
So how's my butt?
Not bad.
Really?
Yeah.
Is it cute though?
I don't know.
Are we grading
on a curve?
When was the last time you were out there?
Uh... Uh, uh...
Jimmy Carter, 1978.
Things are a little different now.
First, you have to be friends.
You have to like each other.
Then you neck.
This could go on for years.
Then you have tests,
then you get to do it
with a condom.
The good news is you split the cheque.
I don't think I could let
a woman pay for dinner.
Great! They'll throw a parade
in your honour.
You'll be Man of the Year in Seattle Magazine.
Tiramisu.
What is tiramisu?
You'll find out.
Well, what is it?
You'll see.
Some woman is gonna
want me to do it to her,
and I'm not gonna know.
You'll love it.
Oh, this is gonna be tough.
Tough, tough. It's gonna be
much tougher than I thought.
What about that decorator on the Bennett job?
Victoria?
Yeah. She's perky.
Oh, no, I don't...
What?
I'm far away from that.
What? No.
I'm just assembling notes. I'm not...
Notes.
How would I do that?
What do you mean? Call her up.
You say, "Come,
let's get together.
We'll look at swatches."
Call her on the phone to say,
"Let's look at swatches"?
Yeah, you know, colour schemes.
She's not gonna see through that?
No, you don't do it
like I do it. You do it
in your own suave way.
Think Cary Grant.
Cary Grant would call up
and say, "Come over
and look at my swatches"?
How do you know?
Maybe he did.
He didn't do it in the movies.
Gunga Din? He didn't call...?
Gunga Din is not a swatch kind of movie.
Who knows what he did in real life.
He did that with Dyan Cannon?
Yeah, sure.
[IMITATES CARY GRANT]
"Hello, Dyan!
Take a look at these swatches."
Jonah, I'm home!
Hey, Jonah!
Jonah?
Hey, Jonah.
Hi, Dad. This is Jessica.
Well, it's nice to meet you, Jessica.
JONAH:
Dad, this is amazing.
If you play this backwards,
it says "Paul is dead."
Yeah, yeah. I know.
How do you know?
Dad, could you shut the door?
Sure. Sure.
H and G.
Hi and goodbye.
[GENE AUTRY'S "BACK IN
THE SADDLE AGAIN" PLAYS]
♪ I'm back in the saddle again ♪
♪ Out where a friend is a friend ♪
♪ Where the longhorn cattle feed ♪
♪ On the lowly gypsum weed ♪
♪ Back in the saddle again ♪
♪ Ridin' the range once more ♪
♪ Totin' my old.44 ♪
♪ Where you sleep out every night ♪
Hello, Victoria?
[CLEARS THROAT]
This is Sam Baldwin.
I don't know if you
remember me, but...
Oh, great.
Hi. Uh...
I was wondering if, uh...
If you would like to have a drink with me?
Dinner?
Dinner would be even better.
Friday would be great, yeah.
How...? I hear
that's a good place.
7:30 would be fine.
And I'll, uh...
Okay, I'll meet you there.
Okay. All right.
Um... So it's Friday
at 7:30 for dinner.
Great.
Me too. Bye.
♪ Back in the saddle again ♪♪
[TYPEWRITER CLICKING]
Are you in love with him?
I'm not now.
Now those were the days
when people knew
how to be in love.
You're a basket case.
They knew it.
Time, distance,
nothing could separate them
because they knew.
It was right. It was real. It was...
It's a movie.
That's your problem.
You don't wanna be in love.
You wanna be in love in a movie.
Read it to me.
"Dear Sleepless and Son.
I've never written a letter
like this in my life..."
That's what everyone
writes at the beginning
of letters to strangers.
I know that.
You think I don't
know that?
What about Walter?
Oh, Walter.
Oh, I'd give anything to marry Walter.
He's so unexpected.
You think you can tell
what he's like by just looking
at him, but you can't.
I should write something in this about magic.
What?
Something! What if I never meet him?
What if this man is my destiny,
and I never meet him?
Your destiny
can be your doom.
Look at me and Rick.
"I want to meet you"...
GRANT:
Top of the Empire State Building.
On the top of the Empire State Building.
Sunset, Valentine's Day.
I'll be in New
York with Walter.
I can squeeze it in.
I'll be in New York with Walter!
Do you wanna hear about destiny?
If I hadn't married Martin
I never would've bought
the house with
the dead tree.
On account of which I got divorced.
On account of which
I hit a car and met Rick
while buying a neck brace.
Wait a minute. You never
told me you got a divorce
because of a dead tree?
The tree man.
You fell in love with the tree man?
I did not say "love."
Did I say "love"?
This is my favourite part.
It's now or never.
Never is a frightening word.
We'd be fools to let happiness pass us by.
KERR:
Uh-huh.
Winter must be cold
for those with
no warm memories.
We've already missed the spring.
GRANT: Yes.
Men never get this movie.
I know.
JONAH:
Mummy! Mummy!
Mummy!
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm here. I'm coming.
Dad!
It's all right. It's okay.
It's okay.
Hey, it's all right.
What was that about, huh?
It was sinking.
What was?
Our house.
There was water coming in all the windows.
Oh.
Well, it's okay now.
So, what should we do?
Your mother used to
sing to you when you
had bad dreams.
"Bye Bye Blackbird."
Yeah.
I miss her.
What do you think happens
to someone after they die?
I don't know.
Like, do you believe in heaven?
I never did.
Or the whole idea
of an afterlife.
But now, I don't know.
Because I have these dreams
about your mum.
Yeah. And we have long talks.
About you.
How you're doing.
Which she sort of knows, but I tell her anyway.
So, what is that?
It's sort of an afterlife, isn't it?
I'm starting to forget her.
She could peel an apple
in one long, curly strip.
[JOE COCKER'S
"BYE BYE BLACKBIRD" PLAYS]
The whole apple.
♪ Pack up all my cares and woes ♪
♪ Feeling low ♪
♪ Here I go ♪
♪ I said bye ♪
♪ Bye ♪
I love you, Jonah.
I love you, Dad.
♪ Where somebody waits for me ♪
BECKY:
See you tomorrow.
♪ Sugar sweet so is she ♪
♪ Bye ♪
♪ I said bye ♪
♪ Blackbird ♪
♪ No one seems to love ♪
♪ Or understand me ♪
♪ And all the hard luck stories ♪
♪ They keep handing me ♪
♪ Where somebody shines the light ♪
♪ I'm be coming on home tonight ♪
♪ Bye, bye ♪
♪ I wanna say ♪
♪ Blackbird ♪
♪ Lord have mercy ♪
♪ Wait for me darling, yeah ♪♪
[PHONE BEEPING]
Laurie?
Hi, it's Annie.
Fine, fine. I'm fine.
Listen, I'm doing an article
on call-in radio shows.
Do you know anyone who works
for someone named
Dr. Marcia Fieldstone?
I'm a writer for the Baltimore Sun,
and a friend of Laurie Johnson's.
I'm doing a piece on how people
handle bereavement.
And I understand you had
a caller the other night,
some guy from Seattle.
JONAH [ON MACHINE]:
This is Jonah Baldwin.
We're not in right now, but you can...
Baldwin.
[♪♪♪]
Architect.
Psst.
SAM: Okay, Clarise.
I'm gonna be back either by
midnight or 8:30,
if disaster strikes.
Here's one for the both of us.
"Sleepless and Son, Baltimore."
If there's any problem,
here's the number
to the paediatrician.
Here's a bottle of Ipecac
if anybody drinks poison.
It's right next to the juice glasses.
Fine.
How do I look?
Great.
Do I look okay? I look all right?
I look stupid. I
look stupid. I look like
I'm trying too hard.
I was gonna get a haircut,
but I'd just look like
I got a haircut.
This is a good letter, Dad.
The heels on these are grotesque.
I look like I'm trying to be tall.
Her name is Annie Reed.
SAM: Now I'm late. Bye.
Dad, read this.
Read this!
"Sleepless and Son...
[MUMBLING]
I've been an excellent
third baseman, and while
we're on it, let's just say right now:
Brooks Robinson
was the best
third-base men ever.
It's important you agree
with me on that because
I'm from Baltimore."
She thinks Brooks
Robinson is the greatest.
So do you.
Everyone thinks so.
It's a sign.
Come here.
I'll show you a sign.
Here's a sign.
All right.
Where's Seattle?
Right. Where is Baltimore?
Ah! It's right there! Look!
One, two, three.
There's, like, 26 states between
here and there. Now, that's a sign.
I'm out of here. Goodbye!
Good night! I love you.
Clarise, did you move your car?
Huh?
[SAM GRUMBLES]
Thank you, Derrick.
You're welcome.
I'll have...
White wine spritzer?
Yes.
And you, sir?
I'm fine. Thank you.
Hi.
You look good.
You look good yourself.
I thought you'd never call me.
You did?
I really wanted you to.
And I thought you were never going to.
MAN: Excuse me, Mr. Baldwin?
Yes.
There's a phone call for you.
Excuse me.
Thank you. Hello.
JONAH: Dad, can we go to
New York City
for Valentine's Day?
What?
Annie Reed from Baltimore
wants to meet us at the top
of the Empire State Building
on Valentine's Day.
Jonah?
What?
Have you fallen down?
Are you bleeding?
Is Clarise there?
Has she been strangled?
No.
This is the only reason for this call?
If we book now, we can get an excursion fare.
Jessica's parents are travel agents...
I'm not having this conversation.
We'll talk about it at a later time.
I can't believe
this conversation has lasted
this long. You go to bed.
Everything all right?
Oh, yeah.
Do you have kids?
No.
Do you want mine?
[LAUGHS]
I'll have an Absolut straight up, please.
[VICTORIA LAUGHING]
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
Hey, hey! Put that down.
Stop it!
There she is.
JONAH: Why is she bringing
those groceries?
She's gonna cook us something
so be prepared.
Hi, Sam. Thanks.
Thanks. And let me guess.
You must be Jonah.
Hi.
So this it?
Yeah.
The car's down this way.
Great.
She's on her sixth painter
and we are never going
to finish this job.
Now she wants the fireplace rebricked.
I know her.
I could give her a call.
No, I've got it solved.
I'll just hit her with
one of those bricks.
[VICTORIA LAUGHING]
That's so funny.
You're so funny.
When she wants something
done she says, "Oh, I don't know.
I'm stupid. You know what's best.
But couldn't we flip the house
around so that everything in
the back is now in front?
And could the whole front
of the house open on a hinge
so I can get in with a garage opener."
"Yes, we can. We'll just..."
"Move the kitchen cabinets."
Hey, Jonah,
bring some of that stuff
around, all right?
Do you like baseball?
Yes, I do. In fact my firm
has box seats to the Mariners.
Why don't we all go some time.
Hey!
What about camping?
What about it?
Do you like camping?
I went camping once.
You know, Dad, we should
start camping more often.
You're right. Camping is good.
Time for bed.
It's only 10:00.
Yeah, 10:00. Time for bed.
Good night.
Hey, don't you wanna
thank Victoria for
this delicious dinner?
Thanks for dinner.
I never saw anybody
cook potatoes that way.
I'm glad you liked it.
Good night, Jonah.
Yeah, we don't see a lot
of potatoes around here.
We're rice men.
[♪♪♪]
[VICTORIA LAUGHING]
VICTORIA:
Oh, God.
[PHONE RINGING]
Oh! Oh!
Ow.
I'm sorry, Walter.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
BECKY: Turn on your radio.
What?
The kid is on.
You've got me
listening to this garbage.
Go, turn it on.
Who is it?
It's Becky. She's having
trouble with Rick again.
I'll go downstairs.
Becky, I'll call you back.
I'm sorry, Walter.
Are you bleeding?
[WALTER GRUNTS AND GROANS]
[WHEEZES]
[♪♪♪]
JONAH:
He's kissing her right this minute!
FIELDSTONE:
Oh, really?
Jonah, tell the truth:
Are you spying on your father?
Who is he kissing?
JONAH: I have to make them stop.
How will I explain this to Walter?
JONAH:
She came over and cooked dinner.
She brought two bags of
groceries like she was
staying here for a year!
FIELDSTONE: Jonah, it's good
that your father's dating.
It's just hard on you.
It's something you think you want,
but then when it happens,
it scares you.
JONAH:
That's not true.
FIELDSTONE:
Okay, now think.
Shouldn't your father be
the judge of whether someone
is right or wrong for him?
JONAH:
He's not sane enough
to judge anything.
Now he's kissing her on the lips.
My dad's been captured by a ho!
What am I going to do?
FIELDSTONE: Jonah, calm down.
Tomorrow, when you're
sitting down to breakfast,
tell him how you feel.
It's not good to keep
your feelings inside you.
[SCREAMS]
Miss Scarlet.
In the broom closet.
With the radio.
Walter, you scared me.
Don't ever do that again.
I thought I saw a black widow spider.
You scared me to death.
You scared Victoria to death.
It was right over there.
Next time you think you see
a black widow spider
I want you to say:
"Dad, excuse me,
but I believe a poisonous insect
is in the house."
And I will calmly come
and take care of it. You scream
like that again, I'll kill you.
Becky heard this guy
on the radio, she was
sure it was Rick.
She was completely hysterical.
And then it turned out
the guy lived in Duluth.
Where's Duluth?
That doesn't make any sense.
I know. I know, Walter.
It doesn't make any sense at all.
Thank God my life is in place.
Duluth? That's in North Dakota.
[♪♪♪]
I love this letter.
You have to write to her.
You think so?
It's Y-O-H.
Yeah. What's that?
Your only hope.
[♪♪♪]
I thought I would look into doing
a story on those radio shows.
You'd have to go somewhere
to really look into them.
Definitely.
Couldn't you do a phone interview?
Not for the kind of piece I wanna do.
I won't be in Chicago long.
When you get back, I'll be gone.
Then I'll see you in New York.
I'll get it.
PILOT [OVER PA]:
This is Captain Browning.
We're cruising at 35,000 feet.
The weather is clear to the west
and we'll be in Seattle on schedule.
Don't you hate flying?
Yes, I do.
And I've just told the most terrible
one to the man I'm about to marry.
Do you feel that any lie is a betrayal?
I said flying.
Oh.
[SIGHS]
Thanks for bringing me here.
Well, he likes the planes.
Can I bring something
back for you? A souvenir?
Does he like those little snow globes?
You know, you shake them up
and then the snow floats down.
Sure, I'd really like that.
Thank you so much.
He's 8.
He's good at it.
I've read an article about
this. Children are hideous
at the age of 8.
It's quite normal.
Well...
Maybe when I come back, the two of us
ought to spend some time
together on our own.
What do you think?
Bye. Bye, Jonah.
Bye.
Jonah.
Listen to me.
You don't know Victoria.
I hardly know her myself.
She's, in fact, a mystery to me.
She tosses her hair a lot.
Why does she do this?
I have no idea. Is it a twitch?
Does she need a haircut?
Could she use a barrette
to keep her hair out of her face?
These are the things I'm
willing to get to the bottom of.
That is why I am dating her.
That's all I'm doing.
I'm not living with her.
I'm not marrying her.
Can you appreciate the difference?
This is what single people do.
They try other people on
and see how they fit.
But everybody's an adjustment.
Nobody's perfect.
There's no such thing as a perfect...
[♪♪♪]
Come on.
Dad, I was talking to
Jessica about reincarnation.
She says you knew Annie in another life.
SAM: Who's Annie?
The one who wrote us.
But Jessica says, you and Annie
never got together in that life.
So your hearts are like
puzzles with missing pieces.
And when you get together,
the puzzle's complete.
Goddamn it.
The reason I know this and you don't,
is because I'm younger and
pure, so I'm more in touch
with cosmic forces.
Who told you this stuff?
Jessica.
I sincerely hope you're not marrying Jessica.
[HARRY CONNICK, JR.'S
"A WINK AND A SMILE" PLAYS]
♪ I remember the days ♪
♪ Of just keeping time ♪
♪ Of hanging around ♪
♪ In sleepy towns forever ♪
♪ Back roads empty for miles ♪
♪ Well, you can't have a dream ♪
♪ And cut it to fit ♪
♪ But when I saw you, I knew ♪
♪ We'd go together ♪
♪ Like a wink and a smile ♪
♪ Leave your old jalopy ♪
♪ By the railroad track ♪
♪ We'll get a hip double-dip tip-toppy ♪
♪ Two-seat Pontiac ♪
♪ So you can rev her up ♪
♪ Don't go slow ♪
♪ It's only green lights and all rights ♪
♪ Let's go together ♪
♪ With a wink and a smile ♪
♪ Give me a wink and a smile ♪
♪ We go together ♪
♪ Like a wink and a smile ♪
♪ Now my heart is music ♪
♪ Such a simple song ♪
♪ Sing it again ♪
♪ The notes never end ♪
♪ This is where I belong ♪
♪ Just the sound of your voice ♪
♪ The light in your eyes ♪
♪ We're so far away from yesterday ♪
♪ Together with a wink and a smile ♪
♪ We go together ♪
♪ Like a wink and a smile ♪♪
ANNIE:
I watched him play with
his son at the beach.
BECKY [ON PHONE]:
Did you talk to him?
Couldn't do it.
How did I get here?
You told a lie and got on a plane.
That's not what I mean.
I'm going back over there tomorrow
and talk to him. I am.
Okay. Good. Goodbye.
Beck.
What?
Is this crazy?
No, that's the weirdest part about it.
Thank you. I love you.
I love you too.
Good night.
Bye.
[♪♪♪]
[GIGGLING]
It's so good to see you.
Where's Greg?
[HORN HONKING]
[♪♪♪]
Hello.
[HORN HONKING]
BECKY: So then what happened?
ANNIE: So then I left, obviously.
You were standing in the middle of the street?
You know that dream when you're
walking down the street naked
and everyone is looking at you.
I love that dream.
That was nothing compared
to this humiliation. Nothing!
But he saw you, right?
He saw me.
You were face to face.
He said hello.
And what did you say?
And all I could say was hello.
Oh, my God.
KERR: All I could say was hello.
It's a sign.
It's a sign that I have watched
this movie too many times.
So stupid! From the minute
I listened to that stupid programme
on the radio, I've been a complete jerk.
You are not a jerk.
Thank you. An idiot!
You don't know who she was, Annie.
I saw her. I have a picture of her.
I'll show you a picture of her.
That detective in Seattle
sent me a picture of her.
Here! See, that's
exactly what she looks like.
This is a picture of someone's back.
Well, it's her and he was crazy about her.
What's this?
This is from Seattle.
Becky.
So I mailed your letter.
"Dear Annie.
Thanks for your letter.
It was great.
You sound neat.
We're very excited about meeting
you in New York on Valentine's Day
and seeing if we are...
M-F-E-O.
See you soon.
Sleepless in Seattle."
M-F-E-O?
Made for each other.
It's cute. It's like a little clue.
[SCREAMS]
So he can't write. Big deal.
Verbal ability is a highly
overrated thing in a guy.
And our pathetic need
for it is what gets us
into so much trouble.
I'm going to run back
to Walter's arms,
if he'll still have me.
What about the letter?
It's nothing. It was written before
I went out there. Before the ho.
The only thing is, she didn't look like a ho.
She looked like
somebody we would
have been friends with.
Ugh!
You saw her in the airport and then here?
And I tried to talk to her.
It was like I knew her
or something. It was weird.
You mean like a déjà-vu thing?
It was very French déjà-vu-ish
kind of thing. Oui?
Oui. At least you're out there seeing
people again. That's terrific.
Well, I mean, there's really just the one.
Victoria.
You don't like Victoria?
She laughs like a hyena.
Is this true?
No!
Sort of. Yeah, a little bit.
But, tell them what you did.
Dad...
SAM: Tell them about the radio show.
Go ahead.
Dad...
They wanna hear it.
Go ahead. Tell them.
Tell them.
Christmas Eve, he phones in
one of those radio call-in shows.
And tells them I need a new wife.
Oh, you're kidding.
That's so sweet.
Now he's obsessed with
this one woman who wrote me.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
She wants to meet me
at the top of Empire
State Building.
On Valentine's Day.
It's like that movie.
What movie?
An Affair to Remember.
Did you ever see it?
Oh, God. Cary Grant
and Deborah Kerr.
Is that "Karr" or "Kerr"?
Kerr.
Karr.
Okay. She's gonna meet him
at the top of the Empire
State Building.
Only she got hit by a taxi.
And he waited and waited.
And it was raining, I think.
And then she's too proud
to tell him that she's...
crippled. And he's too proud
to find out why she doesn't come.
But he comes to see her anyway.
And I forget why, but...
Oh, it's so amazing when he comes to see her.
Because he doesn't even notice
that she doesn't get up to say hello.
And he's very bitter.
You think he's just going
to walk out the door
and never know why.
She's just lying there, you know.
Like, on the couch with this
blanket over her shrivelled
little legs.
And...
Are you all right?
She's fine.
And suddenly, he goes, "I saw the painting"
And he, like, goes to the bedroom.
And he looks, and he comes out and looks at her.
And he kind of just...
They know and hug and it's so...
That's a chick's movie.
I would say so.
What kind of a person would write
to someone they heard on the radio?
I got hundreds of letters
from women all over the country.
Desperate women.
Just because someone is looking
for a nice guy, it doesn't make
them desperate.
How about rapacious
and love-starved?
No.
It's easier to be killed
by a terrorist than to
find a husband
after the age of 40...
That is absolutely untrue!
Right, honey. Right.
Well, I'm not looking
for a mail-order bride.
I just want somebody
that I can have a decent
conversation with over dinner.
You know, without it falling down
into weepy tears over some movie
that she just saw.
She's very emotional.
Although, I cried at the end of The Dirty Dozen.
Well, who didn't?
Jim Brown was throwing
these hand grenades down these air shafts.
And Richard Jaeckel and
Lee Marvin we sitting on top
of this armoured personnel carrier.
They were dressed up like Nazis.
And it was...
Trini Lopez...
He busted his neck when
they were parachuting down
behind the Nazi lines.
Stop it!
Richard Jaeckel, at the beginning,
he had on a shiny helmet,
because he was an MP.
Please, no more.
God, I love that movie.
[MUSIC PLAYS ON TV]
This is the best movie
I've ever seen in my life.
What's so great about it?
You have to find her, Jonah.
You have to go to her.
Do you know how much money
it costs to go to New York?
Nobody knows.
It changes practically every day.
How much money do you have?
80 dollars.
I have 42. That'll probably cover cabs.
But how would I get there?
Honey, I have to run these
tickets over to someone.
Can you keep an eye on things
out front till I get back?
Sure, Mum.
You want a window seat or aisle?
Window.
You want a fruit plate?
I don't know. Do I?
I'd rather die than eat airplane food.
I'm telling them you're 12
so you can fly unaccompanied
and the stewardess
won't carry you around
and stuff like that.
Are you crazy?
Who'd believe I'm 12?
If it's in the computer,
they'll believe anything.
Are you sure?
Do you want me to say that you're
really, really short for your age,
and they shouldn't say anything
because it would hurt your feelings?
Yeah. That's a great idea!
[TAMMY WYNETTE'S
"STAND BY YOUR MAN" PLAYS]
♪ Sometimes it's hard to be a woman ♪
♪ Giving all your love to just one man ♪
Walter.
You're gonna miss the train.
No, I'm not.
I'm so happy, Becky.
Finally, I feel happy.
This is right. This is real.
Everything else is what happens
when you watch too many movies.
And you completely lose sight of what counts.
Please, don't tell anybody what happened.
Because I would be so
absolutely mortified if
anyone knew I did anything
even remotely close to what I have done.
Thank you, thank you.
Do you promise?
I promise.
Sleepless in Seattle is history.
♪ ... hard to understand ♪
♪ And if you love him ♪
♪ Oh, be proud of him ♪
♪ 'Cause after all he's just a man ♪
♪ Stand by your man ♪♪
I was just...
Go ahead.
No, you go.
Okay. Well, I was just gonna
say that ever since Christmas...
you've been different,
kind of distracted, distant.
But now it feels as if
you're coming back
from wherever you were.
I am.
I was just...
I just... I just got...
I think I got nervous.
But that's normal, right?
I mean, don't you ever
feel nervous about... you know?
What?
Forever.
No.
Well...
I did.
And... You know what
I think? I think I thought
it was too perfect, you know.
I started to wonder if
we were the human equivalent
of two rights making a wrong.
You know what it was?
It was like kismet, but not,
if you see what I mean.
You have to grow up.
You just can't keep
having all these adolescent
fantasies about...
how exciting life is gonna be.
Don't hate me, but I love this pattern.
You couldn't.
I do.
This is just like my grandmother's china.
How many place settings?
Ten.
[CHUCKLES]
Exactly. Eight is too few,
twelve is
BOTH:
Too many.
Walter.
It was my mother's.
I had them size it down.
She had really fat fingers.
It's so beautiful.
It's exactly what I'd pick out
if I had every ring in the whole
world to choose from.
You see what I mean?
There are people who
would like a relationship
to be full of surprises,
but I am not one
of those people.
No, siree.
Surprises are highly overrated.
SAM: I'm leaving first thing
in the morning,
but I'm only gonna be gone one night.
Clarise is gonna be here.
So you'll be able to see plenty
of Geraldo and Nightmare on
Elm Street 12. I will never know.
Are you going with her?
I'm going with Victoria, yes.
Don't try anything tricky.
Understand?
[DOOR SLAMS]
Don't go rolling in poison ivy
as soon as I leave the house.
Or lock yourself in the closet
or do anything that makes
you need stitches.
If your finger falls off, it's staying off.
No one's gonna pack it on
ice and take you to hospital,
so that you can be a
breakthrough in laser surgery.
Is this about that woman in Baltimore?
Annie.
I don't care what you do!
Good! Fine!
I'll tell you what I'm doing this weekend.
I'm getting laid.
1990s and nobody's getting laid.
I'm the only man
in the America who's getting
laid this weekend.
And I haven't been laid that much.
Six girls in college. Maybe seven.
How long have you been there?
Forever.
What did you hear me just say?
"Six girls in college.
Maybe seven."
Seven. Eight! Mary Kelly.
This is the one I like.
Jonah, the fact is, you're
not gonna like any woman,
because it isn't your mother.
How do you know?
What's wrong with Annie?
Oh, Jonah, shut up!
Shut up? Shut up? Mum
never said shut up to me.
Mum never yelled at me.
This conversation is finished.
Why can't we go to New York?
There is no way that we are going on a plane
to meet some woman
who could be a crazy,
sick lunatic.
Didn't you see Fatal Attraction?
You wouldn't let me.
Well, I saw it!
And it scared the shit out of me.
It scared the shit out of every man in America!
I'm not leaving till you say yes.
I hate you! I hate you!
I hate you!
That's good!
You'll have a lot to tell Oprah
how your dad destroyed your life
because he had to go off for a
weekend special at the Holiday Inn!
[KNOCKING]
Jonah, Clarise is here and I've got to go.
Hey, Jonah.
Jonah?
All right. Jonah, listen,
I've got to go.
Jonah.
Hey, Jonah.
Jonah!
Jessica, honey.
You have tell us where he is.
Jonah's daddy is very upset.
Jessica, this is your father.
Tell us where he is.
Right this minute!
N-Y.
SAM: What is that?
"No way."
That's N-W!
New York. He's on
his way to New York.
What?
How?
United, 597.
JESSICA'S MOTHER: Jessica.
When does it leave?
Seven thirty.
[CUCKOO CLOCK CHIMES]
[♪♪♪]
Here you go.
Here's a nice pin for you
for flying with us.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Can I take this for you?
No.
Where to, kid?
Empire State Building.
Hold on.
Get a little further away
from the curb next time, mac.
There it is. What are you going
to do up there? Spit off the top?
No, I'm going to meet my new mother.
Excuse me. I'm Jonah.
Are you Annie?
No, I'm Cynthia.
Excuse me, are you Annie?
Great table. Thanks.
Is something wrong?
Can I get you a drink?
Some champagne?
Fine. Fine.
Can we have a bottle of Dom DeLuise.
[CHUCKLING]
Just kidding.
It was a joke.
He meant Dom Perignon.
I got it.
Ohh. Beautiful view.
Walter...
There's something
I have to tell you.
[♪♪♪]
Hey! Sorry, I have an emergency.
[SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
SAM:
Money, money, money, see?
[♪♪♪]
So he could be on top of
the Empire State Building now?
No.
I guess he could be.
It's not him, Walter. It's me.
I can't do this.
Look, Annie, I love you.
But let's leave that out of this.
I don't want to be someone
that you're settling for.
that anyone settles for.
Marriage is hard enough
without bringing such low
expectations into it.
Isn't it?
Walter, I don't deserve you.
No, I wouldn't put it that way.
But okay.
You okay?
Yeah.
[SIGHS]
[GASPS]
What?
Look.
[♪♪♪]
It's a sign.
Who needed a sign?
Walter, I have to go.
[SIREN WAILING]
[WHISTLES]
Jonah!
Dad! Dad!
Jonah?
[♪♪♪]
What if something happened to you?
What if I couldn't get to you?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
What would I have done?
You are my family.
You're all I've got.
I thought she'd be here.
I thought she'd come.
We're doing okay, aren't we?
I mean, are we okay?
Aren't we all right?
So far, have I done
anything stupid?
No.
Have I screwed it up for the both of us?
[HORNS HONKING]
[♪♪♪]
Observation deck?
Sorry, ma'am, but it's too late.
Oh. No, please.
I really need to get up there.
We're closing up.
No more runs tonight.
Listen...
can I just take a look?
There's someone
I was supposed to meet.
He's probably not there,
but if I don't at least look,
I'll always wonder about it.
Cary Grant, right?
You know that movie?
It's one of my wife's favourites.
Maybe when we get home, we'll get a dog.
JONAH:
Okay.
SAM:
What do you mean, okay?
Wouldn't you like to have a dog?
JONAH: Sure.
I'm sorry, ma'am. Empty.
Can I take a minute?
Go ahead.
[♪♪♪]
I left it by the telescopes.
It's you.
It's me.
I saw you in the street.
Are you Annie?
Yes.
You're Annie?
This must be yours.
I'm Jonah.
This is my dad.
His name is Sam.
Hi, Jonah.
Sam.
And who's this?
Howard.
Oh, Howard. Hello, Howard.
[GUARD CLEARING THROAT]
We'd better go.
Shall we?
[JIMMY DURANTE'S
"MAKE SOMEONE HAPPY" PLAYS]
♪ It's so important ♪
♪ To make someone happy ♪
♪ Make just one someone happy ♪
♪ Make just one heart to heart you ♪
♪ You sing to ♪
Sam, it's nice to meet you.
♪ One face that lights ♪
♪ When it nears you ♪
♪ One girl you're ♪
♪ You're everything to ♪
♪ Fail if you win it ♪
♪ Comes and goes in a minute ♪
♪ Where's the real stuff in life ♪
♪ To cling to ♪
♪ Love is the answer ♪
♪ Someone to love is the answer ♪
♪ Once you've found her ♪
♪ Build your world around her ♪
♪ Make someone happy ♪
♪ Make just one someone happy ♪
♪ And you will be happy too ♪♪
[CELINE DION & CLIVE GRIFFIN'S
"WHEN I FALL IN LOVE" PLAYS]
♪ When I fall in love ♪
♪ It will be forever ♪
♪ Or I'll never fall in love ♪
♪ I'll never, never fall in love ♪
♪ In a restless world ♪
♪ Like this is ♪
♪ Love is ended before it's begun ♪
♪ And too many ♪
♪ Moonlight kisses ♪
♪ Seem to cool ♪
♪ In the warmth of the sun ♪
♪ When I give my heart ♪
♪ It will be completely ♪
♪ Or I'll never give my heart ♪
♪ And the moment I can feel ♪
♪ That you feel that way too ♪
♪ Is when I fall in love ♪
♪ When I fall in love ♪
♪ With you ♪♪
[LOUIS ARMSTRONG'S "A KISS
TO BUILD A DREAM ON" PLAYS]
♪ Give me a kiss ♪
♪ To build on and my imagination ♪
♪ Will thrive upon that kiss ♪
♪ Sweetheart I ask no more than this, ♪
♪ A kiss to build a dream on ♪
♪ Give me a kiss ♪
♪ Before you leave me ♪
♪ And my imagination ♪
♪ Will feed my hungry heart ♪
♪ Leave me one thing before we part ♪
♪ A kiss to build a dream on ♪