1
00:00:00,984 --> 00:00:02,262
Previously on Suits...

2
00:00:02,263 --> 00:00:04,818
What I want is to work
at Pearson Specter

3
00:00:04,842 --> 00:00:05,789
and to keep seeing you.

4
00:00:05,790 --> 00:00:07,401
Those two things are not
both gonna happen.

5
00:00:07,425 --> 00:00:08,902
You've been here
for three months.

6
00:00:08,926 --> 00:00:10,955
All you've done is hit singles,
and I need a goddamn home run.

7
00:00:10,979 --> 00:00:12,095
- Jonathan, listen...
- I don't want to hear it.

8
00:00:12,113 --> 00:00:13,541
Start making us some real money.

9
00:00:13,565 --> 00:00:15,242
A man like Walter Gillis

10
00:00:15,266 --> 00:00:17,244
isn't gonna listen
to a guy like you,

11
00:00:17,268 --> 00:00:19,630
offering to save him
with sunshine and rainbows.

12
00:00:19,654 --> 00:00:21,915
Walter, I can't guarantee you
we'll win,

13
00:00:21,939 --> 00:00:25,442
but I can guarantee you
that I will never sell you out.

14
00:00:25,460 --> 00:00:27,421
All right, I'm in.

15
00:00:27,445 --> 00:00:28,445
You're talking hostile takeover.

16
00:00:28,463 --> 00:00:29,590
Gillis industries...

17
00:00:29,614 --> 00:00:30,947
Logan, we have a conflict.

18
00:00:30,965 --> 00:00:32,282
You're either with me
or against me.

19
00:00:32,300 --> 00:00:34,761
That includes all $1 billion
of my business.

20
00:00:34,785 --> 00:00:37,931
Get moving on drawing up a
tender offer for Logan Sanders.

21
00:00:37,955 --> 00:00:39,266
Do you remember when I told you

22
00:00:39,290 --> 00:00:42,736
that I once had an affair
with a married man?

23
00:00:42,760 --> 00:00:44,862
It was him.

24
00:00:48,566 --> 00:00:50,077
You're up early.

25
00:00:50,101 --> 00:00:52,079
So are you.

26
00:00:52,103 --> 00:00:53,914
Well, I have to be. You don't.

27
00:00:53,938 --> 00:00:58,118
I was already awake. Thinking.

28
00:00:58,142 --> 00:00:59,503
About last night?
Look, Mike, I...

29
00:00:59,527 --> 00:01:02,339
it's okay. I'm good.

30
00:01:02,363 --> 00:01:05,148
You're good with me working
on the takeover with Logan?

31
00:01:05,166 --> 00:01:06,760
Why do you not
seem to believe me?

32
00:01:06,784 --> 00:01:08,318
Because you weren't good
last night.

33
00:01:08,336 --> 00:01:09,730
Which was before this morning

34
00:01:09,754 --> 00:01:13,467
when I realized that
that's work.

35
00:01:13,491 --> 00:01:14,991
This isn't.

36
00:01:17,178 --> 00:01:21,108
So as long as we don't let
that affect this...

37
00:01:21,132 --> 00:01:22,499
We won't.

38
00:01:22,517 --> 00:01:25,529
In that case, let's set
some in-home ground rules.

39
00:01:25,553 --> 00:01:27,414
Obviously, the first...

40
00:01:27,438 --> 00:01:29,650
Uh, respecting
each other's privacy.

41
00:01:29,674 --> 00:01:30,784
Exactly.

42
00:01:30,808 --> 00:01:32,419
The left-hand side of the desk
belongs

43
00:01:32,443 --> 00:01:33,843
to the United Nation of Ross.

44
00:01:33,861 --> 00:01:37,208
- You're not a nation.
- I have a flag.

45
00:01:37,232 --> 00:01:38,792
Fine.

46
00:01:38,816 --> 00:01:41,378
As long as we agree
that any perusal of my phone

47
00:01:41,402 --> 00:01:44,354
is considered a breach
of my borders.

48
00:01:44,372 --> 00:01:45,689
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.

49
00:01:45,707 --> 00:01:47,857
I thought you liked it
when I breached your borders.

50
00:01:47,875 --> 00:01:51,838
Mm, well, those are
different kind of borders.

51
00:01:51,862 --> 00:01:54,007
In that case,
a breach is allowed.

52
00:01:54,031 --> 00:01:57,367
- Allowed?
- Encouraged.

53
00:01:57,385 --> 00:02:01,037
- Requested.
- Demanded.

54
00:02:01,055 --> 00:02:03,734
Let's go make you late for work.

55
00:02:03,758 --> 00:02:07,020
Mm.

56
00:02:07,044 --> 00:02:08,822
Jessica, I am telling you.

57
00:02:08,846 --> 00:02:10,658
The S.E.C. is gonna send
Jeff Malone after us,

58
00:02:10,682 --> 00:02:13,883
and nobody is better suited
to beat him down than...

59
00:02:13,901 --> 00:02:15,051
You guessed it

60
00:02:15,069 --> 00:02:17,581
because we all know that

61
00:02:17,605 --> 00:02:21,034
this is better than this,

62
00:02:21,058 --> 00:02:23,870
which will result in this,

63
00:02:23,894 --> 00:02:27,675
which will also result in this

64
00:02:27,699 --> 00:02:30,233
and this

65
00:02:30,251 --> 00:02:33,903
and this.

66
00:02:33,921 --> 00:02:35,905
And what do I want in return?

67
00:02:35,923 --> 00:02:40,187
Oh, you know what I want.

68
00:02:40,211 --> 00:02:42,189
You've always known.

69
00:02:42,213 --> 00:02:44,057
And after I win,

70
00:02:44,081 --> 00:02:48,084
you'll not only be willing
to give it to me.

71
00:02:48,102 --> 00:02:53,334
You're gonna be begging
to give it to me.

72
00:02:53,358 --> 00:02:55,692
Ha!

73
00:02:58,563 --> 00:02:59,707
- Louis.
- B... not now.

74
00:02:59,731 --> 00:03:01,742
- Louis, I have to talk to you.
- B... not now.

75
00:03:01,766 --> 00:03:03,099
How many times have I told you?

76
00:03:03,117 --> 00:03:05,296
Unless you have photoshopped
my head onto a dragon,

77
00:03:05,320 --> 00:03:06,964
do not interrupt me
while I'm perfecting my pitch.

78
00:03:06,988 --> 00:03:08,549
Your pitch doesn't need
to be perfect.

79
00:03:08,573 --> 00:03:09,583
It needs to be now.

80
00:03:09,607 --> 00:03:10,940
- Why?
- Malone is here.

81
00:03:10,958 --> 00:03:13,520
- He's here?
- In the lobby.

82
00:03:13,544 --> 00:03:14,865
And Jessica just asked
to see you.

83
00:03:14,879 --> 00:03:16,923
Oh, out of my way.

84
00:03:16,947 --> 00:03:19,259
Aren't... aren't you going
to bring your easel?

85
00:03:19,283 --> 00:03:22,252
Oh, I don't need an easel
to kick this sucker's ass.

86
00:03:25,139 --> 00:03:27,434
Jessica.

87
00:03:27,458 --> 00:03:30,937
Jessica, I got your message,
and I just wanted to...

88
00:03:30,961 --> 00:03:32,773
Louis, this is Jeff Malone.

89
00:03:32,797 --> 00:03:35,632
Yeah, I know who he is.
He's with the S.E.C.

90
00:03:35,650 --> 00:03:38,412
He was until this morning.

91
00:03:38,436 --> 00:03:39,969
We brought him over
because we have reason

92
00:03:39,987 --> 00:03:41,498
to believe
they'll be coming after us.

93
00:03:41,522 --> 00:03:43,083
Wait, what?

94
00:03:43,107 --> 00:03:44,785
Jeff is
our newest senior partner.

95
00:03:44,809 --> 00:03:50,457
He's going to be taking on
the S.E.C.

96
00:03:50,481 --> 00:03:51,925
Because you suck.

97
00:03:51,949 --> 00:03:54,484
And I wanted to introduce him
to you first

98
00:03:54,502 --> 00:03:56,764
because you're a loser.

99
00:03:56,788 --> 00:04:00,934
Who can get him up to speed
on Felton Securities.

100
00:04:00,958 --> 00:04:06,663
Because you're never
going to be name partner.

101
00:04:06,681 --> 00:04:09,076
And you're both experts
in finance.

102
00:04:09,100 --> 00:04:11,144
Louis, I'm really looking
forward to working with you

103
00:04:11,168 --> 00:04:14,170
on Felton Securities.

104
00:04:15,506 --> 00:04:18,786
Yeah, me too.

105
00:04:18,810 --> 00:04:22,122
You suck. You're a loser.

106
00:04:22,146 --> 00:04:25,209
Louis?

107
00:04:25,233 --> 00:04:27,494
Is there something else?

108
00:04:27,518 --> 00:04:30,687
No.

109
00:04:30,705 --> 00:04:32,122
Nothing.

110
00:04:46,721 --> 00:04:48,148
How long you been
working on that?

111
00:04:48,172 --> 00:04:49,233
Two hours.

112
00:04:49,257 --> 00:04:50,551
You know it's called
a brief, right?

113
00:04:50,575 --> 00:04:52,019
You know
his name's Harvey, right?

114
00:04:52,043 --> 00:04:53,987
You make a compelling argument.

115
00:04:54,011 --> 00:04:55,021
So I got your note.

116
00:04:55,045 --> 00:04:59,215
What do you wanna talk about?
Um...

117
00:04:59,233 --> 00:05:00,216
Logan Sanders.

118
00:05:00,234 --> 00:05:01,361
What about him?

119
00:05:01,385 --> 00:05:05,054
We sort of dated
a few years ago.

120
00:05:05,072 --> 00:05:08,391
Wait, hang on. Define "sort of."

121
00:05:08,409 --> 00:05:11,638
- Definitely.
- Define "dated."

122
00:05:11,662 --> 00:05:13,073
We had an affair
while he was married.

123
00:05:13,097 --> 00:05:14,097
Holy shit.

124
00:05:14,102 --> 00:05:15,426
I know. And I...

125
00:05:15,450 --> 00:05:16,927
Yes, you have to tell Harvey.

126
00:05:16,951 --> 00:05:19,212
Because, Rachel, if there's
two things that Harvey hates,

127
00:05:19,236 --> 00:05:22,716
it's things being kept from him
and things being kept from him.

128
00:05:22,740 --> 00:05:24,651
- I know.
- Then what am I doing here?

129
00:05:24,675 --> 00:05:26,075
I don't know how to tell him.

130
00:05:26,093 --> 00:05:28,689
Quickly, because Logan's
gonna be here in an hour.

131
00:05:28,713 --> 00:05:30,023
What?

132
00:05:30,047 --> 00:05:31,915
And, Rach, it's less important
how you tell Harvey

133
00:05:31,933 --> 00:05:33,560
than that you tell Harvey.

134
00:05:33,584 --> 00:05:36,396
Go.

135
00:05:36,420 --> 00:05:39,500
Okay.

136
00:05:39,524 --> 00:05:42,119
Hmm. These are nice.

137
00:05:42,143 --> 00:05:45,706
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪

138
00:05:45,730 --> 00:05:49,176
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪

139
00:05:49,200 --> 00:05:52,296
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪

140
00:05:52,320 --> 00:05:55,849
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪

141
00:05:55,873 --> 00:05:58,825
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪

142
00:05:58,826 --> 00:06:02,826
♪ Suits 4x02 ♪ Breakfast, Lunch and
Dinner Original Air Date on June 18, 2014

143
00:06:02,827 --> 00:06:04,361
♪ all right

144
00:06:04,382 --> 00:06:09,813
♪ all that time imagine this ♪

145
00:06:09,837 --> 00:06:11,639
♪ The greenback boogie

146
00:06:11,663 --> 00:06:13,663
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man.

147
00:06:19,527 --> 00:06:20,838
I was wondering all day
if you would be...

148
00:06:20,862 --> 00:06:22,089
I can't do this.

149
00:06:22,113 --> 00:06:23,647
What? Rachel...

150
00:06:23,665 --> 00:06:25,649
It's wrong.

151
00:06:25,667 --> 00:06:28,128
Wrong?
You're the one who kissed me.

152
00:06:28,152 --> 00:06:29,930
And I was wrong.

153
00:06:29,954 --> 00:06:31,655
No, you weren't.

154
00:06:31,673 --> 00:06:32,766
My whole life
I've done everything

155
00:06:32,790 --> 00:06:33,830
that I was supposed to do,

156
00:06:33,841 --> 00:06:36,437
and all it did
was make me miserable.

157
00:06:36,461 --> 00:06:39,607
Ever since I met you...

158
00:06:39,631 --> 00:06:42,192
I can't stop thinking about you,
and all I want to do...

159
00:06:42,216 --> 00:06:44,478
Logan... Logan, if we do this,

160
00:06:44,502 --> 00:06:47,003
someone's gonna find out
at some point and then what?

161
00:06:47,021 --> 00:06:51,141
I don't care.

162
00:07:04,706 --> 00:07:07,357
Okay.

163
00:07:07,375 --> 00:07:09,720
Harvey, I need to tell you...

164
00:07:09,744 --> 00:07:11,828
Rachel?

165
00:07:12,880 --> 00:07:16,477
Logan.

166
00:07:16,501 --> 00:07:17,478
Where's Harvey?

167
00:07:17,502 --> 00:07:18,812
I don't know. I'm early.

168
00:07:18,836 --> 00:07:20,704
He doesn't like it when people...

169
00:07:20,722 --> 00:07:24,708
- What are you doing here?
- I'm Harvey's associate.

170
00:07:24,726 --> 00:07:26,487
You did it.
You went to law school.

171
00:07:26,511 --> 00:07:28,789
Not exactly. I'm in law school.

172
00:07:28,813 --> 00:07:30,023
Rachel, that's great.

173
00:07:30,047 --> 00:07:31,381
I'm really proud of you.

174
00:07:31,399 --> 00:07:33,193
I'm just gonna come back.

175
00:07:33,217 --> 00:07:36,830
You came in here to tell him
about us, didn't you?

176
00:07:36,854 --> 00:07:38,415
How'd you know?

177
00:07:38,439 --> 00:07:40,056
It's all over your face.

178
00:07:40,074 --> 00:07:41,558
- Logan...
- Please don't tell him.

179
00:07:41,576 --> 00:07:44,171
I have to tell him.

180
00:07:44,195 --> 00:07:47,508
Rachel...

181
00:07:47,532 --> 00:07:49,065
Do you know what people think

182
00:07:49,083 --> 00:07:51,178
when a son
takes over his father's company?

183
00:07:51,202 --> 00:07:52,680
That his father's proud of him?

184
00:07:52,704 --> 00:07:54,682
That he didn't earn it.

185
00:07:54,706 --> 00:07:56,883
Which is why I'm not looking
to advertise the fact

186
00:07:56,907 --> 00:07:58,602
that I once had an affair.

187
00:07:58,626 --> 00:08:01,438
You're not advertising it.
You're disclosing it to counsel.

188
00:08:01,462 --> 00:08:03,890
Okay, look, you want the truth?

189
00:08:03,914 --> 00:08:06,560
I'm not proud of the way I was
back then.

190
00:08:06,584 --> 00:08:10,447
The way I treated Allison,
the way I treated you.

191
00:08:10,471 --> 00:08:11,949
But I'm not that person anymore,

192
00:08:11,973 --> 00:08:14,118
and I don't want people
to think that I am.

193
00:08:14,142 --> 00:08:16,259
And I understand that,
but I work for Harvey,

194
00:08:16,277 --> 00:08:19,095
and I can't keep things from him
that he needs to know.

195
00:08:19,113 --> 00:08:20,574
- He doesn't need to know this.
- Yes, he does.

196
00:08:20,598 --> 00:08:22,932
Why is that?

197
00:08:22,950 --> 00:08:25,012
Because I happen to live
with the man on the other side

198
00:08:25,036 --> 00:08:28,872
of the takeover battle.

199
00:08:35,112 --> 00:08:37,391
Oh, no.
You need some me time already?

200
00:08:37,415 --> 00:08:39,143
It's not me time.

201
00:08:39,167 --> 00:08:40,894
It's "I'm gonna kick
your ass" time.

202
00:08:40,918 --> 00:08:44,231
I think we both know you only
kick ass after eating a hot dog.

203
00:08:44,255 --> 00:08:46,483
I could be drinking a juice
box and still kick your ass.

204
00:08:46,507 --> 00:08:48,792
I don't think so,
because I have this.

205
00:08:48,810 --> 00:08:51,321
Just read it to me.

206
00:08:51,345 --> 00:08:54,491
"Harvey Specter,
you are summoned to"...

207
00:08:54,515 --> 00:08:56,994
You gotta be kidding me.
You're subpoenaing me?

208
00:08:57,018 --> 00:08:59,213
Oh, yeah. I filed a T.R.O.

209
00:08:59,237 --> 00:09:00,581
I'm gonna block
your tender offer.

210
00:09:00,605 --> 00:09:01,805
Bullshit, you are.

211
00:09:01,823 --> 00:09:03,417
Well, we'll see what the judge
has to say.

212
00:09:03,441 --> 00:09:05,002
Oh, right.
You got your hands full.

213
00:09:05,026 --> 00:09:06,670
Here, let me get that for you.
There you go.

214
00:09:06,694 --> 00:09:08,645
Hearing's at 2:00.
I'll see you then.

215
00:09:08,663 --> 00:09:10,224
Oh, Harvey, the suit...

216
00:09:10,248 --> 00:09:13,483
It's a little dated for court,
don't you think?

217
00:09:15,336 --> 00:09:17,153
Did you get everything
settled with hr?

218
00:09:17,171 --> 00:09:19,349
Yeah.

219
00:09:19,373 --> 00:09:22,325
Corner office.
You really must like me.

220
00:09:22,343 --> 00:09:25,439
Don't get too excited.

221
00:09:25,463 --> 00:09:26,907
You know, the last two partners
that had this office

222
00:09:26,931 --> 00:09:28,308
didn't survive the year.

223
00:09:28,332 --> 00:09:29,999
Then it's a good thing
I'm much better than they were.

224
00:09:30,017 --> 00:09:31,779
You don't even know
who they were.

225
00:09:31,803 --> 00:09:33,336
That doesn't matter, Jessica.
I know who I am.

226
00:09:33,354 --> 00:09:36,673
Me too...
Cocky lawyer in a corner office

227
00:09:36,691 --> 00:09:38,652
who hasn't done a thing
for me yet.

228
00:09:38,676 --> 00:09:41,321
Yet.

229
00:09:41,345 --> 00:09:43,540
By the way, I understand it's
tradition for the name partner

230
00:09:43,564 --> 00:09:44,964
to welcome a new partner
with lunch.

231
00:09:44,982 --> 00:09:48,518
Jeff, when I told you
that our relationship

232
00:09:48,536 --> 00:09:50,831
is now purely professional,
I was serious.

233
00:09:50,855 --> 00:09:53,550
Jessica, what's not
purely professional about lunch?

234
00:09:53,574 --> 00:09:55,886
Unless you mean the sex
that will be following lunch?

235
00:09:55,910 --> 00:09:57,838
Oh, you're not hearing me.

236
00:09:57,862 --> 00:10:00,340
Oh, I'm hearing you.
I'm just ignoring you.

237
00:10:00,364 --> 00:10:02,726
But I promise I won't be
ignoring you at lunch.

238
00:10:02,750 --> 00:10:04,634
Cocky.

239
00:10:12,260 --> 00:10:14,321
Harvey. Harvey, can I talk
to you for a minute?

240
00:10:14,345 --> 00:10:15,572
Yeah, sure, come on in.

241
00:10:15,596 --> 00:10:17,491
I was actually hoping
that we could talk in my office.

242
00:10:17,515 --> 00:10:18,742
What's the... You're early.

243
00:10:18,766 --> 00:10:21,528
- Did you...
- Oh, you two haven't met.

244
00:10:21,552 --> 00:10:23,163
Rachel, Logan. Logan, Rachel.

245
00:10:23,187 --> 00:10:24,665
- I guess you didn't.
- Didn't what?

246
00:10:24,689 --> 00:10:26,222
We actually have met before.

247
00:10:26,240 --> 00:10:28,252
That's why I was trying
to find you.

248
00:10:28,276 --> 00:10:30,087
- To tell me you met our client?
- No.

249
00:10:30,111 --> 00:10:33,229
To tell you that we used to be
in a relationship together.

250
00:10:36,367 --> 00:10:37,544
You looking
to get back together?

251
00:10:37,568 --> 00:10:38,679
Both: No.

252
00:10:38,703 --> 00:10:40,570
- Then I don't give a shit.
- Good.

253
00:10:40,588 --> 00:10:42,599
Then we can move on to why
you didn't tell me that the guy

254
00:10:42,623 --> 00:10:44,768
on the other side of this fight
used to be your associate.

255
00:10:44,792 --> 00:10:46,720
- I was going to.
- When?

256
00:10:46,744 --> 00:10:48,244
In 20 minutes, when you were
scheduled to be here.

257
00:10:48,262 --> 00:10:49,690
Unfortunately,
I have to reschedule.

258
00:10:49,714 --> 00:10:52,058
- Why?
- I have court.

259
00:10:52,082 --> 00:10:53,193
Mike's alleging
I broke privilege.

260
00:10:53,217 --> 00:10:55,195
- Did you?
- Yes, technically,

261
00:10:55,219 --> 00:10:57,030
when I told you to move up
our timeline.

262
00:10:57,054 --> 00:10:58,732
Now, if you'll excuse me.

263
00:10:58,756 --> 00:11:01,591
W-wait a minute.
If you... if you broke privilege,

264
00:11:01,609 --> 00:11:02,930
what are you gonna
tell the judge?

265
00:11:02,944 --> 00:11:04,705
I don't know,
but until I think of something,

266
00:11:04,729 --> 00:11:06,540
I'm going to confuse the shit
out of everyone I can.

267
00:11:06,564 --> 00:11:08,292
That doesn't make any sense.

268
00:11:08,316 --> 00:11:10,744
- It makes total sense.
- No, it doesn't, Your Honor.

269
00:11:10,768 --> 00:11:12,346
All right, hold on.
Let me get this straight.

270
00:11:12,370 --> 00:11:14,581
You work for him?
Worked. I was his associate.

271
00:11:14,605 --> 00:11:16,082
Not the best associate,
Your Honor.

272
00:11:16,106 --> 00:11:17,217
Is that relevant?

273
00:11:17,241 --> 00:11:18,635
No, but I'd like it
on the record.

274
00:11:18,659 --> 00:11:20,888
Well, it's on there now
whether we want it there or not.

275
00:11:20,912 --> 00:11:23,256
And all I'm saying is, there's
no attorney-attorney privilege.

276
00:11:23,280 --> 00:11:24,391
Finally, a fact.

277
00:11:24,415 --> 00:11:25,392
An irrelevant fact,

278
00:11:25,416 --> 00:11:26,760
because at the time
of the conflict,

279
00:11:26,784 --> 00:11:28,595
I was his client.
Not the best client either.

280
00:11:28,619 --> 00:11:31,064
Mr. Specter, shut up.
Now you're his client?

281
00:11:31,088 --> 00:11:33,317
No, I was his client... okay.

282
00:11:33,341 --> 00:11:35,152
I was an associate
at Pearson Specter,

283
00:11:35,176 --> 00:11:36,960
and then I left
to become an investment banker.

284
00:11:36,978 --> 00:11:38,205
It's very confusing.

285
00:11:38,229 --> 00:11:39,462
I'd dismiss the whole motion,
Your Honor.

286
00:11:39,480 --> 00:11:41,992
I said, "shut up."

287
00:11:42,016 --> 00:11:43,466
Are you an attorney
or an investment banker?

288
00:11:43,484 --> 00:11:44,778
I'm an investment banker.

289
00:11:44,802 --> 00:11:46,135
Then what the hell
are you doing in my chambers?

290
00:11:46,153 --> 00:11:47,915
Acting as my own attorney.

291
00:11:47,939 --> 00:11:50,250
And no matter how much he tries
to confuse the issue, he can't.

292
00:11:50,274 --> 00:11:52,719
I told him I was going
after the same company he was,

293
00:11:52,743 --> 00:11:54,721
and he used that knowledge
to move up his tender offer.

294
00:11:54,745 --> 00:11:55,839
He waived conflict.

295
00:11:55,863 --> 00:11:57,480
That doesn't apply to privilege.

296
00:11:57,498 --> 00:12:00,093
Bottom line is, he doesn't
have proof of anything.

297
00:12:00,117 --> 00:12:01,317
I don't, but he does.

298
00:12:01,335 --> 00:12:03,987
Unfortunately,
he can't force me to testify.

299
00:12:04,005 --> 00:12:04,988
There's no precedent.

300
00:12:05,006 --> 00:12:07,017
Fortunately, there is.

301
00:12:07,041 --> 00:12:11,511
So go ahead, ask him
if he did what I'm saying.

302
00:12:13,381 --> 00:12:16,577
Mr. Specter,
do I need to swear you in?

303
00:12:16,601 --> 00:12:18,445
Give him the T.R.O.

304
00:12:18,469 --> 00:12:19,913
You know,
I'll do more than that.

305
00:12:19,937 --> 00:12:22,532
Not only can't your client make
a tender offer for 60 days,

306
00:12:22,556 --> 00:12:27,644
they can't purchase any more
stock until then either.

307
00:12:29,897 --> 00:12:32,826
I'm telling you,
we need to negotiate with him.

308
00:12:32,850 --> 00:12:34,127
You mean pay him off?

309
00:12:34,151 --> 00:12:35,685
Yes, that's exactly what I mean.

310
00:12:35,703 --> 00:12:39,522
Every day this drags on, it's
millions out of your pocket.

311
00:12:39,540 --> 00:12:41,718
Well, from where I'm sitting,
all I can see is a lawyer

312
00:12:41,742 --> 00:12:42,936
trying to distract me
from the fact

313
00:12:42,960 --> 00:12:44,504
that this whole thing
is his fault.

314
00:12:44,528 --> 00:12:45,862
If I didn't break privilege,

315
00:12:45,880 --> 00:12:46,863
he might have locked
this whole thing up

316
00:12:46,881 --> 00:12:47,864
before you knew what hit you.

317
00:12:47,882 --> 00:12:49,643
Fine. We'll negotiate.

318
00:12:49,667 --> 00:12:53,230
No, I'll negotiate.

319
00:12:53,254 --> 00:12:55,181
No, not without me.

320
00:12:55,205 --> 00:12:56,483
Do I need to draw you a picture?

321
00:12:56,507 --> 00:12:58,485
You, Mike, Rachel.

322
00:12:58,509 --> 00:13:00,821
Harvey, I appreciate
your concern,

323
00:13:00,845 --> 00:13:02,689
but this is my first deal, so
unless you're gonna pay him off

324
00:13:02,713 --> 00:13:06,850
with your money,
I'm gonna be at that meeting.

325
00:13:10,604 --> 00:13:12,666
What are you doing?

326
00:13:12,690 --> 00:13:14,835
I'm writing in my diary.

327
00:13:14,859 --> 00:13:16,803
Isn't that
what your dictaphone is for?

328
00:13:16,827 --> 00:13:19,372
No, my dictaphone
is for my singular triumphs,

329
00:13:19,396 --> 00:13:22,009
like when Harvey told me
I was the man,

330
00:13:22,033 --> 00:13:25,762
and my diary is
for my most agonizing defeats,

331
00:13:25,786 --> 00:13:28,571
such as when Jessica just told
me I'll never make name partner.

332
00:13:28,589 --> 00:13:31,852
- Louis, she didn't say that.
- Well, she might as well have.

333
00:13:31,876 --> 00:13:34,744
She just gave Malone
the corner office.

334
00:13:34,762 --> 00:13:35,745
Oh, my God.

335
00:13:35,763 --> 00:13:37,914
Yeah.

336
00:13:37,932 --> 00:13:39,559
And what's more is
I think I agreed

337
00:13:39,583 --> 00:13:41,194
to give him Felton Securities.

338
00:13:41,218 --> 00:13:43,920
Well, un-agree to it.

339
00:13:43,938 --> 00:13:45,198
I can't.

340
00:13:45,222 --> 00:13:47,090
I shook his hand.
The die is cast.

341
00:13:47,108 --> 00:13:48,201
God damn it, Louis.

342
00:13:48,225 --> 00:13:50,203
You know how this works.

343
00:13:50,227 --> 00:13:51,672
First it's a case.
Then it's a client.

344
00:13:51,696 --> 00:13:54,764
Before you know it, you're
on the 38th floor with Ted.

345
00:13:54,782 --> 00:13:57,678
- Who's Ted?
- Exactly.

346
00:13:57,702 --> 00:14:00,937
Holy shit. What did I just do?

347
00:14:00,955 --> 00:14:02,382
I'll tell you
what you're gonna do.

348
00:14:02,406 --> 00:14:04,551
You're gonna stop writing
in that pussy diary,

349
00:14:04,575 --> 00:14:06,720
and you're gonna show Jessica
you're the one

350
00:14:06,744 --> 00:14:11,558
who should be sitting
in that corner office.

351
00:14:11,582 --> 00:14:16,002
Ready the dictaphone.
We're gonna need it.

352
00:14:20,318 --> 00:14:22,985
Hey. How are things
going Logan Sanders.

353
00:14:22,986 --> 00:14:25,265
- You have no idea.
- Do I want to have an idea?

354
00:14:25,289 --> 00:14:27,490
Not unless you want to hear
about how Mike Ross

355
00:14:27,508 --> 00:14:28,852
is still causing us trouble.

356
00:14:28,876 --> 00:14:30,904
Nope.

357
00:14:30,928 --> 00:14:33,773
You don't care about
Logan Sanders at all, do you?

358
00:14:33,797 --> 00:14:35,575
No.

359
00:14:35,599 --> 00:14:38,811
This isn't
a coincidental encounter, is it?

360
00:14:38,835 --> 00:14:40,697
No, it is not.

361
00:14:40,721 --> 00:14:43,083
You are having lunch
with Jeff Malone today.

362
00:14:43,107 --> 00:14:44,534
Come on, Jessica.
You banged him.

363
00:14:44,558 --> 00:14:45,869
The least you could do
is take him to lunch.

364
00:14:45,893 --> 00:14:47,454
That is not funny.

365
00:14:47,478 --> 00:14:49,678
Wait a second,
you want me to take him to lunch

366
00:14:49,697 --> 00:14:50,846
because you banged him.

367
00:14:50,864 --> 00:14:53,659
Harvey...

368
00:14:53,683 --> 00:14:55,962
I want you to go ahead
and say "banged"

369
00:14:55,986 --> 00:14:58,854
to my face one more time.

370
00:15:00,357 --> 00:15:03,636
I'm not going to but not
because I'm scared of you.

371
00:15:03,660 --> 00:15:07,163
Whatever lets you sleep
at night, white boy.

372
00:15:10,167 --> 00:15:12,979
Donna, tell Paul Porter
he's meeting me for lunch.

373
00:15:13,003 --> 00:15:15,538
When he gets there, tell them
to seat him with Jeff Malone.

374
00:15:15,556 --> 00:15:16,983
Who's he not having lunch with?

375
00:15:17,007 --> 00:15:19,069
- Jessica.
- Oh, done.

376
00:15:19,093 --> 00:15:21,121
Aren't you gonna ask me why?

377
00:15:21,145 --> 00:15:22,906
She asked you to go
because she didn't want to.

378
00:15:22,930 --> 00:15:25,024
You're sending Porter
because you don't want to,

379
00:15:25,048 --> 00:15:27,527
but you didn't have the balls
to say no to her face.

380
00:15:27,551 --> 00:15:28,528
Is that it?

381
00:15:28,552 --> 00:15:30,029
The balls are debatable.

382
00:15:30,053 --> 00:15:34,723
Balls are never debatable.

383
00:15:37,194 --> 00:15:39,139
- Ah, hey there.
- Hey.

384
00:15:39,163 --> 00:15:41,063
Louis, listen, I just, um...

385
00:15:41,081 --> 00:15:42,708
I just wanted to say
one more time

386
00:15:42,732 --> 00:15:44,761
how much I'm really looking
forward to working with you.

387
00:15:44,785 --> 00:15:46,930
Aww, well, I would just like
to say for the first time

388
00:15:46,954 --> 00:15:48,214
that you will not be
working with me,

389
00:15:48,238 --> 00:15:50,383
because I will not be giving you
my jock,

390
00:15:50,407 --> 00:15:51,384
let alone my case.

391
00:15:51,408 --> 00:15:53,186
Yeah.

392
00:15:53,210 --> 00:15:54,743
Okay, I get it.

393
00:15:54,762 --> 00:15:57,023
So you're the guy?

394
00:15:57,047 --> 00:15:59,058
Yeah, I am the guy.

395
00:15:59,082 --> 00:16:01,611
No, not that guy, Louis.
Definitely not that guy.

396
00:16:01,635 --> 00:16:03,446
You're the guy in every office
who wants to piss

397
00:16:03,470 --> 00:16:06,732
on the new guy, you know,
to mark your territory.

398
00:16:06,756 --> 00:16:08,952
So why don't I just walk you on
down to my office?

399
00:16:08,976 --> 00:16:11,137
I'm gonna let you get your
little piss on in my corner,

400
00:16:11,145 --> 00:16:12,172
and then we can move on.

401
00:16:12,196 --> 00:16:13,623
Oh, I've moved on.

402
00:16:13,647 --> 00:16:15,431
I've set the deposition
for Todd Smith tomorrow.

403
00:16:15,449 --> 00:16:16,793
You don't think
I know about that?

404
00:16:16,817 --> 00:16:18,211
I don't give a shit
whether you know it or not.

405
00:16:18,235 --> 00:16:20,713
It's my job to determine
whether Todd Smith is guilty.

406
00:16:20,737 --> 00:16:22,857
And who do you actually think
is better at determining

407
00:16:22,873 --> 00:16:25,685
whether a guy is guilty
of insider trading, Louis?

408
00:16:25,709 --> 00:16:27,470
A career prosecutor
for the S.E.C.

409
00:16:27,494 --> 00:16:29,222
or a monkey
in some Italian suit?

410
00:16:29,246 --> 00:16:30,890
- A monkey?
- Monkey.

411
00:16:30,914 --> 00:16:32,892
Well, you're nothing
but a crowing cock.

412
00:16:32,916 --> 00:16:34,727
And the last cock that walked
into my office

413
00:16:34,751 --> 00:16:36,529
learned what
all the other cocks learned...

414
00:16:36,553 --> 00:16:39,149
That I eat cock for breakfast,
lunch, and dinner.

415
00:16:39,173 --> 00:16:40,817
Louis, you're gonna let me
in that deposition tomorrow

416
00:16:40,841 --> 00:16:42,035
whether you like it or not.

417
00:16:42,059 --> 00:16:43,570
Why, because you're gonna run
to Jessica?

418
00:16:43,594 --> 00:16:46,156
No, simply because I'm gonna
tell everyone here in the office

419
00:16:46,180 --> 00:16:48,992
that you said you eat cock for
breakfast, lunch, and dinner.

420
00:16:49,016 --> 00:16:51,744
Yeah, that's right.
It's goddamn delicious.

421
00:16:51,768 --> 00:16:54,270
Mmm! Mmm, mmm.

422
00:16:57,941 --> 00:16:59,669
So what, you think
you can handle Todd Smith

423
00:16:59,693 --> 00:17:01,120
better than me?

424
00:17:01,144 --> 00:17:04,080
Well, let's just see.
Let's just see what you got.

425
00:17:06,617 --> 00:17:08,651
Saw you scheduled a meeting
with Mike.

426
00:17:08,669 --> 00:17:10,680
I assume that means you're going
to offer him a deal.

427
00:17:10,704 --> 00:17:12,985
It could mean I'm going to
offer him a trip to Disneyland.

428
00:17:12,989 --> 00:17:14,323
But it doesn't.

429
00:17:14,341 --> 00:17:16,469
Of course not, he'd probably
want to wear mouse ears,

430
00:17:16,493 --> 00:17:17,970
and then nobody wins.

431
00:17:17,994 --> 00:17:19,138
You're welcome.

432
00:17:19,162 --> 00:17:20,857
I didn't thank you.

433
00:17:20,881 --> 00:17:23,042
Since you scheduled the meeting
when I'm at law school,

434
00:17:23,050 --> 00:17:24,667
which you did to cut me out.

435
00:17:24,685 --> 00:17:26,835
Did you get your name
on the wall since lunch?

436
00:17:26,854 --> 00:17:28,031
No.

437
00:17:28,055 --> 00:17:29,315
Then let's get
something straight.

438
00:17:29,339 --> 00:17:31,034
I didn't set that meeting.
Donna did.

439
00:17:31,058 --> 00:17:34,420
And if I didn't want you there,
I'd just tell you to your face.

440
00:17:34,444 --> 00:17:37,724
So let me tell you now, you're
not going to that meeting.

441
00:17:37,748 --> 00:17:39,709
Because you think
I can't handle it?

442
00:17:39,733 --> 00:17:41,711
Because I'm not throwing
gasoline on a pile of matches

443
00:17:41,735 --> 00:17:43,129
just to see what happens.

444
00:17:43,153 --> 00:17:45,431
Now, if you're done
wasting my time,

445
00:17:45,455 --> 00:17:49,001
you just gave me an idea.

446
00:17:49,025 --> 00:17:50,960
You're welcome.

447
00:17:56,833 --> 00:17:57,977
Harvey, what are you doing here?

448
00:17:58,001 --> 00:17:59,178
You said it yourself.

449
00:17:59,202 --> 00:18:01,036
I never brought you a gift
when you moved in.

450
00:18:01,054 --> 00:18:04,250
- Still don't see an orchid.
- Flowers die.

451
00:18:04,274 --> 00:18:07,220
I thought I'd bring
something better.

452
00:18:07,244 --> 00:18:08,905
Me...

453
00:18:08,929 --> 00:18:11,574
Across the table from you.

454
00:18:11,598 --> 00:18:13,576
- Where's your client?
- He doesn't need to be here.

455
00:18:13,600 --> 00:18:15,495
This fight started
with you and me.

456
00:18:15,519 --> 00:18:17,163
So let's you and me
settle it right now.

457
00:18:17,187 --> 00:18:19,388
You mean you don't want him
here because you don't think

458
00:18:19,389 --> 00:18:21,167
Logan Sanders and I
can be in the same room.

459
00:18:21,191 --> 00:18:23,002
I don't think. I know.

460
00:18:23,026 --> 00:18:24,137
Harvey, I'm a grown man.

461
00:18:24,161 --> 00:18:25,755
I can sit across the table
from somebody

462
00:18:25,779 --> 00:18:27,090
who had a history with Rachel.

463
00:18:27,114 --> 00:18:28,758
Maybe, but you both
have a brain and a dick,

464
00:18:28,782 --> 00:18:30,343
and if you get in that room
together,

465
00:18:30,367 --> 00:18:33,402
the brains aren't gonna be
leading that conversation.

466
00:18:33,420 --> 00:18:35,315
Fine, you tell me
that you have the authority

467
00:18:35,339 --> 00:18:38,718
to negotiate a deal,
and I'll negotiate.

468
00:18:38,742 --> 00:18:41,410
But you can't 'cause you don't.

469
00:18:41,428 --> 00:18:43,889
And I'm not gonna agree
to something here today

470
00:18:43,913 --> 00:18:46,081
just to have Logan reject it
tomorrow.

471
00:18:46,099 --> 00:18:48,027
So go home, get some sleep,
and then the three of us

472
00:18:48,051 --> 00:18:52,054
will do this again
in the morning.

473
00:18:57,826 --> 00:18:59,141
Look, here's the thing Todd.

474
00:18:59,165 --> 00:19:01,140
You're not actually our client.

475
00:19:01,164 --> 00:19:02,698
Felton Securities is.

476
00:19:02,716 --> 00:19:04,843
And it's my job to find out
if you're telling the truth.

477
00:19:04,867 --> 00:19:06,368
Bullshit. It's my job.

478
00:19:06,386 --> 00:19:08,870
- Louis, I'm handling this.
- No, you're not.

479
00:19:08,888 --> 00:19:10,539
If he doesn't stop lying to me,
I'm gonna cut him looser

480
00:19:10,557 --> 00:19:13,069
than Jared's pants
after a Subway diet.

481
00:19:13,093 --> 00:19:15,238
- I'm not lying to you.
- You took a tip.

482
00:19:15,262 --> 00:19:17,212
All right, Todd, you took a tip,
used it for your client...

483
00:19:17,230 --> 00:19:18,691
Yes, and now you're trying...

484
00:19:18,715 --> 00:19:20,859
God damn it, Louis!

485
00:19:20,883 --> 00:19:23,084
Listen, if you don't back
the hell off my interrogation,

486
00:19:23,103 --> 00:19:25,197
I'm gonna pick
his scrawny ass up

487
00:19:25,221 --> 00:19:27,166
and use him to beat
the shit out of you!

488
00:19:27,190 --> 00:19:28,467
Stop it!

489
00:19:28,491 --> 00:19:29,468
You think I don't know
what you're doing?

490
00:19:29,492 --> 00:19:32,538
You're trying to rattle me.

491
00:19:32,562 --> 00:19:33,923
- Uh-oh.
- What?

492
00:19:33,947 --> 00:19:35,341
Uh, your vein.

493
00:19:35,365 --> 00:19:36,676
- Here?
- It's bulging.

494
00:19:36,700 --> 00:19:38,094
Just like mine did,
right before my heart attack.

495
00:19:38,118 --> 00:19:39,878
- Louis, he's not gonna...
- What? Have a heart attack?

496
00:19:39,902 --> 00:19:42,404
That was exactly my thought
ten seconds before I was slumped

497
00:19:42,422 --> 00:19:43,683
on the courtroom floor.

498
00:19:43,707 --> 00:19:45,184
Oh, wow, it's just like Jenkins.

499
00:19:45,208 --> 00:19:47,270
- Jenkins?
- No shit, Jenkins too?

500
00:19:47,294 --> 00:19:49,411
He was sitting
right next to me, hand to God.

501
00:19:49,429 --> 00:19:51,357
And, Louis, you should have
seen his wife and kids

502
00:19:51,381 --> 00:19:52,725
at the funeral. Funeral?

503
00:19:52,749 --> 00:19:55,417
- Yeah, you have kids, Todd?
- Yeah, I have two kids.

504
00:19:55,435 --> 00:19:57,697
Yeah, well, whether it's
a heart attack or prison time,

505
00:19:57,721 --> 00:19:59,565
if you do not stop lying to us,

506
00:19:59,589 --> 00:20:01,284
they're never going to see
their father again.

507
00:20:01,308 --> 00:20:03,035
Do you understand
what I just said?

508
00:20:03,059 --> 00:20:04,259
You are never going to play
soccer with them...

509
00:20:04,277 --> 00:20:06,928
Okay. Okay, I am lying to you.

510
00:20:06,946 --> 00:20:08,597
But please, you gotta help me.

511
00:20:08,615 --> 00:20:09,931
Well, we want to.

512
00:20:09,949 --> 00:20:12,545
But, T-dog, you gotta be
straight up with your homies

513
00:20:12,569 --> 00:20:13,546
if you want us
to have your back.

514
00:20:13,570 --> 00:20:17,105
The truth is, I'm germaphobic.

515
00:20:17,123 --> 00:20:19,084
I have to wash my hands
throughout the day.

516
00:20:19,108 --> 00:20:21,587
And they get dry...
I mean really dry...

517
00:20:21,611 --> 00:20:24,056
So I have to put on
a lot of lotion.

518
00:20:24,080 --> 00:20:26,058
And I know
this sounds ridiculous,

519
00:20:26,082 --> 00:20:27,783
but my finger must have slipped
on the keyboard, and I...

520
00:20:27,801 --> 00:20:29,595
I hit the wrong stock.

521
00:20:29,619 --> 00:20:31,981
You're saying that you didn't
even mean to buy that stock?

522
00:20:32,005 --> 00:20:34,066
Nope, but then it skyrocketed,

523
00:20:34,090 --> 00:20:35,868
and I wasn't gonna tell
everybody that I only bought it

524
00:20:35,892 --> 00:20:37,987
because I suffer from dry skin.

525
00:20:38,011 --> 00:20:39,961
Please, you can't cut me loose.

526
00:20:39,979 --> 00:20:43,442
I mean, I-I can't go to prison.

527
00:20:43,466 --> 00:20:46,735
Unsanitary.

528
00:20:51,024 --> 00:20:52,668
Not that
it's any of my business,

529
00:20:52,692 --> 00:20:53,975
but it was straight before.

530
00:20:53,993 --> 00:20:55,143
I know.

531
00:20:55,161 --> 00:20:56,839
Oh, I get it.

532
00:20:56,863 --> 00:20:59,892
Look less together.
Get underestimated.

533
00:21:03,286 --> 00:21:06,288
You gotta wave your hand slower.

534
00:21:08,291 --> 00:21:09,658
- Thanks.
- No problem.

535
00:21:09,676 --> 00:21:12,638
If you want soap, you just click
your heels together three times.

536
00:21:12,662 --> 00:21:15,241
How do you think I'm planning
on getting that dryer to work?

537
00:21:15,265 --> 00:21:16,575
You know, you think you wouldn't
have these problems,

538
00:21:16,599 --> 00:21:17,999
considering what
you guys charge.

539
00:21:18,017 --> 00:21:19,478
Oh, no, I don't work here.

540
00:21:19,502 --> 00:21:24,083
- But you, uh...
- I used to.

541
00:21:24,107 --> 00:21:26,308
You're Mike Ross.

542
00:21:28,611 --> 00:21:32,625
And you're Logan Sanders.

543
00:21:32,649 --> 00:21:34,516
Paper towel?

544
00:21:34,534 --> 00:21:37,996
Don't mind if I do.

545
00:21:38,020 --> 00:21:39,521
After you.

546
00:21:39,539 --> 00:21:41,801
- Don't mind if I do.
- I see you two have met.

547
00:21:41,825 --> 00:21:43,135
We have.

548
00:21:43,159 --> 00:21:45,638
And don't underestimate him
because of his tie.

549
00:21:45,662 --> 00:21:50,226
I have always estimated
that tie correctly.

550
00:21:50,250 --> 00:21:51,644
Now, can we talk about business?

551
00:21:51,668 --> 00:21:54,536
Depends on what
you're proposing.

552
00:21:54,554 --> 00:21:55,848
That you walk away.

553
00:21:55,872 --> 00:21:57,683
That doesn't sound
like much of a deal.

554
00:21:57,707 --> 00:21:59,184
Well, he forgot to add
the part where you walk away

555
00:21:59,208 --> 00:22:01,287
$20 million richer.

556
00:22:01,311 --> 00:22:03,021
Pure profit. No risk.

557
00:22:03,045 --> 00:22:05,213
Win-win.

558
00:22:05,231 --> 00:22:08,183
All right.

559
00:22:10,854 --> 00:22:12,915
Sounds good.

560
00:22:12,939 --> 00:22:15,167
Guess I just have one question.

561
00:22:15,191 --> 00:22:17,503
What exactly are you going to do
with this company?

562
00:22:17,527 --> 00:22:20,172
All due respect, I don't see
how that's any of your concern.

563
00:22:20,196 --> 00:22:22,174
All due respect, you're the
one coming to me with an offer.

564
00:22:22,198 --> 00:22:23,732
So if I say it's my concern,
it is.

565
00:22:23,750 --> 00:22:26,762
Mike, you're asking about
a competitor's business plan.

566
00:22:26,786 --> 00:22:28,547
And if he wants
to not be competitors,

567
00:22:28,571 --> 00:22:30,683
then he needs to answer
my question.

568
00:22:30,707 --> 00:22:32,073
Okay, I'll tell you.

569
00:22:32,091 --> 00:22:35,911
I'm gonna do what anyone would
and sell it for parts.

570
00:22:35,929 --> 00:22:38,441
No deal.

571
00:22:38,465 --> 00:22:41,082
Okay, Mike.

572
00:22:41,100 --> 00:22:43,228
You win.

573
00:22:43,252 --> 00:22:46,254
Let's, uh, make it 30 million.

574
00:22:46,272 --> 00:22:47,566
You could make it
a billion, Logan,

575
00:22:47,590 --> 00:22:49,368
and the answer is still
gonna be the same,

576
00:22:49,392 --> 00:22:51,537
'cause I made a promise
to Walter Gillis

577
00:22:51,561 --> 00:22:53,706
that I would fight
to keep his company alive.

578
00:22:53,730 --> 00:22:56,292
And I don't think he's gonna
believe that cutting a deal

579
00:22:56,316 --> 00:22:59,295
to sell his workers out
is keeping that promise.

580
00:22:59,319 --> 00:23:00,629
I thought you said he was smart.

581
00:23:00,653 --> 00:23:02,465
I am, which I why I know
what's going on here.

582
00:23:02,489 --> 00:23:04,917
What exactly is that?

583
00:23:04,941 --> 00:23:07,686
No one ever tells you no.

584
00:23:07,710 --> 00:23:09,945
You're used to getting
what you want.

585
00:23:09,963 --> 00:23:12,358
But that's gonna stop right now.

586
00:23:12,382 --> 00:23:15,928
You're right.
I do always get what I want.

587
00:23:15,952 --> 00:23:17,229
I don't see how this time's
gonna be any different.

588
00:23:17,253 --> 00:23:18,731
I'll tell you
how it's gonna be different.

589
00:23:18,755 --> 00:23:21,233
This time you're talking about
something that I care about.

590
00:23:21,257 --> 00:23:22,735
So if you think I'm gonna
step aside and let you do...

591
00:23:22,759 --> 00:23:24,937
Yeah, I don't care
if you step aside or not.

592
00:23:24,961 --> 00:23:27,373
When I see something I want,
I take it,

593
00:23:27,397 --> 00:23:28,824
and then I do whatever the hell
I want with it.

594
00:23:28,848 --> 00:23:31,800
And what I wanna do with
this company is strip it down,

595
00:23:31,818 --> 00:23:32,878
flip it over...
Okay, that's enough.

596
00:23:32,902 --> 00:23:33,969
No, no, no, let him talk.

597
00:23:33,987 --> 00:23:35,331
I wanna hear this.
Keep going, Sanders.

598
00:23:35,355 --> 00:23:37,355
No, I don't need to
because you know how this ends.

599
00:23:37,357 --> 00:23:39,552
Yeah, I do, with me
and Walter Gillis on one side

600
00:23:39,576 --> 00:23:41,453
and you crying to your daddy
on the other.

601
00:23:41,477 --> 00:23:42,454
We're done.

602
00:23:42,478 --> 00:23:43,889
You're right.

603
00:23:43,913 --> 00:23:46,759
We are.

604
00:23:46,783 --> 00:23:49,317
Listen, the next time I say
"Don't come to a meeting,"

605
00:23:49,335 --> 00:23:50,930
don't come to a meeting.

606
00:23:50,954 --> 00:23:52,130
He came at me just as hard as...

607
00:23:52,154 --> 00:23:53,349
I don't give a shit what he did.

608
00:23:53,373 --> 00:23:55,351
Now, if you'll excuse me.

609
00:23:55,375 --> 00:23:57,770
- Where are you going?
- To get you this company.

610
00:23:57,794 --> 00:23:59,605
- What are you talking about?
- Weren't you listening?

611
00:23:59,629 --> 00:24:03,048
He just gave up his weak spot.

612
00:24:04,684 --> 00:24:06,645
Was that true about Jenkins?

613
00:24:06,669 --> 00:24:08,531
I don't even know a Jenkins.

614
00:24:08,555 --> 00:24:12,117
But I do know Todd's vein
wasn't bulging.

615
00:24:12,141 --> 00:24:14,152
And, Louis, you were actually
pretty good in there.

616
00:24:14,176 --> 00:24:16,344
Yeah, I was. And so were you.

617
00:24:16,362 --> 00:24:17,756
So we're in agreement.

618
00:24:17,780 --> 00:24:19,041
Yeah, you don't completely suck.

619
00:24:19,065 --> 00:24:21,159
I just meant that
we should stick by Todd Smith.

620
00:24:21,183 --> 00:24:23,929
That story was so ridiculous,
it just might be true.

621
00:24:23,953 --> 00:24:26,098
Great, I'll call Felton
and make the recommendation.

622
00:24:26,122 --> 00:24:28,834
Well, hold up.
You're gonna do what now?

623
00:24:28,858 --> 00:24:30,669
Call my client? Louis.

624
00:24:30,693 --> 00:24:32,838
It may be your client,
but it's still my case.

625
00:24:32,862 --> 00:24:33,889
Like hell it is, Jeff.

626
00:24:33,913 --> 00:24:37,059
- Okay. Okay, you call.
- Oh, I plan to.

627
00:24:37,083 --> 00:24:38,394
And when I do,
I'll be telling them

628
00:24:38,418 --> 00:24:40,178
that Mr. Slippery Fingers
is no longer our problem.

629
00:24:40,202 --> 00:24:42,481
Just one second ago,
you said you believed him.

630
00:24:42,505 --> 00:24:44,873
Yeah, I also told you that
his story was so ridiculous

631
00:24:44,891 --> 00:24:46,318
and nobody would believe it.

632
00:24:46,342 --> 00:24:48,454
Well, then it's our job
to make them believe it, Louis,

633
00:24:48,478 --> 00:24:49,878
or this guy could wind up
in prison.

634
00:24:49,879 --> 00:24:51,880
He is not my concern, Jeff.

635
00:24:51,898 --> 00:24:54,483
Felton Securities is.

636
00:25:03,776 --> 00:25:05,176
Walter Gillis knows
what he's doing.

637
00:25:05,194 --> 00:25:06,338
Yeah, so do I.

638
00:25:06,362 --> 00:25:07,923
He's letting your pension
go unfunded,

639
00:25:07,947 --> 00:25:09,731
so he can hoard $1 billion.

640
00:25:09,749 --> 00:25:13,596
No, that money is earmarked
for expansion into Asia,

641
00:25:13,620 --> 00:25:15,097
and I believe
in Walter's vision.

642
00:25:15,121 --> 00:25:18,239
You might, but do the workers
you represent?

643
00:25:18,257 --> 00:25:20,436
You're acting
as if our fund is empty.

644
00:25:20,460 --> 00:25:22,655
I'm acting as if it's 40% full.

645
00:25:22,679 --> 00:25:25,357
And let me guess,
you're gonna fill up the rest.

646
00:25:25,381 --> 00:25:28,583
Someone else wants to acquire
Gillis' company

647
00:25:28,601 --> 00:25:30,418
before we can make an offer.

648
00:25:30,436 --> 00:25:32,197
If you vote to block it,

649
00:25:32,221 --> 00:25:35,724
we will fully fund your pension
the day we take over.

650
00:25:37,777 --> 00:25:40,122
You're talking about me
selling out my friend.

651
00:25:40,146 --> 00:25:42,791
I'm talking about $500 million.

652
00:25:42,815 --> 00:25:44,510
And why can you fund it
and they can't?

653
00:25:44,534 --> 00:25:46,629
Well, they can with half
that billion, but they won't.

654
00:25:46,653 --> 00:25:49,437
Because like I said, he's
hoarding it for that pipe dream.

655
00:25:49,455 --> 00:25:52,107
You're gonna take that billion
for yourselves.

656
00:25:52,125 --> 00:25:53,585
Half.

657
00:25:53,609 --> 00:25:55,521
The other half goes to you
and your union...

658
00:25:55,545 --> 00:25:58,590
The men Walter Gillis
supposedly cares about.

659
00:25:58,614 --> 00:26:02,061
Pete, this is gonna happen
whether it's me or someone else.

660
00:26:02,085 --> 00:26:04,196
And someone else may not
give you the chance to do

661
00:26:04,220 --> 00:26:07,265
what you were elected to do:

662
00:26:07,289 --> 00:26:09,174
Protect your people.

663
00:26:14,857 --> 00:26:16,857
Hey. Hey.

664
00:26:18,201 --> 00:26:22,398
How'd your meeting
with Harvey go today?

665
00:26:22,422 --> 00:26:25,134
I thought talking about work
was against the rules.

666
00:26:25,158 --> 00:26:27,853
Mm, talking about work is.
Talking about our day isn't.

667
00:26:27,877 --> 00:26:30,239
I mean, if we can't do that,
then we're letting the case

668
00:26:30,263 --> 00:26:33,976
come between us, right?

669
00:26:34,000 --> 00:26:36,946
My meeting with Harvey
went fine.

670
00:26:36,970 --> 00:26:39,849
But you didn't take the deal.

671
00:26:39,873 --> 00:26:44,754
Because it wasn't a good deal.

672
00:26:44,778 --> 00:26:48,257
Fine.

673
00:26:48,281 --> 00:26:50,492
Okay, what's the matter
with you?

674
00:26:50,516 --> 00:26:53,546
What's the matter is that
I heard what happened.

675
00:26:53,570 --> 00:26:56,382
- From him?
- No, from Donna.

676
00:26:56,406 --> 00:26:58,023
But it could have been
from any of the 50 people

677
00:26:58,041 --> 00:26:59,191
who saw the two of you
going at it.

678
00:26:59,209 --> 00:27:00,836
- Rachel...
- Just tell me this.

679
00:27:00,860 --> 00:27:03,172
Did you refuse the deal
because it wasn't good enough

680
00:27:03,196 --> 00:27:04,696
or because it came from Logan?

681
00:27:04,714 --> 00:27:06,058
You think I didn't take
this deal

682
00:27:06,082 --> 00:27:07,866
because of your history
with this asshole?

683
00:27:07,884 --> 00:27:09,511
Well, you did
just call him an asshole.

684
00:27:09,535 --> 00:27:11,536
He's an asshole because he's
willing to decimate a company

685
00:27:11,554 --> 00:27:13,816
just to put some money
in his pocket.

686
00:27:13,840 --> 00:27:15,818
Look, I gave my word
to Walter Gillis.

687
00:27:15,842 --> 00:27:17,787
That's what I told Harvey
and what I told Logan

688
00:27:17,811 --> 00:27:19,488
and what I didn't think
I'd have to tell you.

689
00:27:19,512 --> 00:27:24,660
I'm just saying, all of this
could have been over today.

690
00:27:24,684 --> 00:27:25,911
You think I don't want this
to be over?

691
00:27:25,935 --> 00:27:27,496
I do.

692
00:27:27,520 --> 00:27:28,798
But I can't take that deal.

693
00:27:28,822 --> 00:27:31,167
And we said we wouldn't let this
come between us.

694
00:27:31,191 --> 00:27:34,076
So don't.

695
00:27:36,780 --> 00:27:38,207
- Hi, Donna.
- Hey, Louis.

696
00:27:38,231 --> 00:27:39,564
What can I do for you?

697
00:27:39,582 --> 00:27:45,380
Oh, well, I just came in
to bring you this and this

698
00:27:45,404 --> 00:27:51,243
and all of these.

699
00:27:51,261 --> 00:27:53,439
Those are the last seven
Todd Smiths you evaluated.

700
00:27:53,463 --> 00:27:54,607
- Donna...
- Seven.

701
00:27:54,631 --> 00:27:56,192
And you didn't cut
one of them loose.

702
00:27:56,216 --> 00:27:58,393
- You heard me and Malone.
- I did.

703
00:27:58,417 --> 00:27:59,862
And you're cutting this guy
loose just to spite him.

704
00:27:59,886 --> 00:28:01,086
That's ridiculous.

705
00:28:01,104 --> 00:28:03,449
Okay, so this has nothing
to do with Malone?

706
00:28:03,473 --> 00:28:06,091
Nothing.

707
00:28:07,944 --> 00:28:09,594
Where'd you get that?

708
00:28:09,612 --> 00:28:11,707
Come on.
You know where I got it.

709
00:28:11,731 --> 00:28:14,032
Louis...

710
00:28:16,769 --> 00:28:18,270
I know he took your dream.

711
00:28:21,991 --> 00:28:24,220
I mean, she didn't even
consider me.

712
00:28:24,244 --> 00:28:26,138
Just brings him in,
had me train him,

713
00:28:26,162 --> 00:28:30,476
and gives him the corner office.

714
00:28:30,500 --> 00:28:32,478
Hey, did I ever tell you
about the time that I auditioned

715
00:28:32,502 --> 00:28:35,597
for Hamlet in college?

716
00:28:35,621 --> 00:28:36,899
Obviously, you played Ophelia.

717
00:28:36,923 --> 00:28:39,124
No, Chrissy Kiff did.

718
00:28:39,142 --> 00:28:40,820
I was her understudy,

719
00:28:40,844 --> 00:28:43,155
and I was so jealous.

720
00:28:43,179 --> 00:28:45,708
I found myself wishing that
something would happen to her,

721
00:28:45,732 --> 00:28:49,801
that she would get sick
or she would twist an ankle.

722
00:28:49,819 --> 00:28:55,417
And then, the day
before we closed...

723
00:28:55,441 --> 00:28:59,621
Her father died.

724
00:28:59,645 --> 00:29:00,756
Donna, that wasn't your fault.

725
00:29:00,780 --> 00:29:03,559
But I still felt horrible

726
00:29:03,583 --> 00:29:06,061
and ashamed

727
00:29:06,085 --> 00:29:11,633
'cause my jealousy had brought
out something really ugly in me.

728
00:29:11,657 --> 00:29:16,328
And as you can tell,
I still regret that.

729
00:29:16,346 --> 00:29:18,357
You know you've never
told me a story

730
00:29:18,381 --> 00:29:21,193
about yourself like that before.

731
00:29:21,217 --> 00:29:24,613
I've never told anyone
that story before.

732
00:29:24,637 --> 00:29:27,973
Louis, I know how badly
you wanted this.

733
00:29:30,693 --> 00:29:33,372
But this is a man's life.

734
00:29:33,396 --> 00:29:34,874
We won't cut him loose.

735
00:29:34,898 --> 00:29:38,183
I'll tell Malone.

736
00:29:39,685 --> 00:29:41,686
I'm proud of you, Louis.

737
00:29:46,659 --> 00:29:49,388
Did you get an offer
to walk away from your takeover?

738
00:29:49,412 --> 00:29:50,606
I did.

739
00:29:50,630 --> 00:29:51,974
What was the offer?

740
00:29:51,998 --> 00:29:53,342
$30 million.

741
00:29:53,366 --> 00:29:55,811
And you turned it down?
What the hell is wrong with you?

742
00:29:55,835 --> 00:29:57,202
They're gonna rip
the company apart.

743
00:29:57,220 --> 00:29:59,114
I don't care if they wanna use
Walter Gillis' head

744
00:29:59,138 --> 00:30:00,482
as a paperweight.

745
00:30:00,506 --> 00:30:01,483
You said you wanted
a grand slam.

746
00:30:01,507 --> 00:30:02,785
That offer is a double.

747
00:30:02,809 --> 00:30:04,209
Well, I'd rather have a double
than nothing.

748
00:30:04,227 --> 00:30:05,210
Look, I know
what I am doing here.

749
00:30:05,228 --> 00:30:06,488
Do you?

750
00:30:06,512 --> 00:30:08,157
Because they just
flipped the head of the union.

751
00:30:08,181 --> 00:30:10,048
And without his vote,
we don't have shit.

752
00:30:10,066 --> 00:30:11,883
- What?
- These guys play to win.

753
00:30:11,901 --> 00:30:13,495
They just promised
$1/2-billion donation

754
00:30:13,519 --> 00:30:14,964
to their pension fund.

755
00:30:14,988 --> 00:30:18,918
And unless Walter Gillis is
gonna match it, we're done.

756
00:30:18,942 --> 00:30:20,002
Yeah.

757
00:30:20,026 --> 00:30:22,638
That's what I thought.

758
00:30:22,662 --> 00:30:24,673
You get that $30 million,

759
00:30:24,697 --> 00:30:28,166
or you find yourself
another job.

760
00:30:31,237 --> 00:30:34,216
Donna, did you need something?

761
00:30:34,240 --> 00:30:37,653
No, but Louis does.

762
00:30:37,677 --> 00:30:40,155
He was planning to pitch you
that he take on Jeff Malone

763
00:30:40,179 --> 00:30:42,024
before you and Harvey
even met him.

764
00:30:42,048 --> 00:30:43,108
He saw Woodall coming
before we did?

765
00:30:43,132 --> 00:30:44,393
And if he won,

766
00:30:44,417 --> 00:30:48,063
he was hoping that
that would mean name partner.

767
00:30:48,087 --> 00:30:50,332
I empathize with that, Donna.
I do.

768
00:30:50,356 --> 00:30:51,423
But I have to make decisions

769
00:30:51,441 --> 00:30:53,235
based on what's best
for the firm.

770
00:30:53,259 --> 00:30:54,592
And I'm not here
to change your mind,

771
00:30:54,611 --> 00:30:56,405
but maybe if you did
something else for Louis...

772
00:30:56,429 --> 00:30:57,595
Such as?

773
00:30:57,614 --> 00:30:59,431
Giving him the corner office.

774
00:30:59,449 --> 00:31:01,210
You mean Jeff Malone's office?

775
00:31:01,234 --> 00:31:03,846
He could move to Louis'.

776
00:31:03,870 --> 00:31:06,748
I appreciate
you letting me know about Louis,

777
00:31:06,772 --> 00:31:08,106
but I'm not going to do that.

778
00:31:08,124 --> 00:31:09,418
Well, why not?
Jeff Malone just got here.

779
00:31:09,442 --> 00:31:11,420
Because I said so.
Now if you'll excuse me...

780
00:31:11,444 --> 00:31:13,255
You're sleeping with him.

781
00:31:13,279 --> 00:31:14,640
- What?
- Of course.

782
00:31:14,664 --> 00:31:17,426
That glow, the morning meetings,
you had Harvey take your lunch.

783
00:31:17,450 --> 00:31:19,784
How could I miss it?
I'm losing my edge.

784
00:31:19,802 --> 00:31:24,973
Donna, there is nothing
going on between...

785
00:31:26,676 --> 00:31:27,987
You're not losing your edge.

786
00:31:28,011 --> 00:31:31,156
But I ended my relationship
with Jeff Malone

787
00:31:31,180 --> 00:31:33,298
the day that I hired him.

788
00:31:33,316 --> 00:31:34,743
And I respect that.

789
00:31:34,767 --> 00:31:36,045
But you said you make decisions

790
00:31:36,069 --> 00:31:38,998
based on what's best
for the firm.

791
00:31:39,022 --> 00:31:43,942
Isn't giving Louis his dignity
back good for the firm?

792
00:31:46,829 --> 00:31:48,146
Hey, I got your message.

793
00:31:48,164 --> 00:31:49,981
Usually when someone
wants to talk business...

794
00:31:49,999 --> 00:31:52,678
I want to take your offer.

795
00:31:52,702 --> 00:31:56,321
Mike, that offer's gone.

796
00:31:56,339 --> 00:31:58,934
And what if I told you
I'd take less?

797
00:31:58,958 --> 00:32:00,302
I'd say I can't give you less.

798
00:32:00,326 --> 00:32:01,770
Come on, you're the guy
who settles.

799
00:32:01,794 --> 00:32:04,907
I'm telling you I wanna settle.

800
00:32:04,931 --> 00:32:06,775
You're telling me
you have to settle.

801
00:32:06,799 --> 00:32:08,193
And I know that
you can get that offer back.

802
00:32:08,217 --> 00:32:10,195
It's not my job to get it back.

803
00:32:10,219 --> 00:32:12,031
And even if it was, you think
he's gonna give you a nickel

804
00:32:12,055 --> 00:32:13,699
after what you said to him?
What I said to him?

805
00:32:13,723 --> 00:32:14,867
What about what he said to me?

806
00:32:14,891 --> 00:32:16,201
I don't care what he said
to you.

807
00:32:16,225 --> 00:32:17,319
I gave you a way out,

808
00:32:17,343 --> 00:32:18,843
and you insisted
on going to that meeting.

809
00:32:18,861 --> 00:32:21,062
You didn't do that for me.
You did that for your client.

810
00:32:21,064 --> 00:32:23,709
What difference does it make?
It was a win-goddamn-win.

811
00:32:23,733 --> 00:32:25,627
And you shit all over it.

812
00:32:25,651 --> 00:32:26,879
Now I'm saying, I'll take it.

813
00:32:26,903 --> 00:32:28,353
Yeah, well,
it doesn't work that way.

814
00:32:28,371 --> 00:32:29,998
I'm here as a courtesy.

815
00:32:30,022 --> 00:32:32,023
You're only here
because you lost.

816
00:32:32,041 --> 00:32:34,136
- Harvey, I'm...
- Enough.

817
00:32:34,160 --> 00:32:37,506
That company's fate is sealed.
It always has been.

818
00:32:37,530 --> 00:32:40,342
And the next time you walk away
from the table,

819
00:32:40,366 --> 00:32:43,835
be prepared to walk away
from the table.

820
00:32:57,447 --> 00:32:59,926
Hmm.

821
00:32:59,950 --> 00:33:01,031
Wanna pour me one of those?

822
00:33:01,034 --> 00:33:04,847
Help yourself.

823
00:33:04,871 --> 00:33:07,823
So what's going on
with Mike Ross?

824
00:33:07,841 --> 00:33:09,135
How do you know I'm thinking
about Mike Ross?

825
00:33:09,159 --> 00:33:10,937
Who else would it be?

826
00:33:10,961 --> 00:33:13,406
He got you on the ropes?

827
00:33:13,430 --> 00:33:15,942
No, I got him.

828
00:33:15,966 --> 00:33:17,833
And he's about to go down.
How do you know?

829
00:33:17,851 --> 00:33:19,478
'Cause the only way
to stay in the game

830
00:33:19,502 --> 00:33:23,482
is to get Walter Gillis
to give up his dream.

831
00:33:23,506 --> 00:33:25,284
And you don't think
he has the stomach

832
00:33:25,308 --> 00:33:27,286
to rip off the arm
to save the body.

833
00:33:27,310 --> 00:33:29,372
No, he doesn't.

834
00:33:29,396 --> 00:33:31,323
You don't seem to feel good
about that.

835
00:33:31,347 --> 00:33:33,459
No, I don't.

836
00:33:33,483 --> 00:33:36,685
Harvey.

837
00:33:36,703 --> 00:33:38,714
Do you remember when I gave you
the Collins case?

838
00:33:38,738 --> 00:33:39,966
Yeah.

839
00:33:39,990 --> 00:33:42,602
It was brutal,
what we had to do.

840
00:33:42,626 --> 00:33:44,693
It was my first taste
of that kind of thing.

841
00:33:44,711 --> 00:33:46,361
And you loved it.

842
00:33:46,379 --> 00:33:47,640
What's your point?

843
00:33:47,664 --> 00:33:50,977
Some people love
the taste of blood.

844
00:33:51,001 --> 00:33:54,013
Other people, hmm.

845
00:33:54,037 --> 00:33:57,039
Better to find out
who you are sooner than later.

846
00:33:57,057 --> 00:33:58,618
You saying
I'm doing him a favor?

847
00:33:58,642 --> 00:34:02,572
I'm saying,
you're being who you are

848
00:34:02,596 --> 00:34:07,149
and letting him be who he is.

849
00:34:18,411 --> 00:34:22,397
What are you doing?

850
00:34:22,415 --> 00:34:23,709
I'm just thinking about how much

851
00:34:23,733 --> 00:34:25,511
I'm going to miss
having my own office.

852
00:34:25,535 --> 00:34:28,403
Put your pride away, okay?
You can still go back to Harvey.

853
00:34:28,421 --> 00:34:29,738
I went back to Harvey.

854
00:34:29,756 --> 00:34:34,487
The money's off the table.

855
00:34:34,511 --> 00:34:36,745
Then you have to flip that vote.

856
00:34:36,763 --> 00:34:39,058
The only way to do that
is to get Walter Gillis

857
00:34:39,082 --> 00:34:43,252
to put $500 million
into that pension fund.

858
00:34:43,270 --> 00:34:45,698
And if he does that,
he loses his expansion.

859
00:34:45,722 --> 00:34:47,066
Mike, then do it.

860
00:34:47,090 --> 00:34:50,425
Amy, when his son died,
this company became his family.

861
00:34:50,443 --> 00:34:52,788
If he doesn't expand, then
his company's gonna die too.

862
00:34:52,812 --> 00:34:55,074
I ask him to do that,
then I'm no better than Logan.

863
00:34:55,098 --> 00:34:56,909
No, you are better,
because after you do this,

864
00:34:56,933 --> 00:34:58,461
you're still gonna fight
to keep them alive.

865
00:34:58,485 --> 00:35:00,079
Gillis is not gonna see it
that way.

866
00:35:00,103 --> 00:35:02,215
He's just gonna see
some slick banker

867
00:35:02,239 --> 00:35:04,050
who sold him a bill of goods
just to end up doing

868
00:35:04,074 --> 00:35:06,919
what everybody else
was at least up front about.

869
00:35:06,943 --> 00:35:09,421
Mm.

870
00:35:09,445 --> 00:35:11,046
Then why don't you
just pack up your shit

871
00:35:11,047 --> 00:35:13,142
and crawl out of here with
your tail between your legs?

872
00:35:13,166 --> 00:35:15,728
Because if you don't have
the stomach to handle this,

873
00:35:15,752 --> 00:35:20,139
then you don't belong here.

874
00:35:21,758 --> 00:35:23,903
Hey, uh, got your message.

875
00:35:23,927 --> 00:35:25,371
Is there something wrong
with Felton Securities?

876
00:35:25,395 --> 00:35:26,372
Not at all.

877
00:35:26,396 --> 00:35:27,873
Oh, thank God.

878
00:35:27,897 --> 00:35:30,465
I just assumed since you wanted
to meet here in Malone's office.

879
00:35:30,483 --> 00:35:32,445
Oh, this isn't his office
anymore.

880
00:35:32,469 --> 00:35:33,913
Oh, did he get fired?

881
00:35:33,937 --> 00:35:36,999
No, but he is moving.

882
00:35:37,023 --> 00:35:40,219
Louis, I know it hasn't always
been easy for you

883
00:35:40,243 --> 00:35:42,722
to embrace new partners,

884
00:35:42,746 --> 00:35:45,647
but you've made
a great effort with Jeff.

885
00:35:45,665 --> 00:35:47,510
All in a day's work.

886
00:35:47,534 --> 00:35:51,230
And your day's work has
benefited this firm for years.

887
00:35:51,254 --> 00:35:53,132
So we thought it was time
to show you

888
00:35:53,156 --> 00:35:56,091
a little overdue appreciation.

889
00:36:04,467 --> 00:36:07,336
This office?

890
00:36:12,008 --> 00:36:13,119
I gave this office to Jeff

891
00:36:13,143 --> 00:36:15,871
because I wanted him
to feel valued here.

892
00:36:15,895 --> 00:36:20,626
But the truth is, I...
I should have given it to you.

893
00:36:27,040 --> 00:36:28,301
I don't know what to say.

894
00:36:28,325 --> 00:36:30,770
Oh, okay.

895
00:36:30,794 --> 00:36:33,439
All right, let it out.

896
00:36:33,463 --> 00:36:34,557
No way.

897
00:36:34,581 --> 00:36:36,309
Pete Kreeling would never side
with them.

898
00:36:36,333 --> 00:36:37,893
He would, and he has,

899
00:36:37,917 --> 00:36:39,368
because they offered
what you couldn't...

900
00:36:39,386 --> 00:36:40,946
Security for his workers.

901
00:36:40,970 --> 00:36:42,051
They're my goddamn workers.

902
00:36:42,055 --> 00:36:43,983
Then show them
that you care about them.

903
00:36:44,007 --> 00:36:46,208
Fund the pension,
and fund it now.

904
00:36:46,226 --> 00:36:47,737
You told me you'd fight
to keep this from happening.

905
00:36:47,761 --> 00:36:49,688
I told you I would fight
to protect your company.

906
00:36:49,712 --> 00:36:51,741
And right now, this is
the best way of doing that.

907
00:36:51,765 --> 00:36:54,410
You're talking
about using my expansion money.

908
00:36:54,434 --> 00:36:55,461
If you don't use it now,

909
00:36:55,485 --> 00:36:57,246
there's gonna be
nothing to expand.

910
00:36:57,270 --> 00:36:59,531
You son of a bitch,
you manipulated me.

911
00:36:59,555 --> 00:37:00,666
No, I told you a war was coming

912
00:37:00,690 --> 00:37:02,201
and that you needed a war chest.

913
00:37:02,225 --> 00:37:03,869
Well, now is the time
to crack it open.

914
00:37:03,893 --> 00:37:07,423
You told me what I wanted
to hear to get me on your side.

915
00:37:07,447 --> 00:37:08,758
You're the same as them.
You're wrong.

916
00:37:08,782 --> 00:37:10,709
I looked you in the eye,
and I told you that I wanted

917
00:37:10,733 --> 00:37:12,234
to save your company.

918
00:37:12,252 --> 00:37:13,346
They looked me in the eye

919
00:37:13,370 --> 00:37:14,680
and told me they wanted
to rip it apart.

920
00:37:14,704 --> 00:37:16,215
You're the same as them!

921
00:37:16,239 --> 00:37:18,267
And you're an naive old man
having a tantrum

922
00:37:18,291 --> 00:37:22,077
because he's not getting
his way!

923
00:37:35,642 --> 00:37:38,871
That expansion was my dream.

924
00:37:38,895 --> 00:37:41,029
I know.

925
00:37:47,737 --> 00:37:51,300
But now it's time to wake up.

926
00:37:51,324 --> 00:37:54,720
Fund the pension, Walter.

927
00:37:54,744 --> 00:38:00,526
Pete Kreeling's vote
stays in our favor, and...

928
00:38:00,550 --> 00:38:03,218
We live to fight another day.

929
00:38:11,394 --> 00:38:12,822
No.

930
00:38:12,846 --> 00:38:15,607
I just wanted to thank you,
you know, for the new office.

931
00:38:15,631 --> 00:38:16,631
It's a downgrade.

932
00:38:16,649 --> 00:38:18,411
Not to me.

933
00:38:18,435 --> 00:38:20,246
I also wanted to thank you
for lunch.

934
00:38:20,270 --> 00:38:22,114
- I didn't show up for lunch.
- I know.

935
00:38:22,138 --> 00:38:23,916
You thought you were
sending me a message.

936
00:38:23,940 --> 00:38:25,251
I was sending you a message.

937
00:38:25,275 --> 00:38:27,286
Not the one you wanted, Jessica.

938
00:38:27,310 --> 00:38:28,671
You see,
because what I heard is that

939
00:38:28,695 --> 00:38:31,646
you don't trust yourself
around me.

940
00:38:31,664 --> 00:38:34,343
If I didn't,

941
00:38:34,367 --> 00:38:36,011
I wouldn't have put you
right next door.

942
00:38:36,035 --> 00:38:38,487
Jessica, say what you will,

943
00:38:38,505 --> 00:38:40,266
but we both know
where this is headed...

944
00:38:40,290 --> 00:38:43,158
You and me watching these.

945
00:38:43,176 --> 00:38:45,660
You think you know me that well?

946
00:38:45,678 --> 00:38:47,329
Well, if I don't,

947
00:38:47,347 --> 00:38:51,166
I'm about to.

948
00:38:51,184 --> 00:38:53,185
Neighbor.

949
00:38:58,024 --> 00:39:02,288
More. More. More. Ah, ah.

950
00:39:02,312 --> 00:39:04,696
Thank you.

951
00:39:10,019 --> 00:39:13,933
Happy corner office.

952
00:39:13,957 --> 00:39:16,792
Open it.

953
00:39:18,411 --> 00:39:20,172
- Is this...
- Me.

954
00:39:20,196 --> 00:39:23,509
As Ophelia.

955
00:39:23,533 --> 00:39:24,777
But I thought you...

956
00:39:24,801 --> 00:39:27,646
Yeah, well,

957
00:39:27,670 --> 00:39:31,567
sometimes bitter memories

958
00:39:31,591 --> 00:39:35,404
become bittersweet

959
00:39:35,428 --> 00:39:38,430
when you share them
with a friend.

960
00:40:14,100 --> 00:40:16,862
- You here to pick up Rachel?
- No.

961
00:40:16,886 --> 00:40:19,754
No, I just came by
to say thanks.

962
00:40:19,772 --> 00:40:21,000
For what?

963
00:40:21,024 --> 00:40:25,704
For not giving me a way out.

964
00:40:25,728 --> 00:40:26,705
You funded the pension.

965
00:40:26,729 --> 00:40:29,908
100%.

966
00:40:29,932 --> 00:40:32,011
You just got rid
of half your war chest.

967
00:40:32,035 --> 00:40:36,738
Maybe, but I also did
what you thought I couldn't do.

968
00:40:38,124 --> 00:40:40,252
I got the vote back.

969
00:40:40,276 --> 00:40:45,024
Maybe now you'll realize that
I'm willing to go the distance.

970
00:40:45,048 --> 00:40:46,191
All you did was make it
to round two.

971
00:40:46,215 --> 00:40:47,476
Oh, so you thought

972
00:40:47,500 --> 00:40:50,229
this was gonna be like
one of those early Tyson fights,

973
00:40:50,253 --> 00:40:54,122
the ones that only lasted
45 seconds.

974
00:40:54,140 --> 00:40:55,200
Remember what happened
the first time

975
00:40:55,224 --> 00:40:57,236
someone made it
out of round one?

976
00:40:57,260 --> 00:41:00,239
And what ever did happen
to Buster Douglas?

977
00:41:00,263 --> 00:41:02,491
I don't know,
but wherever he is,

978
00:41:02,515 --> 00:41:05,601
they can't take that title away
from him.

979
00:41:15,995 --> 00:41:17,145
Hey.

980
00:41:17,163 --> 00:41:19,224
Hey.

981
00:41:19,248 --> 00:41:21,176
What you working on?

982
00:41:21,200 --> 00:41:23,985
You know what I'm working on.

983
00:41:24,003 --> 00:41:25,320
You wanna go home?

984
00:41:29,125 --> 00:41:31,570
Harvey.

985
00:41:31,594 --> 00:41:34,973
Guess that means you're
gonna be working late, huh?

986
00:41:34,997 --> 00:41:37,716
Um...

987
00:41:39,719 --> 00:41:41,947
Thanks to the guy
we're up against.

988
00:41:41,971 --> 00:41:46,118
He is proving to be much tougher
than everyone expected.

989
00:41:46,142 --> 00:41:48,860
- Everyone?
- Not everyone.

990
00:41:53,783 --> 00:41:56,428
He sounds like
a real douche bag.

991
00:42:00,323 --> 00:42:04,436
You know, he's not that tough.

992
00:42:04,460 --> 00:42:06,805
I can work on this tomorrow.

993
00:42:06,829 --> 00:42:10,832
Let's get out of here.

994
00:42:14,671 --> 00:42:18,540
You really gonna
work on that tomorrow?

995
00:42:18,558 --> 00:42:20,375
No, I'm going to work on it
later tonight,

996
00:42:20,393 --> 00:42:23,712
but at least I'll be home.

997
00:42:23,730 --> 00:42:25,213
Think I can take a look at it
when you're done?

998
00:42:25,231 --> 00:42:26,214
I think not.

999
00:42:26,232 --> 00:42:27,626
Just a proofread?

1000
00:42:27,650 --> 00:42:32,387
Ah, still no.

1001
00:42:32,411 --> 00:42:38,411
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man

