Previously on "Suits"...
What do you mean
you can't take the case?
Jessica won't lay out
the money for the man-hours.
One of the victims
was my uncle Keith.
Please.
These people need your help.
I didn't come forward.
They found me.
And I'm not pulling
any associate shit.
Then what do you call
this pathetic excuse
of a candidates list?
I call it inevitable,
because our students can read.
Our future is slipping away,
and offering Jack
name partner or praying
to God that Harvey
just gets Mike off the hook
isn't gonna stop it
from happening.
Then you get your ass
back up to Harvard,
and you make sure Sheila
doesn't show up to that trial.
It's a ticket
to Argentina.
I need you to go there
until the trial's over.
Court's not about bullshit
like this; it's about facts.
And the fact is,
you're not a goddamn lawyer.
Are you saying what
I think you're saying?
Because if you're thinking it,
you're a fool.
You heard her.
She said the fact is, is that
I'm not a goddamn lawyer.
Well, the only way
to change that fact
is for a jury to see me be
a goddamn lawyer.
You try that,
all they're gonna see
is someone going to prison.
It's my call,
and I'm making it.
We have a problem.
They found Trevor.
♪
Please raise
your right hand.
Do you swear to
tell the truth,
the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth,
so help you God?
I do.
You may be seated.
Mr. Evans, how long
have you known Mr. Ross?
Since we were kids.
Almost 20 years.
So you were close to him?
Yeah, he was
my best friend.
Are you still
close to him?
Well, I doubt
we will be after this.
After what?
After you ask me about
the series of events
that have led us all
to be here today.
Well, we'll get to your
history in a minute,
but first, I want to ask you
a question about current events.
Did Mike Ross approach you
three days ago
in an attempt to get you
not to testify against him?
[dramatic music]
Yes, he did.
How exactly did that
conversation go?
[cars rumbling, horn blares]
What are you doing here?
You know exactly what
I'm doing here.
You said you would
not testify.
Yeah, well, that was before
Anita Gibbs dragged me in
and told me she was gonna
put me away for ten years.
I don't give a shit
what she told you.
You said you were gonna
call a lawyer.
Yeah, well, before
I had a chance to do that,
they showed me
what they had,
which is names, dates,
witnesses, and everything else
they need to put me away
for as long as they want.
Wait, wait,
how would they have--
You think I want
to do this?
I don't.
But I cannot risk
prison for you.
And I am telling you
that whatever they have,
Harvey can get you
out of this.
And from what
she told me,
Gibbs can get you
out of this.
She offered you a deal that can
make this whole thing stop.
Now, instead of telling me
not to testify against you,
why don't you think about
testifying against Harvey?
Because unlike you, I would
never do that to a friend!
Yeah, well, unlike you,
when they put me away,
I'm not going to
a white-collar prison.
So if I don't rip you to shreds
up there on the stand,
they're gonna rip me
to shreds behind bars.
♪
Harvey, it's late.
I've had a long day.
So if you don't mind...
We have a problem.
What now?
My condo's on fire?
Mike wants to
represent himself.
Is he crazy?
He can't do that.
That's what
I tried to tell him.
You don't try;
you just tell him.
Yeah, the only problem
with that is,
he knows
it's his decision.
Not to mention, the only
thing that's stopping him
from going to Gibbs
and pointing his finger
at you or me
is his loyalty to us.
So that's it?
He's representing himself?
I'm not saying that.
Then what exactly
are you saying?
I'm saying
I have a plan,
but I need you
to sign off on it.
Oh, whatever it is,
I'm in.
Because if that kid
handles his own defense,
you and I are going to be
the next ones on trial.
♪
[knocking]
If you're here to find out
if Trevor's testifying, he is.
I can handle Trevor.
Harvey,
we've been over this.
And I said we're not done
being over it.
Listen to me, I know that
fool-for-a-client bullshit.
But the thing I'm being accused
of is not being a lawyer.
So if I represent myself,
every second I'm up there,
they're gonna see me
as a lawyer.
And if she rattles you for one
of those goddamn seconds,
they're gonna see you
as a fraud, and they're never
gonna see you
as anything else.
Okay.
I got it.
You said your piece.
It's my call.
I'm done talking about it.
Then we'll do a trial run
to get you ready.
♪
Are you crazy?
You want to waste my time,
not to mention
air our dirty laundry,
in front of the whole firm?
Mike, in a week and a half,
our dirty laundry is gonna be
aired in front of
the whole world.
And Gibbs is gonna
come at you in ways
you've never even
thought about.
Oh, so I get it.
You don't want a trial run
to get me ready;
you want a trial run
to show me that I'm outmatched.
You are outmatched
by me and Gibbs,
and you're afraid
to find out.
I'm not afraid of Gibbs,
and I am not afraid of you.
Then you won't mind agreeing,
if I beat you,
you let me represent you
in court.
[laughs]
♪
Okay, Harvey,
you want to go?
Let's go.
But you better
bring your A game.
Because you might be
the best closer in the city,
but I'm the one
fighting for my life.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ Suits 5x14 ♪
Self Defense
Original Air Date on February 17, 2016
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Thank you.
There he is.
Harold.
What are you doing here?
I know what's
going on, okay?
I know about the trial
coming up.
Then you know I'm
pretty busy right now.
Right, which is why
I wanted to talk to you.
Listen, you're gonna need
someone to testify
that you went to Harvard.
I want to be that guy.
Harold,
that's an amazing offer, but--
Mike, come on, man.
We both know that you
didn't go to Harvard.
But honestly, if anyone
would have asked me
up until this point,
I would have sworn
that you did.
that I saw you
at that--that
party with Gilcrest
or those pizza nights
at Pinocchio's
or pretty much any other memory
I have of that time,
which means, if they put me
up there on that stand,
I'd basically be
telling the truth.
I can't tell you how much that
means to me, Harold, but...
Mike, I want to
do this for you, please.
I know you do.
But I got myself
into this mess,
and I got to get
myself out of it.
Okay.
But listen,
if you change your mind,
you know where to find me.
Ladies and gentlemen
of the jury,
you're gonna be
hearing a lot of things
over the next
several days,
but the truth is,
this case is about
nothing more
than cold, hard--
Innuendo.
And the fact is, I'm capable
of reciting every element
of jurisprudence
in the state of New York.
And yet despite that,
the prosecution is gonna
try to convince you
that I am a--
Fraud, who not only
didn't pass the bar or go
to law school, he didn't
even graduate college.
There isn't one piece
of hard evidence
proving that I didn't go
to Harvard Law.
There's no record
of tuition being paid.
No record
of a Boston address.
There isn't even a simple
picture in the yearbook.
Let's talk about
the yearbook.
As he told you,
I'm not in the yearbook.
Where is Mike Ross?
Though what he didn't
tell you is that
25 other students
are also not in this yearbook.
Are those other students
being charged with fraud?
Of course not, because
we don't put people on trial
for being sick on picture day,
and no matter--
What he says, the fact is,
Mike Ross is not a lawyer.
He's a fraud.
And we will prove that
beyond a shadow of a doubt.
The defense would like
to call its first witness.
Right there--
he's such a non-lawyer,
he doesn't even know
the prosecution goes first.
And you obviously don't know
Jarvis v. the State of New York,
1937,
when calling
of the first witness
is of such special nature
as to disrupt
the flow of the trial
once it's started.
What the hell special nature
are you talking about?
When the defense
wants to call the prosecutor
as its first witness.
Harvey, unless you have
something to overturn this,
I'm gonna need you
to have a seat.
Mr. Specter, you said
there's no record of me
ever having an apartment
in Boston.
Can you explain to the jury
why there's no record
of you ever having
lived there?
I'm not the one
on trial here.
No, you're not.
You're the one in that chair,
so why don't you answer
the question,
or we can stop this whole thing
right now.
There's no record
of me living there
because I sublet up there
when I had my place down here.
So it is possible
that a person not have
a Boston address
without it meaning that
they didn't attend Harvard.
Great.
Thank you so much.
This witness is excused.
And what, exactly,
is your reason
for not having
an address up there?
Unless you're too afraid
to answer my questions.
No, I'm not afraid
of you at all.
My reason is that I chose
to live with my friend
Trevor during that time.
The only problem
with that is,
your friend Trevor has lived
in Brooklyn his entire life.
Exactly a 3 hour and 20 minute
drive from Harvard.
So you're saying
you made that drive every day?
No,
I only went up for tests
because that's
all I had to do.
I guess you needed
some extra tutoring, huh?
You expect these people
to believe that you graduated
from the most competitive
law school in the world
without ever going to class?
See, that's funny,
because you actually
expect these people
to believe
that I never went
to law school at all
and yet still somehow
managed to convince
the smartest lawyers
in the world
to make me their
youngest partner ever.
Whose story is looking
more far-fetched now?
Oh, no answer?
Great.
No more questions,
Your Honor.
I don't know if you've
noticed this or not,
but he's kicking your ass.
And I'm about
to kick back.
Are you two
discussing something
that defense should
be made aware of?
Just talking about
the Knicks.
Now is the prosecution ready
to call their first witness?
The prosecution's first
witness is this affidavit
from every single member
of the defendant's
supposed graduating class.
Objection, Your Honor.
I haven't seen that.
Well, then let me
read it to you.
"We collectively
come forward to swear
"the following regarding
Michael James Ross:
"We never saw him.
We never knew him.
"We never heard of him.
"And it makes us sick that
he's taking the good name
"of Harvard Law School and
throwing it down the toilet.
Please find him guilty
on all counts."
Your Honor, I move to strike
that document right now.
On what grounds?
On the grounds that
it's completely fabricated.
Where's your proof?
Besides the fact that
I actually went to Harvard,
there's no way
you could have contacted
all of those people
since last night.
Then I suggest you call
every one of these people
and put them on the stand.
But when you do, every single
one of them is gonna
look you in the eye and say,
"Who the hell are you?"
♪
What?
No snappy comeback?
You can try to trick
these people all you want.
But the fact is,
you didn't go to Harvard,
and this proves it.
Objection.
He's testifying.
What I'm doing is winning.
All right, that's enough.
I think this is a good time
to take a break.
[gavel thuds]
♪
Louis Litt.
I'm Anita Gibbs.
Yeah, I know
who you are.
Question is,
what are you doing here?
And the answer is,
I don't give a shit.
I came here
to compliment you
on getting rid
of Sheila's ass.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Really?
You think I don't know
what's going on here?
You two were in a relationship,
and when you found out
that it was her
that wrote that email,
you went up to Cambridge
and convinced her to go to
Argentina for
the duration of the trial.
[laughs]
You're out of your mind.
Am I?
You flew to Boston three times
in the last two weeks.
You took two cabs
to her house
and another to within 100 feet
of the admissions office.
You have no proof
of anything.
I don't need proof.
Because while she may
be in Argentina now,
she's not gonna
stay there forever,
which means when
she gets back,
I get you for
witness tampering.
Do me a favor
and leave me the hell alone.
I will.
For now.
But if she's not back
by the start of trial,
I'm gonna assume that you want
to be brought up on charges.
[dramatic music]
You son of a bitch.
This isn't real.
I don't give a shit
whether it's real or not.
You think Gibbs isn't
gonna do things like that?
She is not gonna enter
false evidence, and you know it.
But she is gonna
set up traps for you
to bungle into
like I just did.
This is such bullshit.
You are just pissed because
I was kicking your ass
so now you're cheating.
Me?
You're the one
who testified in your
opening statement
and every chance you get.
Because that's exactly what
me being my own lawyer gives us.
I don't care.
If I represent you
and it turns out that you
need to testify, we can
call you up to the stand.
And if we do that, then
Gibbs gets to cross-examine me
and make me
look like a liar.
Well, I don't know
if you've noticed,
but you're looking
like a liar right now.
And I'm trying to keep you
from looking like a fool.
You know what?
I'm getting pretty tired
of you using
that word with me.
Too bad,
because for all your
bullshit up there, you still
can't produce one person
who remembers you
from Harvard.
So if you want to have a chance
at representing yourself,
get out of my face
and go work on your defense
'cause I got a lot more
where that came from.
[dramatic music]
♪
What can I do for you,
Louis?
- Gibbs knows what I did.
- What?
She knows I got Sheila
out of the country.
She was waiting for me
this morning,
and she threatened to
bring charges against me.
- Did you admit that to her?
- No.
Then she's not gonna
charge you with anything.
Did you hear
what I just said?
She knows I went
to Sheila's place
the same night
she went to Argentina.
And what does that prove?
It proves that I knowingly
bought a witness a ticket
out of the country
in the middle of
an ongoing investigation.
All it proves is, you rewarded
a Harvard employee
who's been steering lawyers
towards this firm
for the last ten years.
Okay, Jessica, Gibbs can
easily go down to Argentina
and ask Sheila--
Louis, listen to yourself.
She's not going to do that.
And even if she did,
it's not witness tampering
if a subpoena
was never issued.
Then Gibbs is gonna say
that I had knowledge
of an impending subpoena;
therefore it is tampering.
You know what, Louis?
I don't give a shit
what Gibbs says.
♪
Where are you going?
Give that woman a taste
of her own goddamn medicine.
Where the hell
are you going?
We've got Mike on the ropes;
we have to put him away.
Sorry, Harvey.
Something more pressing
just came up.
What the hell could be
more pressing than this?
You worry about your shit,
and I'll worry about mine.
Oh, I've got my shit
taken care of.
Well, maybe you do,
and maybe you don't.
But what I've learned
from recent history is,
if you really were Anita Gibbs,
no matter what you had planned,
you'd be planning
something else.
♪
Donna, please,
not right now.
I'm so busy.
That's fine.
I just came by
to let you know that
Jessica had to go out,
so the trial is done
for the rest of the day.
And Harvey wasn't
gonna tell me
because he's
playing dirty.
He's not your enemy, Mike.
He's just doing
what he thinks is best.
Then I'm gonna do
what I think is best.
And what exactly
is that?
Look, Donna,
he may not be my enemy,
and you may not be my enemy,
but as long as we're in
this trial run,
I'm not trusting you
with anything.
♪
That's my boy.
Jessica Pearson,
I wasn't aware we had
an appointment today.
We don't.
I just stopped by to give you
this restraining order,
preventing you from
contacting Louis Litt
without his attorney
present.
And let me guess--
his attorney is you.
Bingo.
So unless you're
going to arrest him,
you so much as text him
without me present,
and you're in violation
of a court order.
You're done driving a wedge
between me and my people.
We'll see how strong
your bond is with your people
when I parade every one of them
on the stand
and ask them point-blank,
"Did you know Mike Ross
was a fraud?"
You think we're gonna have
different answers to that?
No, I think you're all
gonna take the Fifth.
And you're gonna tell yourselves
it implies no guilt,
but in the eyes of the jury,
you might as well
all just stand up there
and say he did it.
So you tell your client
he's off the hook for now.
But the next time I talk to him,
it will be on the stand.
♪
Hey, I got your message.
So here I am.
But let me tell you
something, Mike,
if you're here to ask what
I think you're gonna ask,
gonna be a short conversation.
I need you to say
you remember me from Harvard.
There's just
one small problem, Mike.
I don't remember you.
'Cause you didn't go there,
did you?
Look me in the eye
and tell me that I'm wrong.
God damn you, Mike.
I--I knew it.
Jimmy--Jimmy!
When we first started,
you begged me
to help you
save your career.
No, no, no, no, Mike.
This is not the same thing.
I-I could have
gotten you disbarred.
But it couldn't have got me
sent to jail, and you know it.
I don't care!
All right?
I need your help.
Mike, you are asking me
to perjure myself,
and I don't even know
who you are.
Yes, you do.
I am the same guy you came to
when your aunt needed help.
Wow.
What? So I owe you
for that too?
Yeah, you do.
You and I both know
if I get convicted,
that settlement's
gonna get reopened.
Then why the hell
did you take it, Mike?
Why?
♪
Jimmy,
I took a shortcut, man.
Just like you took
a shortcut once.
Now, if I could take it
all back, I would, but I can't.
And just like
you begged me once,
I am coming to you
and begging you right now.
Please.
Please help me.
♪
No one in their right mind
would do what
you're asking me to.
That's not true.
- Harold come to you?
- Mm-hmm.
But you know Harold
won't hold up on the stand
and I would.
Right?
- Jimmy, I need you--
- Michael.
[sighs]
Look, brother,
I'm sorry.
I really wish I could help,
but I cannot risk
going to prison for you.
I can't.
♪
[cell phone buzzing]
Hello?
Louis, it's me.
Sheila,
I explicitly told you,
"Do not call me until
after the trial is over."
We can't take any chances--
Someone approached me,
Louis.
What do you mean
someone approached you?
At my hotel.
I was in the lobby.
A man came up to me
and started talking.
He said he was
from New York.
He wanted to know
how long I'd been
planning a trip
to Argentina.
Then he asked how long
I was planning on staying
and, finally, did anyone pay
for my ticket
to come down here?
W-what did you tell him?
That it was
none of his business.
Good.
That was smart.
You didn't show them
that they got to you.
Louis, they did get to me.
Listen to me.
They did not subpoena you,
so you did nothing wrong.
You just took a trip.
Now, if Gibbs can prove
anyone did anything, it is me.
And I will do anything
to protect you, okay?
I'm sorry, Louis.
I have to go.
[dramatic music]
♪
I don't believe you.
You're calling Rachel
as your first witness?
I sure as hell am.
Gibbs can't call Rachel.
We took care of that.
We took care of her
going out of bounds
to get Rachel
to turn on you.
We didn't do anything
to stop her calling Rachel
to the stand,
and you know it.
Fine, then I'm
stipulating right now
Rachel's taking the Fifth
to any questions.
Oh, bullshit.
You know as well as I do,
she can't take the Fifth
to personal questions.
So you're just
gonna humiliate her
so you can rattle me?
You're damn right I am.
Gibbs is gonna do
the exact same thing.
She is not gonna
do that to Rachel
in front of a jury, because it
will make her look like shit.
She doesn't care about that.
No, you're the one that
doesn't care about that.
'Cause this is no longer about
what's best for my case;
it's because you don't
want to lose to me.
I'm not going to lose
to you.
You know what, Harvey?
I am--
That's enough.
While you two have been
having your pissing contest,
I've been poring over discovery,
and I came across
the class rankings
from Mike's first year.
Don't tell me--
he's not on it.
- No, he's not.
- Doesn't make any sense.
Yes, it does.
Lola must not have covered
all the bases.
Then we need to get her
to cover all the bases.
Are you out of your mind?
You go to Lola,
you lead Gibbs right to her,
and this thing is over
before it even gets started.
Okay, then we get
Benjamin to do it.
We are not letting another
person in on your secret.
Well, then what do you
suggest we do?
What we were gonna do
with every other piece
of evidence that
makes us look like shit.
We find a way to make it
look like shit.
There is no way that Harvard
accidentally forgets
to put a student on this list.
I say we go to Benjamin.
And I say
I'll lock you in a room
until this trial starts
if you say that again.
♪
Then I guess whoever wins
makes the call.
You go to Benjamin behind
my back before we're done,
and you going to prison
is gonna be
the least of your problems.
♪
Mike, you like you've been
through the wringer.
I have to ask you a question,
and...
I want you to tell me
the truth.
Well, of course.
Do you really think
I should be the one up there
fighting for my life, or do you
think Harvey should be?
♪
I think that...
you're the best person
to make that call,
and that whatever you decide,
I'm with you 100%.
Well, then I need to ask
Benjamin to do something for us,
and Harvey is really
not gonna like it.
♪
Whatever it is,
if you think we need to do it,
I'm with you.
♪
It's done?
Yes.
It won't hold up forever,
but it will hold up for now.
Thank you, Benjamin.
I--
I didn't expect it
for a couple of hours.
I-I haven't had a chance
to get you any bacon.
That's quite all right,
Michael.
This one is on the house.
You know, you never
asked if what
they're saying about me
is true.
I didn't need to.
I knew it was true
the second I heard it.
I don't understand.
All these kids
who went to Harvard,
they never gave me
the time of day.
All they cared about
was letting me know
where they went to school
and I didn't.
You've never
done that to me.
Not one time.
[sighs]
I--I don't know
what to say.
Say that when you're done
and you've beaten this thing,
you won't start acting like some
asshole who went to Harvard.
Well, I mean, can't really
promise you that, Benjamin.
I'll have gone to Harvard.
That's not funny,
Michael.
[solemn music]
♪
[envelope slaps]
Is the prosecution ready
to call its next witness?
Prosecution calls
Rachel Zane.
Objection.
Your Honor, the witness
cannot object to testifying
simply because she intends
to take the Fifth.
The witness doesn't have to
testify because she's my wife.
What?
I have
a marriage certificate here
from the state of Nevada
showing that
the witness and I
were married in Las Vegas
six weeks after
we started dating.
Both of you up here, now.
Where the hell
did you get that?
What do you mean?
You didn't marry her,
and you know it.
Then why do I have everything
I need proving I did?
Because you did some bullshit
to get out of this.
Oh, look who's
crying about it now.
Keep your voices down.
You think
this is a joke?
You try this in court,
Gibbs is gonna prove
you're not married,
and Rachel's gonna
go to jail for perjury.
He's right; you better know
what the hell you're doing.
Who said that I was gonna
use this in the real trial?
I get it.
This is a fake, just like you.
I said keep
your goddamn voice down.
This is as real
as that affidavit was, okay?
Now, you wanted to rattle me;
I've rattled you.
What are you gonna
do about it?
Prosecution calls
Rachel Zane to the stand.
Objection.
We just went over this.
When spousal privilege
is invoked in the moment,
prosecution has
the right to challenge
the validity of the marriage.
- This is ridiculous.
- Objection overruled.
Ms. Zane,
take the stand.
We can skip swearing her in
since she's just gonna
lie about it, anyway.
Objection!
Ms. Zane, if you got married
six weeks after dating
the defendant, why are you
engaged to him right now?
Because we did it on a whim.
And we had planned
to have an annulment,
but once we fell more in love,
we thought that it
might be wonderful
to reveal it to our families
after we were married again.
And how, exactly,
did it go
when you got married
the first time?
We were in Las Vegas--
Yeah, yeah, I don't
give a shit where you were.
What color was your dress?
What color was the cake?
- Objection.
- Who was there?
Were there any witnesses?
Your Honor, he's badgering--
Who were the witnesses?
And what goddamn time was it?
Your Honor,
get him off of her!
- Harvey...
- Tell me right now.
Let the witness answer.
The dress was white.
And the cake was vanilla
with a buttercream frosting.
It was a small ceremony
at around 10:00 p.m.
And I remember
the man who married us
like it was yesterday
because it was the most
special day of my life.
And when you came up
with this story,
did Mr. Ross at least
give you the courtesy of
letting you make up
your own memories
of your supposedly
sacred day?
Objection.
Since, if he represents
himself at trial,
you won't have a real wedding
for at least two to five years.
Harvey.
And I've got
one more question:
did you vow to remain
faithful to Mr. Ross
throughout your marriage?
Yes, I did.
Yeah, then I guess
when you cheated on him
with Logan Sanders,
it means you lied to him
at that non-existent ceremony,
just like you're lying
to all of us right now.
That's enough.
If you want to bring more
outside information
to dispute this marriage,
feel free, but for right now...
this witness is excused.
[gavel thuds]
[dramatic music]
Louis, whatever it is,
it's going to have to wait.
No, it's not gonna wait,
because you said
you'd take care of Gibbs.
I did take care of Gibbs.
Well, then why the hell
did someone from her office
contact Sheila in Argentina?
Louis, they're just
trying to scare you.
And even if she tells them
everything,
you did nothing wrong
with Sheila.
What about what
we did with Mike?
The only proof they'll ever
have that we knew about Mike
is if we tell them.
And when they ask me,
I'm going to take the Fifth,
and you are going to do
the same thing.
That is not good enough.
I don't want
to take the Fifth.
- Excuse me?
- You heard me.
You get called first,
you get up there,
and you look them
straight in the eye,
and you tell them
Mike went to Harvard.
It was your decision
to hire him,
and you stand by it 100%.
What's going on?
What's going on is that
Jessica's happy asking me
to witness tamper,
but when it comes to her
getting on the stand,
she won't--
Witness tamper?
What did you have him do?
She had me move Sheila
out of the country.
Are you crazy?
Look, I did
what I had to do.
Then why won't you do
what you have to do for me?
Because if I did that,
it would open me up to perjury.
If Mike gets convicted,
what does it matter
if you perjure yourself?
Both of you be quiet.
Look who's coming.
Look who it is.
The Three Musketeers.
And we happen to be
in the middle of a meeting.
That's okay; I just
dropped by to let you know
it looks like the trial's
been moved up till tomorrow.
What the hell
did you do?
I went to the judge,
and I said, "Your Honor,
"I'd like to start
this thing before
every single witness
I have disappears."
No way she granted this
without us present.
Oh, you can fight it,
if you want.
We'll wait for Ms. Sazs
to finish her trip.
Oh, Mr. Litt seems
upset about that.
Looks like the wedge
I'm driving between you
is starting to work.
Your wedge hasn't
done shit.
[dramatic music]
And I'm gonna tell you
something else.
You put me on that stand,
and I will look the jury
straight in the eye
and tell them that
Mike Ross is the best
goddamn Harvard-educated
attorney I have ever met.
I hired him.
It was my decision,
and I stand by it 100%.
And everyone that
comes after me
will say the same thing.
♪
You think she bought that?
I don't care
if she bought it or not.
I wasn't bluffing.
And you and Mike
better figure out
what the hell
you're going to do
because the trial
starts tomorrow.
♪
What a coincidence
running into you here
twice in one week.
You can skip
trying to cheer me up,
because it's not
gonna work.
- Rachel--
- I don't want to hear it.
He humiliated me
in front of the entire firm.
Yeah, he did.
But you weren't sure if Mike
could handle this or not.
And at least now,
if he can't,
you won't have to be
the one to tell him.
That is so easy for you to
say, because you have no idea
what it felt like
to go through that.
You're wrong.
I know exactly what
it feels like.
What are you talking about?
Try to imagine how he treated
me when I left him for Louis.
Maybe you do know.
Yeah.
I do.
And...
I also know that,
like nobody else,
Harvey has this ability
to just shut off and not
see you as a person anymore.
Well, that ability
makes me sick.
It's also probably
one of the things
that makes him
such a great lawyer.
♪
[knocking]
- What are you doing here?
- We got a problem.
You mean besides
what you did today?
- Mike, listen to me.
- No, you listen to me.
That was over the line--
The trial starts tomorrow.
What?
No.
Gibbs can't do that.
Technically she can't,
but trust me, we don't
have a leg to stand on.
Fine.
Then I'm filing the motion
to be my own attorney.
- Mike--
- No, I don't want to hear it.
You didn't beat me,
all right?
So you can be second chair or
no chair, but I am first chair.
God damn it, Mike.
You don't know what
you're doing.
Do you really think
I'm gonna let you
protect me after what
you did to Rachel today?
I did that to Rachel
for you,
and if you can't see that,
you can't win this trial.
I can, and I will!
That's enough!
Rachel, it's fine.
I can handle this.
I don't care.
I don't want you to handle this.
♪
What?
You said you were
with me 100%.
Was that a lie?
No, but what Harvey had
to do to me today was brutal,
and whoever ends up
representing you has to do
the same thing to Trevor.
You don't think I can do
the same thing to Trevor?
I know you can.
But I hated Harvey while
he was doing it to me,
and they're going to hate you
while you're doing it
to Trevor.
And, Mike, we can't have
the jury hating you,
but we can let them
hate Harvey.
♪
Mr. Evans, is it true that
you were living with Mr. Ross
in and around the time he claims
to have attended Harvard?
Yes, we shared an apartment
at 5307 Huntington Boulevard
in Brooklyn.
And how exactly
did he pay his rent?
He worked as a bike messenger
and made money on the side
taking the LSATs for people.
Oh, wait, I'm confused.
Why would he
have to resort to that
if he were
a college graduate?
Because he wasn't
a college graduate.
What?
You mean he never
graduated from college?
No, he was kicked out of
college for cheating on a test.
Well, isn't it possible
that while he was
living with you,
he went back to school
and completed his degree?
Well, I don't see how,
since most of his spare time
was spent sitting around
smoking weed with me.
Well, let me
get this straight.
Before he was employed
at Pearson Specter,
to the best of your knowledge,
he worked as
a bike messenger and
a part-time LSAT imposter?
Yes.
One last question,
Mr. Evans.
Is it at all possible
that Mike Ross
ever attended
Harvard Law School?
Not unless they had
a satellite campus at
5307 Huntington Boulevard
in Brooklyn.
♪
No more questions,
Your Honor.
Given that you smoked
all this pot, Mr. Evans,
isn't it possible that
if Mike Ross commuted one day
a week to Harvard Law that
you might not remember that?
I'd remember.
Yeah, maybe you would,
but you'd lie
through your teeth
about it anyway, wouldn't you?
Objection.
Mr. Evans, isn't it true
that you're a long-time
drug dealer and your testimony
today is only happening
because you signed a deal with
Ms. Gibbs giving you immunity?
Doesn't mean I'm lying.
Because you wouldn't lie
just to get out
of going to prison?
No, I would not.
Well, how about if the other
reason was to get back
at someone you've been
jealous of your entire life?
I've never been jealous
of Mike Ross in my entire life.
And I just caught you
in a lie.
Objection, Your Honor.
Mr. Evans, my next move
is gonna be to call
Jenny Griffith to the stand,
and she's gonna testify
that you lied to her for years
about dealing,
and when she found out about it,
she left you
for Mike Ross.
Objection.
Badgering.
She's also gonna say that
you were jealous of his mind
your entire life,
and when you found out
that she left you for him,
you were as jealous
as a human being can be.
Now, is that true or not?
Your Honor.
Let me rephrase.
Is Ms. Griffith going to be
perjuring herself or are you?
Yeah, I was jealous of him.
And if he lied about all of
that, what's to make us believe
that he wasn't lying
about everything else?
♪
No further questions,
Your Honor.
♪
Your Honor, prosecution calls
Donna Paulsen to the stand.
♪
Don't worry, Donna.
She won't ask you point-blank
if you knew Mike was a fraud.
What if she does?
If you lie,
they'll never know.
♪
Ms. Paulsen, it's my
understanding that you arranged
Mr. Specter's interviews for
the position currently filled
by Michael Ross.
Is that correct?
I assisted in
the process, yes.
Did you find it
suspicious that Mr. Ross
wasn't listed on
the Harvard class ranking
from his first year?
- No, I didn't.
- And why is that?
Because I've never been
on any class ranking,
and I'm the best legal
secretary in the city.
Wow, that's a quippy
response, Ms. Paulsen.
But if you were so good
at your job, how would you
allow someone who wasn't even
on the interview list
to get in a room alone
with Harvey Specter?
I'm sure you'll
recognize this list.
After all, you typed it up.
And it looks like his name
isn't on this one either.
No, he wasn't on the list,
but he was smart enough
to talk to his way in,
which is what a good lawyer
does and exactly
what I was looking for.
How exactly did he
talk his way in?
Answer the question,
Ms. Paulsen.
He took someone else's spot.
You mean he said
he was someone else.
You're under oath,
Ms. Paulsen.
May I remind you that
perjury carries a sentence
of up to five years?
Did he say
he was someone else?
- He said he was Rick Sorkin.
- Ha.
So your first introduction
to Mr. Ross was as an imposter?
I didn't say that.
You said he lied
about what his name was.
That makes him an imposter.
Are you going to recant
your testimony?
Don't look at him.
[dramatic music]
No, I'm not recanting.
All right.
So now we've established
that Mr. Ross is a liar.
And now we're gonna find out
if you're a liar.
So, Ms. Paulsen,
to the best of your knowledge,
did Mike Ross go to
Harvard Law School or not?
♪
I'd like to assert
my Fifth Amendment right.
[crowd murmuring]
♪
Don't feel bad,
Ms. Paulsen.
I'm sure others
will do the same thing too...
because...
the defense cannot produce
one person
who can place Mike Ross
at Harvard Law.
♪
The witness could be excused,
Your Honor.
I think we've heard
all we need to hear.
♪
Defense would like to call
Jimmy Kirkwood to the stand.
Objection.
His name was not
on the witness list.
Rebuttal witness.
She just said we can't
produce someone who places
Mike at Harvard,
and I say we can.
Your Honor--
Mr. Specter
is within his rights.
Mr. Kirkwood can
take the stand.
How did you know
he'd testify?
I didn't until just now.
♪
Well, when I first met Mike,
I thought,
"Who is this asshole
who only ever shows up
for tests?"
Cockiest son of a bitch
I ever saw.
But then I really got to know
Mike when we were arguing
over an ethics question
in Professor Gerard's class.
Should a lawyer
who's crossed a line
be given a second chance?
I didn't think so,
but Mike did,
and that's when I realized that
Mike Ross has more integrity
and compassion
in his little finger
than any other lawyer
I've ever met.
And if I was on trial
for my life,
there's no one I'd rather
have on my side
than my fellow Harvard alum
Mike Ross.
Just so we're 100% clear,
was Mike Ross a student
at Harvard Law School with you?
Yes, he was.
No further questions,
Your Honor.
Now we've heard enough.
Ms. Gibbs, I'll give you
24 hours to prepare for cross.
Oh, I don't need 24 hours,
Your Honor.
Mr. Kirkwood, isn't it true
that two days ago,
Mr. Ross contacted you on
the street outside of your
office and the two of you got
into a heated argument?
I have the pictures.
Would you like to see them?
Yes, it's true.
And isn't it also true
that Mike Ross
got your aunt a large
settlement several months ago,
and if he gets convicted,
it's likely
that that settlement
gets overturned?
Objection.
Calls for speculation.
He's a Harvard lawyer.
He's qualified to speculate.
- Overruled.
- No, you're right.
It'd probably get overturned,
but if you think
that's why I said what I said,
then obviously
you don't know me.
So Trevor Evans could lie
because he's jealous,
but you wouldn't lie
for your aunt?
I'm not lying for my aunt.
But you are lying,
because a person
who's telling the truth wouldn't
say they're lying at all.
Objection.
Testifying.
You Honor, I've had enough
of this witness.
He's excused.
And the prosecution rests.
♪
Donna.
Come in.
What can I do for you?
I'm actually here
to see Mike.
Mike's not here.
He went to go
and see Harvey.
[sighs]
- Look, is this about--
- It is about today.
Donna, I--
You know, I always talk like
nothing can get to me.
Well, it did today.
I crumbled up there,
and I hurt Mike's case.
And I'm ashamed of myself,
and I don't know what to do.
Okay.
Here's what you're gonna do.
It's okay.
You are going to
sit down with me
and have a glass of wine
and relax.
Because juries aren't stupid,
and they aren't allowed
to infer anything from what
you said, so they won't.
♪
Harvey, I got to tell you,
I think we got 'em.
Mike, sit down.
What's going on?
We had a good day,
but it wasn't enough.
What are you talking about?
Jimmy came through.
Mike--
Look, I know she landed
a punch with him.
And I'm telling you,
he wasn't enough.
Harvey, all we need
is reasonable doubt.
And if I was on that jury,
I wouldn't have it.
I'd find you guilty.
[scoffs]
That's great.
So you just
called me over here
to make me
want to kill myself?
I called you here because
this is not about doubt.
We need to give them a reason
to want to let you go.
And how exactly
are we gonna do that?
By doing what you wanted
to do in the first place.
[foreboding music]
No.
Now?
Are you kidding me?
It's the only way
to get you to testify
without taking the stand.
And you said if we had to,
we'd put me on the stand.
And you were right.
She's too good at crossing.
Well, it's a great idea,
Harvey; I wish I'd had it.
The only problem is,
they're not gonna let me change
my goddamn lawyer
in the middle of a trial!
And I'm telling you
we need to figure out
a way to make them.
Because if we don't...
We're gonna lose.
♪
You're not allowed
to talk to me.
That's true,
but if you don't tell anyone,
then no one's gonna know,
and I don't think you're
gonna want to tell anyone.
Okay.
What do you want?
I have to admit that until
you got rid of Sheila,
I honestly thought you weren't
part of this whole thing,
but then I did
a little checking,
and I think I can pinpoint
the exact day
you found out
about Mike Ross.
I'm calling Jessica.
They let you resign,
you found out about Mike,
and you used it to return
as a name partner.
And you know what that
makes me think about you?
You're resourceful,
maybe a little sleazy,
but you didn't hire that kid
in the first place.
♪
I'm not turning on
my partners.
You had to blackmail them
to get what you deserve.
That's got to stick
in your craw.
- Go.
- I will go, Louis.
But you know what else I found
out when I was looking into you?
You like the ballet.
You like to go mudding.
You enjoy the creature
comforts in life,
but they don't have comforts
like that in prison.
They're gonna lose this trial.
You know it, I know it,
and they know it.
You have one last chance
to save yourself.
Think about it.
And, uh...
call me.
Before it's too late.
♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man