Previously on... Suits
113 female employees
across all 22 divisions.
You know what they have
in common?
All denied promotions due
to the fact that they're women.
How often does Louis
ask you out?
- Every single day.
- There are laws
to protect you from
sexual harassment, you know.
- What are you doing here?
- Delivering champagne.
I see you can afford it,
since the money
you've been stealing
from our clients
hasn't been going to
your wife's cancer treatments.
Hey, Monica, how's it going?
What the hell are you doing?
Trying to get Monica Eton
to file
a sexual harassment suit
against Daniel Hardman?
I know you think you're trying
to help me, but drop it.
- Did Mike pull it off?
- Yep.
- He suspect you were in on it?
- Nope.
Sign
this confidentiality agreement.
I'll waive my claim.
One-time offer,
take it or leave it.
I decided to farm out the case.
Let me guess. Daniel Hardman.
Please state your name
for the record.
Sloane Moseley.
And what is your position
at Folsom Foods?
This was all established
during my client's first
and second deposition.
I'm sorry.
I'm just getting up to speed.
I like to establish
my own facts.
- Or manufacture them.
- Excuse me?
Let's show opposing counsel
some respect.
Both: [Whispering] Douchebag.
Regional Vice President
of Marketing and Research.
And how many female executives
work alongside you?
- Three.
- Making a total
of four in a department of nine.
Is there a question?
Yes.
What is the ratio
of men to women senior partners
at Pearson Hardman?
What? She has no knowledge
of that.
Then I direct the question
to you.
And I have the answer,
but it's not relevant
to this case.
What do you mean?
Jessica Pearson's hiring
and firing practices are
directly relevant to the case.
If the next question
isn't regarding Folsom Foods,
this deposition's over.
Folsom Foods?
Ah. [Laughs]
So sorry.
As you know, I just took over
45 different cases.
I get confused.
I thought we were deposing
Pearson Hardman today.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Oh, my God. Did...
did I forget to give you
the subpoena?
Pearson Hardman is being sued
for wrongful termination
in the amount of $10 million.
You have been served.
Wrongful termination?
You're lucky you're not in jail.
It's not on his behalf.
It's on Monica Eton's.
I actually got the idea
from you.
Excuse me?
What this firm did to
that woman was unconscionable.
You piece of shit.
Monica Eton deserved
to get fired.
Huh.
The eight women I'm gonna stack
the jury with might disagree
with that.
Not once they learn
she was sleeping with you
while you were embezzling
from this firm.
And how, exactly,
are they going to learn that?
One of the three people
in this room is gonna tell them.
I'm guessing it won't be you.
I'm afraid it won't be
one of you either.
You gonna kill us?
Oh, I won't need to.
You're bound
by the confidentiality agreement
Jessica signed
the night I left.
"All knowledge of any activity
of Daniel Hardman..."
I know what it goddamn says.
You signed it so quickly,
I wasn't sure.
Fine.
I know a shakedown
when I see one.
What do you want?
It's not what I want.
It's what Monica wants.
And what is that?
Payback.
You see, when Mike Ross
brought that trumped-up suit
to her, she was very upset.
It brought back the memory
of what you did to her.
I didn't do shit to her.
That wasn't how she saw it.
Yet you didn't lift a finger
to help her.
I wanted to at the time.
But I couldn't very well attack
my own firm, now could I?
- Never stopped you before.
- Touche.
But you can't mention
that either.
We're done.
Harvey, will you escort
this piece of filth
out of the building,
make sure he doesn't commit
any crimes on the way out?
Oh, by the way, Mike Ross,
virtuoso job drafting
that complaint.
All I had to do was search
and replace "Daniel Hardman"
with "anonymous."
Almost as virtuoso
as the job he did
convincing you Lawrence Kemp
signed that affidavit.
Must stick in your craw...
Having to walk by my name
day after day.
Oh, we'll get to it.
First we had to turn
your old office
into the new conference room.
When Jessica and I
engineered our coup,
she had that sign down
within minutes.
Schmidt, Gordon, van Dyke.
Jessica wanted it down
the second you were gone.
I told her it was too soon.
No.
You asked her to be name
partner, and she said "no."
And do you know why?
Because deep in her heart,
she doesn't trust you.
She trusted me
to kick your ass.
Twice.
[Elevator dings] Maybe.
But I saw that look back there.
She didn't tell you about
the confidentiality agreement,
did she?
[Sighs]
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right
♪ all that time imagine this ♪
♪ The greenback boogie
What the hell
were you thinking?
I don't want to discuss this,
Harvey.
He gave up his partnership,
his money,
and his voting rights.
It was a good deal.
I did it, and it's done.
And now it's come back
to bite us in the ass.
We have to settle.
I am not settling.
Our backs are against the wall,
and we're gonna drain
our resources on a case
that we can't win
just because you boxed us in?
It was
a take-it-or-leave-it offer.
I had one minute.
I wanted to be done
with the man, so I took it.
You told me
never to make rash decisions,
and then you do this.
I told you,
I didn't have a choice.
Did you have a choice when
you decided to keep it from me?
I didn't think
it would ever come up again.
That is not
a good enough reason.
What did he tell you?
He told me you'd never put
my name on the door.
He told me
you'd come after me someday,
maybe even threaten my family
the same way you threatened his.
A little something you never
bothered to consult me on.
I didn't have to.
You'd have told me
to do whatever it took.
- That's not the point.
- Well, what's the point?
You kept it from me.
I let it go
because I knew he was just
trying to get into my head,
the same way he's trying
to get into your head now.
What's gonna happen
when he deposes you,
and you can't tell
the full story?
I don't know, Harvey.
But I trusted you
to beat him before,
and I'm trusting you
to beat him again now.
[Sighs]
Hey, uh, do you have a minute?
That's about all I have.
I'm under pressure.
I've got to get this done.
Yeah, I know.
We're all swamped with this
Folsom Foods thing, but, uh,
I need your help with a case
that's a little more... personal.
I am swamped with Folsom Foods,
but I came in early
to carve out
an hour to work on something
personal of my own.
Hmm, what is it?
Harvard application.
Rachel, that's great.
It's great if I get in,
and I'm not gonna get in
if I don't get this done,
and I'm not gonna get it done
if people keep bothering me.
Do people keep bothering you?
No.
Okay.
So this is going well then.
Less than
1 out of every 12 people
who applies gets in.
What if I'm not
one of those people?
I don't know, maybe you'll
get in somewhere else.
You're kidding me.
I don't want to have
a fallback.
You mean backup?
A logical plan "B"?
Mike, I've been
half-in, half-out
of committing to this for years.
I'm done with that.
Going to law school
is committing.
I don't want to go
to law school.
I want to go to Harvard.
Just because your father
went there doesn't mean
you need to go there too.
That's not why.
[Sighs] You want to work
at Pearson Hardman.
And if I don't go there,
then I can't work here.
You need any help?
No, it's okay.
I'm gonna do this on my own.
- Okay. [Clears throat]
- I'm so sorr...
what did you need help with?
It's okay.
I'm gonna do it on my own.
Donna, I need your help.
With what?
Hardman.
I want you to convince Harvey
to let me
on the Monica Eton case.
I'm sorry, Louis.
I can't do that.
Donna, come on.
He made me look like a fool.
He did the same thing to me!
Well, I need revenge.
[Exhales sharply] So do I.
See, then why won't you
ask Harvey for me?
Because Harvey needs
to handle this himself.
So this has nothing to do with
any residual issues you've had
with me and my past behavior?
No.
Because I never told him.
I never told Harvey
how sorry I was
for trusting someone
that betrayed us all.
- Louis, he knows.
- I mean, that bastard
wouldn't even be here right now
if it wasn't for me.
He'd just be some partner
skulking around,
never having won
if I hadn't voted for him.
Look, it's gonna be okay.
Success is the best revenge.
Bullshit.
Revenge is the best revenge.
- Harvey, where are you going?
It's only 10:30.
- You gonna dock my pay?
- I'm serious.
I've got
some really good stuff here.
First of all, Hardman's
non-compete is still in effect.
He can't even be practicing law.
In New York.
Where the hell
do you think we are?
He's working out of Jersey.
He's got an office of one.
Bank account, car service,
cell phone.
I mean, all of them
are based in New York.
We can fight it.
- That's exactly what he wants.
- What?
Articles of incorporation,
office, landline,
company car, all in Jersey.
He's constructed it,
so we'd be tempted to fight him,
waste our time and resources,
then lose.
Okay, fine.
Then what we need to do next
is dig into Monica Eton.
I think...
Hold on.
You're on Folsom Foods,
not Monica Eton.
Harvey, they're using
the exact lawsuit I wrote,
word for word.
I know how to fight it.
Did he tell you that?
No, he didn't need to.
I read it.
I mean, he didn't just get
the idea from me,
he got the whole execution
from me.
He's doing that because
he's trying to get in your head.
This isn't your fault.
We did this together.
Then let me help you fix it.
I'm sorry.
Those papers can't help me,
and neither can you.
[Car engine starts]
Har...
[doorbell rings]
- Oh.
- Rachel.
Yes, yes. I know who you are.
I just wasn't expecting you.
Um, I don't live here.
You must be here to see my dad.
Yes, I am.
Please, come in.
He's just in the back.
He TiVo'd the game.
- Jets?
- Giants.
Man after my own heart.
[Sports announcer in background]
Why is it the defensive line
is always packed with a bunch
of big, strong, black guys
and the offensive line
packed
with big, fat, white guys?
Well, I don't know.
But looking at you,
you've got a foot
in both camps.
I guess you're not here
to ask a favor.
No. I'm here to do you a favor.
[Pauses game]
Get rid of him
while you still can.
Jessica...
You do not know who you are
in bed with, Robert.
I went to law school
with the man.
Well, he might have been
a prince back then,
but he sure as hell
isn't one now.
Then enlighten me.
Because from what I know,
he left the firm
to take care of his wife,
and when he came back,
you forced him out.
[Chuckles] That's nowhere
near the full story.
What else is there?
I'm listening.
You signed
a confidentiality agreement.
I am precluded from speaking
on that topic.
Then I'm afraid
you're precluded
from convincing me
to take him off this case.
- Robert...
- What's it gonna cost you
to violate the agreement?
Give me a number. Hmm?
I'll assume
it's in the millions.
15.
You said I didn't know the
kind of man I was in bed with?
From the looks of it,
I'm in bed with the kind of man
who's got you by the balls.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
[Unpauses game]
Enjoy your game.
Oh, by the way...
Giants lost by one.
All right, Harvey.
It's the middle of the night,
you wanted in.
What can I do for you?
I need to talk hypothetically.
Is this hypothetically
about a suit being brought
by an ex-name partner
against his old firm?
Because, you know I can't talk about
a case that's on my own docket.
Would you prefer I tell the IRS
about a hypothetical
conversation I had
with an up-and-coming judge
nine years ago?
[Sighs] Give it to me.
The name partner in question
was the one she had
an affair with while he was
embezzling money from the firm.
So bring it up. Make your case.
We can't.
He got you to sign
a confidentiality agreement.
Yes.
But the spirit of the agreement
was to shield him.
If we had a sealed hearing,
how would you rule
on tossing the confidentiality?
- I'm afraid you'd lose.
- Why?
If he were the plaintiff,
it'd be one thing,
but he's the attorney.
I can't punish the woman
for her choice of attorney.
What if he doesn't make
that argument?
He will.
He came to see you too.
Two weeks ago.
Sorry, Harvey.
[Elevator dings]
Excuse me.
I'm here for my...
Oh, I know
what you're here for.
Jessica's deposition.
3:00 on the nose.
I'm nothing if not prompt.
You're nothing
if not an asshole.
Is that why you're sitting
out here?
To call me that?
No. I just wanted to personally
escort you
to the conference room.
Mm. Lucky me.
We'll see about that.
My old office.
Harvey wasn't kidding. My idea.
It took a while
to feng shui the evil out.
Look, Donna, I understand...
You piece of shit.
Is that all you've got?
Oh, I will go right now.
Are you gonna sue me?
Because I don't think anybody
here is gonna testify.
I never meant to hurt you.
You mean when you planted
that memo and got me fired?
I did no such thing.
And any implication otherwise
from within this firm
is actionable.
Yeah, right.
But you never meant to hurt me.
I'd imagine
whoever planted that memo
thought that
you would bring it forward.
And if you had, the only thing
that would have happened
to you is
you would have been scolded.
And Harvey's career
would have been over.
So it really is like that
between the two of you.
You can go now.
Jessica's deposition is
in the other conference room.
[Exhales]
Please state your full name
for the record.
Jessica Lourdes Pearson.
Monica Eton's reviews
from '03 to '07,
all excellent, agreed?
Yes.
Then why was she let go?
That was determined
by a variety of factors.
Was one of the factors
that she was having
an affair with a partner?
I'm so glad
you brought that up,
you little son of a bitch,
because...
Off the record.
Hmm, so soon.
[Whispering]
I told you this would happen.
He's baiting you
into breaching confidentiality.
And I'm ready to bite down
and drag him in with me.
Don't. We can't afford it.
No.
The affair itself
was not a factor.
With whom was she having
this affair?
- I refuse to answer that.
- Why?
Were you in love with him?
In love with him?
I thought
she was bottom-feeding.
I might have actually vomited
when I heard.
Okay, that's enough.
We're not answering
this line of questioning.
Move on.
You said my client's dismissal
was due
to a variety of factors.
And then you said
it wasn't the affair,
and it wasn't job performance.
So I ask you, what was it?
Is it a personal dislike?
Are you jealous of her?
Or do you just hate other women?
Tread lightly, Daniel.
Let's try some questions
your client can answer.
Were you in a relationship
at the time
of my client's dismissal?
Excuse me?
Jessica Pearson's personal
life is not an issue here.
Well, I beg to differ.
And since your client can't seem
to find her words today,
I, for one, can testify that
she was not in a relationship
at the time.
She's always been married
to her job.
And she wants
her female associates
to be equally committed,
so that as soon as they have
anything else in their lives...
in other words, sex...
she cuts 'em loose.
This is bullshit.
- Then tell me differently.
- We're done here.
The truth is,
Monica was younger than you,
prettier than you,
sexually active,
and of child-bearing age...
all of the things you are not,
and you fired her for it.
We gonna talk
about what happened?
- Not tonight.
- Jessica...
Son of a bitch all
but called me bitter and barren.
He did call you that,
but it's only gonna get worse.
And you should have jumped
to my defense
sooner than you did.
I'm your lawyer,
not your husband.
And if I didn't jump in
when I did, we'd be broke.
Look, I told you before,
we need to settle.
And I told you before,
we're not settling.
Don't you see what he's doing?
He's trying to make this case
about gender.
- It's not!
- It doesn't matter.
Look, you can't be
the name defendant
on a gender discrimination case
while we're suing Folsom Foods
for the same thing.
I am not capitulating
to that man.
Then you're gonna look
like a fool.
That's enough. [Elevator dings]
You're not calling the shots,
I am.
And whether you think
my call is wrong or not,
it is still my name
on that goddamn wall.
You.
Hey, um, sorry,
I don't want to bother you
if you're still working
on your application,
but I need a favor.
Uh, no, I finished.
What do you need?
I need to see a transcript
of Jessica's deposition.
- That's confidential.
- That's why I need your help.
- Mike...
- Rachel, please?
I need it.
By the way, congratulations
on finishing your application.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Are you looking for anything
in particular?
- No, not exactly.
- Uh-oh.
- Oh, my God.
- It just keeps going.
It's worse and worse.
She had to sit through this.
Oh, God. This is all my fault.
- Wait, Mike...
- No, I-I used you to get
to Monica, and then I used her,
and now he's taking it out
on Jessica.
Yeah, you couldn't have known
it was gonna lead to this.
- [Sighs]
- It's okay.
No, it isn't.
I need to use this.
Either you print it
or I type it out from memory,
but I have to. Why?
You said you wanted
to go to Harvard
so that you could work
at Pearson Hardman, right?
Yeah.
Well, if I don't fix this,
there might not be
a Pearson Hardman.
You can't talk to me.
Actually, I can.
I don't have any equity
in the firm,
and I'm not working
on this case.
You're an interested party,
and you drafted
the original complaint.
Any judge in the world
sides with me.
Listen, Monica. Monica!
I'm not trying to set you up.
I'm trying to take
responsibility here.
For what?
For doing exactly
what you just said I did.
For drafting
the original complaint,
starting this whole thing off.
I'm... I'm sorry.
No, no.
The only thing you're sorry
about is your little maneuver
backfired.
Yeah, but it didn't backfire
on me.
It backfired on Jessica.
That's too bad.
That's exactly
what I'm happy about.
What? Jessica didn't screw you,
Hardman did.
Daniel Hardman didn't show up
in my office to fire me,
without cause, notice,
or a letter of recommendation.
- She had cause.
- Did she?
When I told her I knew nothing
about Daniel's embezzlement,
do you know what she said?
"I don't care."
And then five years later,
she sends you
to turn me against him.
That's just it, she didn't.
Look at that.
The attack dog defends
its owner.
Blame me,
you can even blame Harvey,
but Jessica had nothing
to do with it.
If you think I'm gonna buy
for one second
she wasn't behind you coming
to me with that lawsuit,
you are even more naive
than I was.
Please just look
at what he did to her.
I don't have to
because I don't care.
Monica.
- Louis.
- How are you?
- I'm fine.
- Good.
You know,
I wanted to tell you...
I can't really talk right now,
Louis.
Right, because you've got
the deposition?
- I'm meeting Daniel.
- Daniel.
Okay, well, it was really...
it was really nice seeing you.
You too.
- A little busy at the moment.
- Monica Eton, I know.
Look,
Harvey didn't want my help,
but I thought
that maybe you would.
Harvey is right.
I need you
on top of Folsom Foods.
This is about Folsom Foods.
What do you have?
If you can get Monica to admit
that her affair was with Daniel,
this isn't
about gender anymore.
Because they
were both dismissed.
A man and a woman.
Puts you back in the driver's
seat on Folsom Foods.
Okay, do you have
a line of questioning?
Right here.
You ready?
He is.
I want you to let him
take the lead on this.
- What?
- Not a discussion.
Where are you going?
Oh, I'm not spending
another moment
in the same room
with those people.
Miss Eton... Him?
You're bringing in
the "B" team?
As you pointed out,
the "B" team drafted
this suit in the first place.
- And ran you out of Dodge.
- Right into Jersey.
Well, if he doesn't do well,
he can always approach my client
outside of her place
of employment, again.
Hmm?
I guess he must
have learned from you
not to always tell dad
what he's up to.
You want to know
what he learned from me?
Not to let some two-time loser
get in his head.
Miss Eton,
there's been a lot of talk
about the affair you had
while at Pearson Hardman.
I have just one question.
Who was that affair with?
I never said I had an affair.
But your lawyer said you did.
Your people said
it was irrelevant.
I didn't, and it's not,
and I have a lot of questions
about it.
Which we won't be answering.
- Well, you'll have to in court.
- We're not in court.
No, but you are on the record.
But since you don't want
to answer the question,
let me ask you
another question.
If you didn't have an affair,
then what reason could there
possibly be
for you to be fired?
Because I was being harassed,
and I made it clear
I didn't like it.
Harassed? By who?
- Don't answer that.
- Oh, no.
My client is going
to answer the question
that your associate asked,
and we're gonna get some things
on the record, right here.
- No, we're done.
- I was being harassed
by Louis Litt.
What?
Go on, Monica.
He asked me out repeatedly,
after I rebuffed him
again and again.
He would stare at me, wait at
the elevator outside my office,
the diner, everywhere.
- Anything else?
- Yes.
He was partner, and I had
to say "no" to him.
And it made me feel disgusting
every single day.
Will people corroborate
your account?
It was common knowledge
within the firm.
Any number of people knew,
including him.
Let the record show
that my client
indicated Harvey Specter.
Monica, I have one more question
for you.
To whom did Jessica tell you
to hand in your resignation?
Louis Litt.
So in conclusion,
you were being
sexually harassed,
it was well-known,
Jessica Pearson dismissed you,
and you were actually told
to hand in your resignation
to the very man
who did the harassing.
Yes.
That statement is entirely true.
Gentlemen?
I get it, that was your plan,
to blame it on Louis
the whole time.
Monica always was
a good lawyer.
Nothing she said in there
wasn't true.
What's it gonna take
to settle this case?
What ever do you mean?
We break confidentiality,
Monica loses,
you get your $15 million.
Tempting.
But we're not gonna do that,
and you know it.
So you want to settle
with Monica
and get out of your jam.
I want a number, and it better
be less than three.
This isn't about numbers.
It's about responsibility.
Monica wants to see
a jury find Jessica guilty.
Bullshit.
You want to see a jury
find Jessica guilty.
Nope.
I assure you, it is Monica.
I don't really care
whether a jury
finds Jessica guilty or not.
You just want blood.
- It's already there.
- Because of you.
Huh. Nonetheless, I smell it.
Allison Holt, Robert Zane
both came after you,
and now you have 45 cases
you can't afford.
So pay me $15 million,
fight Monica, and lose.
Fight Monica and win.
It doesn't matter.
Any way you slice it,
I'm gonna bleed you dry.
[Knock on glass]
They promised a brunette.
Well, I guess there's a few.
I want to talk to you
like a person.
Kenny G?
What's on your mind, Louis?
I know Donna told me that, uh,
you didn't need my help,
and I know we haven't
really spoken
since you ripped up
my letter of resignation.
But I want to help.
I need to help.
Trust me. It's not a good idea.
He's using Monica
the same way that he used me.
And no one knows that
better than me.
I know.
If I could just talk
to her outside
the confines of everything,
you know?
If I could...
I just know I can convince her
to drop this case, I know it.
- Louis...
- Harvey, please.
I'm begging you.
What's this? Just read it.
Mike led the deposition.
[Laughs] Starts off bold.
Oh, he shouldn't have
asked that.
That's a rookie move.
What... what?
"Rebuffed again and again."
She felt disgusted.
"Common knowledge." Louis...
She pointed at you.
- That doesn't mean...
- No, no, no, no, no.
You used to tease me about her.
Remember how I used
to stare at her?
That was teasing.
This is bullshit.
- They're twisting everything.
- They are.
He is.
Drink your drink.
What are you doing here?
I needed some air.
How'd you know
how to get up here?
- Donna. You?
- Donna.
I lied.
- The essay?
- I couldn't do it.
Just think of it
like a closing argument.
Why should they take you?
Exactly.
Why should they take me?
Why do you want to be a lawyer?
Just... don't think, tell me.
- My dad.
- Okay. Why?
Do you remember when I told you
that, when I was a little girl,
people would just tell him
how smart he was?
Right, it had nothing to do
with him being black or white,
he was just amazing.
And I want to be amazing too.
You are.
Am I?
Because every time I sit down
at that keyboard, I think,
"I'm a paralegal.
That's all I've ever been.
That's all I'll ever be."
Did I ever tell you
about my interview with Harvey?
No... But I'm assuming
it went well.
He laughed me out of the room.
- Are you kidding?
- No, I'm not.
He basically told me I didn't
even belong in the interview.
He actually told me to leave.
What did you do?
I decided I didn't give a shit
what the other applicants had
that I didn't.
If I was going
through that door,
he'd have to pick me up
and throw me out.
You must have said something.
Yeah.
Yeah, I told him
I'd be the best damn lawyer
he'd ever seen.
I wish I could have been
a fly on that wall.
Yeah, you have no idea.
[Laughs]
[Chuckles]
What the hell
is wrong with you?
Me?
You tried to settle
with Daniel.
You're damn right I did.
Did you read what happened
in that deposition?
I don't care what happened
in that deposition.
I do. You're out of control.
What did you just say to me?
Mike Ross wasn't ready
for this.
- He volunteered.
- He went to see Monica Eton.
You've done the same.
I'm a senior partner,
not an associate.
Me to you, you to him.
Fine.
You want to know
why he went to see Monica?
I'm sure you're gonna tell me.
Because he doesn't know
the idea to stir her up
against Daniel was yours
in the first place.
He doesn't need to know.
So you don't trust him
with that,
but you trust him to go up
against Daniel himself.
He came to me with a way
to put us back in a position
to win Folsom Foods.
Well, it failed.
We're behind on both.
- Excuse me.
- Mike.
I just wanted to apologize
to you both for yesterday.
It was a good idea,
just didn't have
the right execution.
- What are you saying?
- I'm saying it was a good idea,
but the questions were being
asked of the wrong person.
Three on one.
All for a deposition
of little, old me.
Would you be more comfortable
over there,
where your old desk used to be?
No need. We won't be here long.
Our confidentiality agreement
prohibits most questions.
Actually,
it only prohibits disclosures.
We can ask you any question that
any lawyer who hadn't signed
a non-disclosure agreement
could ask.
We just can't make statements.
I'm sure if you were
to ask Judge Henderson,
say, out by his pool,
he would agree.
There's no court reporter here.
I thought you might want
to talk off the record.
[Camera powers down]
If you ask me anything
about embezzlement,
I'll deny it.
If you bring any proof forward,
it's a violation
of our non-disclosure.
That's why we won't be asking
about your embezzlement.
We'll be asking you
about your affair with Monica.
And if you lie about that,
we won't be the ones who need
to come forward with proof.
Because we found six people
working at the hotel
who are willing to provide it.
No, you didn't.
Room service,
concierge, housekeeping.
You really should tip better,
Daniel.
Maybe you want a cigarette?
Remind you of the woman
you cheated on.
[Camera powers on]
Go ahead. Ask your questions.
Did you have an affair
with Monica Eton
while you were employed
at Pearson Hardman?
Yes, I did.
Any other questions?
I think we're good.
Yep.
You got me to embarrass myself.
But you already did that,
the day you told everyone
in the office
about my affair with Monica.
You and you.
Yeah, I know
what you told Monica
about Jessica not knowing.
But take a good look.
She was behind it.
Who needs a cigarette now?
And as far
as my admission goes?
You're still the one
who fired her,
24 hours after you found out.
That's what a jury's
gonna focus on.
Nobody's gonna care
about what I did.
You piece of shit.
There's the fire
I helped nurture.
You didn't nurture
a goddamn thing.
You don't teach.
You don't inspire.
You don't mentor.
All you do is betray.
Like you betrayed me
at that last vote.
- How dare you.
- How dare I what?
You were more than happy
to help out
when it served your purposes.
I voted the way
I did the second I realized
it was all a lie.
And look how it turned out.
You're a senior partner now.
You're welcome.
You think I give a shit?
I think that's all
you ever cared about.
You know what I cared about?
Monica.
She was so smart
and so beautiful.
And I knew she was
out of my league,
but I kept trying
because I just thought
if she just got to know me...
and then I found out
that whole time she was...
- With me.
- Yeah. With you.
Why are you telling me this?
I want you to know exactly
what it is that you twisted,
so you know exactly what it was
that put me over the edge.
Are you threatening me, Louis?
Threatening you?
No, I'm telling you.
You ever do anything
to me ever again,
you ever so much as tell me
the incorrect time,
I'll kill you.
I will rip your smug face
off your fat neck,
and I'll kill you.
You here to depose me again?
Didn't go too well
for you last time.
No, I'm here to say I'm sorry.
You were right...
about Jessica.
You really didn't know
it was her.
Welcome to the world.
Stings, doesn't it? Yeah.
It does.
So you came all the way here
just to tell me you're sorry?
No, I didn't.
Jessica was wrong to fire you,
but she didn't fire you
because you're a woman.
She fired you
because she didn't trust you.
- I know that.
- So then you also know
that keeping this suit alive
is sticking it to her.
That's the whole point.
No, the whole point
is that she's not
the only one
you're sticking it to.
What I said about Louis Litt
is factually accurate.
And if you think I'm gonna drop
the case because of him, I'm...
I'm not talking about him.
I'm talking about the 113 women
who are suing.
Folsom Foods right now
for gender discrimination.
Those cases
are their own thing.
They're being told
they can't get where they want
because they're not
good enough.
That has nothing to do with me.
[Scoffs] Who's being naive now?
He's using your suit
to drive us into the ground,
and driving us into the ground
means losing these cases.
What do you want?
Just read these files.
Decide for yourself.
These women deserve to be
treated the same way you were?
What makes you think
I would even care?
I'm naive, remember?
Mike Ross went
to see Monica Eton again.
- At your direction?
- On his own.
Goddamn kid.
He's another you. Not exactly.
He went to apologize for lying
to her the first time.
- He didn't lie.
- No.
We did.
Like the two of you lied to me
about him being a lawyer?
How about we call it even?
It's nowhere near even.
- Isn't it?
- What's this?
He got her to settle.
- There wasn't an offer.
- There is now.
This does not get us off easy.
Hell of a lot less
than $15 million.
- She doesn't deserve a dime.
- Doesn't matter.
I was right to fire her.
That's not what this is about,
and you know it.
He made me look
like a fool with her then,
and he's made me look
like a fool with her now.
No one cares what he said
in that deposition.
You think I give a shit about
what he said in that deposition?
I meant getting me
to sign that agreement.
You can't win every move.
I should have seen it coming.
You made a decision
under the gun.
- I let him put me there.
- We beat him
because you kept your cool
when I wanted to lose mine.
Keep your cool now,
sign this agreement,
and let's beat him again.
You look happy.
So do you.
The pressure's off.
No more essay.
- You finished it.
- I had a breakthrough.
Uhoh. What was it?
I'm a paralegal.
Rachel, please tell me
that that doesn't...
No, I don't...
I don't mean that in a bad way.
I mean it in a great way.
Do you know what the length
of an average corporate lawyer's
career is?
30 years.
Wrong.
- Whoa!
- Because they hate it.
Not me.
I've been here longer than 75%
of our associates,
and I love it.
Which means when you get out,
you won't be disillusioned.
No. I'll be unleashed.
And that's what I told them
in my essay.
In other words...
You're gonna be
the best damn lawyer
they've ever seen.
- I'm going to Harvard.
- You really are.
[Laughs] Yeah. Yeah.
What?
Oh, nothing.
It just... just hit me.
You're not gonna
be here anymore.
I mean, you'll...
you know, you'll be there.
Boston. Cambridge.
I guess I'll just have
to get used to that.
I guess I'll have
to get used to that too.
[Elevator dings]
You going home?
Unless there's
something pressing?
- No, I was just gonna, uh...
- Hey, what happened here?
What are you talking about?
- It's off.
- Looks fine to me.
It isn't.
Wait a second.
Your eye for detail?
One record askew, and I don't
hear the end of it for a week.
You scratched my Miles Davis.
It was me.
- What were you thinking?
- I was pissed.
- You're so emotional.
- I lost my cool.
- You shouldn't have done that.
- I know.
I shouldn't have hit Hardman.
- You didn't.
- I did.
- When?
- Right before Jessica's depo.
- Closed fist?
- Open palm.
- Bitch slap!
- Damn straight.
How'd it feel?
Good enough
that I did it again.
[Laughter]
Look at you. You're beautiful.
You have a date?
As a matter of fact, I do.
Bitter and barren, my ass.
Someone special?
You never know.
Could be the one.
[Elevator dings]
Oh, and why don't you go ahead
and take that damn name down.
You keep showing up here,
Laura's gonna kick your ass.
Oh, you'd be surprised at
the strength of a jealous woman.
[Laughs]
She has nothing to worry about.
[Chuckles]
Once again, I guess you're
not here to ask for a favor.
You want to know who Daniel is?
Read his own words.
He's not the first man
to have an affair.
Maybe the first
to turn around and sue
his former colleagues
for his own actions.
[Laughs] That's all you have?
Tip of the iceberg.
Believe me, he will turn on you
if you let him in.
No one's letting him in.
He's a contractor.
He's not a partner,
he's not of counsel,
he's not an associate.
I'm telling you,
kick him off of Folsom Foods.
Don't let him in your house.
And I just told you,
he's not in my house.
You're in my house.
What if our houses
were the same?
Oh, now.
You're moving pretty fast.
I told you,
my wife's the jealous type.
You offered a merger once.
Let's settle these cases,
get it done.
You hate him that much?
Yes or no?
Here's the problem.
Merger looked good before,
but now we have you
on the ropes.
So when Pearson whatever
goes under,
we'll pick up the pieces
for free.
You do not have us
on the ropes.
Oh, you'll get it tomorrow.
We're filing to try
seven different cases
in seven different jurisdictions
all at the same time.
- Rocket docket.
- Yeah.
It was Daniel's idea.
He'll see you in court.