Hey, Mike, it's Rachel.
I know I shouldn't
be doing this.
I know you're seeing Jenny,
but I can't stop thinking
about the kiss,
and I can't go back.
[Elevator dings]
Morning, Jessica.
Ms. Pearson.
Hey, I just wanna
thank you so much
for keeping me on despite the...
I guess, I just
want to let you know
that I'm gonna work hard,
and I'm gonna... you know,
I'm gonna make you proud.
Not... not like a son...
you know...
I mean, we don't really
look that much alike, I guess.
That's a... that's
a strange thing to say.
Uh, I just... what I meant
is that I really appreciate
everything that you... okay.
[Construction sounds]
- Hardman?
- One would assume.
- Did he ask you?
- No, he did not.
He needs your signature.
And yet there was a wall
here yesterday.
Well, at least he didn't ask
for his office back.
I wouldn't have given it back.
I wouldn't have given
yours back to you.
Unless you asked really nicely.
Isn't that...
- Mine.
- Shot across the bow.
No, an act of war.
I love the smell of napalm
in the morning.
[Sighs]
It's not taupe.
The color, the walls.
Hardman asked for taupe.
I mean, it might be tan,
or beige with a hint of mauve.
But it definitely isn't taupe,
and don't try to tell me
that it is.
Hey, Louis, what color shades
would go well
with these taupe walls?
- Enough.
- I didn't even say anything.
Did you want something?
Yes, chain of command
is everything to me.
If I don't know
who to answer to,
I might as well be living
naked on a kibbutz
in the middle of Africa.
An option worth considering,
though we'd miss you.
[Mouths silently] Not really.
Your point?
Who do I work for?
I assume I work for you,
but Hardman just asked me
to personally summarize
every case at this firm.
And I was hoping maybe
that you can
let him know that
I answer to you.
You do answer to me, Louis.
And Daniel and I are
on the same page on this.
You're the right man
for the job.
Well, thank you,
that's all I needed to hear.
Why'd you lie?
Because you don't
let the children know
that mommy and
daddy are fighting.
Uh, Rachel.
Hi. I'm busy.
Oh, okay. How's it going?
Busy, so if you don't mind, I...
I need to talk to you
for a second, okay?
- Okay.
So Zane, I need you.
In my office. Now.
- You were saying?
- I just, um...
What part of "now"
wasn't clear?
Ugh.
By the time I'm in my chair.
I should probably go.
No, I...
I got your message.
[Whispers] Yes!
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right
♪ all that time imagine this ♪
♪ The greenback boogie
We're taking the offensive.
Good, give me a gun
and tell me where to point it.
Hardman has designs on my job.
He's gonna need a power base.
I need to make sure
every department is happy.
I can't do that alone.
Well, that's where I come in.
Everybody loves me.
Not real estate.
There was a thing once...
with a guy.
With a couple of guys.
But anywhere else...
No, contracts
thinks you're a dick.
Their word, not mine.
Why don't you join us?
Oh, thanks. Love to.
- Taxes?
- Oh... no.
- Mergers?
- Hate him.
- But I...
- Didn't work.
- Really?
- I am tied in, Harvey.
There are a lot of underbelly
things that I can tell you,
but trust me,
this is not one of them.
- Even Norma knows.
- What?
People just don't like that
he's right all the time.
You think I like it?
What's his standing
in bankruptcy?
Excellent. I think.
We don't do a lot of work
with bankruptcy.
Remind me to fire you.
Remind me to give you a raise.
Bankruptcy.
I need you to court
Paul Porter.
You don't have some hot coals
I could walk across instead?
I don't like him either.
He's always been dubious of me.
I don't know if it's because
I'm a woman or black or maybe
he just doesn't like...
Your overbearing nature?
Your holier-than-thou attitude?
This is not a joke, Harvey.
How this is gonna
go down is he's...
I know, he's gonna
worm his way in,
and then one day,
call for a vote.
And when that day comes,
every vote will count.
- Even Paul's.
- Hardman is awesome.
I mean, he, um, brought in this
omelet bar for the associates,
but it's no... big deal.
Really good.
This pineapple was growing on
a plantation on Lanai yesterday.
Do not trust it.
Don't trust the pineapple?
Hardman.
Would you... come on.
- I don't want it.
- Are you serious?
You're afraid of the pineapple?
I know it's got a rough
exterior, but it's all sweet
on the inside, I promise.
"Come on. I love you, Harvey."
It'll be good for you.
- Mmm.
- See?
It's spectacular.
But this doesn't change
the fact
that this is what he does.
He's coming back and people
are gonna have to choose sides.
Can I choose his side?
Sure.
Support a man you never met
over a partner
who knows you never
went to Harvard,
knows you're not really a lawyer
and is keeping you on anyway.
Jessica it is.
Ready to serve.
I need you on Paul Porter.
- The bowtie guy?
- Every case he has...
read, summarize,
find weaknesses.
I want to know
everything he knows.
- What, is he getting fired?
- Nope.
He's getting lunch.
So, Hardman's back.
It's interesting stuff, huh?
Lots to talk about.
Do you have a question, Louis?
Yes.
I mean, you know Jessica.
That's not a question.
- She seems bothered.
- Huh. Still not a question.
Hardman was managing partner,
now she's managing partner.
Do you even know
what a question is?
Donna... look.
I need information.
Now I wanna know what
the whole story is
so I can formulate
some sort of strategy.
You mean formulate
whose ass to kiss?
I have two house seats
to the stage reading
of a new Albee play.
- Edward Albee?
- Yes.
Meryl Streep... [Gasps]
And Glenn Close.
No!
- We can go.
- No. No.
I cannot tell you
what I do not know, Louis.
Okay.
Well, you know where they are.
Curtain's at 8:00.
[Clears throat]
[Clears throat again]
Hi.
Wait a minute,
I kiss you like that
and all you have
to say to me is "hi"?
Come on, admit it.
I kind of rocked your world.
Look, Mike,
it was a good kiss, but...
Oh...
Jenny?
We broke up.
It turns out I kind of have
feelings for this other girl.
So... it's over?
Well, um, in that case,
then, yes, it was a good kiss.
But just so we're clear,
I rocked your world.
You did.
[Whispering] Now tell me
what would you say...
[Loudly]
to helping me with my work
in a professional capacity?
Smooth.
Actually, you know what,
you could.
I have to summarize all those
cases in bankruptcy over there.
It's funny because
I have to summarize
all of the cases at the firm.
For Hardman.
Ooh.
So you don't like him. I don't.
You wanna tell me why
over dinner?
- Are you asking me out...
- On a date?
Yeah, I am.
To talk about Hardman?
Hardman who?
No, I wanna talk about
our kiss.
And when I say, "talk about,"
I mean repeat.
[Whispering]
And when I say, "kiss," I mean...
[loudly]
Redacting all those phone calls
in the Slessinger filing.
Mmhmm. Getting better.
- Quick study.
- A date it is.
And by "date" I mean...
- Okay, no more of this.
- Yeah, of course.
So this is what it's like, huh?
This is what what's like?
Being closed by Harvey Specter.
I don't resent it.
It's a great meal, great table.
But let's not pretend
it's not self-serving.
Hardman is back.
Jessica doesn't want
to go back to the kitchen.
Jessica Pearson
was never the "housewife."
You know where
my office is, Harvey?
46.
I've been knocked down
three floors in five years
on Jessica's watch.
We have to look into that.
I don't want a new office.
I want respect.
What you want is for someone
to help you with Madison 25.
You've done your homework.
You are about
to lose a huge client, Paul.
I don't want to close you.
Let me close him.
The problem is Tom Klapperich.
He's like you.
He thinks he knows
better than everyone.
Truth is he doesn't know his ass
from a hole in the ground.
He needs to declare bankruptcy
and he doesn't wanna hear that.
Well, let me keep him
in the family
in exchange
for backing Jessica.
Well, you close him,
then we'll talk.
That's not so reassuring.
You came to me.
I didn't come to you.
I'll see you on the first tee.
No, you won't.
Oh, is this where
you make your threat?
I've had the carrot,
now I get the stick?
That's not my style.
The person you're gonna meet
on the tee is Fred Couples.
And just so we're clear,
that's being closed
by Harvey Specter.
Let's talk football.
Peyton Manning goes down
you lose your first 13 games.
You gotta protect your assets
and build for the future.
You don't wanna pay
28 million for a guy
who may not play next year.
So what do you do?
You move on.
The season isn't over, Harvey.
You're 200 million in the red
with 1/4 billion due
in two days.
Madison 25
is going to be built.
Madison 25 should be built,
but the market's changed.
Vacancies are up,
rents are down,
and you can't take out
a loan against your future
if the money's
never gonna flow.
It's time to protect
your franchise.
Really? I should just skate
while the hundreds of
contractors and subcontractors
that I've made financial
commitments to,
they should just wait in line
with their hands held out,
hoping for 50¢ on the dollar?
They know how
the business works.
Look, I know that Paul feels
I should protect myself.
I should protect
my family business,
but I want to protect
my family name.
There's no shame
in declaring bankruptcy, okay?
It's a tool that
will allow you to survive.
Wanna know the kind of guy
I am, Harvey?
I'm the kind of guy,
that when the clock says,
"The game's over, take a knee,"
that's when
I throw a hail Mary.
Everybody throws a hail Mary
when they got nothing to lose.
You got something to lose.
I like long odds.
Let's just say,
I won't declare bankruptcy.
What are my other options?
I have an idea.
You were right...
about Hardman and Jessica.
- You want something from me.
- I do.
Mike needs an extension
on a $1/4 billion loan.
And you want me to believe
that you're here for Mike?
Yes.
- Mm-mm.
Harvey needs me.
I know you're amazing
at dealing with banks, Louis.
[Laughs] What, do you think
I'm gonna fall for that shit?
I mean just, like, the best.
What bank?
- National Metropolitan.
- The gatekeeper?
Elaine Cohen?
[Chuckles] Exactly.
So, you think
you can get him in?
Well, you know
I can get him in.
But you also know
I can keep him out.
Okay, what's it gonna take?
Five details
of the Pearson Hardman divide.
- No. No.
- Three? One?
One.
And I get the Albee tickets.
We get the Albee tickets.
Tell a soul, deal's off.
Done.
I love Tom.
I love Madison 25, really.
But I'm afraid if you look
at the fine print,
the terms of the loan
are what they are,
and what they aren't
is subject to renegotiation.
Are you kidding me?
The terms of loans
are adjusted all the time.
And you can see
he has the assets.
What I see?
Is that I'm gonna have to give
you a 50% haircut on that.
That is not liquid.
You're never gonna
be able to sell
a minority partnership interest,
and that...
a monkey could tell
you could never monetize that.
You know what else
a monkey could tell you?
You're about to ruin a property
that will make you millions.
I'm so sorry, gentlemen,
but this is not 2007.
We don't play that game
anymore.
The days of you
high-flying people
claiming you're richer than God
when all you're really doing is
moving assets around are over.
Today we're gonna take
a look up your skirt
and see what you have.
And I'm afraid
you don't have much.
- She actually said that?
- Yes.
Please don't make me relive it.
As it is, I may drink a lot
on our date.
You know,
if we're really gonna do this,
we should probably be careful
talking about it here.
Oh, you're right. Yeah.
We should definitely set some
dating ground rules.
You're not taking me home,
to my place or yours.
Whoa, okay, I'm not talking
about ground rules for sex.
I'm talking about ground rules
for keeping this thing quiet.
Oh. So you think if we went
to my place or yours,
that means sex?
Uh, no. I mean...
you... [Laughs]
Uh... [Clears throat]
What I meant was that I know you
didn't want to date anyone
in the office, and I assume you
have a reason for that.
Oh, okay, there is.
There's a story.
I see it right there.
There's no story there.
I dated someone here once.
It didn't work out. That's it.
No more questions.
Those are my ground rules.
Hmm, note to self:
Touchy about dating history.
Wow, I smell pheromones
in the air.
Which suggests to me, Ms. Zane,
that you failed to grasp
the importance of the task
that I assigned.
Or unless you're done.
- Well, I...
- No?
You do realize you asked her
to summarize every case
in the firm, right?
I'm so sorry,
was I talking to you?
Because I already
did your job for you.
Actually,
the bank didn't budge.
I got you in, Michael.
What, do you expect me
to do everything?
Now, do I have to gather
every first year
and make them stay the night
because the paralegal
was too busy flirting
and couldn't get it done?
Actually, all the associates
are leaving early tonight.
Excuse me?
Yeah, Hardman invited everyone
to his box at the Garden.
Springsteen.
The boss?
Wait, didn't he invite you?
You think I want to spend
my evening with a bunch of
douche bag associates
at a concert
given by a goddamn
octogenarian?
Get it done.
If I wanted to sink his
business to keep his business,
I could have done that myself.
Hello, Paul.
Make yourself at home.
You made him think he could
risk, not just this project,
but everything he owns,
on a personal guarantee.
Are you crazy? What I am, Paul,
is working my ass off
to make your client happy.
You think I haven't
tried everything
to keep his dream alive?
The fact is, the bank
is going to foreclose.
Tom needs to be protected,
and your plan
is too big a risk.
For you, yes, but not for Tom,
and as I understand it,
we work for him.
[Laughing] No, no, no, no.
I work for him.
You are working for me.
I said he needed
to declare bankruptcy,
but, oh, you...
you played it your way.
Well, Jessica may give
you free rein to do that,
but I can't imagine
Hardman will.
You know, Paul, couples passed
on a little tip for you.
He said your game was weak
because you were too cautious.
I said, "It's not your game,
it's who you are."
Harvey, I may have been
knocked down to the 46th floor,
but bankruptcy
is on the rise.
My influence in this firm
is not nothing.
You get Tom
to sign those papers.
Is that a threat?
I don't make threats.
I just do what I do.
You find anything?
Oh, I'm gonna make
Paul love you.
That's doubtful. He got wind
of our little maneuver.
- [Laughs]
- What?
You said "got wind."
[Clears throat] Anyway,
I have another maneuver.
A better one.
Paul says we tell Tom
there's no other way.
But there is another way.
Oh, wait, you don't even want
to hear it?
Of course I want to hear it.
Since when do I take marching
orders from a bow tie?
There are eight projects
being built
in the two blocks
around Madison 25.
Every one of them
started after it.
Madison 25 is the centerpiece
of the whole development.
If it's not finished,
they're all worthless.
That's not the bank's problem.
But it is, 'cause guess
what six of these buildings
have in common.
National's backing them all?
Doesn't make sense for them
to foreclose and devalue
all their other projects.
Unless they have
another agenda.
Huh, I wonder where we could
ever find evidence of that?
Think that helps us?
I think we can take this
to the bank.
Now, you see, that's funny
because we're actually going
to a bank.
That's good.
Twice in one day, Mr. Specter.
I understand how
your client must feel.
Actually,
he's feeling fantastic.
You know why that is?
'Cause I told him the balloon
payment's going away.
Okay, I'll bite.
Why is it going away?
Because as much
as people hate lawyers,
you know who they hate more?
Bankers.
After all, you were the ones
that got us into this recession
in the first place, right?
Oh, gentlemen.
I do not need a history lesson.
Then let's talk
about the future.
What happens to Madison 25 after
you force it into bankruptcy?
Maybe someone steps in
and finishes it.
Someone whose recent
merger leaves them
needing a large
downtown address?
Oh, now that you mention it,
there's a little item
in your shareholder letter
about the search for
a new corporate headquarters.
- Yeah, I like to read.
- Well, I don't...
You intend to leverage
this foreclosure
to get a prime piece
of real estate at a song.
You see, Elaine,
we looked up your skirt.
And the six clients
you represent
surrounding Madison 25...
well, it turns out
Pearson Hardman actually
reps three of them.
And when the other three find
out about what you've done,
which will happen right after
I leave here,
we'll rep all six.
And when we move
their business elsewhere,
they'll take roughly, mm...
Mm, a shitload of money
out of your bank.
- Shitload?
- Well, give or take.
It's important that nobody
knows about this.
I've never...
done anything like this before.
Louis, there's nothing
to be ashamed of.
Exploring your options
is something
everybody does these days.
Sometimes you're
in a relationship,
they take you for granted.
You shouldn't be taken
for granted.
I wouldn't take you
I've never even
considered this.
Really?
People do it all the time.
Well, not me.
I never even let myself
think it, let alone...
Sometimes, Louis,
the only way to move on
is try something new.
[Chuckles]
You're trying to seduce me.
I'm merely saying,
if Jessica Pearson can't see the
quality of the work that you do,
I know half a dozen firms
who will.
Litt, nothing, and nobody.
I mean, who does
she think she is?
So... high and mighty.
The question isn't,
"Can I get you an offer?"
It's, "How good an offer
can I get you?"
Uh, solicitation.
Drugs and prostitution,
that's what you think of me?
I've guessed everything else.
Okay, what were
you arrested for?
Uh, jaywalking? Murder?
- [Imitates buzzer]
- Spill it.
Nope, mm-mm.
I will have to remain
a mystery to you.
So, um...
it was a nice date.
Great restaurant.
- I actually picked it myself.
- Did you?
I actually asked Donna myself.
See, honesty,
I-I love that in a man.
Uh.
- Um...
- [Clears throat]
Look, I know that
we joked about not
going home together...
I think you were right, so...
you know, if we're
gonna do this, let's...
let's do it right.
Okay. [Sighs]
Yeah. Let's do it right.
Good night.
[Chuckles]
[Knock at door]
Remind me to move.
No forwarding address.
Come to think of it,
how did you get my address
in the first place?
That's a nice tux.
Where were you tonight?
It's not where I was,
it's where I'm going.
You're going out now?
Oh, I know, it's already
past your bedtime.
- [Laughs]
- Go.
So listen,
everything became clear
tonight, okay?
- I was out with Rachel...
- Oh, gosh, here it comes.
Days of Our Lives.
I'm serious, okay?
I need to... I need to talk
to you about this.
I need to tell you something.
Listen...
I need to make sure that
you understand that I...
Look, I understand.
I think we've covered this.
I'm not interested
in your personal life.
I realize that
because you don't have one.
Oh, yeah, great, you're
an international man of mystery,
but I'm not you, all right?
I want a personal life.
And I don't want
to be a liar, so...
I'm gonna tell Rachel.
Everything.
No, you're not.
All these lies keep coming
back to haunt me, Harvey.
All right, I-I can't do it.
I-I can't live my life
that way.
I wanted to tell you,
now you know.
[Chuckles]
Have fun in Monte Carlo.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
- Harvey, please...
- After everything I did
to keep your job, you're just
gonna start spreading it around
that you're a fraud?
I'm not spreading it around.
I'm telling Rachel.
She's on our side.
No, she's not.
Because when you
do something stupid,
which won't take very long,
you don't know what she'll do.
Harvey, I understand...
No, what you fail to understand
is our firm is under attack.
And if this gets to Hardman,
we're done.
You, me, and Jessica.
You want to take down
the firm, Mike?
So you can get laid?
Hey, maybe for you
relationships are all about
getting laid, but not for me.
I actually care about her.
Weren't you just
with that other girl last week?
Isn't that what led
to Jessica making me
fire you in the first place?
What are you saying?
You're saying that
I can't date Rachel?
Date Rachel!
Or don't, I don't care.
But you're not gonna tell her.
I can't be in a relationship
based on a lie.
Then I guess
you have your answer.
But being honest
with her about this?
- That is off the table.
- There is no "about this."
I'm either honest with her,
or I'm not.
You tell her, and you're done.
[Door closes]
[Knock at door]
I really do need to move.
I'm telling you, you better
be here to tell me that I was...
Jessica. Come on in.
I just got a call
from the bank.
And you ran right over
to tell me I was awesome.
You are decidedly not awesome.
Oh, I beg to differ.
I just strong-armed one of the
premier financial institutions
in this country into allowing
our client to pursue his dreams.
That's almost patriotic.
Did you really miss the point
of what I asked you to do,
or can you just
not help being a dick?
My word this time.
Jessica...
Your job was
to make Paul happy,
not take over a case
and do it your way.
- The client's way.
- No, it's the client's way
because you told the client
it could be done.
And I was right!
And yet the experts,
the people I pay
to know bankruptcy
feel that Paul's client...
oh, yes, Harvey,
Paul's client...
stands to put more money
at risk
when he can get out now
and move on.
This is better.
This is a win-win.
No, it's lose-lose,
and I'm not losing this one.
You are not to pitch this
to the client.
- I can't keep it from him.
- You're not hearing me, Harvey.
This isn't a discussion.
Tell the client it didn't work.
You tried, you failed.
Move on.
I'm sorry if Paul's ego
is bruised...
This isn't about his ego.
It's about yours.
Make it go away,
and then walk away.
I even told him
about the time I got arrested.
It's crazy, it's like
we can talk about anything.
That's, um... that's great.
I can tell you're nervous.
Don't be.
We're gonna find
a secret meeting spot
somewhere outside
of the office.
No one here will have
any idea what's going on.
Watch this.
Good morning, Mr. Ross.
Eh... Uh, morning.
You still need
some work on that.
Harvey told me.
I know you work for him,
but he's wrong about this.
If he really cared about me,
he wouldn't be
handing out ultimatums.
Ow.
Do you like this office?
Sure.
Do you know how much Harvey
likes this office?
Harvey loves this office.
But for you, he was willing
to give it up.
He's giving me his office?
How do you think he kept
your job, fraud man?
Hmm? Because Harvey said
it was a package deal.
She fired you, she fired him.
So before you go mouthing off
about him not caring about you,
you think about that.
Wait a minute.
He did that for me?
[Sighs] I just...
what... what am I supposed
to say to her?
I mean, Rachel and I are both
finally in the right place.
I told her that I wanted this,
and now...
I'm gonna look like
such an asshole.
Just do it gently.
Firmly, but...
[Sighs]
Gently.
- And... and that's gonna help?
- No, probably not.
How are we even supposed to
work together after that, huh?
It's possible.
It is?
It is.
And how do you get
from here to...
The feelings just go away.
Eventually.
Can I help you, Louis?
Jessica, listen, um,
I know you've got
a lot going on right now,
um, but I just wanted
to tell you that I...
Jessica. We need to talk.
Excuse me. Hi, I was...
Now.
Never mind, it can wait.
Yes, Paul?
I want to make sure that you
and I are on the same page.
I gave you and Harvey
an opportunity.
I didn't give you a client.
I am well aware
of your position, Paul.
If you'll excuse me? Mm.
[Sighs]
[Door opens]
What?
- Sorry, um...
- Oh, put it right here.
And get out.
Daniel Hardman? [Chuckles]
The XJS 5000 dictaphone?
How the hell did he know?
[Laughs]
I heard the bank came through.
Jessica told me
to tank the deal.
Sucks, doesn't it?
Being told what to do.
What not to do.
What are you gonna do
about what we talked about?
I don't know.
I think you do know.
I think you know what's right,
whether I had
to tell you or not.
So, Tom.
Harvey has something
to tell you.
Did you find me my miracle?
The bank agreed to alter
the terms of the loan.
No balloon payment.
Madison 25 is safe.
No bankruptcy.
Oh, oh, man. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Well, Paul. Mm.
Looks like you found me
the right quarterback
for the fourth quarter.
[Laughs]
I won't forget this.
No, nor will I.
I have been irritated by you,
exasperated with you,
and angry at you,
but I never thought
I'd feel betrayed by you.
I put together a good deal.
- It was a safe deal...
- I don't care.
You just ensured that a voting
partner would never back me.
If his mother were dying
of cancer and I saved her,
I still wouldn't get his vote.
I know you're angry,
but I took the restructured deal
to real estate.
That puts them in your pocket.
Real estate has always been
in my pocket.
It's only you they hated.
And I'm beginning
to understand why.
- This isn't me against you.
- Hardman is back.
You were the one person
I could trust.
- Jessica...
- I've always known
what you are, Harvey,
and I thought that was
my greatest asset.
Now I'm wondering if you're
not my biggest liability.
This isn't about bankruptcy.
You're still pissed off
about Mike Ross.
- Damn right I am.
- I offered to walk away.
That offer was bullshit,
and you know it.
You hired that kid
to amuse yourself,
and now I'm vulnerable.
And after everything
that's happened,
you still couldn't put me
ahead of you.
The client asked me
to save his dream.
I did.
You're actually starting
to believe your own bullshit.
- Jessica, come on.
- Just go, Harvey.
I will get past this.
I will move on.
And I will accept that
at the end of the day,
that I am alone in this.
- Hey.
Four blocks from the office,
I sort of love
this clandestine thing.
Kind of sexy, right? [Laughs]
[Laughs] Oh, thank you.
Look, I was thinking about
what you said last night,
and you're right,
I have been so scared about
taking the LSATs, I know I have.
Rachel, I, uh...
there's something
I need to tell you.
We can't do this anymore.
Okay.
It's not that I don't want to...
Wait, where's this coming from?
Because last night you... eh...
this was all your idea.
- I know.
- So?
Collin McCarthy?
- What about Collin McCarthy?
- You dated him.
- Yeah, I know.
- He was a first-year.
You broke up with him,
and his work went off a cliff,
and then he was fired
two months later.
That's why you don't want
to date someone
from the office, right?
This is ridiculous.
He has nothing to do
with you and me.
But he does.
I know that you and I both
want this, okay, but...
chances are,
I'm gonna screw it up.
I love my job,
and I love...
I love working with you.
And I'm afraid, okay?
I'm afraid that...
that this will ruin that.
So...
Wow, that was a lot
of words, Mike.
Why don't you just say it?
You know what, actually,
don't say it.
I can say it for you
because it doesn't take me days
to hear your message.
I hear your message
loud and clear.
I'm just not good enough
for you.
Have Norma send up
a bouquet of flowers,
and make sure that they
repolish the cherrywood.
It's walnut.
I just wanted to make sure
that the place was ready.
I had them redo the walls.
This is taupe. Mm.
I want it to be perfect
for when Daniel gets back.
You wanted something
this morning.
I'm sorry, I was rushed.
I'm not now.
Do you still need me?
No.
Checking up on me?
Checking in on you.
Well, don't worry, Harvey.
You were right, as always.
I don't like having
to tell you to do something
that you don't want to do.
Why is it that I have to do
everything that you tell me to,
but you can ignore whatever
Jessica tells you to do?
You have plenty of time
to find the right girl, Mike.
[Chuckles] Well, thank you.
Guess I should get my book,
take some notes.
Harvey Specter's dating tips.
'Cause I'm sure you told
yourself that at 25 and 30
and 35, and I'm sure you'll be
telling yourself that
when you're 50.
You know I was right.
Doesn't make it any better.
[Rattling]
You're not alone in this.
Put it over there.