1
00:00:01,826 --> 00:00:03,187
And you got your name
on the wall.

2
00:00:03,212 --> 00:00:04,853
Now I want the respect
that comes with it.

3
00:00:04,998 --> 00:00:05,998
Meaning?

4
00:00:06,000 --> 00:00:07,143
I want one of Harvey's clients.

5
00:00:07,167 --> 00:00:08,813
My clients are my clients,

6
00:00:08,837 --> 00:00:10,281
and if you don't get out
of my office

7
00:00:10,306 --> 00:00:11,483
in the next three seconds,

8
00:00:11,508 --> 00:00:13,229
something's gonna happen
between you and me,

9
00:00:13,344 --> 00:00:15,230
and I guarantee
it won't end with you

10
00:00:15,347 --> 00:00:16,908
keeping all of your teeth.

11
00:00:16,933 --> 00:00:18,494
Avery McKernon
was the first client

12
00:00:18,519 --> 00:00:19,903
I ever brought into the firm.

13
00:00:20,022 --> 00:00:21,499
And they win, like me.

14
00:00:21,524 --> 00:00:24,527
They know Trevor
isn't in the class,

15
00:00:24,663 --> 00:00:27,449
so they know he couldn't have
been the one to steal the test.

16
00:00:27,584 --> 00:00:28,944
I'm not going to expel
your friend.

17
00:00:28,953 --> 00:00:30,254
Thank you, sir. I...

18
00:00:30,372 --> 00:00:31,850
There's just one thing.
I'm gonna call Harvard.

19
00:00:31,875 --> 00:00:34,761
Believe me when I tell you
you're never going there.

20
00:00:34,880 --> 00:00:36,932
Remember this? No, you don't.

21
00:00:37,050 --> 00:00:39,091
Because you can't remember
something you never knew.

22
00:00:39,220 --> 00:00:40,254
You can't fire me.

23
00:00:40,355 --> 00:00:42,067
Why would I fire you
when I can break you?

24
00:00:42,091 --> 00:00:46,563
You see, I'm going to bury you
under a mountain of shit so big,

25
00:00:46,699 --> 00:00:48,651
you're going to be begging me
to take it off.

26
00:00:55,080 --> 00:00:57,309
First of all,
give me that Manhattan

27
00:00:57,333 --> 00:00:59,335
and go get yourself a drink
a man would order.

28
00:00:59,470 --> 00:01:00,754
Come back here in 15 minutes,

29
00:01:00,922 --> 00:01:03,424
and if I still remember
who you are, I'll be shocked.

30
00:01:05,764 --> 00:01:08,767
Okay, so why are we really here?

31
00:01:08,902 --> 00:01:11,215
I mean, you didn't just bring me
out to talk about Khaleesi.

32
00:01:11,239 --> 00:01:13,775
I did. Paul Porter says
I look like her translator.

33
00:01:13,910 --> 00:01:15,077
He's a Throner?

34
00:01:15,196 --> 00:01:16,975
Though he says
I'm a less-attractive version

35
00:01:16,999 --> 00:01:18,093
of her translator.

36
00:01:18,117 --> 00:01:19,678
Okay, you're just trying
to get me to say

37
00:01:19,703 --> 00:01:20,823
that you're hotter than her.

38
00:01:20,838 --> 00:01:22,288
- Am I?
- You're way hotter.

39
00:01:22,457 --> 00:01:24,186
But she has that accent.

40
00:01:24,210 --> 00:01:25,427
Fair point.

41
00:01:25,546 --> 00:01:29,851
You know, look, the reason
that I brought you here

42
00:01:29,970 --> 00:01:32,472
is to tell you that I know
that you told Louis

43
00:01:32,641 --> 00:01:34,192
that I got Katrina a job.

44
00:01:35,980 --> 00:01:37,815
- Look, I...
- Relax, I'm not mad at you.

45
00:01:37,949 --> 00:01:39,651
But I do remember you
being the person

46
00:01:39,786 --> 00:01:40,986
who told me not to force things

47
00:01:40,988 --> 00:01:41,988
that weren't meant to be.

48
00:01:41,990 --> 00:01:44,970
Rachel, just because
a person gives advice

49
00:01:44,994 --> 00:01:47,155
doesn't mean that they have
to follow that same advice.

50
00:01:47,165 --> 00:01:48,860
That's one of the core
principles outlined

51
00:01:48,884 --> 00:01:50,646
in "The Book of Donna."

52
00:01:50,670 --> 00:01:52,649
Seriously, though,
I didn't mean to tell Louis.

53
00:01:52,673 --> 00:01:54,308
It just came out. I'm sorry.

54
00:01:54,426 --> 00:01:55,926
Like I said, it's fine.

55
00:01:56,063 --> 00:01:58,492
He actually ended up asking
if we could be friends again.

56
00:01:58,516 --> 00:01:59,827
And?

57
00:01:59,852 --> 00:02:03,156
And I told him that things would
never be the same between us

58
00:02:03,274 --> 00:02:04,691
unless he forgave Mike.

59
00:02:04,827 --> 00:02:06,077
And what did he say?

60
00:02:06,196 --> 00:02:09,249
He said he couldn't do it.

61
00:02:09,367 --> 00:02:11,203
That's easy.
The jumper over Ehlo.

62
00:02:11,337 --> 00:02:15,375
Wrong, the switch-hand layup
over Perkins and Green.

63
00:02:15,544 --> 00:02:16,688
I'm surprised at you, Harvey.

64
00:02:16,713 --> 00:02:18,274
The Ehlo jumper
was a game-winner.

65
00:02:18,299 --> 00:02:19,549
The layup was a statement.

66
00:02:19,685 --> 00:02:22,054
"I can do whatever I want.
I own this league."

67
00:02:22,188 --> 00:02:24,785
Are you talking about Jordan
or yourself now?

68
00:02:24,810 --> 00:02:26,728
Is there a difference?

69
00:02:26,863 --> 00:02:28,230
A big difference,

70
00:02:28,365 --> 00:02:31,295
which brings me to why I'm here.

71
00:02:31,320 --> 00:02:33,433
You can't do
whatever you want, Harvey.

72
00:02:33,457 --> 00:02:36,470
You want me to make things right
with Louis.

73
00:02:36,495 --> 00:02:38,130
He made things right
between Jeff and me.

74
00:02:38,248 --> 00:02:40,834
So I'm supposed to kiss his ass
forever because of that?

75
00:02:40,969 --> 00:02:43,148
No, you're supposed
to make peace.

76
00:02:43,172 --> 00:02:46,152
Jessica, I'm willing
to make peace,

77
00:02:46,177 --> 00:02:47,371
but that's never gonna happen.

78
00:02:47,396 --> 00:02:48,596
Why not?

79
00:02:48,732 --> 00:02:50,734
Because Louis
is never gonna forgive Mike.

80
00:02:50,852 --> 00:02:53,938
Then figure out a way
to make him forgive Mike.

81
00:03:02,371 --> 00:03:03,956
Donna, how many times
have I told you

82
00:03:04,090 --> 00:03:05,184
I want you out front?

83
00:03:05,209 --> 00:03:06,961
I'm the only associate
with a secretary.

84
00:03:07,095 --> 00:03:09,108
It would be nice if people
could see my secretary.

85
00:03:09,132 --> 00:03:11,194
Well, then maybe your next
secretary can figure out

86
00:03:11,218 --> 00:03:14,806
where to put this
without coming into your office.

87
00:03:14,942 --> 00:03:16,787
- You're kidding?
- Not kidding.

88
00:03:16,811 --> 00:03:17,978
You didn't forge this?

89
00:03:18,147 --> 00:03:20,032
I am a lot of things,
but I am not a monster.

90
00:03:20,150 --> 00:03:22,319
I would do that
to neither Michael nor you.

91
00:03:22,487 --> 00:03:24,573
- Oh, so he's Michael now?
- Well, I'm Donna to him.

92
00:03:24,707 --> 00:03:27,493
He's Michael to me, which
is what I told His Airness

93
00:03:27,629 --> 00:03:28,712
when he called.

94
00:03:28,831 --> 00:03:30,883
Wait a second.
You're not kidding.

95
00:03:31,001 --> 00:03:32,061
He signed with me?

96
00:03:32,086 --> 00:03:33,564
Well, technically,
he signed with me.

97
00:03:33,589 --> 00:03:36,392
Holy shit, Donna.
We have to celebrate tonight.

98
00:03:36,509 --> 00:03:38,010
Oh, I'm gonna celebrate.

99
00:03:38,179 --> 00:03:40,158
You, on the other hand,
are having drinks with Louis.

100
00:03:40,183 --> 00:03:42,352
What? We've been over this.

101
00:03:42,486 --> 00:03:44,582
Whenever Louis asks
to have drinks with me,

102
00:03:44,607 --> 00:03:45,607
the answer's always no.

103
00:03:45,741 --> 00:03:48,444
Listen to the words
that I'm saying.

104
00:03:48,580 --> 00:03:50,759
You are getting drinks
with Louis tonight.

105
00:03:50,784 --> 00:03:52,586
Fairchild's retiring?

106
00:03:52,703 --> 00:03:55,099
Fairchild's dead.

107
00:03:55,123 --> 00:03:56,724
That's almost as good
as the Jordan news.

108
00:03:56,843 --> 00:03:57,853
Eh, not to Fairchild.

109
00:03:57,878 --> 00:03:59,239
Who gives a shit
about Fairchild?

110
00:03:59,264 --> 00:04:01,326
The real tragedy is
I have to get drinks with Louis.

111
00:04:01,350 --> 00:04:03,112
Which is why I got you
a secluded restaurant

112
00:04:03,136 --> 00:04:05,199
with a table in the back
where no one will see you.

113
00:04:05,224 --> 00:04:08,060
And you'll call a half an hour
in and say there's an emergency.

114
00:04:08,229 --> 00:04:10,231
Already in place,
and if I can't get through,

115
00:04:10,365 --> 00:04:12,628
then I'll just have the waiter
spill drinks all over Louis.

116
00:04:12,652 --> 00:04:14,213
- You could have that done?
- Oh, please.

117
00:04:14,238 --> 00:04:15,438
I could have Louis held captive

118
00:04:15,457 --> 00:04:17,125
in a Tibetan monastery
if I wanted to.

119
00:04:17,243 --> 00:04:18,720
Yeah, I don't think
you have that...

120
00:04:18,745 --> 00:04:20,145
Now get the hell out
of your office.

121
00:04:20,248 --> 00:04:21,248
I got work to do.

122
00:04:24,889 --> 00:04:27,174
Hmm.

123
00:04:33,320 --> 00:04:37,419
Excuse me. Can you tell me
where Jim O'Donnell's office is?

124
00:04:37,443 --> 00:04:39,611
That depends. What do you know
about immigration law?

125
00:04:39,747 --> 00:04:41,893
What, are we talking visas,
or are you trying to process

126
00:04:41,917 --> 00:04:43,284
a labor certification?

127
00:04:43,419 --> 00:04:44,953
You know about immigration law?

128
00:04:45,122 --> 00:04:47,124
Doesn't everybody?

129
00:04:47,258 --> 00:04:49,688
Okay, tough guy,

130
00:04:49,713 --> 00:04:52,466
what do you think
about my strategy on this?

131
00:04:52,601 --> 00:04:56,166
Hmm.

132
00:04:56,190 --> 00:04:58,142
- I think it's a winner.
- Why is that?

133
00:04:58,276 --> 00:05:00,539
Because everyone knows Gonzalez
versus State of Maryland

134
00:05:00,564 --> 00:05:03,377
was a kick-ass precedent,
but your case is better.

135
00:05:03,402 --> 00:05:05,298
It was a kick-ass precedent,

136
00:05:05,322 --> 00:05:06,883
but I'm not sure that my case
is better.

137
00:05:06,908 --> 00:05:07,968
Oh, it is.

138
00:05:07,993 --> 00:05:08,876
Well, what about Viteri versus...

139
00:05:08,994 --> 00:05:10,211
Trust me, it's better.

140
00:05:10,330 --> 00:05:14,051
Viteri needed magic dust
and a sympathetic judge to win.

141
00:05:14,170 --> 00:05:15,972
- Have we met?
- Nope.

142
00:05:16,090 --> 00:05:17,702
But I'm Mike, by the way.

143
00:05:17,726 --> 00:05:18,726
Claire.

144
00:05:22,066 --> 00:05:23,878
Are you sure?
Because you look very familiar.

145
00:05:23,902 --> 00:05:26,155
Oh, that's probably because
I've been delivering packages

146
00:05:26,272 --> 00:05:27,750
to your office
for the last two months.

147
00:05:27,775 --> 00:05:29,420
But you haven't given me
the time of day,

148
00:05:29,444 --> 00:05:32,759
because you didn't think I was
smart enough for you.

149
00:05:32,783 --> 00:05:34,535
It's 915.

150
00:05:34,670 --> 00:05:36,432
Wait. That worked?

151
00:05:36,456 --> 00:05:38,235
It's working so far,
but I'm gonna need to know

152
00:05:38,259 --> 00:05:39,988
your full story
if it's gonna keep working.

153
00:05:40,012 --> 00:05:41,189
Well, I'll tell you
the full story

154
00:05:41,214 --> 00:05:42,441
once you give me
your phone number.

155
00:05:42,466 --> 00:05:44,362
I'll give you my number
when I know the full story.

156
00:05:44,386 --> 00:05:47,439
How about this? I'll tell you
everything you want to know

157
00:05:47,558 --> 00:05:48,975
at dinner tomorrow night.

158
00:05:51,564 --> 00:05:54,233
In that case, I'll show you
where Jim O'Donnell's office is.

159
00:05:54,402 --> 00:05:56,654
Jim O'Donnell's office?

160
00:05:56,790 --> 00:05:59,125
Where do you think
I just came from?

161
00:06:09,594 --> 00:06:12,096
I need you do something for me.

162
00:06:12,232 --> 00:06:13,265
Okay, what is it?

163
00:06:13,399 --> 00:06:14,984
Never mind what it is.

164
00:06:15,102 --> 00:06:17,081
Unless you want to go back
to whatever you were doing

165
00:06:17,106 --> 00:06:19,358
before I hired you,
you'll be here at 9:00 a.m.

166
00:06:20,778 --> 00:06:22,173
This is the address
for your car club.

167
00:06:22,198 --> 00:06:23,364
Oh, yeah, your memory.

168
00:06:23,500 --> 00:06:25,502
I'd remember this
even if I had your memory.

169
00:06:25,620 --> 00:06:27,341
It was right before
our first case together.

170
00:06:27,456 --> 00:06:29,006
You're right, McKernon Motors.

171
00:06:29,125 --> 00:06:32,189
So this time be on time
and put your seat belt on,

172
00:06:32,214 --> 00:06:34,466
because we're about to take
a trip down memory lane.

173
00:06:37,773 --> 00:06:41,611
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪

174
00:06:41,729 --> 00:06:44,983
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪

175
00:06:45,118 --> 00:06:48,289
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪

176
00:06:48,407 --> 00:06:51,327
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪

177
00:06:51,461 --> 00:06:54,581
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪

178
00:06:54,718 --> 00:06:58,723
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪

179
00:06:58,840 --> 00:07:00,007
♪ All right ♪

180
00:07:00,143 --> 00:07:04,145
♪ Suits 4x13 ♪ Fork in the Road
Original Air Date on February 11, 2015

181
00:07:04,147 --> 00:07:05,684
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪

182
00:07:05,686 --> 00:07:07,354
♪ The greenback boogie ♪

183
00:07:07,378 --> 00:07:13,882
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man.

184
00:07:14,475 --> 00:07:17,278
Morning, sunshine.

185
00:07:19,450 --> 00:07:23,215
- What are you...
- I think you call it a prunie.

186
00:07:23,240 --> 00:07:25,970
Congratulations, Donna told you
my favorite breakfast drink,

187
00:07:25,994 --> 00:07:27,889
but what does that have to do
with the price of tea

188
00:07:27,914 --> 00:07:28,914
in Antarctica?

189
00:07:29,082 --> 00:07:30,667
Donna also told me
that you were pissed,

190
00:07:30,802 --> 00:07:32,637
because you found out
I gave you a client

191
00:07:32,756 --> 00:07:34,316
I didn't want
in the first place.

192
00:07:34,341 --> 00:07:36,070
Hmm. And you think this is gonna
make up for that?

193
00:07:36,094 --> 00:07:39,348
No, but I think giving you 50%
of McKernon Motors will.

194
00:07:40,485 --> 00:07:41,829
What's the catch?

195
00:07:41,854 --> 00:07:44,774
The catch is, you and I
are about to take a road trip

196
00:07:44,908 --> 00:07:47,444
to their corporate headquarters
right now.

197
00:07:49,700 --> 00:07:50,761
You serious?

198
00:07:50,785 --> 00:07:52,647
I don't joke
about McKernon Motors,

199
00:07:52,671 --> 00:07:54,506
and you know that as well
as I do.

200
00:07:57,428 --> 00:07:59,357
To Fairchild.

201
00:07:59,382 --> 00:08:02,135
To Fairchild. God rest his soul.

202
00:08:02,304 --> 00:08:03,771
Screw his soul.

203
00:08:03,890 --> 00:08:06,476
You know how they say
"Heaven just got another angel"?

204
00:08:06,610 --> 00:08:09,530
They ain't saying it now.

205
00:08:09,649 --> 00:08:11,149
Why do you keep checking
your phone?

206
00:08:11,318 --> 00:08:14,154
- No reason. I just...
- Please, I'm not an idiot.

207
00:08:14,323 --> 00:08:16,052
We've been here 28 minutes,
and in 2 minutes,

208
00:08:16,076 --> 00:08:18,138
Donna's gonna call
with some preplanned emergency.

209
00:08:18,163 --> 00:08:19,497
Louis, that's not...

210
00:08:19,632 --> 00:08:21,918
Look, why do you think I used
Fairchild's retirement

211
00:08:22,052 --> 00:08:23,313
to get you to have drinks
with me?

212
00:08:23,338 --> 00:08:25,284
Because you knew I thought
it would never happen?

213
00:08:25,308 --> 00:08:26,909
Because he doesn't have
an heir apparent.

214
00:08:26,927 --> 00:08:29,990
Louis, if you're thinking
what I think you're thinking...

215
00:08:30,015 --> 00:08:32,067
Hardman's not gonna make
one of us senior partner.

216
00:08:32,186 --> 00:08:33,855
I'm not talking about one of us.

217
00:08:33,989 --> 00:08:36,108
I'm talking about both of us
convincing Hardman

218
00:08:36,242 --> 00:08:38,161
that two kick-ass
junior partners are worth

219
00:08:38,279 --> 00:08:41,750
as much as one new
senior partner.

220
00:08:41,869 --> 00:08:45,373
Louis, that is the best idea
you've had since I've known you.

221
00:08:45,541 --> 00:08:47,710
Yeah?

222
00:08:47,879 --> 00:08:49,714
Here's another one.

223
00:08:55,190 --> 00:08:56,550
When did you come up
with this one?

224
00:08:56,559 --> 00:08:57,836
When you were in the bathroom
wasting 7 minutes

225
00:08:57,861 --> 00:08:58,861
of our half hour.

226
00:09:01,567 --> 00:09:03,713
Don't you have to get that?

227
00:09:03,738 --> 00:09:05,456
No, I don't.

228
00:09:05,574 --> 00:09:06,908
Let's drink to this.

229
00:09:11,049 --> 00:09:12,416
Asshole.

230
00:09:14,722 --> 00:09:15,839
That was Donna, wasn't it?

231
00:09:15,974 --> 00:09:18,476
Trevor, this is so stupid.

232
00:09:18,595 --> 00:09:19,655
It's not stupid, dickhead.

233
00:09:19,680 --> 00:09:21,041
I want you to see it
for the first time

234
00:09:21,066 --> 00:09:22,243
from the middle of the room.

235
00:09:22,267 --> 00:09:24,102
It's your apartment, assface,

236
00:09:24,271 --> 00:09:26,941
and don't even think about
giving me a wet Willie.

237
00:09:27,075 --> 00:09:28,670
You suck the fun
out of everything.

238
00:09:28,694 --> 00:09:30,279
Go ahead.
Open your eyes, dickfoot.

239
00:09:30,415 --> 00:09:31,976
- "Dickfoot"?
- I was gonna use "assface."

240
00:09:32,001 --> 00:09:33,094
It's all I could think of.

241
00:09:33,118 --> 00:09:34,429
How do you even manage
in the world?

242
00:09:34,454 --> 00:09:35,932
Are you just gonna stand there
with your your eyes closed

243
00:09:35,957 --> 00:09:37,317
and mock my "dickfoot"?

244
00:09:37,342 --> 00:09:39,543
I'm definitely not gonna
open them to see your dickfoot.

245
00:09:39,545 --> 00:09:41,358
That's a good point.
I wouldn't do that either.

246
00:09:41,383 --> 00:09:42,549
Go ahead. Open your eyes.

247
00:09:45,105 --> 00:09:47,441
Wow. Holy shit.

248
00:09:47,558 --> 00:09:49,193
I thought you were getting
a studio.

249
00:09:49,312 --> 00:09:51,982
Yeah, I was going to,
but then I realized

250
00:09:52,116 --> 00:09:56,204
we can't both live in a studio.

251
00:09:56,323 --> 00:09:57,323
What?

252
00:09:57,325 --> 00:09:59,711
Welcome to Casa Evans and Ross.

253
00:09:59,829 --> 00:10:01,858
Trevor, I can't afford
half this rent.

254
00:10:01,883 --> 00:10:02,883
That's the best part.

255
00:10:03,001 --> 00:10:04,167
Don't worry about it.

256
00:10:04,303 --> 00:10:05,864
I'm gonna pay
for your whole first year.

257
00:10:05,889 --> 00:10:07,366
No, you're not.
I can't let you do that.

258
00:10:07,391 --> 00:10:09,176
Michael, I start my new job
on Tuesday.

259
00:10:09,311 --> 00:10:11,457
On top of that, I have
my friends and family business

260
00:10:11,482 --> 00:10:12,849
on the side.

261
00:10:12,984 --> 00:10:14,462
That doesn't mean I'm gonna
take charity from you.

262
00:10:14,487 --> 00:10:15,847
Look, are you gonna
make me say it?

263
00:10:15,855 --> 00:10:18,167
It's not charity.

264
00:10:18,192 --> 00:10:19,359
I graduated, and you didn't,

265
00:10:19,495 --> 00:10:22,058
because you took the fall
for something I did.

266
00:10:22,082 --> 00:10:23,399
I owe you.

267
00:10:28,543 --> 00:10:30,378
Okay, I'll think about it.

268
00:10:30,513 --> 00:10:32,715
All right, in the meantime,
think about this.

269
00:10:32,849 --> 00:10:34,360
Ahh... no, I can't.

270
00:10:34,385 --> 00:10:35,863
- I got a date tonight.
- All right.

271
00:10:35,888 --> 00:10:38,868
Wow, clubfoot, mustache,
all of the above?

272
00:10:38,893 --> 00:10:41,756
First dickfoot
and then clubfoot?

273
00:10:41,781 --> 00:10:43,816
Are words with "foot"
all you've got now?

274
00:10:43,951 --> 00:10:46,904
All right, smart guy, describe
her with one of your SAT words.

275
00:10:47,073 --> 00:10:49,435
- Bigfoot.
- That's what I'm talking about.

276
00:10:49,460 --> 00:10:54,334
For the record,
she's really hot.

277
00:10:56,421 --> 00:10:57,755
Let me get this straight.

278
00:10:57,890 --> 00:10:59,491
Instead of promoting
an existing partner,

279
00:10:59,593 --> 00:11:02,429
you want me to make both of you
junior partners.

280
00:11:02,598 --> 00:11:04,183
Well, not make us.
We've earned it.

281
00:11:05,653 --> 00:11:07,070
Earned partnership status?

282
00:11:07,189 --> 00:11:09,775
That's a pretty bold statement
coming from two fifth-years.

283
00:11:09,910 --> 00:11:11,111
Not just any fifth-years.

284
00:11:11,279 --> 00:11:13,280
We're the best fifth-years
this firm has ever seen,

285
00:11:13,282 --> 00:11:14,449
and you know it.

286
00:11:14,585 --> 00:11:16,503
May I inquire whose idea
this was?

287
00:11:16,621 --> 00:11:18,182
- It was both of ours.
- I was Louis'.

288
00:11:18,207 --> 00:11:19,407
That's generous of you

289
00:11:19,509 --> 00:11:20,626
to give him credit.

290
00:11:20,761 --> 00:11:24,383
It was generous of him to come
to me with the idea.

291
00:11:24,517 --> 00:11:27,353
The truth is, I wasn't
gonna make anyone partner.

292
00:11:28,808 --> 00:11:30,476
But I do like admire
your gumption.

293
00:11:30,611 --> 00:11:34,149
So here's
what I'm willing to do.

294
00:11:34,283 --> 00:11:37,319
I will advance one of you
if you prove to me

295
00:11:37,455 --> 00:11:39,323
which one it should be.

296
00:11:39,459 --> 00:11:40,769
No, see, that's the whole point.

297
00:11:40,794 --> 00:11:42,379
We came in as a package deal.

298
00:11:42,497 --> 00:11:43,858
You came in with a proposal.

299
00:11:43,883 --> 00:11:47,087
I'm giving you a counter,
and it's take it or leave it.

300
00:11:47,222 --> 00:11:49,807
What sort of proof
are we talking about?

301
00:11:49,925 --> 00:11:52,928
Let's just say McKernon Motors
is in play,

302
00:11:53,064 --> 00:11:55,994
and landing them could go
a long way to making your case.

303
00:11:56,019 --> 00:11:57,352
No way. We're not gonna...

304
00:11:57,488 --> 00:11:58,888
All right, Daniel.

305
00:11:59,024 --> 00:12:01,076
You want McKernon?

306
00:12:01,195 --> 00:12:03,413
I'll get you McKernon.

307
00:12:06,036 --> 00:12:08,788
We're going to McKernon Motors,
not your senior prom.

308
00:12:08,923 --> 00:12:10,400
Why can't we just take
the car service?

309
00:12:10,425 --> 00:12:12,571
Because we're going to
an engine manufacturer.

310
00:12:12,596 --> 00:12:15,382
We need to show up
with a bad-ass car.

311
00:12:15,518 --> 00:12:17,270
How about this little bad boy
right here?

312
00:12:17,387 --> 00:12:18,387
That's no good.

313
00:12:18,388 --> 00:12:19,388
Why the hell not?

314
00:12:19,390 --> 00:12:21,726
Because it's not just
the two of us.

315
00:12:21,895 --> 00:12:23,697
What do you mean?

316
00:12:23,814 --> 00:12:24,898
You son of a bitch.

317
00:12:25,067 --> 00:12:26,461
You said you and I
are going up there.

318
00:12:26,486 --> 00:12:27,763
You lied to me.

319
00:12:27,787 --> 00:12:30,028
Because if I didn't, you would
have never agreed to come.

320
00:12:30,041 --> 00:12:31,052
There is no way I'm going.

321
00:12:31,077 --> 00:12:32,627
Yes, you are.

322
00:12:32,746 --> 00:12:34,558
I don't care if I have
to tie you to the roof.

323
00:12:34,582 --> 00:12:35,976
By the time we get to McKernon,

324
00:12:36,001 --> 00:12:38,087
you and Mike are gonna
work your shit out.

325
00:12:53,739 --> 00:12:55,801
I can't believe you did that.

326
00:12:55,825 --> 00:12:58,027
The plan was to present
a united front.

327
00:12:58,146 --> 00:12:59,546
And we did,
and he didn't go for it.

328
00:12:59,565 --> 00:13:00,949
Then you stab me in the back?

329
00:13:01,068 --> 00:13:03,297
I didn't stab you in the back.
I took what he gave us.

330
00:13:03,321 --> 00:13:04,956
He didn't give us
anything, Harvey.

331
00:13:05,074 --> 00:13:06,468
He pitted us against each other.

332
00:13:06,493 --> 00:13:09,139
Louis, we've been pitted against
each other since day one.

333
00:13:09,164 --> 00:13:10,381
What are you talking about?

334
00:13:10,500 --> 00:13:12,395
How many of the 50 associates
we started with

335
00:13:12,419 --> 00:13:13,864
do you think
are gonna make partner?

336
00:13:13,889 --> 00:13:16,652
I don't give a shit
about the other associates.

337
00:13:16,677 --> 00:13:19,813
We toasted to making
partner together.

338
00:13:19,932 --> 00:13:21,851
I don't make the rules, Louis.
Hardman does.

339
00:13:21,985 --> 00:13:24,154
And as much as we say
he's an asshole,

340
00:13:24,272 --> 00:13:26,751
I respect him for at least
telling us the deal out loud.

341
00:13:26,776 --> 00:13:27,920
You want something out loud?

342
00:13:27,945 --> 00:13:29,495
I'm gonna give you
something out loud.

343
00:13:29,614 --> 00:13:33,452
No way on Earth am I gonna
let you land McKernon Motors.

344
00:13:39,630 --> 00:13:47,308
♪ ♪

345
00:13:51,867 --> 00:13:53,548
- Hey, what the hell?
- What the hell what?

346
00:13:53,570 --> 00:13:54,987
This isn't a joyride, Louis.

347
00:13:55,122 --> 00:13:57,241
You don't want to talk,
you're gonna sit in silence

348
00:13:57,376 --> 00:13:58,469
until you're ready to talk.

349
00:13:58,494 --> 00:14:00,390
Well, you can make me sit
in silence all you want,

350
00:14:00,414 --> 00:14:01,975
but you can't make me
work it out with him.

351
00:14:02,000 --> 00:14:03,467
- Then what can, Louis?
- Excuse me?

352
00:14:03,586 --> 00:14:06,222
You worked it out
with Donna and Rachel.

353
00:14:06,341 --> 00:14:08,226
You lied to Malone for Jessica.

354
00:14:08,344 --> 00:14:09,989
What's it gonna
take to work it out with me?

355
00:14:10,013 --> 00:14:12,826
Well, I forgave those people,
because they were victims

356
00:14:12,851 --> 00:14:15,664
infected with the disease
known as Mike Ross.

357
00:14:15,689 --> 00:14:18,192
Now I'm stuck in a car
with patient zero.

358
00:14:18,327 --> 00:14:20,947
Okay, Outbreak, patient zero
is the first person

359
00:14:21,082 --> 00:14:22,867
actually infected
with the disease,

360
00:14:23,035 --> 00:14:25,371
not the disease itself,
and for your information,

361
00:14:25,538 --> 00:14:28,068
I'm stuck in the same car
as you.

362
00:14:28,093 --> 00:14:30,489
At least you don't have to look
at the back of your own stupid,

363
00:14:30,514 --> 00:14:33,133
fat, balding head.

364
00:14:34,270 --> 00:14:35,437
What's so goddamn funny?

365
00:14:35,555 --> 00:14:37,140
You two are finally talking.

366
00:14:37,275 --> 00:14:38,595
I think you earned
a little music.

367
00:14:41,615 --> 00:14:46,906
♪ ♪

368
00:14:48,493 --> 00:14:49,937
- That's it?
- Yeah.

369
00:14:49,962 --> 00:14:51,808
All you have to do is pick one
of two characters.

370
00:14:51,832 --> 00:14:53,276
And whichever character
I don't pick

371
00:14:53,301 --> 00:14:55,397
is removed
from film history forever?

372
00:14:55,421 --> 00:14:56,804
It's like they never existed.

373
00:14:56,923 --> 00:14:57,984
It's a piece of cake.

374
00:14:58,009 --> 00:15:00,928
Okay, Han Solo or Indiana Jones?

375
00:15:01,064 --> 00:15:03,266
- I'm out.
- What's the problem?

376
00:15:03,400 --> 00:15:05,079
You just said it was gonna be
a piece of cake.

377
00:15:05,104 --> 00:15:06,415
The problem is, you just picked
the two greatest characters

378
00:15:06,439 --> 00:15:07,439
of all time, so...

379
00:15:07,441 --> 00:15:08,801
You're right about that.
I'm sorry.

380
00:15:08,910 --> 00:15:10,137
Let me start with something
easier for you.

381
00:15:10,162 --> 00:15:11,529
- All right.
- Butch or Sundance?

382
00:15:11,664 --> 00:15:13,165
Mm, check, please.

383
00:15:13,284 --> 00:15:15,146
Yeah, we're done.

384
00:15:15,170 --> 00:15:17,433
No.

385
00:15:17,457 --> 00:15:18,790
This is really nice.

386
00:15:18,926 --> 00:15:23,131
Yeah, I'm having
a really good time too.

387
00:15:23,266 --> 00:15:25,029
So when do I get to hear
the answer to what you do

388
00:15:25,053 --> 00:15:26,971
besides being a bike messenger?

389
00:15:27,140 --> 00:15:28,474
Who says I do anything?

390
00:15:30,729 --> 00:15:32,029
Look, Mike,
there's nothing wrong

391
00:15:32,148 --> 00:15:36,547
with being a bike messenger,
but I'm serious about my life.

392
00:15:36,572 --> 00:15:38,333
I'm not going to law school
just to cash out.

393
00:15:38,458 --> 00:15:39,992
I really want to help people.

394
00:15:40,161 --> 00:15:42,997
Bike messengers
don't help people?

395
00:15:43,133 --> 00:15:45,228
No, not in the way
that a man I want to be

396
00:15:45,252 --> 00:15:48,507
in a relationship with does.

397
00:15:52,731 --> 00:15:55,768
Well, then today
is your lucky day.

398
00:15:58,525 --> 00:16:00,360
I knew it. Where do you go?

399
00:16:00,494 --> 00:16:02,028
Mm-mm, you first.
Where do you go?

400
00:16:02,197 --> 00:16:04,199
- NYU.
- Columbia.

401
00:16:04,367 --> 00:16:06,536
I win.

402
00:16:08,124 --> 00:16:09,792
- Good morning, Jessica.
- Hi, Daniel.

403
00:16:09,926 --> 00:16:12,072
- I still haven't received...
- This year's budget?

404
00:16:12,096 --> 00:16:13,691
I was just on my way
to give it to you.

405
00:16:13,715 --> 00:16:15,611
And I thought maybe you hadn't
gotten around to it

406
00:16:15,635 --> 00:16:17,831
because you were too busy
pitting Harvey against Louis.

407
00:16:17,856 --> 00:16:19,106
You disapprove.

408
00:16:19,225 --> 00:16:21,611
I don't mind a little
healthy competition.

409
00:16:21,728 --> 00:16:23,947
But I do mind the empty promise
of partnership.

410
00:16:24,066 --> 00:16:26,107
What makes you so sure
there's no reward at the end?

411
00:16:26,119 --> 00:16:27,380
The last time we discussed this,

412
00:16:27,405 --> 00:16:28,549
you said Harvey wasn't ready.

413
00:16:28,574 --> 00:16:29,790
And you said Louis wasn't.

414
00:16:29,908 --> 00:16:31,937
Well, I'm giving them both
the chance to prove it.

415
00:16:31,962 --> 00:16:33,223
So partnership is on the table.

416
00:16:33,248 --> 00:16:36,061
Partnership was already
on the table.

417
00:16:36,085 --> 00:16:38,221
What makes you so sure
it's gonna be Harvey?

418
00:16:38,339 --> 00:16:41,403
Because Harvey will do
whatever it takes to win.

419
00:16:41,428 --> 00:16:43,574
If doing whatever it takes
is the criteria,

420
00:16:43,598 --> 00:16:46,150
my money is on Louis.

421
00:16:46,269 --> 00:16:48,632
What are you talking about?

422
00:16:48,656 --> 00:16:52,611
I think we should continue
this conversation in my office.

423
00:16:56,202 --> 00:17:01,603
Hi, I've got a delivery
for a Zoltan Freastmeisterson.

424
00:17:01,628 --> 00:17:04,130
I'm afraid there's no one
in this office with that name.

425
00:17:04,298 --> 00:17:05,465
I'm afraid you're mistaken.

426
00:17:05,634 --> 00:17:06,967
- Really?
- Yeah.

427
00:17:07,103 --> 00:17:08,664
Because I'm willing to bet that
there's no one on this planet

428
00:17:08,689 --> 00:17:09,805
with that name.

429
00:17:09,941 --> 00:17:11,452
Okay, fine, but if you could
just point me towards.

430
00:17:11,477 --> 00:17:14,363
Kumquat McGillicuddy's office,
I'll be on my way,

431
00:17:14,482 --> 00:17:16,617
because I certainly
did not bike down here

432
00:17:16,735 --> 00:17:18,704
with two fictitious deliveries
just to tell you

433
00:17:18,822 --> 00:17:20,968
what a great time I had
last night.

434
00:17:20,992 --> 00:17:23,828
Good, because I have a lot
of work to do.

435
00:17:23,964 --> 00:17:26,477
So, if you could please just hop
on that little bike of yours...

436
00:17:26,501 --> 00:17:27,918
- Claire?
- Yeah.

437
00:17:28,053 --> 00:17:30,094
When you're finished flirting
with Quicksilver here,

438
00:17:30,224 --> 00:17:31,558
you might want to get down
to INS.

439
00:17:31,677 --> 00:17:33,489
Hector Suarez just got taken in.

440
00:17:33,513 --> 00:17:35,348
Shit. His visa's expired.

441
00:17:35,482 --> 00:17:37,628
They're gonna send him back
to the Dominican Republic.

442
00:17:37,653 --> 00:17:39,939
Wait. Maybe I can help.

443
00:17:40,073 --> 00:17:41,467
No offense,
I don't see how you can...

444
00:17:41,492 --> 00:17:43,003
No, no, no, Nathan,
he's not just a bike messenger.

445
00:17:43,028 --> 00:17:44,028
He's in law school.

446
00:17:44,197 --> 00:17:45,614
Really?

447
00:17:45,750 --> 00:17:47,702
- Where are you in law school?
- Columbia.

448
00:17:47,836 --> 00:17:51,040
And he happens to know visas
better than either one of us.

449
00:17:51,208 --> 00:17:52,569
Well, I really
can't pay you, so...

450
00:17:52,594 --> 00:17:54,406
No, I don't need any money.

451
00:17:54,430 --> 00:17:55,490
I just want to help.

452
00:17:55,515 --> 00:17:57,684
All right, Columbia,
be my guest.

453
00:17:57,802 --> 00:18:00,221
Got a hearing Tuesday morning,
9:00 a.m.

454
00:18:01,309 --> 00:18:03,394
Mike, that is amazing.
Thank you.

455
00:18:03,562 --> 00:18:05,683
Oh, no, don't thank me yet.
I haven't even done any...

456
00:18:12,744 --> 00:18:16,915
Um, this might not be relevant,
but I actually saved.

457
00:18:17,051 --> 00:18:21,757
Kumquat McGillicuddy's life
this morning, so...

458
00:18:21,925 --> 00:18:23,426
I'm gonna go do some work.

459
00:18:24,814 --> 00:18:26,064
Thank you.

460
00:18:28,186 --> 00:18:31,607
Mr. McKernon, Harvey Specter.

461
00:18:31,775 --> 00:18:34,277
Mr. Specter, would you mind
telling me why I have

462
00:18:34,413 --> 00:18:37,309
two different Pearson Hardman
lawyers on my schedule today?

463
00:18:37,334 --> 00:18:38,595
I don't know, but after this,

464
00:18:38,619 --> 00:18:40,096
you won't need to meet
the other one.

465
00:18:40,121 --> 00:18:41,148
You're cocky.

466
00:18:41,173 --> 00:18:42,257
I'm right.

467
00:18:42,376 --> 00:18:43,816
You're also traveling
a little light.

468
00:18:43,928 --> 00:18:45,963
Where's your
PowerPoint presentation?

469
00:18:46,098 --> 00:18:48,183
I don't need
a PowerPoint presentation.

470
00:18:48,302 --> 00:18:49,529
Why is that?

471
00:18:49,553 --> 00:18:52,022
Because every lawyer in the city
has tried to dazzle you,

472
00:18:52,141 --> 00:18:54,504
and you're still looking
for a date to the big dance,

473
00:18:54,528 --> 00:18:58,510
because they don't know
what you're looking for.

474
00:18:58,535 --> 00:19:00,881
What exactly am I looking for?

475
00:19:00,906 --> 00:19:02,825
Loyalty.

476
00:19:04,412 --> 00:19:06,808
You're right.

477
00:19:06,832 --> 00:19:09,384
I built this company
from the ground up,

478
00:19:09,503 --> 00:19:11,649
and everybody that started
with me is still here.

479
00:19:11,673 --> 00:19:12,900
And I know why.

480
00:19:12,925 --> 00:19:14,342
You don't downsize
in the bad times.

481
00:19:14,478 --> 00:19:16,373
They stick with you
in the good times.

482
00:19:16,397 --> 00:19:18,683
And no other lawyer
has figured that out.

483
00:19:18,818 --> 00:19:20,079
Not a single one.

484
00:19:20,104 --> 00:19:21,498
Well, I'm the one, Avery,

485
00:19:21,523 --> 00:19:24,052
which is why I know
you don't want me dumping you

486
00:19:24,076 --> 00:19:26,362
for a bigger client
down the line.

487
00:19:26,498 --> 00:19:29,010
How do I know you won't do that?

488
00:19:29,034 --> 00:19:31,454
Because that's not the way
I work.

489
00:19:31,589 --> 00:19:33,435
Well, it's a hell
of a nice sentiment.

490
00:19:33,459 --> 00:19:35,571
But how do I know you're not
full of shit?

491
00:19:35,596 --> 00:19:37,442
I'm glad you asked,

492
00:19:37,466 --> 00:19:42,054
because here's my
PowerPoint presentation.

493
00:19:56,747 --> 00:19:58,274
Okay...

494
00:19:58,299 --> 00:20:02,171
I have a hearing tomorrow
against Fletcher Engines.

495
00:20:02,306 --> 00:20:04,725
You win that, you're my lawyer.

496
00:20:12,938 --> 00:20:13,972
Ok, just don't change lanes.

497
00:20:13,997 --> 00:20:14,849
Don't change lanes.

498
00:20:14,874 --> 00:20:16,910
Don't do this. Great.
Okay, you know what?

499
00:20:16,911 --> 00:20:19,080
This is ridiculous.
You drive like a savage animal.

500
00:20:19,214 --> 00:20:20,725
Louis, be a man and suck it up.

501
00:20:20,750 --> 00:20:22,502
Suck it up?
I'm sitting in the death seat.

502
00:20:22,637 --> 00:20:24,900
Fine. I'll pull over, and you
can sit in the back with Mike.

503
00:20:24,924 --> 00:20:26,725
Hey, I'm not sitting in the back
with a fraud,

504
00:20:26,727 --> 00:20:28,989
and before you even think it,
you're not putting him up here

505
00:20:29,014 --> 00:20:30,125
and sticking me back there.

506
00:20:30,149 --> 00:20:31,316
Then what do you want, Louis?

507
00:20:31,434 --> 00:20:32,674
Because there is no way in hell

508
00:20:32,770 --> 00:20:34,415
I'm letting you
behind the wheel of this car.

509
00:20:34,439 --> 00:20:36,658
It's crystal goddamn clear.

510
00:20:36,777 --> 00:20:38,840
You and I sit in the back, and
he chauffeurs the both of us.

511
00:20:38,864 --> 00:20:41,226
Whoa, no. Even if Harvey would
agree to that, which I doubt...

512
00:20:41,250 --> 00:20:42,334
Shut the hell up.

513
00:20:42,452 --> 00:20:43,847
You're not talking.
You don't get to refuse.

514
00:20:43,872 --> 00:20:46,958
I'm not refusing, Louis.
I don't know how to drive.

515
00:20:49,096 --> 00:20:50,630
Holy shit.

516
00:20:56,893 --> 00:20:57,953
You wanted to see me?

517
00:20:57,978 --> 00:20:59,362
Uh, yes.

518
00:20:59,480 --> 00:21:01,316
I heard you did well
with Avery McKernon.

519
00:21:01,483 --> 00:21:03,369
Well, then you heard wrong,

520
00:21:03,487 --> 00:21:05,656
because I killed it
with Avery McKernon.

521
00:21:05,791 --> 00:21:08,377
- Congratulations, Harvey.
- Thank you, Daniel.

522
00:21:08,495 --> 00:21:10,381
You're welcome.

523
00:21:10,498 --> 00:21:12,167
Unfortunately,
we can't represent.

524
00:21:12,301 --> 00:21:13,645
McKernon Motors after all.

525
00:21:13,670 --> 00:21:15,031
Why not?

526
00:21:15,056 --> 00:21:16,567
Well, it turns out
Fletcher Engines

527
00:21:16,592 --> 00:21:18,059
wants to sign with us.

528
00:21:18,178 --> 00:21:20,397
Because they found out
I'm about to land McKernon.

529
00:21:20,514 --> 00:21:23,568
Yes, and they're three times
the size of McKernon Motors.

530
00:21:23,686 --> 00:21:25,237
Well, I don't care
how big they are.

531
00:21:25,356 --> 00:21:27,718
I'm not dropping my client.

532
00:21:27,743 --> 00:21:29,912
Yes, you are.

533
00:21:32,451 --> 00:21:34,430
This was your plan all along.

534
00:21:34,454 --> 00:21:36,623
Of course it was.
That's how the world works.

535
00:21:36,758 --> 00:21:38,627
I don't give a shit
how the world works.

536
00:21:38,761 --> 00:21:40,774
I gave my word
to Avery McKernon.

537
00:21:40,798 --> 00:21:42,181
Watch yourself, Harvey.

538
00:21:42,300 --> 00:21:44,469
I haven't gotten where I am
by watching myself, Daniel.

539
00:21:44,605 --> 00:21:47,107
And I don't appreciate
being used as a stalking horse.

540
00:21:47,225 --> 00:21:51,090
Well, you may not appreciate it,
but let me remind you,

541
00:21:51,115 --> 00:21:52,542
you work for me.

542
00:21:52,567 --> 00:21:56,956
And I'm giving you the chance
to show me you understand that.

543
00:21:57,075 --> 00:22:00,128
Let me remind you you said
partnership was on the table.

544
00:22:00,247 --> 00:22:03,133
I'm gonna hold you to that,
and so will Jessica.

545
00:22:12,734 --> 00:22:13,817
Hey, fart taster.

546
00:22:13,935 --> 00:22:16,905
I thought you were coming over.

547
00:22:17,024 --> 00:22:18,909
What, nothing? It's a classic.

548
00:22:19,028 --> 00:22:20,756
I'm implying your job
is to literally taste...

549
00:22:20,780 --> 00:22:22,559
Hey, Trevor,
I'm in the middle of something,

550
00:22:22,583 --> 00:22:24,168
so I'll come over later, okay?

551
00:22:24,286 --> 00:22:25,981
In the middle of what?

552
00:22:26,005 --> 00:22:27,984
That girl I told you about,

553
00:22:28,008 --> 00:22:29,843
she interns at a legal clinic,

554
00:22:29,962 --> 00:22:32,014
and I am helping her
with a case.

555
00:22:32,132 --> 00:22:33,276
Dickfoot gave you homework?

556
00:22:33,301 --> 00:22:36,532
Okay, first of all, from now on,
her name is Claire.

557
00:22:36,556 --> 00:22:38,975
And second of all,
this is important, so...

558
00:22:39,110 --> 00:22:42,196
Dude, what the hell
are you talking about?

559
00:22:45,654 --> 00:22:48,657
I might have told her
that I'm in law school.

560
00:22:48,793 --> 00:22:50,805
Holy shit.

561
00:22:50,829 --> 00:22:52,330
You will do anything
to get laid.

562
00:22:52,465 --> 00:22:53,882
I am not trying to get laid.

563
00:22:54,001 --> 00:22:56,647
I really like this girl,
and I have zero chance with her

564
00:22:56,672 --> 00:22:58,006
if all I am is a bike messenger.

565
00:22:58,141 --> 00:23:00,120
Yeah, well, you're definitely
gonna have no chance

566
00:23:00,145 --> 00:23:01,678
if she finds out
that you lied to her.

567
00:23:01,814 --> 00:23:04,934
Trevor, I don't want to talk
about this anymore.

568
00:23:05,069 --> 00:23:08,273
You don't really want to talk
about anything anymore.

569
00:23:11,863 --> 00:23:13,247
It's about the apartment,
isn't it?

570
00:23:13,366 --> 00:23:15,868
- Yes it's about the apartment.
- Okay, you want the truth?

571
00:23:16,004 --> 00:23:17,906
I haven't given you an answer
because of Grammy.

572
00:23:18,040 --> 00:23:19,184
You think I didn't know that?

573
00:23:19,209 --> 00:23:20,737
Then you know
she's never forgiven you

574
00:23:20,762 --> 00:23:22,022
for what happened in college,

575
00:23:22,047 --> 00:23:24,193
and she is never, ever going
to let me live with you.

576
00:23:24,217 --> 00:23:26,136
Then explain to her
that this is my way

577
00:23:26,270 --> 00:23:27,697
of making up for what I did
in college.

578
00:23:27,722 --> 00:23:28,889
That is never gonna work.

579
00:23:29,025 --> 00:23:30,943
You know what, Michael?

580
00:23:31,061 --> 00:23:34,459
If you're gonna do all of this
for some girl you just met,

581
00:23:34,484 --> 00:23:38,289
maybe it's time you stood up
to Grammy for me.

582
00:23:42,163 --> 00:23:44,381
How'd it go
against Fletcher Engines?

583
00:23:44,500 --> 00:23:46,646
You cut them off at the knees
or put them in the ground?

584
00:23:46,670 --> 00:23:48,422
They put me in the ground,

585
00:23:48,591 --> 00:23:50,987
and on top of that, it was
in front of Avery McKernon.

586
00:23:51,011 --> 00:23:52,144
You lost in court?

587
00:23:52,263 --> 00:23:55,651
I didn't just lose.
I looked like a fool.

588
00:23:55,768 --> 00:23:56,768
Harvey, what happened?

589
00:23:56,770 --> 00:23:58,656
The general counsel
for Fletcher Engines

590
00:23:58,773 --> 00:24:00,942
knew every move I was gonna make
before I even made it.

591
00:24:01,078 --> 00:24:02,138
How could he...

592
00:24:02,162 --> 00:24:03,997
Because Hardman
must have tipped him off.

593
00:24:04,115 --> 00:24:05,435
You really think
he would do that?

594
00:24:05,451 --> 00:24:07,786
I wouldn't have yesterday,
but I sure as hell do today.

595
00:24:07,955 --> 00:24:09,624
Then you have to go to Jessica.

596
00:24:09,758 --> 00:24:10,819
And say what?

597
00:24:10,844 --> 00:24:13,179
Hardman's managing partner.
She's not.

598
00:24:13,297 --> 00:24:15,299
I don't have any proof,
and I never will.

599
00:24:15,468 --> 00:24:16,862
Well, then
what are you gonna do?

600
00:24:16,887 --> 00:24:19,366
I don't know,
but I have less than 14 hours

601
00:24:19,390 --> 00:24:21,643
to dig through 1,000 pages
of patent law.

602
00:24:23,197 --> 00:24:25,293
If only there was somebody
in the office who was an expert

603
00:24:25,317 --> 00:24:26,317
on patent law.

604
00:24:26,452 --> 00:24:28,154
Donna, I am not going to Louis.

605
00:24:28,289 --> 00:24:29,656
He'll never help me.

606
00:24:29,824 --> 00:24:31,905
Well, that's too bad,
because if you can't figure out

607
00:24:31,911 --> 00:24:33,579
how to patch things up
with Louis,

608
00:24:33,714 --> 00:24:35,693
then you don't deserve
Avery McKernon

609
00:24:35,718 --> 00:24:37,970
or that partnership.

610
00:24:42,679 --> 00:24:46,233
What's all this?

611
00:24:46,351 --> 00:24:50,083
Uh, a grandson can't order in
and set a table

612
00:24:50,108 --> 00:24:52,026
for his grandmother?

613
00:24:52,161 --> 00:24:53,611
A grandson can do
whatever he wants.

614
00:24:53,747 --> 00:24:56,918
But the answer
to your question is no.

615
00:24:57,035 --> 00:24:59,705
You haven't even heard
what it is yet.

616
00:24:59,873 --> 00:25:01,819
I know what it is,
because I've been waiting for it

617
00:25:01,843 --> 00:25:03,511
since that kid graduated,

618
00:25:03,629 --> 00:25:05,848
and you are not
gonna live with him.

619
00:25:05,967 --> 00:25:09,532
That boy is the reason
you got kicked out of school.

620
00:25:09,556 --> 00:25:12,442
You're the one that told me
to tell the dean the truth.

621
00:25:12,561 --> 00:25:14,924
That was before I knew
it would cost you graduating.

622
00:25:14,949 --> 00:25:16,449
And he's trying
to make it up to me.

623
00:25:16,568 --> 00:25:18,737
He's gonna pay for my whole
first year's rent.

624
00:25:18,904 --> 00:25:21,624
That will not make up
for putting your whole life

625
00:25:21,743 --> 00:25:23,076
into a tailspin.

626
00:25:23,245 --> 00:25:25,191
- It's a head start.
- No, it's not a head start!

627
00:25:25,215 --> 00:25:26,893
That boy is gonna drag you
back down with him!

628
00:25:26,917 --> 00:25:28,529
Grammy, I'm never gonna let
that happen!

629
00:25:28,553 --> 00:25:30,839
God damn it! I forbid it!

630
00:25:38,269 --> 00:25:40,905
I'm sorry, Michael.
I lost my temper.

631
00:25:41,024 --> 00:25:44,472
But I know what he does to you,

632
00:25:44,496 --> 00:25:49,453
and I know he'll
always be the same.

633
00:25:49,588 --> 00:25:51,841
Has it occurred to you
that maybe I'm not the same?

634
00:25:51,958 --> 00:25:54,127
What's changed?

635
00:25:54,263 --> 00:25:56,015
I met someone.

636
00:25:58,302 --> 00:26:02,785
And I'm gonna figure out a way
to finish school, and...

637
00:26:02,810 --> 00:26:04,978
and then I'm gonna go
to law school.

638
00:26:06,449 --> 00:26:08,200
Good.

639
00:26:08,318 --> 00:26:10,537
Then do it from here.

640
00:26:18,752 --> 00:26:20,337
What's on your mind, Mike?

641
00:26:20,505 --> 00:26:21,672
You look lost in thought.

642
00:26:24,010 --> 00:26:25,929
I was just thinking
about my grandmother.

643
00:26:27,851 --> 00:26:31,689
We took a train trip
to D.C. once.

644
00:26:31,823 --> 00:26:33,575
We played I Spy.

645
00:26:33,694 --> 00:26:37,031
That's a nice story, Mike,
but we are not playing I Spy.

646
00:26:37,166 --> 00:26:39,585
I'll play. It'll remind me of
dominating Esther on our trips

647
00:26:39,703 --> 00:26:41,230
to see our smelly Aunt Frida.

648
00:26:41,255 --> 00:26:43,791
All right, if it will get
you and Mike talking, sure.

649
00:26:45,212 --> 00:26:48,132
I spy a fraud who probably
never even knew his grandmother.

650
00:26:48,267 --> 00:26:50,386
All right, God damn it,
you got a problem with me,

651
00:26:50,554 --> 00:26:51,998
take it up with me,
but don't ever talk

652
00:26:52,023 --> 00:26:53,250
about my grandmother again.

653
00:26:53,275 --> 00:26:54,954
Oh, I forgot, the poor orphan

654
00:26:54,978 --> 00:26:57,124
from New York City
who I should feel sorry for

655
00:26:57,149 --> 00:26:58,293
because he never
learned to drive.

656
00:26:58,317 --> 00:26:59,597
I'm telling you, watch yourself.

657
00:26:59,702 --> 00:27:00,713
Why?
Because I hurt your feelings?

658
00:27:00,738 --> 00:27:01,905
- Louis!
- I don't care.

659
00:27:02,040 --> 00:27:03,719
For all I know, you're probably
not even an orphan.

660
00:27:03,743 --> 00:27:05,912
It sure as hell wouldn't be
the first time a con man

661
00:27:06,046 --> 00:27:07,056
tried to make that claim.

662
00:27:07,081 --> 00:27:08,321
- That's enough.
- No, it isn't.

663
00:27:08,334 --> 00:27:09,778
Yes, it is.
Pull the car over right now.

664
00:27:09,803 --> 00:27:11,588
I'm gonna beat the shit
out of him.

665
00:27:19,161 --> 00:27:20,829
Hey, you got a minute?

666
00:27:20,962 --> 00:27:22,213
Oh, wait. Let me turn my back,

667
00:27:22,331 --> 00:27:23,776
so I can give you the right
angle to...

668
00:27:23,800 --> 00:27:26,052
You were right.
We should have stuck together.

669
00:27:27,923 --> 00:27:29,340
I get it... you need my help,

670
00:27:29,476 --> 00:27:32,239
because you got your ass wiped
in court this morning.

671
00:27:32,264 --> 00:27:35,044
You're right. I did get my ass
kicked this morning,

672
00:27:35,069 --> 00:27:36,149
but it wasn't a fair fight.

673
00:27:36,237 --> 00:27:37,520
What are you talking about?

674
00:27:37,656 --> 00:27:39,668
Hardman accessed my computer

675
00:27:39,693 --> 00:27:41,695
and fed the other side
my game plan.

676
00:27:41,863 --> 00:27:44,065
Okay, I'm still waiting
for the part

677
00:27:44,200 --> 00:27:45,477
where I'm supposed
to give a shit.

678
00:27:45,502 --> 00:27:47,848
Hardman did it because
I refused to dump McKernon

679
00:27:47,873 --> 00:27:49,423
for Fletcher
after I gave him my word.

680
00:27:49,542 --> 00:27:50,742
And why should I help you

681
00:27:50,878 --> 00:27:52,490
when you couldn't live up
to your word to me?

682
00:27:52,514 --> 00:27:53,848
I did live up to my word.

683
00:27:53,966 --> 00:27:55,551
- We went to Daniel...
- Oh, bullshit.

684
00:27:55,686 --> 00:27:57,053
No, it's not bullshit.

685
00:27:57,188 --> 00:27:59,084
I welcomed your idea
with open arms,

686
00:27:59,108 --> 00:28:00,870
and by the way, when he asked
whose idea it was,

687
00:28:00,894 --> 00:28:02,261
I gave you the credit.

688
00:28:02,363 --> 00:28:05,032
You see, Harvey, that's the part
you will never understand.

689
00:28:05,151 --> 00:28:07,320
I didn't want the credit.

690
00:28:07,454 --> 00:28:08,715
I wanted us to be a team.

691
00:28:08,740 --> 00:28:09,980
Then let's be a team right now.

692
00:28:10,076 --> 00:28:11,376
But you don't want to be a team.

693
00:28:11,495 --> 00:28:12,895
You want me to help you
get McKernon

694
00:28:12,914 --> 00:28:14,275
so you can make partner.

695
00:28:14,300 --> 00:28:17,136
I want you to help me so I can
keep my word to Avery McKernon.

696
00:28:17,255 --> 00:28:20,592
And when I become partner,
I'll keep my word to you.

697
00:28:22,313 --> 00:28:24,148
What the hell word is that?

698
00:28:24,266 --> 00:28:26,245
That someday what you wrote
on that napkin

699
00:28:26,269 --> 00:28:28,521
goes up on the goddamn wall.

700
00:28:33,998 --> 00:28:36,000
You seem to have done
a lot of work here, Mike.

701
00:28:36,119 --> 00:28:37,263
Oh, it's no big deal.

702
00:28:37,287 --> 00:28:38,670
It is a big deal.

703
00:28:38,789 --> 00:28:42,010
Mike found a loophole
in the Immigration Act of 1975,

704
00:28:42,128 --> 00:28:43,345
and it's gonna blow you away.

705
00:28:43,463 --> 00:28:44,847
I don't know about that,

706
00:28:44,966 --> 00:28:46,968
but it may help Hector Suarez
stay in the country.

707
00:28:47,102 --> 00:28:48,303
That's great.

708
00:28:48,471 --> 00:28:50,334
And you're more than welcome
to stay and watch.

709
00:28:50,359 --> 00:28:52,978
Unfortunately, Claire, I need
you to run back to the office.

710
00:28:53,112 --> 00:28:54,279
Marshall called in sick.

711
00:28:54,398 --> 00:28:56,533
I need someone
to handle the walk-ins, so...

712
00:28:56,652 --> 00:28:59,850
Okay.

713
00:28:59,874 --> 00:29:02,410
Call me. Tell me how it goes.

714
00:29:02,544 --> 00:29:05,047
Yeah.

715
00:29:11,810 --> 00:29:13,250
What the hell are you doing?
That's...

716
00:29:13,262 --> 00:29:14,823
Gonna keep Hector Suarez
in the country?

717
00:29:14,848 --> 00:29:16,683
Yeah.

718
00:29:16,851 --> 00:29:18,496
Yeah, nothing's gonna keep him
in the country.

719
00:29:18,520 --> 00:29:20,333
So what I'm going to do is
I'm gonna buy him some time

720
00:29:20,358 --> 00:29:21,718
so he can get his affairs
in order,

721
00:29:21,860 --> 00:29:23,505
and then I'm gonna give
his children a chance to stay.

722
00:29:23,529 --> 00:29:25,915
I'm just... I'm... I'm sorry.

723
00:29:26,033 --> 00:29:28,346
Are you jealous of me
and Claire or...

724
00:29:28,371 --> 00:29:30,873
Hey, look, I'm not jealous,
and I was waiting

725
00:29:31,008 --> 00:29:33,260
for her to leave to save you
the embarrassment.

726
00:29:33,379 --> 00:29:34,262
The embarrassment of what?

727
00:29:34,381 --> 00:29:35,848
That's good work.

728
00:29:35,967 --> 00:29:37,300
I'm not talking about the work.

729
00:29:37,436 --> 00:29:40,138
I'm talking about your
"bike messenger by day,

730
00:29:40,273 --> 00:29:41,583
"law student by night" bullshit.

731
00:29:41,608 --> 00:29:43,704
All right, you don't know
what you're talking about.

732
00:29:43,729 --> 00:29:45,040
What are you gonna tell me next?

733
00:29:45,064 --> 00:29:47,767
Your roommate is a stripper
who's in medical school?

734
00:29:47,902 --> 00:29:51,290
Tell me right now... I call
Columbia, your story holds up.

735
00:29:54,079 --> 00:29:55,139
That's what I thought.

736
00:29:55,164 --> 00:29:57,060
Forget who I am,
and take a look at that folder.

737
00:29:57,084 --> 00:29:58,980
- This is a man's life.
- Don't touch me.

738
00:29:59,004 --> 00:30:00,244
If you know what's good for you,

739
00:30:00,256 --> 00:30:02,141
you'll stay the hell away
from Claire.

740
00:30:12,576 --> 00:30:13,586
Daniel...

741
00:30:13,611 --> 00:30:16,258
Did you know
that some of these species

742
00:30:16,282 --> 00:30:18,951
can live up to 200 years?

743
00:30:19,087 --> 00:30:20,370
Fascinating.

744
00:30:20,506 --> 00:30:24,938
Did you know Fletcher Engines
is picking up the pieces?

745
00:30:24,963 --> 00:30:26,848
I guess congratulations
are in order.

746
00:30:26,966 --> 00:30:28,300
I not here for a pat
on the back.

747
00:30:28,435 --> 00:30:30,197
I'm here to tell you
you're making me partner.

748
00:30:30,221 --> 00:30:32,701
Partner?

749
00:30:32,726 --> 00:30:35,395
I never said signing McKernon
was the key to making partner.

750
00:30:35,530 --> 00:30:36,530
Yes, you...

751
00:30:36,648 --> 00:30:38,544
All I said was landing them
could go a long way

752
00:30:38,568 --> 00:30:39,818
toward making your case.

753
00:30:39,954 --> 00:30:40,954
Bullshit.

754
00:30:40,956 --> 00:30:42,741
You said partnership
was on the table.

755
00:30:42,875 --> 00:30:44,577
And I said I was gonna
hold you to it.

756
00:30:44,711 --> 00:30:46,162
And I'm going to right now.

757
00:30:47,416 --> 00:30:50,219
You don't hold me to anything.

758
00:30:52,976 --> 00:30:57,732
But I did say partnership
was on the table, and it is...

759
00:30:57,850 --> 00:31:00,186
just not for you.

760
00:31:01,990 --> 00:31:03,000
What are you talking about?

761
00:31:03,025 --> 00:31:04,743
Well, I can't very well
make you partner

762
00:31:04,861 --> 00:31:06,947
after I just told Louis
I'm making him partner.

763
00:31:07,082 --> 00:31:09,428
What?

764
00:31:09,452 --> 00:31:12,372
You don't get it, do you?

765
00:31:12,507 --> 00:31:15,020
This isn't about
bringing in business.

766
00:31:15,045 --> 00:31:17,358
This is about figuring out
who would do whatever it takes.

767
00:31:17,382 --> 00:31:19,050
I did whatever it took.

768
00:31:19,185 --> 00:31:20,585
You didn't do a thing.

769
00:31:20,687 --> 00:31:23,534
You had the chance
to triple our business,

770
00:31:23,559 --> 00:31:25,811
and all you had to do
was take a knee.

771
00:31:25,946 --> 00:31:27,792
You mean bend a knee.

772
00:31:27,816 --> 00:31:31,931
Yes, that's exactly what I mean.

773
00:31:31,955 --> 00:31:33,907
But you're
an arrogant little boy

774
00:31:34,043 --> 00:31:35,961
who would rather win
than get in line.

775
00:31:37,632 --> 00:31:40,585
Well, what the hell did Louis do
to get in line?

776
00:31:40,720 --> 00:31:43,473
He did whatever it took.

777
00:31:58,415 --> 00:31:59,976
- Please get away from me.
- Claire, wait.

778
00:32:00,001 --> 00:32:02,147
- Nathan told me everything.
- Just let me explain, okay?

779
00:32:02,172 --> 00:32:03,600
No, explain what...
That you're a sociopath?

780
00:32:03,625 --> 00:32:04,675
I'm not a sociopath.

781
00:32:04,792 --> 00:32:06,187
I'm the same guy that you
hit it off with.

782
00:32:06,212 --> 00:32:07,512
No, you're not. You lied to me.

783
00:32:07,631 --> 00:32:09,443
Yes, I am, and I didn't mean
to lie to you, okay?

784
00:32:09,467 --> 00:32:10,611
I was gonna tell you the truth.

785
00:32:10,636 --> 00:32:13,188
Then why didn't you?

786
00:32:13,307 --> 00:32:15,453
Because you said you wanted
to be with a guy who was doing

787
00:32:15,477 --> 00:32:17,789
something good with his life,
and I wasn't.

788
00:32:17,814 --> 00:32:20,150
So what, now you're here to
tell me that all of a sudden,

789
00:32:20,285 --> 00:32:22,166
you want to dedicate your life
to helping people

790
00:32:22,288 --> 00:32:23,705
or some other lie like that?

791
00:32:23,823 --> 00:32:26,386
It's not a lie, and what I did
would have helped Hector Suarez.

792
00:32:26,411 --> 00:32:28,163
Yeah, but you only did it...

793
00:32:28,331 --> 00:32:29,858
Claire, please,
you have to believe me.

794
00:32:29,883 --> 00:32:32,553
After I met you, I decided
to get my shit together.

795
00:32:32,672 --> 00:32:34,317
I am trying to get
my shit together.

796
00:32:34,341 --> 00:32:36,370
Okay, Mike,
you know what I hate more

797
00:32:36,394 --> 00:32:39,207
than guys who don't have
their shit together?

798
00:32:39,232 --> 00:32:42,319
It's guys who lie about
getting their shit together.

799
00:32:46,861 --> 00:32:49,080
Claire.

800
00:32:53,872 --> 00:32:56,875
Louis, fill up the tank.
I'll be back.

801
00:33:02,687 --> 00:33:06,142
Well?

802
00:33:06,276 --> 00:33:07,310
Well, what?

803
00:33:07,445 --> 00:33:09,814
You heard what he said.
Fill up the tank.

804
00:33:09,949 --> 00:33:11,294
Yeah, I did hear what he said.

805
00:33:11,319 --> 00:33:13,738
He said,
"Louis, fill up the tank."

806
00:33:17,044 --> 00:33:18,555
Well, where I come from, it's
people who didn't go to college

807
00:33:18,580 --> 00:33:19,774
who fill up gas tanks.

808
00:33:19,799 --> 00:33:20,892
Yeah, and where I come from,

809
00:33:20,917 --> 00:33:22,395
if you take another step
towards me...

810
00:33:22,420 --> 00:33:24,065
Oh, what, the tough kid from
the city is gonna beat my ass?

811
00:33:24,089 --> 00:33:25,473
Louis, I'm telling you
right now...

812
00:33:28,897 --> 00:33:32,268
You ruined my life.
You ruined my firm.

813
00:33:32,403 --> 00:33:35,657
Louis!

814
00:34:00,501 --> 00:34:02,503
You son of a bitch.

815
00:34:02,638 --> 00:34:03,671
Wait. Harvey...

816
00:34:03,840 --> 00:34:05,234
Tell me right now
you weren't the one

817
00:34:05,259 --> 00:34:08,072
that gave Fletcher Engines
my game plan.

818
00:34:08,097 --> 00:34:11,161
Hardman told me he wasn't gonna
make you partner anyway.

819
00:34:11,186 --> 00:34:12,998
And once he offered it to me,
all I had to do was...

820
00:34:13,022 --> 00:34:14,416
Sell me out.

821
00:34:14,441 --> 00:34:17,388
How is what I did any different
than you going after.

822
00:34:17,413 --> 00:34:19,175
McKernon Motors
in the first place?

823
00:34:19,199 --> 00:34:22,035
If you don't understand that
on your own, you never will.

824
00:34:22,204 --> 00:34:24,539
So, from now on, you stay
on your side of the yard.

825
00:34:24,707 --> 00:34:27,210
- I'll stay on mine.
- No, Harvey, listen to me.

826
00:34:27,345 --> 00:34:29,324
You told me you would fight
to get our names on the wall

827
00:34:29,348 --> 00:34:30,588
once you got on the other side.

828
00:34:30,684 --> 00:34:32,111
I can do the same for you.

829
00:34:32,136 --> 00:34:33,437
Did you hear what I just said?

830
00:34:33,555 --> 00:34:35,201
I don't want you
doing shit for me.

831
00:34:35,225 --> 00:34:36,786
Oh, so it would be okay
if you were the one

832
00:34:36,811 --> 00:34:38,028
who got there first?

833
00:34:38,146 --> 00:34:39,875
It would have been okay
if you got there first

834
00:34:39,899 --> 00:34:41,283
fair and square,

835
00:34:41,402 --> 00:34:43,547
because then I would have
believed you

836
00:34:43,571 --> 00:34:45,300
when you said you wanted
to be a team.

837
00:34:45,324 --> 00:34:46,741
I do want to be a team, Harvey.

838
00:34:46,877 --> 00:34:48,077
That's why I helped you after.

839
00:34:48,246 --> 00:34:50,442
No, you don't!

840
00:34:50,467 --> 00:34:51,633
You don't want to be a team.

841
00:34:51,751 --> 00:34:53,470
You just want to have it
both ways,

842
00:34:53,588 --> 00:34:55,056
because you're a disloyal rat.

843
00:34:55,174 --> 00:34:56,820
You always have been,
and you always will,

844
00:34:56,844 --> 00:34:59,263
no matter what it says
on your door.

845
00:35:01,651 --> 00:35:03,914
Well, like you said, we've been
pitted against each other

846
00:35:03,938 --> 00:35:05,773
since day one.

847
00:35:08,028 --> 00:35:10,498
You asked how many of the
50 associates we started with

848
00:35:10,615 --> 00:35:12,284
would make partner.

849
00:35:12,419 --> 00:35:13,430
Well, you know what?

850
00:35:13,454 --> 00:35:14,931
I don't give a shit
about the other 49,

851
00:35:14,956 --> 00:35:17,319
because I'm the one who did.

852
00:35:17,344 --> 00:35:20,107
I'm the one who did.

853
00:35:20,132 --> 00:35:21,659
And now get the hell
out of my face,

854
00:35:21,684 --> 00:35:22,801
because I have work to do.

855
00:35:39,880 --> 00:35:42,193
You know he did that
on purpose, right?

856
00:35:42,218 --> 00:35:43,668
Did what on purpose?

857
00:35:43,837 --> 00:35:46,734
He asked you to fill the tank
because he knew what you'd do.

858
00:35:46,758 --> 00:35:48,760
Knew what I would do?
What about what you would do?

859
00:35:50,481 --> 00:35:53,351
He knew that too.

860
00:35:55,189 --> 00:35:56,189
Louis...

861
00:35:56,190 --> 00:35:58,192
You never even said
you were sorry.

862
00:36:05,622 --> 00:36:07,591
I am sorry, Louis.

863
00:36:07,709 --> 00:36:10,112
I'm sorry that I lied to you.

864
00:36:11,799 --> 00:36:15,053
I'm not a con man, Louis.

865
00:36:15,189 --> 00:36:19,444
Every single other thing
I ever told you was true.

866
00:36:26,039 --> 00:36:30,211
Want to know something that I've
never even admitted to myself?

867
00:36:35,471 --> 00:36:37,200
I never learned to drive
for the same reason

868
00:36:37,225 --> 00:36:40,261
I never went to law school.

869
00:36:40,430 --> 00:36:42,993
Both my parents were killed
in a car accident.

870
00:36:43,017 --> 00:36:46,821
And ever since then,
I've never been able to...

871
00:36:46,940 --> 00:36:49,326
Get behind the wheel.

872
00:36:52,115 --> 00:36:55,001
And then Harvey gave me
a license, and I took it.

873
00:36:58,125 --> 00:37:01,596
You were 11 years old.

874
00:37:03,885 --> 00:37:07,856
I mean, you must have felt
so alone.

875
00:37:09,944 --> 00:37:12,065
I thought you said you
didn't believe I was an orphan.

876
00:37:14,401 --> 00:37:18,050
I looked it up.

877
00:37:18,075 --> 00:37:20,471
I had to once I found out that
you never went to law school.

878
00:37:20,495 --> 00:37:23,308
You mean once you found out
that I'm a fraud.

879
00:37:23,333 --> 00:37:25,051
You're not a fraud, Mike.

880
00:37:27,924 --> 00:37:29,642
You just never went
to law school.

881
00:37:32,013 --> 00:37:34,482
Okay, Frazier, you get a grape.

882
00:37:36,104 --> 00:37:38,906
Ali, I got you a fruit punch.

883
00:37:41,495 --> 00:37:43,497
You two work your shit out?

884
00:37:45,202 --> 00:37:47,838
I'll take that as a yes.
Let's get the hell out of here.

885
00:38:01,562 --> 00:38:04,231
I should never have lied to her.

886
00:38:04,367 --> 00:38:05,377
Oh, screw her, man.

887
00:38:05,402 --> 00:38:06,713
If she doesn't like you
for who you are,

888
00:38:06,738 --> 00:38:07,931
she doesn't deserve you.

889
00:38:07,955 --> 00:38:09,718
It's not Claire's fault.
It's mine.

890
00:38:09,742 --> 00:38:11,827
I know you were into her
and everything,

891
00:38:11,962 --> 00:38:13,246
but trust me,

892
00:38:13,415 --> 00:38:14,942
there are plenty of other fish
in the sea.

893
00:38:14,967 --> 00:38:16,051
You don't know that.

894
00:38:16,170 --> 00:38:17,564
For all you know,
I'm never gonna meet

895
00:38:17,588 --> 00:38:18,698
another girl like her again.

896
00:38:18,723 --> 00:38:20,007
Michael...

897
00:38:20,142 --> 00:38:21,526
Trevor, if I'm gonna have
to listen

898
00:38:21,645 --> 00:38:22,925
to whatever you're about to say,

899
00:38:23,014 --> 00:38:24,431
I'm gonna need a joint first.

900
00:38:24,600 --> 00:38:26,662
Come on, I thought you were
trying to turn your life around.

901
00:38:26,686 --> 00:38:29,272
I'll turn my life around
tomorrow.

902
00:38:29,408 --> 00:38:31,470
But tonight
I'm a bike messenger, so...

903
00:38:31,494 --> 00:38:33,329
- Dude...
- Trevor.

904
00:38:36,335 --> 00:38:37,479
All right.

905
00:38:37,504 --> 00:38:40,624
Fine.

906
00:38:40,793 --> 00:38:42,405
And I know Grammy
doesn't want you living here,

907
00:38:42,429 --> 00:38:44,881
but you can crash here tonight
if you want.

908
00:38:56,368 --> 00:38:58,871
Donna.

909
00:38:58,989 --> 00:39:01,185
Something wrong?

910
00:39:01,209 --> 00:39:02,710
Why would something be wrong?

911
00:39:02,829 --> 00:39:06,560
Because I don't believe you've
ever been in my office before.

912
00:39:06,585 --> 00:39:09,171
No, nothing's wrong.

913
00:39:09,306 --> 00:39:10,673
And I know it's not my place,

914
00:39:10,808 --> 00:39:13,204
but I'm here to tell you that
I think you're making a mistake.

915
00:39:13,229 --> 00:39:18,163
Is this about me not giving
people off for Columbus Day?

916
00:39:18,187 --> 00:39:20,667
You know this isn't about that.

917
00:39:20,692 --> 00:39:22,754
Harvey laid it on the line
with Daniel,

918
00:39:22,778 --> 00:39:24,245
and you didn't have his back.

919
00:39:24,364 --> 00:39:27,835
Donna, I've had Harvey's back
since the day I met him.

920
00:39:27,953 --> 00:39:29,671
For your information,
when I found out

921
00:39:29,789 --> 00:39:32,041
what Daniel was up to,
I had him guarantee

922
00:39:32,177 --> 00:39:33,521
partnership was on the table.

923
00:39:33,546 --> 00:39:35,347
And then you let him give it
to the wrong man.

924
00:39:35,349 --> 00:39:37,117
That is on Harvey, not on me.

925
00:39:37,218 --> 00:39:38,352
What are you talking about?

926
00:39:40,524 --> 00:39:42,976
Daniel was worried
that Harvey couldn't put

927
00:39:43,111 --> 00:39:45,397
the firm's best interests
ahead of his own,

928
00:39:45,532 --> 00:39:47,283
and Harvey proved him right.

929
00:39:47,402 --> 00:39:49,298
Or maybe you're just
telling yourself that

930
00:39:49,322 --> 00:39:51,908
because you don't want
to stand up to Daniel Hardman.

931
00:39:52,043 --> 00:39:55,942
Donna, there's a reason
why you are where you are

932
00:39:55,966 --> 00:39:57,561
and I am where I am,
and that is because

933
00:39:57,585 --> 00:40:00,004
one of us sees
the bigger picture.

934
00:40:03,228 --> 00:40:05,513
You knew about Fletcher Engines?

935
00:40:05,648 --> 00:40:08,484
What I know is that
Harvey's time will come.

936
00:40:08,603 --> 00:40:11,356
And if this little incident gets
him to think about other people

937
00:40:11,491 --> 00:40:14,160
for a change, then I'll take it.

938
00:40:21,340 --> 00:40:22,936
You're up early.

939
00:40:22,960 --> 00:40:27,348
I'm up early,
because I couldn't sleep.

940
00:40:27,467 --> 00:40:31,138
Where we you all night?

941
00:40:31,273 --> 00:40:33,775
You know where I was.

942
00:40:36,616 --> 00:40:38,678
I was staying
at my new apartment.

943
00:40:38,702 --> 00:40:40,487
I thought we'd settled this.

944
00:40:40,622 --> 00:40:42,991
You settled it. I didn't.

945
00:40:43,126 --> 00:40:46,881
I'm telling you, that kid...

946
00:40:47,000 --> 00:40:48,480
Grammy, for as long
as I can remember,

947
00:40:48,501 --> 00:40:50,002
you've been calling him
"that kid"

948
00:40:50,171 --> 00:40:51,890
or "that boy" or worse.

949
00:40:52,008 --> 00:40:55,345
His name is Trevor.

950
00:40:55,480 --> 00:40:58,099
And he's my best friend.

951
00:40:59,854 --> 00:41:02,166
Look, I'm gonna do this thing
with our without your blessing,

952
00:41:02,190 --> 00:41:03,859
but...

953
00:41:06,031 --> 00:41:08,116
it sure would be nice
to have it.

954
00:41:10,672 --> 00:41:11,938
Okay, Michael.

955
00:41:12,040 --> 00:41:16,072
I'm not gonna lie to you
and pretend I approve,

956
00:41:16,097 --> 00:41:18,910
but...

957
00:41:18,935 --> 00:41:23,057
you're a grown man,
and I respect your decision.

958
00:41:29,318 --> 00:41:31,904
I love you, Grammy.

959
00:41:32,039 --> 00:41:34,408
I love you too.

960
00:41:39,418 --> 00:41:40,562
Thank you.

961
00:41:40,587 --> 00:41:42,616
I believe that's all
I need to know.

962
00:41:42,640 --> 00:41:44,118
Thank you for your time,
Ms. Pearson.

963
00:41:44,143 --> 00:41:47,680
I will wait to hear from you.

964
00:41:49,986 --> 00:41:52,105
Oh, one more thing...

965
00:41:52,239 --> 00:41:56,828
Does your father know you came
to me for a job?

966
00:41:56,947 --> 00:41:57,947
I-I...

967
00:41:57,949 --> 00:41:59,309
Did you really think
I didn't know

968
00:41:59,334 --> 00:42:01,597
you were Robert Zane's daughter?

969
00:42:01,621 --> 00:42:04,624
Is that why
you're interviewing me?

970
00:42:04,760 --> 00:42:05,843
Because if it is,

971
00:42:05,962 --> 00:42:07,941
I would like to remove myself
from consideration.

972
00:42:07,965 --> 00:42:10,217
If you don't want to work
for your father,

973
00:42:10,352 --> 00:42:12,304
that's your business.

974
00:42:12,439 --> 00:42:14,952
I'm hiring you
because I like what I see.

975
00:42:14,976 --> 00:42:16,393
Hiring me?

976
00:42:16,528 --> 00:42:19,008
You start Monday,
if that's not too much trouble.

977
00:42:19,033 --> 00:42:20,701
I will be the first one in.

978
00:42:26,879 --> 00:42:28,641
Aren't you gonna ask me
why I don't want to work

979
00:42:28,665 --> 00:42:29,715
with my father?

980
00:42:29,834 --> 00:42:31,384
I know why.

981
00:42:31,503 --> 00:42:33,222
I have a dad just like yours.

982
00:42:33,339 --> 00:42:34,423
He has his own law firm?

983
00:42:34,558 --> 00:42:36,343
He's a surgeon.

984
00:42:36,478 --> 00:42:38,396
But it's the same damn thing.

985
00:42:53,589 --> 00:42:55,341
- How are we on time?
- We're perfect.

986
00:42:55,459 --> 00:42:57,071
But I'm not going in there.
You two are.

987
00:42:57,095 --> 00:42:58,963
What are you talking about?

988
00:42:59,099 --> 00:43:00,526
I said I was giving you 50%
of McKernon.

989
00:43:00,550 --> 00:43:02,936
I didn't say I was keeping
the other 50%.

990
00:43:04,891 --> 00:43:07,060
Oh, so you finally realized
they need an upgrade

991
00:43:07,229 --> 00:43:08,612
in representation.

992
00:43:08,731 --> 00:43:09,898
Easy, Frazier.

993
00:43:10,032 --> 00:43:11,713
You'd still be out cold
at that gas station

994
00:43:11,736 --> 00:43:12,953
if I hadn't saved your ass.

995
00:43:13,071 --> 00:43:15,133
Okay, I would have gotten out...
eventually.

996
00:43:15,158 --> 00:43:17,054
- Not from where I was standing.
- I'm slippery.

997
00:43:17,078 --> 00:43:18,638
I told you...
I wrestled in high school.

998
00:43:18,747 --> 00:43:20,499
- I checked on that. He did.
- See?

999
00:43:20,633 --> 00:43:22,919
Oh, and now
you're fighting for him?

1000
00:43:23,088 --> 00:43:24,733
Okay, I guess
my job here is done.

1001
00:43:24,757 --> 00:43:25,974
Wait. Where are you going?

1002
00:43:26,093 --> 00:43:27,453
I'm taking the car back
to the city.

1003
00:43:27,478 --> 00:43:29,547
Well, what the hell are we
supposed to do?

1004
00:43:29,571 --> 00:43:32,819
Ray's waiting on the other side
of the parking lot, isn't he?

1005
00:43:32,843 --> 00:43:34,578
He'll drive you two back
when you're done.

1006
00:43:34,679 --> 00:43:36,464
Wait. You know what?
I have a better idea.

1007
00:43:36,582 --> 00:43:38,244
How about you take Ray,
we take the car,

1008
00:43:38,268 --> 00:43:40,453
and I teach Mike how to drive
on the way home?

1009
00:43:40,589 --> 00:43:42,824
- You'd actually do that?
- Yeah, I would.

1010
00:43:42,959 --> 00:43:44,711
- No way.
- You don't trust me?

1011
00:43:44,829 --> 00:43:46,390
I don't trust you
as far as I can throw you.

1012
00:43:46,415 --> 00:43:47,549
You're a goddamn fraud.

1013
00:43:47,667 --> 00:43:49,312
- That's what I said.
- Harvey, seriously.

1014
00:43:49,337 --> 00:43:51,032
- Come on, I promise...
- Okay, I know you will.

1015
00:43:51,056 --> 00:43:52,758
Louis, you make one dent
in this car,

1016
00:43:52,893 --> 00:43:55,094
Mike's back on the street,
and your name's off the door.

1017
00:43:59,353 --> 00:44:02,189
You think he was serious
about what he just said?

1018
00:44:02,358 --> 00:44:03,993
Okay, well,
I'm just a little nervous,

1019
00:44:04,111 --> 00:44:05,756
'cause I feel like I drank
that power drink,

1020
00:44:05,780 --> 00:44:07,007
and it has a lot
of sodium in it.

1021
00:44:07,032 --> 00:44:08,701
Actually, it's like
drinking a hot dog,

1022
00:44:08,835 --> 00:44:10,564
but the doctor says it raises
my blood pressure, so...

1023
00:44:10,588 --> 00:44:13,374
I'm gonna need you to let me do
the talking in there.

1024
00:44:15,919 --> 00:44:22,423
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man

