1
00:00:01,000 --> 00:00:02,340
Previously on Suits...

2
00:00:02,341 --> 00:00:03,991
I want you to go back
over your work

3
00:00:04,015 --> 00:00:05,163
with a fine-tooth comb.

4
00:00:05,187 --> 00:00:06,670
We're as protected as we can be.

5
00:00:06,695 --> 00:00:08,211
Every partner at this firm

6
00:00:08,236 --> 00:00:10,120
goes over their work
if I say so.

7
00:00:10,144 --> 00:00:12,497
I'm not every goddamn partner.

8
00:00:12,522 --> 00:00:13,737
I made a deal with Forstman.

9
00:00:13,762 --> 00:00:15,078
This has got to be

10
00:00:15,102 --> 00:00:16,919
the most genius thing
you have ever done

11
00:00:16,944 --> 00:00:20,001
in your entire, wonderful life.

12
00:00:20,026 --> 00:00:21,776
Forstman's insisting
that I run the money

13
00:00:21,801 --> 00:00:23,317
through Switzerland
and the Caymans.

14
00:00:23,341 --> 00:00:24,555
Louis, that's illegal.

15
00:00:24,580 --> 00:00:26,398
You didn't see the look
on Harvey's face

16
00:00:26,423 --> 00:00:27,738
when he found out
that I was the one

17
00:00:27,762 --> 00:00:28,910
who saved the day,

18
00:00:28,935 --> 00:00:30,853
and I am not gonna see
the look on his face

19
00:00:30,877 --> 00:00:32,360
when he finds out that I didn't.

20
00:00:32,385 --> 00:00:33,599
There isn't enough money
in the world

21
00:00:33,624 --> 00:00:34,940
for me to ever trust you again.

22
00:00:34,964 --> 00:00:37,184
- Listen to me.
- No, you listen to me!

23
00:00:37,208 --> 00:00:38,680
You're fired.

24
00:00:42,701 --> 00:00:44,385
- No, I can't.
- Rachel. Rachel.

25
00:00:44,410 --> 00:00:45,413
What the hell is this?

26
00:00:45,414 --> 00:00:47,265
A job offer.

27
00:00:47,290 --> 00:00:48,874
I am going to tell Mike
what happened.

28
00:00:48,898 --> 00:00:50,146
If you do this,

29
00:00:50,171 --> 00:00:52,222
you will be risking
your whole life with Mike.

30
00:00:52,246 --> 00:00:55,102
I'm risking it if I don't.

31
00:00:58,142 --> 00:01:06,172
♪ ♪

32
00:01:26,277 --> 00:01:28,329
I heard.

33
00:01:28,354 --> 00:01:29,803
How?

34
00:01:29,827 --> 00:01:30,873
Amy.

35
00:01:30,898 --> 00:01:31,912
Why would she...

36
00:01:31,937 --> 00:01:33,855
So that you wouldn't have to.

37
00:01:33,880 --> 00:01:35,061
Here.

38
00:01:35,085 --> 00:01:37,438
Shit.

39
00:01:37,463 --> 00:01:40,119
I didn't even think
about what would happen to her.

40
00:01:40,144 --> 00:01:41,493
Mike, you don't have
to think about anyone

41
00:01:41,517 --> 00:01:42,832
except for you right now.

42
00:01:42,856 --> 00:01:44,573
I don't want to think about me.

43
00:01:44,598 --> 00:01:47,454
All I've done is let everyone
down, including you.

44
00:01:47,479 --> 00:01:50,033
You have not let me down.

45
00:01:50,057 --> 00:01:51,965
You don't even know
what I've done.

46
00:01:55,685 --> 00:01:59,111
Whatever it is,
it can't be as bad as...

47
00:01:59,135 --> 00:02:00,775
As I think?

48
00:02:04,829 --> 00:02:07,250
Rachel, I lost my job.

49
00:02:07,274 --> 00:02:08,355
I lost the takeover.

50
00:02:08,379 --> 00:02:09,895
I lost Walter Gillis
his company.

51
00:02:09,920 --> 00:02:11,603
I cut a deal to sell out the man

52
00:02:11,627 --> 00:02:13,244
who gave me a chance
in the first place.

53
00:02:13,269 --> 00:02:14,517
And to top it all off,

54
00:02:14,542 --> 00:02:16,996
the guy who made me
do that called me his guy

55
00:02:17,020 --> 00:02:18,536
and then offered me a job.

56
00:02:18,561 --> 00:02:21,115
So what does that make me?

57
00:02:21,140 --> 00:02:22,690
It makes you a human being.

58
00:02:22,715 --> 00:02:30,745
♪ ♪

59
00:02:34,236 --> 00:02:36,389
I don't know what to do.

60
00:02:36,414 --> 00:02:37,595
I don't either.

61
00:02:37,619 --> 00:02:42,015
But we don't have to do
anything tonight.

62
00:02:42,040 --> 00:02:43,791
Louis, you need to calm down.

63
00:02:43,816 --> 00:02:44,829
I broke the law.

64
00:02:44,854 --> 00:02:46,438
Please keep your voice down.

65
00:02:46,462 --> 00:02:48,045
Why? Let any man judge me.

66
00:02:48,069 --> 00:02:49,116
So says the good book.

67
00:02:49,141 --> 00:02:50,289
- No, it doesn't.
- You know what?

68
00:02:50,314 --> 00:02:51,998
I think I know
what the goddamn good book says.

69
00:02:52,022 --> 00:02:53,471
Listen to me.

70
00:02:53,496 --> 00:02:55,514
You did what you had to do.
Oh, really?

71
00:02:55,538 --> 00:02:57,456
Well, that's not what you said
when you found out.

72
00:02:57,481 --> 00:02:58,930
You said,
"Louis, that's illegal."

73
00:02:58,954 --> 00:03:00,772
Because I was trying to get
you not to go through with it.

74
00:03:00,797 --> 00:03:02,514
But you made a decision.
I understand why.

75
00:03:02,539 --> 00:03:04,189
And now that it's done,

76
00:03:04,213 --> 00:03:06,868
I'm not going to let you
beat yourself up about it.

77
00:03:06,893 --> 00:03:08,544
Yeah, well, you may not,
but what do you think Harvey

78
00:03:08,568 --> 00:03:10,017
and Jessica are going to do
when they find out?

79
00:03:10,042 --> 00:03:13,333
Louis, you have been a hero
again and again.

80
00:03:13,357 --> 00:03:15,242
And if the one time
they actually treat you like one

81
00:03:15,267 --> 00:03:16,792
you crossed a little line
to get there,

82
00:03:16,807 --> 00:03:18,725
that doesn't make you horrible.

83
00:03:18,750 --> 00:03:19,831
It makes you Harvey.

84
00:03:19,855 --> 00:03:21,606
You know what?
You're absolutely right.

85
00:03:21,631 --> 00:03:22,980
And as of this second,

86
00:03:23,004 --> 00:03:24,989
I'm going to start acting
like the hero that I am.

87
00:03:25,014 --> 00:03:26,530
Hey, jerk-off.

88
00:03:26,554 --> 00:03:28,495
Who do I have to blow
to get some more nuts?

89
00:03:33,789 --> 00:03:35,539
It turned out he knew
all about the crop reports.

90
00:03:35,564 --> 00:03:36,712
You know what I did?

91
00:03:36,736 --> 00:03:38,788
I nailed him on six counts
of mail fraud.

92
00:03:40,254 --> 00:03:42,272
Did you tell them the one
about how you got your head

93
00:03:42,296 --> 00:03:43,812
stuck up Eric Woodall's ass?

94
00:03:45,612 --> 00:03:47,989
Excuse me for a second.

95
00:03:50,235 --> 00:03:51,751
What the hell
are you doing here?

96
00:03:51,775 --> 00:03:52,889
You think you're the only person

97
00:03:52,914 --> 00:03:54,397
who can have someone followed?

98
00:03:54,421 --> 00:03:55,424
You have no right.

99
00:03:55,426 --> 00:03:56,775
Oh, I have every right.

100
00:03:56,800 --> 00:03:58,450
I just didn't need
to hire someone

101
00:03:58,474 --> 00:04:01,564
'cause it turns out you come to
the same shithole every night,

102
00:04:01,589 --> 00:04:04,043
telling the same stories
to the same people

103
00:04:04,067 --> 00:04:06,823
because you have no place
else to go.

104
00:04:06,848 --> 00:04:08,096
If you're thinking
you can bait me

105
00:04:08,121 --> 00:04:09,206
into taking a swing at you,

106
00:04:09,226 --> 00:04:10,340
you might be right.

107
00:04:10,364 --> 00:04:12,115
Why don't you take a swing
at this?

108
00:04:12,140 --> 00:04:13,991
Oh, you're trying
to bribe me now.

109
00:04:14,015 --> 00:04:16,335
That's a certified letter
outlining everything

110
00:04:16,360 --> 00:04:18,646
that's happened
since you started targeting me,

111
00:04:18,671 --> 00:04:20,355
every bullshit move you've made.

112
00:04:20,379 --> 00:04:22,632
It's not bullshit.
It's an ongoing investigation.

113
00:04:22,657 --> 00:04:24,139
And it's turned up bullshit,

114
00:04:24,164 --> 00:04:26,284
which I've outlined
for Judge Hopkins.

115
00:04:26,308 --> 00:04:28,259
Everything
from targeting my clients

116
00:04:28,283 --> 00:04:29,330
to having me followed.

117
00:04:29,355 --> 00:04:30,470
So now you have ten days

118
00:04:30,495 --> 00:04:32,245
to dispute
my accounting of events,

119
00:04:32,269 --> 00:04:35,058
and when they're done,
I expect to never see you again.

120
00:04:35,083 --> 00:04:36,968
You don't know me that well.

121
00:04:36,992 --> 00:04:39,579
Sean, any time
you want to put the badge down

122
00:04:39,604 --> 00:04:41,957
and fight me man-to-man,

123
00:04:41,982 --> 00:04:44,158
you know where to find me.

124
00:04:53,571 --> 00:04:57,265
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪

125
00:04:57,290 --> 00:05:00,615
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪

126
00:05:00,639 --> 00:05:03,796
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪

127
00:05:03,820 --> 00:05:07,581
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪

128
00:05:07,606 --> 00:05:10,562
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪

129
00:05:10,586 --> 00:05:14,514
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪

130
00:05:14,539 --> 00:05:15,988
♪ All right ♪

131
00:05:16,013 --> 00:05:21,549
♪ Suits 4x07 ♪ We're Done
Original Air Date on July 30, 2014

132
00:05:21,573 --> 00:05:23,346
♪ the greenback boogie ♪

133
00:05:23,371 --> 00:05:25,378
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man.

134
00:05:29,870 --> 00:05:32,179
How's the job hunting going?

135
00:05:32,180 --> 00:05:33,274
What do you want, Forstman?

136
00:05:33,276 --> 00:05:36,735
Oh, now that you don't
want my money, it's Forstman?

137
00:05:36,759 --> 00:05:38,878
No mister?

138
00:05:38,902 --> 00:05:40,719
What happened to the obsequious
little shit

139
00:05:40,744 --> 00:05:43,132
who approached me in a coffee
shop with his hand out?

140
00:05:43,156 --> 00:05:45,141
He realized that you
don't deserve any respect.

141
00:05:45,166 --> 00:05:46,615
I don't need your respect.

142
00:05:46,639 --> 00:05:48,188
I need an answer
on my job offer.

143
00:05:48,213 --> 00:05:49,729
Thought I was pretty clear.

144
00:05:49,754 --> 00:05:52,543
Your mouth said one thing.

145
00:05:52,568 --> 00:05:54,107
Let's see what your eyes
have to say.

146
00:06:00,372 --> 00:06:01,620
A million dollars.

147
00:06:01,644 --> 00:06:04,668
Is this a joke?
It's your signing bonus.

148
00:06:04,693 --> 00:06:07,314
Are you ready
to come work for me now?

149
00:06:07,339 --> 00:06:10,831
Thought I was
an obsequious little shit.

150
00:06:10,856 --> 00:06:13,410
You are, but so was I
when I was your age,

151
00:06:13,434 --> 00:06:16,626
and look what happened to me.

152
00:06:16,651 --> 00:06:19,707
You could make it ten million,
Charles.

153
00:06:19,731 --> 00:06:20,778
I don't want your money.

154
00:06:20,803 --> 00:06:22,420
I'm not gonna make it
ten million.

155
00:06:22,445 --> 00:06:23,761
The offer is one,

156
00:06:23,785 --> 00:06:25,803
and that's where it's standing.

157
00:06:25,827 --> 00:06:27,477
You have a day.

158
00:06:27,502 --> 00:06:29,521
If you decide
not to take my offer,

159
00:06:29,546 --> 00:06:32,167
I will know
you're not only an asshole.

160
00:06:32,192 --> 00:06:34,277
You're a fool.

161
00:06:34,302 --> 00:06:35,908
Let's go.

162
00:06:45,522 --> 00:06:46,803
Jessica.

163
00:06:46,828 --> 00:06:48,344
To what do I owe the honor?
What can I do for you?

164
00:06:48,369 --> 00:06:50,153
Louis, I am coming to you

165
00:06:50,178 --> 00:06:52,297
because the question
isn't what you can do for me,

166
00:06:52,321 --> 00:06:54,674
but what can I do for you?

167
00:06:54,699 --> 00:06:55,814
Harvey and I were very impressed

168
00:06:55,839 --> 00:06:57,288
by what you did
with Charles Forstman.

169
00:06:57,312 --> 00:06:58,596
I'm impressed
that you understand

170
00:06:58,618 --> 00:06:59,732
how impressive it was.

171
00:06:59,757 --> 00:07:01,273
And since we couldn't figure out

172
00:07:01,297 --> 00:07:04,019
how best to show our gratitude,

173
00:07:04,044 --> 00:07:06,297
I'm here to ask you
what you would like.

174
00:07:06,322 --> 00:07:07,973
I'm sorry.

175
00:07:10,040 --> 00:07:11,857
You want to give me... a reward.

176
00:07:11,882 --> 00:07:13,499
- Anything I want?
- All you have to do is ask...

177
00:07:13,523 --> 00:07:15,508
Pearson, Specter, Litt.

178
00:07:15,533 --> 00:07:16,814
- Excuse me?
- I think I was clear.

179
00:07:16,839 --> 00:07:18,423
I want my name on the door.
It can go third.

180
00:07:18,447 --> 00:07:21,102
Louis, named partner isn't
something I can just hand out.

181
00:07:21,126 --> 00:07:22,241
But you just said
I saved the day.

182
00:07:22,265 --> 00:07:24,719
You just said you saved the day.

183
00:07:24,744 --> 00:07:26,829
I said we wanted
to show our gratitude.

184
00:07:26,854 --> 00:07:28,270
By telling me
I get to choose whatever I want,

185
00:07:28,294 --> 00:07:29,843
except for the one thing
I really want.

186
00:07:29,868 --> 00:07:31,083
Maybe I should have been
more clear.

187
00:07:31,108 --> 00:07:32,289
Maybe you should have.

188
00:07:32,313 --> 00:07:35,471
I mean, you're a goddamn lawyer,
after all.

189
00:07:35,495 --> 00:07:36,776
Louis,

190
00:07:36,801 --> 00:07:41,131
then let me be clear right now.

191
00:07:41,156 --> 00:07:43,710
I am giving you an opportunity

192
00:07:43,735 --> 00:07:47,897
to accept a well-deserved
thank-you with grace.

193
00:07:47,922 --> 00:07:49,940
You can either take it,

194
00:07:49,965 --> 00:07:52,151
or you can turn it
into a personal snub

195
00:07:52,175 --> 00:07:54,796
and ruin all the goodwill

196
00:07:54,821 --> 00:07:59,821
that you've just earned
with me and Harvey.

197
00:07:59,845 --> 00:08:01,853
The choice is yours.

198
00:08:04,568 --> 00:08:06,409
- Can I get back to you on that?
- I'm sorry. What?

199
00:08:06,433 --> 00:08:07,848
Can I get back to you on that?

200
00:08:08,909 --> 00:08:11,079
That's all I can hope for,
Louis.

201
00:08:15,665 --> 00:08:16,668
Hey.

202
00:08:16,693 --> 00:08:18,812
So I just wanted
to run through your schedule

203
00:08:18,836 --> 00:08:19,883
for the rest of the week.

204
00:08:19,908 --> 00:08:20,955
Mm, go ahead.

205
00:08:20,981 --> 00:08:23,133
You've got Ellis at 4:00 today,

206
00:08:23,157 --> 00:08:24,975
McKinney at 10:00 tomorrow,

207
00:08:25,000 --> 00:08:26,248
Chamberlain at 2:00,

208
00:08:26,273 --> 00:08:29,430
and when should I pencil you in
to go see Mike?

209
00:08:29,454 --> 00:08:31,842
- See him for what?
- To be a friend.

210
00:08:31,866 --> 00:08:33,449
Donna, as far as he's concerned,

211
00:08:33,473 --> 00:08:35,190
I sold him out
to win the takeover.

212
00:08:35,215 --> 00:08:37,134
I am the last person
he wants to see right now.

213
00:08:37,158 --> 00:08:38,439
And I would agree with all that,

214
00:08:38,464 --> 00:08:41,186
except for the fact
that Mike got fired.

215
00:08:41,210 --> 00:08:43,095
What?

216
00:08:43,120 --> 00:08:44,569
When? Last night.

217
00:08:44,593 --> 00:08:45,741
And I wasn't gonna tell you

218
00:08:45,766 --> 00:08:46,947
because you should be
hearing it from him,

219
00:08:46,971 --> 00:08:48,119
but men are idiots,

220
00:08:48,144 --> 00:08:49,761
and they would rather be
alone and miserable

221
00:08:49,785 --> 00:08:51,033
than ever run the risk
of being accused

222
00:08:51,058 --> 00:08:52,339
of needing someone.

223
00:08:52,364 --> 00:08:53,612
He has Rachel.

224
00:08:53,637 --> 00:08:54,785
Who is the one person
Mike believes

225
00:08:54,809 --> 00:08:56,459
will stand by him
no matter what,

226
00:08:56,484 --> 00:08:58,637
which makes her the one person
he won't believe

227
00:08:58,661 --> 00:09:01,215
when she says
he didn't completely fail.

228
00:09:01,240 --> 00:09:03,761
How important
is the meeting with Ellis?

229
00:09:03,785 --> 00:09:05,000
He says it's urgent.

230
00:09:05,025 --> 00:09:07,670
Tell him I have to reschedule.

231
00:09:11,935 --> 00:09:13,929
That's weird. I already did.

232
00:09:22,174 --> 00:09:23,957
Rachel or Donna?

233
00:09:23,982 --> 00:09:25,633
Who told you to check up on me?

234
00:09:25,658 --> 00:09:26,939
You don't think
I'd do that on my own?

235
00:09:26,964 --> 00:09:28,011
No, I don't.

236
00:09:28,036 --> 00:09:29,250
Well, I wouldn't have

237
00:09:29,274 --> 00:09:30,723
because I didn't think
you'd need it.

238
00:09:30,748 --> 00:09:33,906
Then I found out you got fired.

239
00:09:33,930 --> 00:09:35,078
So what?

240
00:09:35,102 --> 00:09:37,590
People lose their jobs
every single day.

241
00:09:37,615 --> 00:09:39,600
Yeah, not people like you.

242
00:09:39,625 --> 00:09:40,872
Something's going on.

243
00:09:40,897 --> 00:09:41,911
Why'd you get fired?

244
00:09:41,935 --> 00:09:43,060
You mean other than the fact

245
00:09:43,074 --> 00:09:44,624
that I picked a fight
I couldn't win?

246
00:09:44,649 --> 00:09:46,098
I don't care how it turned out.

247
00:09:46,122 --> 00:09:48,542
You went 15 rounds
on your first shot.

248
00:09:48,567 --> 00:09:51,882
No way Jonathan Sidwell
lets you go after that.

249
00:09:55,299 --> 00:09:56,782
It was Forstman, wasn't it?

250
00:09:56,807 --> 00:09:59,529
I only got his money
if I agreed to cut Sidwell

251
00:09:59,554 --> 00:10:01,572
out of the deal.

252
00:10:01,596 --> 00:10:03,145
And Sidwell found out.

253
00:10:03,170 --> 00:10:04,787
He didn't just find out.

254
00:10:04,812 --> 00:10:05,815
Forstman told him.

255
00:10:05,816 --> 00:10:07,768
That son of a bitch.

256
00:10:07,793 --> 00:10:08,974
Yeah, there's more.

257
00:10:08,998 --> 00:10:11,151
That son of a bitch
has offered me a job.

258
00:10:11,176 --> 00:10:13,663
Mike, you can't do it,
and you know it.

259
00:10:13,687 --> 00:10:15,773
What choice do I have?

260
00:10:15,798 --> 00:10:17,581
I was an investment banker
for ten minutes,

261
00:10:17,606 --> 00:10:19,793
and I blew the only deal
I'm ever gonna get near.

262
00:10:19,818 --> 00:10:22,205
Well, that sounds exactly
like the kind of bullshit.

263
00:10:22,229 --> 00:10:24,515
Forstman tells people
to wrap them around his finger.

264
00:10:24,540 --> 00:10:26,224
- Doesn't mean it's not true.
- Yes, it does.

265
00:10:26,248 --> 00:10:28,802
I could get you
five interviews before tomorrow.

266
00:10:28,827 --> 00:10:30,008
And how are you going
to do that?

267
00:10:30,032 --> 00:10:32,051
By making
five goddamn phone calls.

268
00:10:32,076 --> 00:10:34,161
And what are you gonna say
when they answer?

269
00:10:34,186 --> 00:10:35,334
You gonna tell them

270
00:10:35,359 --> 00:10:36,908
I was a Harvard-educated lawyer
working for you?

271
00:10:36,933 --> 00:10:38,047
Because you do that,

272
00:10:38,071 --> 00:10:40,659
I might as well go back
to being a fraud.

273
00:10:42,861 --> 00:10:45,583
What if I can get Jessica
to take you back?

274
00:10:48,053 --> 00:10:49,971
What if you could bring
my parents back to life?

275
00:10:49,995 --> 00:10:51,143
Because both those things

276
00:10:51,168 --> 00:10:53,086
have about the same chance
of happening.

277
00:10:53,110 --> 00:10:54,962
- Mike, I'm trying to help you.
- And I appreciate that.

278
00:10:54,986 --> 00:10:56,669
But I only have two references,
Harvey,

279
00:10:56,694 --> 00:10:58,511
you, who has to lie for me,

280
00:10:58,536 --> 00:11:00,052
and Jonathan,
who wants to kill me.

281
00:11:00,077 --> 00:11:03,469
- Mike.
- Harvey, it's enough.

282
00:11:03,494 --> 00:11:04,775
As much as you want to help me,

283
00:11:04,800 --> 00:11:06,986
you have no idea what it is

284
00:11:07,010 --> 00:11:10,904
to have been a fraud
and have to start all over.

285
00:11:10,929 --> 00:11:13,550
I don't.

286
00:11:13,575 --> 00:11:15,014
But someone else does.

287
00:11:23,764 --> 00:11:25,515
Well, well.

288
00:11:25,540 --> 00:11:29,300
If it isn't employee
number 7611053.

289
00:11:29,324 --> 00:11:30,337
You still remember that.

290
00:11:30,362 --> 00:11:31,510
I lied on my resume.

291
00:11:31,534 --> 00:11:34,491
I never lied about having a head
for numbers.

292
00:11:34,516 --> 00:11:38,511
I never said how sorry I was
for what happened to you.

293
00:11:38,535 --> 00:11:40,017
You don't need to be sorry,
Mike.

294
00:11:40,042 --> 00:11:42,295
The truth is,
I should be thanking you.

295
00:11:42,319 --> 00:11:43,467
What?

296
00:11:43,492 --> 00:11:45,344
You know what I do now?

297
00:11:45,368 --> 00:11:48,793
Statistical analysis
for fantasy baseball.

298
00:11:48,817 --> 00:11:50,535
That's awesome.

299
00:11:50,560 --> 00:11:51,841
You don't know the half of it.

300
00:11:51,866 --> 00:11:53,851
My old, better job,

301
00:11:53,875 --> 00:11:56,764
I sat in my office,
crunched my numbers,

302
00:11:56,789 --> 00:11:58,271
made a lot more money,

303
00:11:58,296 --> 00:12:00,583
barely knew the name
of one person on my floor.

304
00:12:00,608 --> 00:12:03,396
Now my best friends
are people I work with.

305
00:12:07,139 --> 00:12:10,330
Well, why'd you call me?

306
00:12:10,354 --> 00:12:11,670
The last time I saw you,

307
00:12:11,694 --> 00:12:13,110
you had no idea
what you were gonna do

308
00:12:13,135 --> 00:12:16,191
with the rest of your life.

309
00:12:16,215 --> 00:12:19,675
You had
to completely start over,

310
00:12:19,700 --> 00:12:21,249
and it looks like you did.

311
00:12:21,274 --> 00:12:23,427
I guess I... want to know how.

312
00:12:25,729 --> 00:12:27,078
Start by starting.

313
00:12:27,102 --> 00:12:28,885
What does that mean?

314
00:12:28,910 --> 00:12:29,991
It means, for six months,

315
00:12:30,015 --> 00:12:32,536
I threw myself
a giant pity party,

316
00:12:32,561 --> 00:12:33,743
wondered how the hell

317
00:12:33,767 --> 00:12:37,158
I was gonna get out
of the mess I was in.

318
00:12:37,183 --> 00:12:39,235
And then one day
I said, "enough's enough."

319
00:12:39,260 --> 00:12:41,413
And instead of asking questions,

320
00:12:41,437 --> 00:12:44,527
I started looking for answers.

321
00:12:44,552 --> 00:12:46,067
And you found fantasy baseball.

322
00:12:46,092 --> 00:12:48,245
No, I found out
that how much money you make

323
00:12:48,269 --> 00:12:51,762
is not the most important thing
in the world.

324
00:12:51,787 --> 00:12:55,369
Who you spend it with,
every day, is.

325
00:12:59,289 --> 00:13:00,705
Thanks, Stan. I appreciate it.

326
00:13:00,730 --> 00:13:02,514
Whoa, Mike.

327
00:13:02,539 --> 00:13:05,026
Why exactly is it
you need to start over?

328
00:13:06,088 --> 00:13:08,709
That's a long story.

329
00:13:08,734 --> 00:13:10,954
I have time.

330
00:13:10,979 --> 00:13:13,389
Another day, Stan.

331
00:13:15,702 --> 00:13:17,084
- You wanted to see me?
- Yes.

332
00:13:17,108 --> 00:13:18,256
Clear your schedule tonight.

333
00:13:18,281 --> 00:13:19,898
Done. Why?

334
00:13:19,922 --> 00:13:21,672
Jessica offered me
anything I want

335
00:13:21,696 --> 00:13:22,944
as a reward for my heroism,

336
00:13:22,969 --> 00:13:24,485
and we're gonna figure out
what that is.

337
00:13:24,510 --> 00:13:26,294
What's to figure out?
Named partner.

338
00:13:26,319 --> 00:13:28,605
No, not that. Anything but that.

339
00:13:28,630 --> 00:13:29,979
What do you mean,
"anything but that?"

340
00:13:30,003 --> 00:13:31,720
There isn't anything but that.

341
00:13:31,745 --> 00:13:33,071
Oh, you think
I didn't ask for it?

342
00:13:33,085 --> 00:13:34,166
The words were out of my mouth

343
00:13:34,190 --> 00:13:35,639
faster than Esther
when she was 13.

344
00:13:35,664 --> 00:13:37,113
Louis, I don't care
about your slutty sister.

345
00:13:37,137 --> 00:13:38,520
You deserve named partner.

346
00:13:38,545 --> 00:13:39,693
And I don't care
that you don't care

347
00:13:39,717 --> 00:13:41,635
because it's not gonna happen.

348
00:13:41,659 --> 00:13:44,716
Now, we were given a chance
to take the high road,

349
00:13:44,741 --> 00:13:47,764
and that's exactly
what we're gonna do.

350
00:13:47,789 --> 00:13:49,473
If I were ever going to be
attracted to you,

351
00:13:49,497 --> 00:13:51,482
now would be the time.

352
00:13:51,507 --> 00:13:53,760
Instead I'll prepare a list
of demands befitting a hero.

353
00:13:53,785 --> 00:13:55,167
Good.

354
00:13:55,191 --> 00:13:56,875
And don't ever talk about being
attracted to me again.

355
00:13:56,899 --> 00:13:58,271
It weirds me out.

356
00:14:04,938 --> 00:14:06,253
The answer's no.

357
00:14:06,277 --> 00:14:07,660
You don't even know
what I'm here for.

358
00:14:07,684 --> 00:14:09,267
I know what you're not here for.

359
00:14:09,292 --> 00:14:11,043
To tell me after a long night
of soul-searching,

360
00:14:11,067 --> 00:14:12,516
you've decided to give me
full control

361
00:14:12,541 --> 00:14:13,588
of Gillis Industries.

362
00:14:13,613 --> 00:14:14,861
You're right. I'm not.

363
00:14:14,886 --> 00:14:17,932
But I am here to give you
full control of this.

364
00:14:24,732 --> 00:14:26,248
This isn't public information.

365
00:14:26,273 --> 00:14:28,191
It will be in 24 hours.

366
00:14:28,216 --> 00:14:29,632
So it's legal to give it to you.

367
00:14:29,656 --> 00:14:31,072
And it gives me a 24-hour edge

368
00:14:31,097 --> 00:14:32,982
if I decide to act
on this information.

369
00:14:33,006 --> 00:14:34,891
Which, as you can see
from that filing,

370
00:14:34,915 --> 00:14:37,134
would be
a very profitable thing to do.

371
00:14:37,159 --> 00:14:39,446
And all I have to do in return
is use your law firm?

372
00:14:39,470 --> 00:14:41,488
I don't care
what law firm you use.

373
00:14:41,513 --> 00:14:42,560
I just want you to have
Mike Ross

374
00:14:42,585 --> 00:14:43,699
run point on the deal.

375
00:14:43,724 --> 00:14:44,905
Then we're back
where we started,

376
00:14:44,929 --> 00:14:46,278
and you can get the hell
out of my office.

377
00:14:46,302 --> 00:14:48,589
Jonathan, I know what he did,

378
00:14:48,614 --> 00:14:51,704
but he thought he had no choice.

379
00:14:51,729 --> 00:14:54,150
When a person
thinks he has no choice

380
00:14:54,174 --> 00:14:55,857
is when you see
his true character.

381
00:14:55,882 --> 00:14:57,633
You think you have no choice

382
00:14:57,658 --> 00:14:59,341
other than to be vindictive
right now.

383
00:14:59,365 --> 00:15:01,149
This isn't vindictive.
It's common sense.

384
00:15:01,174 --> 00:15:02,523
And where I come from,

385
00:15:02,547 --> 00:15:04,935
you don't give the fox
another run at the henhouse.

386
00:15:04,959 --> 00:15:06,642
You wouldn't have even had
a shot at the henhouse

387
00:15:06,667 --> 00:15:07,915
if it wasn't
for him getting you out

388
00:15:07,940 --> 00:15:09,591
from under Tony Gianopolous.

389
00:15:09,615 --> 00:15:11,666
And I repaid him for that
by giving him his first shot

390
00:15:11,691 --> 00:15:12,806
at investment banking.

391
00:15:12,830 --> 00:15:13,843
And where I come from,

392
00:15:13,868 --> 00:15:15,619
the way you really repay someone

393
00:15:15,644 --> 00:15:18,131
is by giving them
a second goddamn shot.

394
00:15:18,156 --> 00:15:21,514
Then go the hell back
to where you came from.

395
00:15:21,538 --> 00:15:25,533
And, hey,
if you think he's so great,

396
00:15:25,558 --> 00:15:26,964
take him back there with you.

397
00:15:36,745 --> 00:15:39,433
- Louis, you have a minute?
- Not really.

398
00:15:39,458 --> 00:15:41,242
I'm in the middle of some
very important gift-choosing.

399
00:15:41,266 --> 00:15:42,481
What?

400
00:15:42,506 --> 00:15:43,855
Yeah, wouldn't you like to know?

401
00:15:43,879 --> 00:15:45,093
But you never will

402
00:15:45,118 --> 00:15:46,634
because a person only gets gifts

403
00:15:46,659 --> 00:15:48,779
when they fix the mistakes
that Jeff Malone's made.

404
00:15:48,803 --> 00:15:51,424
Actually, Louis,
that's why I'm here.

405
00:15:51,449 --> 00:15:53,601
I wanted to thank you
for catching that error

406
00:15:53,625 --> 00:15:55,610
on the Wexler stock.

407
00:15:55,635 --> 00:15:56,750
You want to thank me?

408
00:15:56,774 --> 00:15:58,659
Yes, Louis, I do.

409
00:15:58,684 --> 00:16:00,468
Look, I know you don't trust me,

410
00:16:00,493 --> 00:16:02,779
but you got us out of a jam,

411
00:16:02,803 --> 00:16:05,089
and I'm here to thank you,
man-to-man.

412
00:16:05,114 --> 00:16:06,497
Bullshit.

413
00:16:06,522 --> 00:16:08,205
You're here to kiss my ass
because you found out

414
00:16:08,229 --> 00:16:09,779
that I'm now above you
in the pecking order.

415
00:16:09,804 --> 00:16:11,253
Louis, I don't care
about the pecking order,

416
00:16:11,278 --> 00:16:14,100
and all I found out is that
you fixed this thing for Harvey,

417
00:16:14,124 --> 00:16:16,343
and I am here to thank you.

418
00:16:16,368 --> 00:16:17,818
I'm not talking about Harvey,
and you know it.

419
00:16:17,843 --> 00:16:19,794
- No, Louis.
- Don't play dumb with me.

420
00:16:19,818 --> 00:16:21,535
I'm talking
about Jessica Pearson,

421
00:16:21,560 --> 00:16:23,445
the woman whose ass
you've really been kissing,

422
00:16:23,469 --> 00:16:25,354
the very same woman
who came to me

423
00:16:25,378 --> 00:16:27,932
and asked me to check your work.

424
00:16:27,957 --> 00:16:31,517
Yeah, uh-huh.

425
00:16:31,542 --> 00:16:32,689
Now, if you'll excuse me,

426
00:16:32,713 --> 00:16:35,257
I have some Llipizzaner stallions
to look at.

427
00:16:45,442 --> 00:16:47,460
You had Louis Litt
check my work?

428
00:16:47,484 --> 00:16:49,469
I was wondering
when we might get into this.

429
00:16:49,494 --> 00:16:51,346
Well, the wondering is over
because it's now.

430
00:16:51,370 --> 00:16:53,388
And if you were going to do
something like that,

431
00:16:53,413 --> 00:16:54,929
you should have discussed it
with me first

432
00:16:54,954 --> 00:16:56,403
before going behind my back.

433
00:16:56,427 --> 00:16:57,809
I did discuss it with you,

434
00:16:57,834 --> 00:17:00,187
and you stood right there
and said your work was perfect

435
00:17:00,212 --> 00:17:01,460
and I should trust you.

436
00:17:01,485 --> 00:17:02,767
You see,
that's the problem right there.

437
00:17:02,792 --> 00:17:04,442
You don't trust me.

438
00:17:04,466 --> 00:17:07,456
And now you're just rubbing
my mistake in my face.

439
00:17:07,480 --> 00:17:09,432
If the goal
was to rub it in your face,

440
00:17:09,457 --> 00:17:10,738
I would have done that already,

441
00:17:10,763 --> 00:17:12,547
and we wouldn't be having
this conversation.

442
00:17:12,572 --> 00:17:14,557
In that case, maybe
we should keep our conversations

443
00:17:14,581 --> 00:17:16,264
on a professional level
for a while.

444
00:17:16,289 --> 00:17:18,274
You're the one
who wanted to do both.

445
00:17:18,299 --> 00:17:20,486
And maybe I was wrong.

446
00:17:20,510 --> 00:17:23,768
I never said I didn't trust you.

447
00:17:23,792 --> 00:17:26,246
I said I didn't trust
your work on Wexler.

448
00:17:26,271 --> 00:17:29,562
That's the difference
between us, Jessica.

449
00:17:29,587 --> 00:17:31,907
You see, when I say, "trust me,"

450
00:17:31,931 --> 00:17:34,451
I mean trust the man
who works for you

451
00:17:34,476 --> 00:17:36,217
and the man that's with you.

452
00:17:46,869 --> 00:17:48,821
You wanted to see me?

453
00:17:48,846 --> 00:17:50,060
You don't seem in a good mood.

454
00:17:50,084 --> 00:17:51,801
I'm not.

455
00:17:51,826 --> 00:17:52,911
We can talk about it later.

456
00:17:52,932 --> 00:17:54,347
I walked all the way down here.

457
00:17:54,372 --> 00:17:55,956
We can talk about it now.

458
00:17:55,980 --> 00:17:58,769
I was just gonna ask
how Louis' talk went.

459
00:17:58,794 --> 00:18:00,243
Bullshit.

460
00:18:00,267 --> 00:18:02,516
That is not an "I have to come
talk to you" conversation.

461
00:18:09,813 --> 00:18:11,497
I want to bring Mike back.

462
00:18:13,230 --> 00:18:15,181
That is not a conversation
I ever want to have.

463
00:18:15,205 --> 00:18:16,219
Jessica...

464
00:18:16,244 --> 00:18:18,195
Harvey, I haven't slept better

465
00:18:18,220 --> 00:18:19,703
since his last night,

466
00:18:19,727 --> 00:18:21,678
except for every night since,

467
00:18:21,703 --> 00:18:23,086
and I'm not going back.

468
00:18:23,110 --> 00:18:25,162
In case
you really were wondering,

469
00:18:25,187 --> 00:18:28,143
Louis took his thank-you
like a dick.

470
00:18:28,167 --> 00:18:30,510
And if that's all,
I'm going home.

471
00:18:43,943 --> 00:18:45,057
Hey.

472
00:18:45,082 --> 00:18:47,235
Hey.

473
00:18:47,259 --> 00:18:49,412
Are you cooking? Mmm.

474
00:18:49,436 --> 00:18:50,517
I make one thing,

475
00:18:50,541 --> 00:18:53,162
and I make it awesome.

476
00:18:53,188 --> 00:18:56,670
Mike, every single guy
thinks that his spaghetti sau...

477
00:19:00,557 --> 00:19:02,944
Oh, my God. That's amazing.

478
00:19:02,968 --> 00:19:06,718
Not every single guy
was raised by his grandmother.

479
00:19:07,858 --> 00:19:09,776
Now you sit down, shut up,

480
00:19:09,801 --> 00:19:12,758
and tell me about your day.

481
00:19:12,782 --> 00:19:15,135
What got you
in such a good mood?

482
00:19:15,160 --> 00:19:16,173
Oh, you know, nothing.

483
00:19:16,198 --> 00:19:17,479
Just spent the afternoon

484
00:19:17,504 --> 00:19:19,356
figuring out what I'm gonna do
with my life.

485
00:19:19,380 --> 00:19:21,231
Well, that sounds
like quite the afternoon.

486
00:19:21,255 --> 00:19:23,833
What did you figure out?

487
00:19:26,179 --> 00:19:27,863
Well, I figured out I don't want

488
00:19:27,888 --> 00:19:29,472
to take the job with Forstman,

489
00:19:29,496 --> 00:19:33,825
and I don't want to be
an investment banker.

490
00:19:33,849 --> 00:19:36,437
So what do you want to be?

491
00:19:36,462 --> 00:19:37,533
I don't know.

492
00:19:40,046 --> 00:19:42,667
But I know
I want to be with you.

493
00:19:42,692 --> 00:19:46,519
- What are you saying?
- I want to start over.

494
00:19:46,544 --> 00:19:47,725
I don't understand.

495
00:19:47,749 --> 00:19:48,831
Rachel, when I met you,

496
00:19:48,855 --> 00:19:50,102
I had nothing in my life

497
00:19:50,127 --> 00:19:53,486
except what came
from being a fraud.

498
00:19:53,511 --> 00:19:56,098
And now I have nothing in it
except being with you,

499
00:19:56,123 --> 00:19:58,108
and I wouldn't go back
even if I could because...

500
00:19:58,133 --> 00:19:59,281
Mike...

501
00:19:59,305 --> 00:20:02,530
I don't care
what I do for a living.

502
00:20:02,554 --> 00:20:03,869
I mean, I'll figure it out,

503
00:20:03,894 --> 00:20:06,583
but as long as I have you,

504
00:20:06,607 --> 00:20:10,033
I have everything.

505
00:20:10,057 --> 00:20:12,879
Rachel?

506
00:20:12,904 --> 00:20:14,688
What...
I didn't mean to make you cry.

507
00:20:14,713 --> 00:20:16,496
I meant to make you feel better.

508
00:20:16,521 --> 00:20:18,506
Hey, hey,
everything's going to be okay.

509
00:20:18,530 --> 00:20:21,219
- No, it's not.
- Rachel, what's wrong?

510
00:20:21,244 --> 00:20:22,560
I'm sorry. I just need a minute.

511
00:20:22,584 --> 00:20:24,201
- Rachel.
- I just need a minute.

512
00:20:24,225 --> 00:20:26,042
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
I'm right here. You can tell me.

513
00:20:26,067 --> 00:20:27,884
What's going on? I can't.

514
00:20:27,909 --> 00:20:29,559
Rachel, stop. Yes you can.

515
00:20:29,583 --> 00:20:31,133
Hey, hey. No, you don't-

516
00:20:31,158 --> 00:20:33,344
I don't deserve you.
- What are you talking about?

517
00:20:33,369 --> 00:20:35,142
Rachel, hey...
Logan and I kissed.

518
00:20:36,885 --> 00:20:39,138
What?

519
00:20:39,163 --> 00:20:41,248
We were just talking,

520
00:20:41,273 --> 00:20:42,823
and then he...

521
00:20:42,848 --> 00:20:44,197
He what?

522
00:20:44,221 --> 00:20:45,804
Mike, please.

523
00:20:45,828 --> 00:20:47,412
I am so sorry.

524
00:20:47,436 --> 00:20:49,019
Mike, no, please.

525
00:20:51,723 --> 00:20:54,411
Please, it didn't mean anything.

526
00:20:54,436 --> 00:20:55,651
Wait.

527
00:20:57,518 --> 00:20:59,393
I'm...

528
00:21:15,172 --> 00:21:16,320
This is how you handle losing?

529
00:21:16,344 --> 00:21:18,095
I'm not here
about Gillis Industries.

530
00:21:18,120 --> 00:21:19,166
Ooh, you gonna fight me?

531
00:21:19,191 --> 00:21:21,812
You stay the hell away
from Rachel.

532
00:21:21,837 --> 00:21:24,225
Well, that's up to her.

533
00:21:24,249 --> 00:21:25,430
But if she does come back here,

534
00:21:25,455 --> 00:21:27,195
it won't be to tell me
to stay away.

535
00:21:37,881 --> 00:21:39,631
Ah!

536
00:21:54,294 --> 00:21:56,312
I don't know what she told you.

537
00:21:58,782 --> 00:22:00,723
But she let it go on
a long time.

538
00:22:05,547 --> 00:22:06,828
And she didn't just like it.

539
00:22:06,853 --> 00:22:09,196
She loved it.

540
00:22:14,992 --> 00:22:17,446
You told him.

541
00:22:17,471 --> 00:22:19,658
I don't even know where he is.

542
00:22:19,682 --> 00:22:21,901
He's at Harvey's.

543
00:22:21,926 --> 00:22:23,677
How do you know?

544
00:22:23,701 --> 00:22:25,273
Where did you go?

545
00:22:32,375 --> 00:22:34,093
Forstman?

546
00:22:34,118 --> 00:22:35,399
Logan.

547
00:22:35,424 --> 00:22:37,945
Gillis.

548
00:22:37,970 --> 00:22:39,720
Rachel.

549
00:22:39,744 --> 00:22:42,399
Get the hell in here.

550
00:22:42,424 --> 00:22:45,850
I never should have told him.

551
00:22:45,874 --> 00:22:48,619
Rachel,
there's no use thinking that.

552
00:22:51,300 --> 00:22:52,849
What if he doesn't forgive me?

553
00:22:52,874 --> 00:22:54,088
You don't know that he won't.

554
00:22:54,113 --> 00:22:56,199
You don't know that he will.

555
00:22:56,224 --> 00:22:57,305
And you're the one that said,

556
00:22:57,329 --> 00:22:59,380
"this will bore a hole
in his head."

557
00:22:59,405 --> 00:23:01,089
And you're the one who said
you had to find a way

558
00:23:01,114 --> 00:23:03,602
to trust him with the truth.

559
00:23:03,626 --> 00:23:04,807
He walked out. I can't just...

560
00:23:04,832 --> 00:23:05,913
Stay here tonight?

561
00:23:05,937 --> 00:23:07,509
Of course you can.

562
00:23:10,073 --> 00:23:11,388
I'm not going back there.

563
00:23:11,412 --> 00:23:12,694
I'm not saying you have to.

564
00:23:12,719 --> 00:23:14,838
I'm saying
you need to calm down.

565
00:23:14,862 --> 00:23:16,411
Would you calm down
after someone

566
00:23:16,436 --> 00:23:17,819
stuck it in your face like that?

567
00:23:17,843 --> 00:23:20,866
I would if I knew he was just
trying to get in my head.

568
00:23:20,891 --> 00:23:22,843
How the hell do you know
that's all it is?

569
00:23:22,867 --> 00:23:25,354
Because that piece of shit
did it to you before,

570
00:23:25,379 --> 00:23:26,895
and I let him
because I'm his lawyer,

571
00:23:26,920 --> 00:23:28,369
but I'm not gonna let him
do it to you now.

572
00:23:28,393 --> 00:23:29,809
Yeah, well, he got in my head.

573
00:23:29,834 --> 00:23:31,719
He put the image in there,
and now I can't get it out.

574
00:23:31,743 --> 00:23:32,891
Mike...

575
00:23:32,916 --> 00:23:34,130
Look, I need to know
if it's true.

576
00:23:34,154 --> 00:23:36,096
And what good
is gonna come of that?

577
00:23:38,910 --> 00:23:42,168
I just need to know.

578
00:23:42,193 --> 00:23:44,346
Then there's only one way
to find out.

579
00:23:44,370 --> 00:23:46,211
But you're not gonna find out
tonight.

580
00:23:47,452 --> 00:23:48,488
Here.

581
00:24:05,940 --> 00:24:07,657
Mike.

582
00:24:07,682 --> 00:24:09,456
Oh, my God, I was so worr...

583
00:24:12,740 --> 00:24:15,261
Oh, my God, your face.
What happened?

584
00:24:15,286 --> 00:24:18,276
You know what happened.

585
00:24:18,300 --> 00:24:20,687
You went to see Logan.

586
00:24:20,712 --> 00:24:22,128
I want you to tell me
exactly what happened

587
00:24:22,152 --> 00:24:25,744
between you and him.

588
00:24:25,769 --> 00:24:27,654
Okay, why don't we just
go home right now,

589
00:24:27,678 --> 00:24:29,163
and we can talk
about all of it there?

590
00:24:29,186 --> 00:24:31,372
You're gonna tell me
what happened right here.

591
00:24:31,396 --> 00:24:33,113
Mike, I...

592
00:24:33,138 --> 00:24:34,319
I need to know
that I can trust you,

593
00:24:34,343 --> 00:24:35,624
because you said

594
00:24:35,649 --> 00:24:37,032
that it didn't mean anything,
but he said...

595
00:24:37,057 --> 00:24:40,549
- Mike, please.
- Did it mean something or not?

596
00:24:40,573 --> 00:24:42,893
It meant something
when it happened, but now...

597
00:24:42,918 --> 00:24:44,702
Okay, look. Okay.

598
00:24:44,727 --> 00:24:46,209
I made a huge mistake,

599
00:24:46,234 --> 00:24:47,516
but you just asked
if you could trust me...

600
00:24:47,541 --> 00:24:49,258
Trust you?

601
00:24:49,282 --> 00:24:50,932
You didn't tell me about this
for a week,

602
00:24:50,957 --> 00:24:52,523
and then when you finally did,
you lied.

603
00:24:52,531 --> 00:24:53,947
I didn't lie.

604
00:24:53,971 --> 00:24:55,487
You walked out before I could
tell you the whole story.

605
00:24:55,512 --> 00:24:56,994
The whole story?

606
00:24:57,019 --> 00:24:58,603
There's no way you were going
to tell me that whole story.

607
00:24:58,627 --> 00:25:01,673
- Mike, please.
- He said that you loved it!

608
00:25:08,775 --> 00:25:09,990
And when I said
that it didn't matter

609
00:25:10,015 --> 00:25:12,760
what I'd do next
because I have you?

610
00:25:14,671 --> 00:25:16,589
I was wrong

611
00:25:16,613 --> 00:25:17,917
because we're done.

612
00:25:29,697 --> 00:25:31,486
Ohhhh, it is busy.

613
00:25:31,730 --> 00:25:34,787
Okay, listen, Rachel.
When you are done can you just...

614
00:25:34,811 --> 00:25:36,059
Holy shit, are you?

615
00:25:36,084 --> 00:25:38,102
No, I'm not.

616
00:25:38,127 --> 00:25:40,347
So help me, if Harvey
mistreated you, I will...

617
00:25:40,372 --> 00:25:41,385
It wasn't Harvey, Louis.

618
00:25:41,410 --> 00:25:42,759
It's Mike.

619
00:25:42,783 --> 00:25:44,165
That son of a bitch.
Where is he?

620
00:25:44,189 --> 00:25:46,666
Because I'll...
It wasn't him. It was me.

621
00:25:49,348 --> 00:25:50,529
Rachel.

622
00:25:50,553 --> 00:25:53,778
Look, I know
that he hurt you with Sheila,

623
00:25:53,803 --> 00:25:56,122
but I love him,

624
00:25:56,147 --> 00:25:57,463
and I lost him.

625
00:25:57,487 --> 00:25:58,701
And I don't really know
what to do.

626
00:25:58,725 --> 00:26:01,346
Oh, come on, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,

627
00:26:01,371 --> 00:26:04,328
listen to me right now, okay?

628
00:26:04,353 --> 00:26:06,170
Whatever I may think of Mike,

629
00:26:06,195 --> 00:26:09,285
I have no doubt
that he loves you.

630
00:26:09,310 --> 00:26:12,535
And when two people
love each other,

631
00:26:12,559 --> 00:26:16,386
no problem is insurmountable.

632
00:26:16,411 --> 00:26:18,899
That's bullshit.

633
00:26:18,923 --> 00:26:21,645
And you of all people know it.

634
00:26:21,670 --> 00:26:22,918
What?

635
00:26:22,943 --> 00:26:24,560
You and Sheila loved each other,

636
00:26:24,584 --> 00:26:26,635
and you still broke up,

637
00:26:26,660 --> 00:26:30,755
even though neither of you
had done anything wrong.

638
00:26:30,779 --> 00:26:32,262
That's different.

639
00:26:32,287 --> 00:26:34,808
Did you hear me?

640
00:26:34,833 --> 00:26:37,052
I did something wrong.

641
00:26:37,076 --> 00:26:38,893
And now he doesn't trust me,

642
00:26:38,918 --> 00:26:43,181
and I can't make him
trust me or forgive me.

643
00:26:43,206 --> 00:26:46,632
So it doesn't matter
how much I love him, okay?

644
00:26:46,656 --> 00:26:48,105
Becau...

645
00:26:48,129 --> 00:26:49,679
Okay, all right, listen.

646
00:26:49,704 --> 00:26:52,392
Rachel, you have so much
going for you.

647
00:26:52,417 --> 00:26:56,010
It's gonna be okay.

648
00:26:56,034 --> 00:26:57,651
And what good is any of it

649
00:26:57,676 --> 00:27:00,589
if I don't have the one person
I want to share it with?

650
00:27:13,920 --> 00:27:15,335
Logan, what are you doing here?

651
00:27:15,360 --> 00:27:19,623
You told Mike after you
explicitly told me not to.

652
00:27:19,647 --> 00:27:23,173
I don't have
to explain myself to you.

653
00:27:23,198 --> 00:27:25,686
- Really?
- I didn't mean for it...

654
00:27:25,710 --> 00:27:27,661
It doesn't matter what you did
or didn't mean to happen.

655
00:27:27,686 --> 00:27:28,801
It happened,

656
00:27:28,825 --> 00:27:29,939
and I know why it did.

657
00:27:29,963 --> 00:27:31,379
What are you talk...

658
00:27:31,404 --> 00:27:35,331
You told him
because deep down inside,

659
00:27:35,356 --> 00:27:36,471
you want to be with me,

660
00:27:36,495 --> 00:27:37,844
and you knew this
would make it happen.

661
00:27:37,869 --> 00:27:39,050
That is bullshit.

662
00:27:39,074 --> 00:27:40,188
Really?

663
00:27:40,212 --> 00:27:42,633
Because that is exactly
what you said to me

664
00:27:42,658 --> 00:27:44,342
when I told Allison about us.

665
00:27:44,366 --> 00:27:45,748
That has nothing
to do with this.

666
00:27:45,773 --> 00:27:46,787
Rachel.

667
00:27:46,812 --> 00:27:47,926
And since
you obviously came here

668
00:27:47,950 --> 00:27:49,567
to find out where it is
we stand,

669
00:27:49,591 --> 00:27:51,609
let me tell you.

670
00:27:51,634 --> 00:27:53,150
There is no us.

671
00:27:53,175 --> 00:27:55,362
There will never be an us.

672
00:27:55,386 --> 00:27:58,777
And no matter what happens
between me and Mike,

673
00:27:58,802 --> 00:28:00,218
this is the last time

674
00:28:00,243 --> 00:28:02,663
that you and I are ever gonna
have a conversation again.

675
00:28:02,687 --> 00:28:05,410
- You're my lawyer.
- Not anymore, Logan.

676
00:28:05,434 --> 00:28:07,151
So whatever real or fake meeting
you have with Harvey,

677
00:28:07,176 --> 00:28:08,457
you can go to it now,

678
00:28:08,482 --> 00:28:10,567
but I won't be in it

679
00:28:10,592 --> 00:28:12,409
or any other meeting
you have here in the future

680
00:28:12,434 --> 00:28:14,309
because we're done.

681
00:28:22,415 --> 00:28:24,467
Louis, glad you're here.

682
00:28:24,492 --> 00:28:26,377
I just got off the phone
with Charles Forstman.

683
00:28:26,401 --> 00:28:28,554
He wants to cross the "T"s,
dot the "I"s,

684
00:28:28,578 --> 00:28:30,362
and be done with this deal,
and so do I.

685
00:28:30,387 --> 00:28:31,635
Oh, believe me, Jessica.

686
00:28:31,660 --> 00:28:33,511
Nobody wants to be done
with that man more than me.

687
00:28:33,535 --> 00:28:35,755
I'm actually heading over there
in an hour,

688
00:28:35,780 --> 00:28:37,129
but before I do,
I just wanted to tell you

689
00:28:37,153 --> 00:28:41,382
that I finally figured out
what I want as my reward.

690
00:28:41,406 --> 00:28:44,698
And what is that?

691
00:28:44,723 --> 00:28:46,105
I want to amend my contract

692
00:28:46,129 --> 00:28:48,951
to allow for telecommuting
whenever I deem appropriate

693
00:28:48,976 --> 00:28:50,961
and a month's more vacation
every year

694
00:28:50,986 --> 00:28:52,570
to be used at my discretion.

695
00:28:52,594 --> 00:28:54,411
Anything else?

696
00:28:54,436 --> 00:28:55,584
I want it in writing,

697
00:28:55,608 --> 00:28:56,822
and I want my partnership
protected

698
00:28:56,847 --> 00:29:00,507
for as long
as this situation persists.

699
00:29:00,532 --> 00:29:01,780
Okay.

700
00:29:01,805 --> 00:29:03,086
Before I give you
what you're asking...

701
00:29:03,111 --> 00:29:04,761
Jessica, you said I could have
whatever I want.

702
00:29:04,785 --> 00:29:06,000
You're not gonna
talk me out of this.

703
00:29:06,025 --> 00:29:07,711
I'm not trying
to talk you out of anything.

704
00:29:07,733 --> 00:29:09,516
I just want to say that the fact

705
00:29:09,541 --> 00:29:12,029
that named partner
isn't happening now

706
00:29:12,054 --> 00:29:14,072
doesn't mean it never will,

707
00:29:14,097 --> 00:29:15,379
and I'd hate to see you

708
00:29:15,404 --> 00:29:18,695
throw in the towel
because you've lost faith.

709
00:29:18,719 --> 00:29:20,302
Yeah, well, the only thing
I'm throwing

710
00:29:20,326 --> 00:29:23,518
is my hat in the ring
for Sheila's heart.

711
00:29:23,543 --> 00:29:25,293
I don't understand.

712
00:29:25,317 --> 00:29:28,340
I love her.

713
00:29:28,365 --> 00:29:31,623
And I miss her.

714
00:29:31,647 --> 00:29:34,536
And I want to try
to win her back,

715
00:29:34,561 --> 00:29:38,177
and I need these things
to make that happen.

716
00:29:40,893 --> 00:29:43,370
Then you have them.

717
00:29:49,869 --> 00:29:51,854
- Rachel, are you okay?
- I don't know.

718
00:29:51,878 --> 00:29:53,227
- Where are you going?
- I don't know.

719
00:29:53,252 --> 00:29:54,801
I just can't be here,
and I can't be at home.

720
00:29:54,826 --> 00:29:56,979
I can't be anywhere.

721
00:29:57,003 --> 00:29:58,720
Go see him.

722
00:29:58,744 --> 00:30:00,886
I don't even know where he is.

723
00:30:02,897 --> 00:30:04,045
Yes, you do.

724
00:30:04,070 --> 00:30:05,251
I did see him.

725
00:30:05,275 --> 00:30:07,931
He came here,
and everything went to shit.

726
00:30:07,955 --> 00:30:11,547
And I tried to explain,
and he wouldn't listen.

727
00:30:11,572 --> 00:30:13,624
And then he said
we're just done.

728
00:30:13,649 --> 00:30:15,925
- Rachel.
- I'm sorry, Donna.

729
00:30:27,516 --> 00:30:28,898
If it's about Mike, I'm busy.

730
00:30:28,922 --> 00:30:31,042
Harvey, I know about
your issues with infidelity,

731
00:30:31,066 --> 00:30:32,079
but...

732
00:30:32,104 --> 00:30:33,587
Donna, stop right there.

733
00:30:33,612 --> 00:30:35,229
No, I'm not gonna stop

734
00:30:35,253 --> 00:30:37,372
because you need to go talk
to Mike about Rachel.

735
00:30:37,396 --> 00:30:41,090
- Need.
- Yes, need.

736
00:30:41,115 --> 00:30:43,368
Listen to me because I'm only
gonna say this once.

737
00:30:43,392 --> 00:30:45,377
What she did
is between the two of them,

738
00:30:45,402 --> 00:30:47,019
and I'm not gonna get
in the middle of it

739
00:30:47,043 --> 00:30:49,530
one way or another,
but if I did,

740
00:30:49,555 --> 00:30:53,482
it sure as shit
wouldn't be to defend her.

741
00:30:53,507 --> 00:30:55,225
Harvey, your lack
of emotional awareness

742
00:30:55,249 --> 00:30:56,363
never ceases to amaze me.

743
00:30:56,388 --> 00:30:57,837
What the hell
are you talking about?

744
00:30:57,861 --> 00:30:59,813
I'm not asking you
to do this for Rachel.

745
00:30:59,838 --> 00:31:01,756
I'm asking you
to do this for Mike.

746
00:31:01,780 --> 00:31:03,655
Like I said, I'm busy.

747
00:31:11,125 --> 00:31:12,742
May I?

748
00:31:12,766 --> 00:31:14,718
Since when do you
need permission?

749
00:31:14,743 --> 00:31:16,393
To come in, I don't.

750
00:31:16,417 --> 00:31:18,269
No, you don't.

751
00:31:18,293 --> 00:31:21,617
And I'll come back when you're
in a more receptive mood.

752
00:31:23,618 --> 00:31:25,761
What exactly
am I being receptive to?

753
00:31:30,887 --> 00:31:37,226
You are not just any partner
in this firm.

754
00:31:37,250 --> 00:31:38,616
You are the man
I am involved with,

755
00:31:38,623 --> 00:31:43,589
and I need to take that
into consideration from now on.

756
00:31:43,614 --> 00:31:46,303
You sound like you're
saying that as damage control.

757
00:31:46,328 --> 00:31:48,447
I'm saying it because I mean it.

758
00:31:48,471 --> 00:31:50,088
Then why does it still sound
like you're talking

759
00:31:50,112 --> 00:31:52,733
to your employee?

760
00:31:52,758 --> 00:31:55,781
Because it's hard for me

761
00:31:55,806 --> 00:31:57,557
to say
that I don't want to lose you

762
00:31:57,582 --> 00:32:00,126
over some stupid work bullshit.

763
00:32:03,443 --> 00:32:06,222
Now, that's
what I'm talkin' about.

764
00:32:09,103 --> 00:32:10,820
So you just wanted to make it
hard for me.

765
00:32:10,845 --> 00:32:13,333
I just wanted
to hear you say it.

766
00:32:13,358 --> 00:32:16,069
It being hard for you is on you.

767
00:32:17,611 --> 00:32:19,596
So we're good.

768
00:32:19,620 --> 00:32:22,945
Oh, yeah. We're good.

769
00:32:22,970 --> 00:32:25,524
All right.

770
00:32:25,549 --> 00:32:27,266
Jessica, one more thing.

771
00:32:27,291 --> 00:32:31,789
If you don't want to lose me
over some stupid work bullshit,

772
00:32:31,813 --> 00:32:34,491
then please don't do
stupid work bullshit.

773
00:32:39,013 --> 00:32:40,720
You're fired.

774
00:32:47,086 --> 00:32:48,167
"Simple term condition,"

775
00:32:48,191 --> 00:32:50,745
blah-blah, blah-blah.

776
00:32:52,445 --> 00:32:53,526
Yeah, it's all there.

777
00:32:53,550 --> 00:32:55,468
You just need to sign
by the arrows.

778
00:32:55,493 --> 00:32:57,980
Mm-hmm.

779
00:32:58,004 --> 00:33:01,094
Walk me through this one
more time.

780
00:33:01,119 --> 00:33:02,334
It says Sanders international

781
00:33:02,359 --> 00:33:05,382
agrees to pay you
the aforementioned amount.

782
00:33:05,407 --> 00:33:07,058
Through a Swiss account
or the Caymans?

783
00:33:07,082 --> 00:33:08,431
Both, per your instructions.

784
00:33:08,455 --> 00:33:10,507
Now are we done?

785
00:33:10,532 --> 00:33:14,761
You went to a lot of trouble
to shelter some money for me.

786
00:33:14,785 --> 00:33:16,703
Because you forced me to.

787
00:33:16,728 --> 00:33:19,484
Which got me to wondering.

788
00:33:19,508 --> 00:33:21,325
What's to keep you from walking
out of here,

789
00:33:21,350 --> 00:33:23,167
growing a conscience,

790
00:33:23,192 --> 00:33:25,646
and telling someone
about our little arrangement?

791
00:33:25,671 --> 00:33:27,455
Because if I do, I'll be
admitting to my own guilt,

792
00:33:27,480 --> 00:33:28,761
which you damn well know.

793
00:33:28,785 --> 00:33:32,970
Right, but what exactly
are you guilty of?

794
00:33:34,614 --> 00:33:35,930
What is this?

795
00:33:35,954 --> 00:33:40,149
That's your fee
for putting this deal together.

796
00:33:40,174 --> 00:33:41,455
I don't want a fee.

797
00:33:41,480 --> 00:33:44,101
That's exactly
why you're gonna take it.

798
00:33:44,126 --> 00:33:45,509
Son of a bitch.

799
00:33:45,533 --> 00:33:47,116
You didn't bring me here
for you to sign on the arrows.

800
00:33:47,140 --> 00:33:48,556
You brought me here for me
to sign on the arrows.

801
00:33:48,581 --> 00:33:50,433
Yep.

802
00:33:50,457 --> 00:33:52,040
And I don't give a shit
what you do with the money

803
00:33:52,064 --> 00:33:53,279
after it goes into your account,

804
00:33:53,304 --> 00:33:54,921
but it's going in there.

805
00:33:54,945 --> 00:33:56,059
I won't.

806
00:33:56,083 --> 00:33:57,499
It's up to you.

807
00:33:57,524 --> 00:33:59,978
Now you can either close
this deal

808
00:34:00,002 --> 00:34:01,418
or go back
to writing in your diary

809
00:34:01,443 --> 00:34:04,399
about what a loser
Harvey Specter thinks you are.

810
00:34:07,740 --> 00:34:09,222
Sign it, pal.

811
00:34:09,246 --> 00:34:17,276
♪ ♪

812
00:34:54,397 --> 00:34:56,348
Mike, what are you doing here?

813
00:34:56,373 --> 00:34:58,559
What are you doing here?

814
00:34:58,583 --> 00:35:02,176
You know what? Doesn't matter.

815
00:35:02,201 --> 00:35:03,482
I'm here to take a job.

816
00:35:03,507 --> 00:35:05,191
Wait. What?

817
00:35:05,215 --> 00:35:07,602
No, you can't do that.

818
00:35:07,626 --> 00:35:10,716
- What do you care?
- Mike, listen to me.

819
00:35:10,741 --> 00:35:13,698
I know I'm mad at you
about Sheila,

820
00:35:13,723 --> 00:35:14,904
but I don't care
about that right now.

821
00:35:14,928 --> 00:35:17,215
You cannot take a job
with that man.

822
00:35:17,240 --> 00:35:19,392
I don't have
any other options, Louis.

823
00:35:19,416 --> 00:35:20,463
And I'm in this position

824
00:35:20,488 --> 00:35:21,971
because you paid that man
greenmail

825
00:35:21,996 --> 00:35:23,779
to walk away from my deal
in the first place.

826
00:35:23,804 --> 00:35:25,019
Believe me, I wish I hadn't.

827
00:35:25,044 --> 00:35:26,962
What the hell
is that supposed to mean?

828
00:35:26,986 --> 00:35:28,871
- Mike...
- You know what?

829
00:35:28,895 --> 00:35:31,349
Doesn't matter.
None of it matters.

830
00:35:31,374 --> 00:35:34,364
This is about Rachel, isn't it?

831
00:35:34,388 --> 00:35:37,110
She told me she hurt you.

832
00:35:37,135 --> 00:35:38,919
Believe me, I understand,

833
00:35:38,944 --> 00:35:41,297
but you cannot do this
because of that.

834
00:35:41,322 --> 00:35:42,604
This is a job, Louis, all right?

835
00:35:42,629 --> 00:35:44,111
I'm not robbing a bank.
It's not a job!

836
00:35:44,135 --> 00:35:45,651
It's a decision,

837
00:35:45,676 --> 00:35:46,957
and I'm not gonna let you
make it.

838
00:35:46,982 --> 00:35:47,996
Yeah?

839
00:35:48,021 --> 00:35:50,909
What are you gonna do about it?

840
00:35:50,934 --> 00:35:52,942
Anything I have to.

841
00:35:59,010 --> 00:36:00,013
You wanted to see me?

842
00:36:00,025 --> 00:36:01,910
I thought you wanted to see me.

843
00:36:01,934 --> 00:36:03,952
I wanted to see you both.

844
00:36:03,977 --> 00:36:05,326
Louis.

845
00:36:05,350 --> 00:36:07,302
Is this about implementing
your request with Sheila?

846
00:36:07,327 --> 00:36:09,412
It's about retracting
my request with Sheila.

847
00:36:09,437 --> 00:36:10,618
What happened? I thought...

848
00:36:10,642 --> 00:36:12,091
Nothing happened.

849
00:36:12,116 --> 00:36:13,900
I hired Mike Ross
back at the firm.

850
00:36:13,925 --> 00:36:15,575
What?

851
00:36:15,599 --> 00:36:16,814
If Sheila and I are meant to be,

852
00:36:16,839 --> 00:36:17,852
we'll make that work,

853
00:36:17,877 --> 00:36:20,365
but Mike was gonna do something

854
00:36:20,389 --> 00:36:22,909
that I could not let him do.

855
00:36:22,934 --> 00:36:25,891
So I'm using my reward on him.

856
00:36:25,915 --> 00:36:27,867
- Okay, Lewis, I...
- It's a great choice.

857
00:36:27,892 --> 00:36:29,642
I'm proud of you.

858
00:36:29,667 --> 00:36:31,451
Why don't you give me a minute
with Jessica

859
00:36:31,475 --> 00:36:33,560
and see if we can't get him
an office?

860
00:36:33,586 --> 00:36:37,548
Thank you, Harvey.
Thank you both.

861
00:36:37,572 --> 00:36:38,987
Is that it?

862
00:36:39,011 --> 00:36:40,662
I'd still like to be able
to take Rosh Hashanah off

863
00:36:40,687 --> 00:36:43,174
if that's okay.

864
00:36:43,198 --> 00:36:45,675
I think we can work
something out.

865
00:36:48,557 --> 00:36:49,906
- No way.
- Jessica.

866
00:36:49,931 --> 00:36:51,949
Mike Ross is not coming back
to this firm.

867
00:36:51,973 --> 00:36:53,557
You heard Louis.
He already gave him the job.

868
00:36:53,582 --> 00:36:55,064
He can un-give him the job.

869
00:36:55,088 --> 00:36:56,654
It's too late for that,
and you know it.

870
00:36:56,663 --> 00:36:58,916
Well, it damn sure didn't help
when you jumped on in there

871
00:36:58,941 --> 00:37:00,122
and told him
it was a great choice.

872
00:37:00,147 --> 00:37:01,563
It was a great choice,

873
00:37:01,587 --> 00:37:03,773
and if I hadn't jumped in
and let you speak your mind,

874
00:37:03,797 --> 00:37:04,945
you know
what he would have heard?

875
00:37:04,970 --> 00:37:06,620
Something's wrong
with Mike Ross.

876
00:37:06,644 --> 00:37:08,729
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do, and so do you.

877
00:37:08,754 --> 00:37:10,338
This is Louis
we're talking about.

878
00:37:10,362 --> 00:37:11,979
And you rejected
his first request.

879
00:37:12,004 --> 00:37:13,553
Because it was unreasonable.

880
00:37:13,578 --> 00:37:15,161
And the only way
you're gonna convince him

881
00:37:15,185 --> 00:37:17,573
that this is unreasonable
is to tell him why.

882
00:37:17,597 --> 00:37:18,878
Harvey...

883
00:37:18,903 --> 00:37:21,223
Jessica, the only way
to make him take that offer back

884
00:37:21,248 --> 00:37:22,496
is to force him to do it

885
00:37:22,521 --> 00:37:24,874
because he's gonna ask you why
again and again.

886
00:37:24,899 --> 00:37:26,214
And no matter what you say,

887
00:37:26,238 --> 00:37:27,822
he's gonna know
you're full of shit.

888
00:37:27,846 --> 00:37:29,813
And then how long do you think
it's gonna take him

889
00:37:29,822 --> 00:37:31,439
to remember that last year,

890
00:37:31,464 --> 00:37:33,841
he wondered if Mike
even went to Harvard.

891
00:37:36,889 --> 00:37:40,716
You could at least pretend
to hide how happy you are.

892
00:37:40,741 --> 00:37:42,290
I may be happy about it,

893
00:37:42,315 --> 00:37:43,765
but you know I'm right.

894
00:37:43,790 --> 00:37:45,775
And the truth is,

895
00:37:45,799 --> 00:37:48,309
I never should have let him go
in the first place.

896
00:37:57,622 --> 00:37:59,875
You look a lot better
than the last time I saw you.

897
00:37:59,900 --> 00:38:01,014
Well, didn't you hear?

898
00:38:01,038 --> 00:38:02,120
I got a new job.

899
00:38:02,144 --> 00:38:04,062
Oh, I heard.

900
00:38:04,087 --> 00:38:05,636
What're you getting at there,
Harvey?

901
00:38:05,661 --> 00:38:07,411
What am I getting at?

902
00:38:07,436 --> 00:38:08,383
Louis hires you.

903
00:38:08,407 --> 00:38:09,655
You don't run it by me.

904
00:38:09,680 --> 00:38:12,000
You don't even tell me
it's happening.

905
00:38:12,025 --> 00:38:15,148
All I am anymore to you
is a clean set of sheets.

906
00:38:15,173 --> 00:38:17,125
Speaking of which, you might
want to up the thread count.

907
00:38:17,149 --> 00:38:18,799
And run it by you?

908
00:38:18,824 --> 00:38:20,842
You were practically begging me
to come back yesterday.

909
00:38:20,867 --> 00:38:21,914
I didn't beg shit.

910
00:38:21,939 --> 00:38:23,422
I posited a theory.

911
00:38:23,446 --> 00:38:24,971
We both knew
it was never gonna happen.

912
00:38:24,987 --> 00:38:26,469
I was just trying to make you
feel better.

913
00:38:26,494 --> 00:38:29,183
I guess it took Louis
to do what you couldn't do.

914
00:38:29,207 --> 00:38:31,794
Hire an unqualified fraud?

915
00:38:31,819 --> 00:38:34,440
I did that already.

916
00:38:34,465 --> 00:38:35,613
Seriously, Mike,

917
00:38:35,638 --> 00:38:38,126
it's good to have things
back to normal.

918
00:38:38,150 --> 00:38:41,229
Yeah. Normal.

919
00:38:44,246 --> 00:38:45,428
Mike, I'm gonna say
something to you

920
00:38:45,452 --> 00:38:47,437
that I have never told
you before.

921
00:38:47,462 --> 00:38:49,480
I admire what you have
with Rachel.

922
00:38:49,505 --> 00:38:51,658
- Harvey...
- No, let me finish.

923
00:38:51,682 --> 00:38:52,997
It's real.

924
00:38:53,021 --> 00:38:54,035
It's hard to come by,

925
00:38:54,060 --> 00:38:55,376
and all you have to do
to keep it

926
00:38:55,400 --> 00:38:56,949
is forgive her.

927
00:38:56,974 --> 00:39:00,298
So if you want to stay
here tonight, by all means,

928
00:39:00,323 --> 00:39:02,767
but I think you should go home.

929
00:39:07,156 --> 00:39:09,677
Where are you going?

930
00:39:09,701 --> 00:39:11,017
I have to take care of something

931
00:39:11,041 --> 00:39:13,350
I should have days ago.

932
00:39:21,090 --> 00:39:22,338
Harvey. You wanted to see me?

933
00:39:22,363 --> 00:39:23,812
Yes.

934
00:39:23,836 --> 00:39:26,022
I wanted you to take a look
at a draft of the paperwork

935
00:39:26,047 --> 00:39:27,262
to wrap up your deal.

936
00:39:27,286 --> 00:39:28,936
Why would you...

937
00:39:28,961 --> 00:39:30,175
Because I wanted to let you know

938
00:39:30,199 --> 00:39:32,587
how things are gonna be
moving forward.

939
00:39:32,612 --> 00:39:35,334
You're gonna sign these papers
at 8:00 a.m. tomorrow,

940
00:39:35,358 --> 00:39:38,583
and at 8:01,

941
00:39:38,607 --> 00:39:40,458
you're gone.

942
00:39:42,928 --> 00:39:44,009
Harvey.

943
00:39:44,033 --> 00:39:45,114
Look, I don't give a shit

944
00:39:45,138 --> 00:39:46,855
how much business
you give my firm.

945
00:39:46,880 --> 00:39:48,497
I never want to see you again.

946
00:39:48,521 --> 00:39:49,669
You're really gonna drop me?

947
00:39:49,694 --> 00:39:50,975
You're damn right I am.

948
00:39:51,000 --> 00:39:53,621
And if you go to Jessica
to try to overrule me,

949
00:39:53,646 --> 00:39:56,535
the next time, it won't be Mike
you get in a fight with.

950
00:39:56,560 --> 00:39:57,932
It'll be me.

951
00:40:04,766 --> 00:40:12,796
♪ ♪

952
00:40:54,371 --> 00:40:56,792
You're home.

953
00:40:56,816 --> 00:40:58,690
I am.

954
00:41:01,337 --> 00:41:04,093
Why aren't you at work?

955
00:41:04,118 --> 00:41:05,467
Because I spent
the whole day moving

956
00:41:05,491 --> 00:41:06,705
from one place to another,

957
00:41:06,730 --> 00:41:09,888
and I just had to talk to you.

958
00:41:09,912 --> 00:41:12,299
How'd you know I'd be here?

959
00:41:12,323 --> 00:41:15,806
I didn't.
I just went to Harvey's.

960
00:41:18,118 --> 00:41:19,567
Yeah.

961
00:41:19,592 --> 00:41:22,347
Not there anymore.

962
00:41:22,371 --> 00:41:23,619
Are you back here?

963
00:41:23,644 --> 00:41:26,032
No.

964
00:41:27,865 --> 00:41:31,491
No, I'm going to stay
somewhere for a while.

965
00:41:31,516 --> 00:41:32,697
Mike...

966
00:41:32,721 --> 00:41:33,902
Rachel,
whatever you're going to say,

967
00:41:33,927 --> 00:41:35,835
now is not the time to say it.

968
00:41:39,420 --> 00:41:43,883
If you want there to be
a chance for us...

969
00:41:43,908 --> 00:41:47,401
At all,

970
00:41:47,425 --> 00:41:48,907
just go back out a little longer

971
00:41:48,932 --> 00:41:51,409
and let me get my things
together.

972
00:41:59,215 --> 00:42:01,424
One more thing.

973
00:42:03,904 --> 00:42:08,602
I'm coming back to work
tomorrow.

974
00:42:08,627 --> 00:42:09,741
If you can't accept that,

975
00:42:09,765 --> 00:42:12,789
then whatever you were going
to say to me

976
00:42:12,814 --> 00:42:14,431
won't matter.

977
00:42:14,455 --> 00:42:22,485
♪ ♪

978
00:42:24,704 --> 00:42:32,734
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man

