- Previously on "suits"...
You hung me out to dry.
- How exactly did i do that?
- By making it seem like
i'm the one
That's taking away
your dream wedding.
- You are the one taking away
my dream wedding!
- We're getting married,
And it can be as small
as possible
With just our close friends,
okay?
- I think we should consider
promoting jack soloff
To name partner.
- Are you crazy?
- Hardman's got something
on him.
- If hardman has something
on him,
Then we need to have it
on him, too.
You want me gone,
call for a vote,
'cause we know what's going on
with daniel's investor,
And harvey's about to put a stop
to it right now.
- Why should i believe you
would even live up to
Your end of the bargain?
- Because i don't give a shit
About your war with
daniel hardman.
All i want to do is see you
get down on your knees
And say, "i quit."
- You're breaking the law
every day.
- Oh, so now i shouldn't
get married?
- I'm saying you should quit.
The longer you go,
The less the money matters.
- You almost got caught,
didn't you?
- I went to talk to someone.
- Who?
- You know who.
- Mom?
Dad!
Grammy, what are you doing here?
Where's mom?
I want to give her a hug.
Dad, too.
- What?
- You told me not to be mad
at them last night, remember?
You said once they got home
i should tell them i was sorry
And give them a hug.
But they didn't wake me up,
so i didn't get to,
And i want to.
- Michael, i have to
tell you something.
- What is it?
- Your... your parents,
Last night they were in
a car accident.
- But they're gonna
be okay, right?
- Michael, they passed away.
- What?
No.
No, they can't be.
You're wrong!
- [cries]
I wish i were, baby.
I wish i...
- Why didn't you wake me up?
I could have gone
to the hospital.
I could have seen them!
- They didn't make it to
the hospital, sweetheart,
And... and i didn't want to
tell you until i had to.
- How could you do this to me?
How could you not wake me up?
[soul music]
♪ ♪
- Hey.
[clears throat]
- What are you doing up
so early?
- Oh, nothing, just going
through this old box of stuff.
- Does that have
something to do with
You seeing trevor last night?
- Yeah.
Yeah, it does.
- Is he still a mess?
- No. No, he's actually
doing really well.
- So what do you mean?
- I mean,
i need to take the day.
- You need to take the day?
- Yeah.
- Is there something wrong?
- No, nothing's wrong.
Just got something i need to do.
- Okay.
[elevator bell dings]
- Jessica.
- Jack.
Did you reconsider my offer?
- About resigning?
Yeah, no, not a chance.
But the bylaws require you
to be given formal notice so...
- You're calling for
An emergency
vote of no confidence today?
- Yes.
- Well, you're shitty
at math, jack,
Because even if
we lost mckernon,
One client is not enough to
turn the partners against me.
- Check your calculator,
jessica,
Because you only had
half the partners,
And every single one of them
is about to lose
The biggest client to
a hostile takeover
Because of your poor leadership.
- We both know the only
hostile takeover you care about
Is the one in here.
- Take a picture,
Because tomorrow morning,
those letters are coming down.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Where the hell is he?
- I don't know.
- Gretchen, i swear, if you
want to have a job tomorrow,
You better tell me
where harvey is.
- Ms. Pearson, every sunday
i lay out all my outfits
For the coming week,
and i have no intention
Of not wearing one of
those babies tomorrow.
So with all due respect,
I don't know.
- Well, if you want to pick out
your clothes for next week,
You better find the hell out.
- ♪ see the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ i'll even eat a bean pie,
i don't mind ♪
♪ me and missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ all right ♪
♪ all step back,
i'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ the greenback boogie ♪
.
- Harvey.
Harvey, wait.
Wait.
I-i made a mistake.
- Don't you touch me.
- You don't understand.
- I understand you made a fool
out of dad for the last time.
- Lily, let me try.
Harvey...
- You get the hell out of
my father's house.
- Bobby, get... get out.
Get out!
Listen, harvey to me.
No, you don't know
what you're doing.
- I know exactly what i'm doing.
- Harvey, think about what
it would do to your father.
To marcus.
It'll kill them.
- You said that once before
and you'd never do this again.
- I know what i said.
- And i said if you did
i'd tell him everything,
And i'm going to.
- Harvey, i am begging you.
Don't tear us all to pieces.
Don't destroy your family.
- Don't you dare
put this shit on me.
[door slams]
- Harvey?
Where did you just go?
- I'm sorry.
I was just thinking about
the time i had to decide
Whether or not
i should tell my father
That my mother was
cheating on him.
- And maybe we should
talk about that.
- I didn't come here
to talk about that.
I came here to figure out
whether or not i should resign.
- And then you started
thinking about your mother.
And if your brain went
to the one,
Then it's connecting it
to the other,
And the best thing
we can do right now
Is to try and figure out why.
- I don't have time for that.
- Harvey, you asked me
to block out the day
For an emergency session,
and i did.
We have time.
- The white ones are best.
- You're just here to
make me go in.
- I am.
Because sometimes
we make choices
We're not old enough to make,
And then we regret them.
I don't want that
to happen to you.
- Why would i regret
not going into that place?
- 'cause it's a chance to
say good-bye to your parents.
- I already missed that.
[grunts]
[rock lands]
- Mike.
Sometimes when people
lose someone they love,
They get mad at them.
- I'm not mad at them.
I'm mad at god.
- I understand
you're mad at god.
Maybe you're even
mad at me, too.
But i came out here
to give you something.
- St. William,
Patron saint of orphans.
- You know who this is.
- I know who all the saints are,
And i don't want it.
I don't want to be an orphan.
- Then don't take it.
[poignant music]
Because the truth is,
orphans are alone,
And you're not.
But not going in there
Isn't gonna change
what happened.
And right now,
your grandmother needs you.
But if you stay out here,
She's gonna have to
face today alone.
♪ ♪
- Well, it's official, harvey.
My fingers are way too old.
- Like hell.
You can still outplay anyone.
- [chuckles]
You're a terrible liar.
But i got to admit,
I do love seeing my boy
in the crowd.
- Actually, dad,
there's something
I wanted to talk to you about.
- I got something for you, too.
It's important.
The band's splitting up.
- What?
- Lenny says he wants to spend
his golden years with marge,
And dave's wrist isn't
getting any better, so...
- Well, what about harry?
- Harry's already got an offer
from another group.
- Well, if they'll take him,
they'll take you.
- [laughs]
You're not listening, harvey.
I don't want them to take me.
I want to come home.
- Dad, music is your life.
- Look, harvey, i'm the same age
your grandfather was
When he died,
And i've already spent
way too much of my life
Away from my family.
- Don't start that.
You've been a great father.
- Maybe the cool father,
but... Not a great one.
And now, i know it's too late
to make that up to you.
I'm just hoping it's not too
late to make it up to marcus.
Anyway, that's my news.
What... what did you want
to talk about?
- Nothing.
I met a girl.
- Great.
What's her name?
- Scottie.
I'm just trying to figure out
the long distance thing.
- All i can tell you there is,
if she's the one,
You'll know, just like with
me and your mother.
- So you didn't tell him?
- No, i didn't.
- But you said that was the
night you decided to tell him.
- That was the night i decided.
- No, you said it as though
it was all one night.
- I told you it was
all one night
Because i'm so used to lying
whenever i tell this story.
My age...
- Why do you lie?
- Because i was a grown man
when it happened,
And grown men keep their words
When they say
they're gonna do something,
Not give in to weakness.
- But it wasn't weakness that
made you break your word.
It was love for your father.
- Then aren't i an asshole?
Because i ended up ruining
everything two weeks later.
- Louis, i need to
talk to you for a minute.
- About what?
- Jack soloff is
calling for a vote
To remove me as
managing partner today.
- What?
Why the hell would he do that
After you offered to make him
name partner?
- Because i didn't offer
to make him name partner.
I told him to resign.
- What happened to our plan?
- It wasn't our plan, louis.
It was your insane idea,
And i was never going to do it.
- Jessica...
- No, you listen to me.
The matter at hand is
Making sure that we have
more people on our side
Than he and daniel have
on theirs.
- What am i supposed to do now?
- You are going to do exactly
what i told you to do
In the first place.
You're gonna find out
what daniel has
On that weaselly son of a bitch,
and do it before 7:00 tonight.
Because if i can't get
enough votes before then,
The only way we win is to make
this whole thing go away.
[dramatic music]
- Cancel my day.
.
- We have to talk.
- I'm studying, grammy.
- I don't care what you say
you're doing.
- What i say i'm doing?
- Father walker called me.
He said you've been acting out.
- Father walker's a priest.
He thinks you're acting out
if you're chewing gum.
- Well, i agree with him.
- Yeah, and you're not at school
and all i do is get as.
- I don't care
what you're getting.
I found these in the trash.
- So what.
- So what?
"the little prince,"
"james and the giant peach,"
Michael, you love these books.
- Yeah, when i was a kid.
- Those books were your
connection to your mother
And father.
- Yeah, well,
i don't want them anymore.
- You don't want
this one either?
Your mother and i
didn't always get along,
But i know that she read this
to you every night
When you were little
because she told me.
And i also know that you'd
never let me read it to you
Because you said
it was so special.
- Like i said,
i'm not a kid anymore.
- Michael,
i'm worried about you.
Father walker is worried.
- I don't care what
father walker thinks,
And i don't care about
these stupid books.
- Well, i do care,
And i think you'd better go talk
to father walker tomorrow
Because you're not
getting all as.
He's giving you an f
on your history paper.
- Louis, what are you
doing here?
How did you get past stacy?
- I walked right by her.
- Well, in that case,
what can i do for you?
- I want to know what the hell
you have on jack soloff.
- I have nothing on jack
other than his trust
And confidence that i'm
a better attorney than jessica.
- Shut your mouth.
You're not fit to
lick her boots.
- Good, because that's
your job, louis, not mine.
- Listen to me.
Remember when i told you
i'd kill you
If you so much as tell me
the incorrect time?
Tell me what you have
on jack right now
Or you're dead in 15 seconds.
- I remember when
you did that, louis.
And right after that,
i went straight to my attorneys
And told them
you had threatened my life.
And now, you've come into
my office and done it again
In front of a witness.
- What witness?
- Stacy, did you get that?
- I got it.
- So as i see it,
Security will be here
in about 60 seconds.
So if you want to kill me,
Now is your chance.
- I swear to god,
i will find out
What you're holding
over jack's head.
- I doubt that,
And i certainly doubt that
you'll find it by 7:00.
So instead of me telling you
what i have on jack,
Let me tell you
what i have on you.
You vote with me today
And your sister's company lives.
- What?
- Oh, it turns out
My client is looking to get into
the muffin business.
- You leave my sister
out of this.
- Sure thing.
As long as you vote
to remove jessica.
- I can't do that.
- Then i'm not only
gonna buy it,
I'm gonna rip that company
of hers apart.
- You son of a bitch!
She never did anything to you.
- No.
But you did.
And jessica did.
And harvey did.
So you have a choice,
Your firm or your family.
- Michael?
It's been a long time.
- People have been calling me
that a lot lately.
- Maybe it's a sign.
How can i help you?
- I need to talk to someone.
I was hoping to do it
under the confessional.
- How long has it been
since your last confession?
- Aren't you supposed to
ask me that after we started?
- We have started.
Have a seat.
- Here?
- Why not?
Confession's meant to be
good for the soul
And no one's ever said anything
about it having to be done
In a little dark box.
Please.
- You gave that paper an f?
It deserves an a.
- What about the fact that
you cut the entire afternoon
Last tuesday?
- I had a doctor's appointment.
- You even had a note
from your grandmother.
- That's right, i did.
- The problem is, michael,
Your grandmother wrote me
a note yesterday
Thanking me for letting
her book club use the library.
And those two signatures,
They don't look the same at all.
- Okay, well, if you're
so sure i did this,
Then why are you
only giving me an f
And not suspending me?
- Because i don't think
it's a coincidence that
You chose to cut class on
parent-teacher conference day.
- That had nothing
to do with it.
- Mike, your grandmother told me
about the books you threw out.
- Every parent in the world
is obsessed
With their kid
cleaning their room.
I actually do it,
And the two of you make
a federal case out of it.
- You didn't throw out
those books to clean.
You did it because you saw
those kids out there
With their parents
And you just couldn't
deal with that pain.
So you cut class, you went home,
And you threw away the books.
- You don't know what i did.
- What i do know is that your
parents came here every sunday
And donated money
to pay for that uniform
Because they wanted you to
be here getting an education
And not cutting class.
- I've gotten a perfect grade
on every assignment
I've ever gotten, all right?
And i don't need to go to
your stupid class to do it.
- I could have suspended you,
And that would have been
much worse than an f.
But you're getting one
or you're getting the other.
So why don't you take
one night off from blaming me,
And you decided what it is
that you're gonna do?
- Harvey,
What are you doing here?
- I wanted to ask you something.
I was wondering if
i could stay with you
While i do my clerkship.
- You want to stay with me
for the summer?
- I promise you won't
even know i'm there.
- Are you crazy?
Do you have any idea what the
people around here would think
If they found out?
- Who says
they're gonna find out?
I mean, no one knows anything
about your personal life anyway.
- Harvey, what's going on?
- Things aren't good at home.
- Your brother?
- It's my parents.
- Listen, harvey,
i know what it's like
To be living in a home
that's not right,
And i also know that you might
be tempted to fix things.
But it's not up to
the children to fix things.
- What if it was?
- Then there's something wrong
with those two people.
- No, there isn't.
There's something wrong
with one of them,
And i don't know whether to
tell the other one or not.
- Look, harvey, i can't
tell you what you should do.
But i can tell you
if you come work for me,
You're gonna have to have
some difficult conversations.
- That's work, this is family.
- There are no more difficult
conversations than that.
But for the record,
If you do come work here,
We're gonna be family, too.
.
- Hey there.
Your father and marcus
will be here any minute,
And, oh, i made your favorite,
chicken parm.
- I'm glad they're not here.
It'll give me a chance
to tell you that
I'll pretend when they're here,
But i am not gonna pretend
when we're alone.
- Harvey, please,
i'm still your mother.
- No, you're not.
- Hey, hey, hey,
look who's here.
I thought you were
working late tonight.
- What's up, douche nozzle?
- You remember bobby from down
at the shop, don't you, harvey?
He's helping us get
the old mustang up and running.
- That's right, harvey,
i'm getting the mustang.
And if you think you're ever
getting behind the wheel
Of that car...
- I'm never gonna get behind
the wheel of that car.
- Because you're jealous.
- Because that car's
a piece of shit.
- Harvey, watch your mouth.
Lil, do we have enough for
an extra plate?
- Sure.
How you doing, bobby?
- I'll be good as soon as
i get this grease off my hands.
Where's the bathroom again?
- It's down the hall, bobby.
You know what?
We don't need an extra plate
'cause i'm not eating.
- What are you talking about?
You're home early.
Your mother made chicken parm.
- Well, why don't you eat it?
Because i can't stand
chicken parm anymore.
- Where you going?
Harvey!
This is still my house,
you know.
- Is it?
- So other people know
about you?
- Not everyone
knows everything, but...
People know that
i don't have a law degree.
- You say that as though
it were just a technicality.
- And you say that
as if you're judging me.
- Isn't that what you
came here for?
- I came here for advice.
- You said you came here
to confess.
But it doesn't matter,
because if...
Well, if you're looking
for absolution,
I can't give it to you.
- Why not?
- Because absolution
requires contrition,
And i'm not hearing that
you even think
You've done anything wrong.
- Because using my brain
to help people
Isn't doing anything wrong.
- You're not using
your brain to help people.
You're using it to fool people,
And you want me to tell you that
you're a good person for it.
- I am a good person.
- You're a person that
wants to have their cake
And eat it, too.
And i'm afraid that
i'm all out of cake with you.
- What is that supposed to mean?
- It means that
i've often wondered
Whether or not
i did the right thing
By not having you arrested
that day.
- That would have completely
screwed up my life.
- Oh, and look at how not
screwed up it is right now.
- You want to know
what kind of man i am?
[stirring music]
♪ ♪
You wanted to see me, father?
- Yes, i did.
I was hoping
you could explain why
We're missing $936
from the collection box.
- I can't.
- Well, that's odd,
because this box was in my desk,
And i also found this
On my desk.
Michael, the next time
you want to send a message,
Just leave me a note.
- The uniform's not a message.
I'm just returning it.
You said i had two options,
get an f or get suspended.
But i thought of a third.
- So you're dropping out?
- No, i'm going to
public school.
And i'm not saying that
i took that cash,
But if i did, i'd be
smart enough to do the math.
My parents put $3 in the
collection plate every week.
$3 a week for 52 weeks
for six years...
- $936.
- And i would have thought that
belonged to my parents
And i would have just been
taking it back.
- You know, i could
have you arrested.
- Then do it.
- Michael, we both know
how smart you are,
But there's a difference between
intelligence and wisdom.
And if you don't figure
that out eventually,
You're gonna have a lot bigger
problems than an f,
Because you can't outsmart...
- God?
- I know.
I know you don't believe in god,
So let's just call them...
Consequences.
- Good-bye, father.
You want to call the police,
you know where to find me.
Wouldn't be the first time
They came to give grammy
some bad news.
- You never spent it.
- Not a penny.
- Get out.
Hey, get out!
Harvey, you and me are going.
Right now.
- No, we're not.
- Yes, we are.
And it's happening whether
you like it or not.
Oh.
Now, you wanna tell me
what was going on
With that bullshit
back at the house?
- What bullshit?
I wasn't hungry so i just left.
- I'm not buying it.
I know something's up with you.
- Nothing's up.
- Nothing?
[both grunting]
Your little brother was
excited to see you
And you didn't give him
the time of day.
- Marcus was excited
to get bobby's car.
- Since when you got
something against bobby?
He never did anything to you.
- Just let it go, dad.
- Since when do i do that?
- Since when were you
around not to?
- Excuse me?
- I said let it go.
- I'm not letting it go!
You disrespected me,
And you disrespected
your brother and your mother
And our guest.
Now, i know
something's up with you.
I want to know what it is.
- It's nothing.
- It's not nothing!
- Why are you doing this?
- 'cause there's something
wrong with my boy.
[groans]
- Something's wrong with me?
What about you?
How can you not see what is
going on under your nose
In your own goddamn house?
- All right.
Son, stop!
- I told her to stop,
but i shouldn't have had to.
It's shouldn't have been me!
- Aah!
[dark music]
- I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- You told her to stop what?
What was your mother doing?
- Bobby.
♪ ♪
- So your parents' marriage
ended?
- It should have ended sooner.
- Harvey, i'm not
defending your mother,
But what if you'd kept
that promise
And then she broke it off
with bobby?
- What difference does it make?
- Well, the difference is
You didn't have to tell
your father like that.
- Yeah, i told him like that
because i had no choice.
- No, no, no, no, telling him
like that was your choice.
- He was attacking me.
- Well, you could have
dropped your guard.
- I wasn't gonna do that.
- He was your father.
- I don't care!
- Why?
- Because i don't lay down!
- And instead of
telling him gently
And making a decision calmly,
You hurt your father even more.
- What are you saying?
- I'm saying that maybe
you're remembering this story
To tell yourself that
your decision with forstman
Isn't about laying down.
It's about something more.
.
- Hey, baby.
You're never going to
believe this.
Harvey asked if he could
live with me today.
- I'm surprised
you didn't say yes.
- What?
- You already live
at the office.
Why not just
bring it home with you?
- Quentin, i told you,
You mean more to me than work.
- Well, actions speak louder
than words.
- I married you.
- You did.
- Mm-hmm.
- But does harvey or anyone else
at the office know that?
Or even know that i exist?
- You know i'm a private person.
I like to keep those parts
of my life separate.
- What i know is, separate
but equal didn't work out there,
And it's not working in here.
- Where are you going with this?
- You know where
this is going, jessica,
Where it's been going
for a long time.
I want a divorce.
- What?
- This isn't working anymore.
- Does this have
anything to do with lisa?
- No.
This has to do with us.
- Oh, you mean me.
- I do.
Now you can focus on what
really matters to you...
Your career.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
- Jessica, can i talk to you?
- I take it
you haven't found out
What hardman has on jack.
- I haven't,
but there's something else.
- Doesn't matter.
I got us the votes.
- You did?
- I went to paul porter
and i turned him
And the three votes that
he comes with.
- So we're up by three?
- No, including harvey,
we're up by one.
- No, we're not.
Hardman's going after
esther's company.
- And he's not going to back off
unless you vote against me.
Louis...
- I know what you're gonna say.
We can stop it.
But i went to jeffrey to get him
to not sell his shares,
And he told me that hardman's
offering 40% over asking.
Jeffrey agreed not to sell,
but everyone else will.
If hardman can't get the stocks,
he's gonna buy the distributor,
And if he can't buy
the distributor,
He's gonna go after
the contracts.
- Louis...
- Forstman is his backer!
- I know.
- Well then, you know that
he has unlimited resources,
And i can't fight a war
on multiple fronts.
- And i could tell you that
if you side with me,
We'll figure out a way
to save esther's company.
But i have a sister, too.
- I'm sorry.
- Louis...
[stirring music]
Whatever happens,
I want you to know...
Pearson will always
consider litt
Her partner.
♪ ♪
- Jessica.
If it had been anybody
other than his sister,
He would never even consider...
- I know, donna.
And you don't have to
apologize for him
Because i know what a bastard
daniel hardman is.
- Is there anything i can do?
- Yes.
We still have some time
before the vote.
I asked gretchen to find harvey
this morning.
I asked the wrong person.
- I'll find him.
♪ ♪
- I knew this was a mistake.
I never should have come here.
- Michael, you didn't
actually have to come here.
I already knew your story.
Trevor came to see me
six months ago.
- Yeah, i know that.
- Yeah, but you didn't know
he spent most of that time
Talking about you or the fact
that he blames himself
For everything that
happened to you.
- Well, maybe he should.
- Maybe you should blame
yourself.
- Right, and maybe i should
blame myself
For every earthquake
or every war.
- That's enough of the vanity,
okay, michael.
- Vanity?
- Yeah, vanity, self-indulgence,
Whatever you want to call
feeling sorry for yourself
Ever since that night...
- How dare you.
- Because that's exactly why
you're in this position
Right now.
- No!
I'm in this position because
trevor put me in this position.
- No, michael, no.
That's the difference
between you and trevor.
He's actually accepted that
his choices were his own,
Which means he actually
wants to change his life.
- You think i don't want
to change?
Why the hell
do you think i'm here?
- I don't know.
Why are you here?
- I told you, i want advice.
- No, no, people do not need the
protection of the confessional
To get advice.
- I did that to protect you.
- No, you did that
to protect you.
So you tell me right now,
why are you here?
- It's not that simple.
- It is that simple.
- I can't.
- Why are you here?
- Because i'm afraid!
[poignant music]
♪ ♪
- What are you afraid of,
michael?
- They left me all alone.
- And now you've found someone
who loves you...
And if you stop being
who you are,
You're afraid
she'll abandon you, too.
- What am i gonna do, father?
- Come with me, michael.
I want to show you something.
♪ ♪
.
- Why'd you tell him?
- He needed to know.
- What he needed was
for us to be a family.
- Families aren't built on lies.
- Well, now all we are
is built on shit
Because nobody's happy about
what you did except for you.
- I didn't do this for me.
- You couldn't stand that
I was about to have them
all to myself.
- You think i did this to
take something away from you?
- You did take something
away from me.
You don't get it.
You get to go back
to law school,
And you're gonna pass the bar,
And you're gonna go live
your big hotshot life,
And i'm gonna be stuck here
on my own.
- You're not on your own.
- Really?
I don't know if you noticed,
but mom just left
And dad's not coming out of
his room, so who's here for me?
Hmm?
- So two weeks later
i got a place in the city,
I moved out,
and i never went back.
- You left your brother
and your father alone
After all that?
- I didn't want to.
- Then why did you?
- Because i couldn't
take knowing that
I was the one that
tore everything to pieces.
- And you think you'll be
doing that again if you resign?
- I will be doing that again
if i resign.
- Well, i think stepping down
Isn't tearing everything
to pieces.
I think it's a chance to
keep everything together.
- She gave me my start.
- Harvey, i once commented
that jessica sounds like
A hell of a woman,
And you said,
"what does it matter?"
Well, you're the one
who led me to believe
She's a hell of a woman.
Maybe you did it for a reason.
- What reason?
- For me to suggest that
maybe she'll understand
That you leaving doesn't mean
that you don't care about her.
It means that you do.
- And what if that's not why
i told you all this?
What if you're wrong?
- Then i'll be wrong.
And you'll be able to
handle that.
- I spent a lot of time here.
- You remember this place?
- I remember everything.
- I know you do, michael.
I was always aware of
what a special child you were.
- Hasn't changed a bit.
- Hasn't it?
- What are you talking about?
- Michael, i think
you came to see me
Because when people
are in crisis
They're searching for
something more,
Usually something they've lost.
- I lost my parents,
and i'm not getting them back.
- No, michael,
you lost your faith.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- Grammy.
- The day after you left school
She gave me the money back.
Her only request was that
we use some of it
To buy this bookcase
To keep these books together.
- They're my father's books.
- And your mother's.
[melancholy music]
♪ ♪
I never knew why she did it.
And now i do.
- [crying]
- Michael, if you're worried
about rachel leaving you,
If you stop doing
what you're doing,
I don't think she will.
- How do you know?
♪ ♪
[cries]
- 'cause i have faith.
♪ ♪
[door opens]
- Can i help you?
- I was just...
Where is he?
- Where is who?
- Harvey.
Please, it's an emergency.
- Well, i'm sorry,
he's not here,
And i'm afraid i don't know
where he went.
- I'm sorry, i just...
Do you mind if i just
sit here for a minute?
- Of course.
- [sighs]
You probably know more about
what's going on that i do,
Don't you?
- I'm sorry,
i can't respond to that.
- As long as i'm here...
Thank you.
- For what?
- A few weeks ago
harvey finally forgave me
For going to louis.
And i know he never
would have done that
If he hadn't come to see you.
- I'm sorry, i can't respond
to that either.
- You just did.
And thank you again for
what you're thinking.
- And what is that?
- That he never would have
come to see you
If it hadn't been for me.
- You really can do that.
- Yeah, i can.
In fact, i can tell you
what you're thinking right now.
- What is that?
- You're thinking two things,
actually.
One, this woman would make
an excellent therapist.
And two...
Harvey has no idea
what he's missing.
[poignant music]
♪ ♪
- Well, it seems
harvey won't be joining us,
So we may as well get started.
We're here because
there's a concern
That i no longer have the best
interests of the firm at heart
But am instead focused
on the selfish interests
Of certain individuals.
For those of you
who feel that way,
There's not much i could do
At this point
to change your minds.
So... I'll say...
I hope it remains my pleasure to
serve this firm.
- I think it's time we vote.
- Well, if you're not gonna say
anything to change their mind,
Then i will.
- You made it.
- Wouldn't have missed it
for the world.
- Okay, fine, you're here,
But there's nothing that says
you can plead her case.
- And there's nothing
that says he can't,
So why don't you
sit your ass down?
- Go ahead, then,
get your speech over with
So we can get to the vote.
- No speech, just this.
A termination letter.
As of now, the company that's
been targeting our clients
Is no longer represented
by daniel hardman.
- Bullshit.
- Go ahead, call him.
Of course, it might take a while
Since you've got to go through
the prison switchboard
To get ahold of him.
Yep, that's right.
That's the kind of man
jack soloff and daniel hardman
Do business with,
one who's already behind bars.
Look, let me be clear.
The attack on this firm was
an attack on me.
Daniel blamed me
for having to leave this firm,
So he was trying to hit me
where it hurt the most,
Namely this firm
And my partners and my friends.
But that's over.
He has no more money,
No more power, no more friends.
All of you,
you're about to vote on whether
Jessica should continue
running this firm.
Now, i know some of you think
that she's turned a blind eye
To my behavior
and... and the risks i've taken,
But for you to remove her would
be the greatest risk of all.
Because if there's one thing
i know,
It's that jessica pearson cares
about this firm
And everyone in it.
Because to her,
we're not just colleagues
Or even friends,
We're family.
[tense music]
- Thank you, harvey.
Let's vote.
- Jessica, i don't think we're
gonna be needing the ballots.
I think everybody knows
where they stand.
All in favor of jessica staying.
♪ ♪
- Then i guess everyone here
is happy
Keeping things the way they are,
except for one.
♪ ♪
- I'm glad you're here.
I need to tell you something.
- Whatever it is,
it might not matter
After i give you this.
- What is it?
- Harvey, you didn't just
give me my dream.
You gave me a family.
But i'm gonna have a family
of my own someday,
And i can't have all of this
hanging over their heads.
- You're resigning.
- I am.
- You know, you once asked me
why i hired you,
And i told you it was
because life is like this
And i like this.
- Harvey, please,
you can't convince me...
- Let me finish.
It was like this
Not because of the risk
we're taking.
It's because of who you are.
- So you're not disappointed?
- Are you kidding me?
After that speech,
if you hadn't done this,
I'd be kicking you out.
And for the record,
You're not the only one who got
more family out of this deal.
[poignant music]
♪ ♪
- You really are so beautiful.
- No one's beautiful in
fluorescent light.
- You are.
- So how did your mysterious
adventure go?
Did you get what you needed?
- I did.
- What's this?
- Early wedding present.
- Oh, yeah?
Mike, this is...
- A copy of my letter
of resignation.
- If this is about
the thing with claire
Or the fight that i got into
with my mom...
- It's not.
This is about us
starting our life right,
With a clean slate.
- You don't have to do this
for me.
- I'm not.
I'm doing it for us.
Because as long as
you're with me...
- I'm with you.
- Well then, let me go say
good-bye to my office,
And let's go home.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- You walked out before we got
a chance to celebrate.
- I'm sorry.
It's just been a long day.
- Harvey, how exactly did you
get that termination letter
From forstman?
- Let's talk about it
in the morning.
- Harvey.
- I agreed to step down.
- Absolutely not.
You are not going to step down.
- It's done.
- Nothing's done.
- Jessica, please, you've given
up everything for this firm.
It's time someone gave up
something for you.
- What if i don't want you
to be the one to do that?
- Then forgive me, because i am.
Good news is,
mike ross is leaving.
- I never thought i'd say this,
But at this moment,
That doesn't feel like
good news.
♪ ♪
- Michael james ross.
- Yes?
- You're under arrest for
conspiracy to commit fraud.
♪ ♪