1
00:00:02,005 --> 00:00:03,947
I just wanted to tell you
that I appreciate you

2
00:00:03,948 --> 00:00:05,208
patching things up with him.

3
00:00:05,233 --> 00:00:08,738
I would do anything
for the woman that I love.

4
00:00:08,905 --> 00:00:10,551
They are gonna come at us
any way they can,

5
00:00:10,575 --> 00:00:11,825
and when they do,

6
00:00:11,961 --> 00:00:13,401
it's not gonna be
about heat sensors,

7
00:00:13,413 --> 00:00:14,975
it's gonna be about you.

8
00:00:15,000 --> 00:00:17,396
I know I'm not the only guy
in that company

9
00:00:17,420 --> 00:00:19,088
that knows
those sensors are faulty.

10
00:00:19,223 --> 00:00:20,667
I'm sorry, what is it
you need again?

11
00:00:20,692 --> 00:00:23,322
All the maintenance work orders
from the past six months.

12
00:00:23,347 --> 00:00:25,565
I can't let you have that
without authorization.

13
00:00:25,684 --> 00:00:29,105
Have you heard of the National
Transportation Safety Board?

14
00:00:29,240 --> 00:00:32,444
That's your secretary
unlawfully gathering evidence,

15
00:00:32,613 --> 00:00:36,284
which means there will be
no settlement of any kind.

16
00:00:36,452 --> 00:00:39,506
And tomorrow, I'm sending this
to the district attorney.

17
00:00:39,625 --> 00:00:42,939
Your whole story about how
Louis got his name on the door

18
00:00:42,963 --> 00:00:44,014
is bullshit.

19
00:00:44,132 --> 00:00:45,266
Jeff.

20
00:00:45,385 --> 00:00:48,355
It's over, Jessica.

21
00:00:48,473 --> 00:00:49,473
We're done.

22
00:00:56,152 --> 00:01:00,018
I can't believe you actually
got them to admit what they did.

23
00:01:00,043 --> 00:01:02,022
You better believe it,
because it's happening,

24
00:01:02,046 --> 00:01:05,417
and it wouldn't be
happening without you.

25
00:01:05,551 --> 00:01:07,397
You mean without me
being greedy.

26
00:01:07,422 --> 00:01:09,006
Joe, that's not
what I was gonna say.

27
00:01:09,174 --> 00:01:11,009
No, no, no, I know that
you don't think I care

28
00:01:11,177 --> 00:01:13,897
about these people, but I do.

29
00:01:14,015 --> 00:01:15,349
But I'm also a working stiff.

30
00:01:15,518 --> 00:01:18,164
I go paycheck to paycheck
for my whole life,

31
00:01:18,189 --> 00:01:19,356
and then a thing like this...

32
00:01:19,492 --> 00:01:21,327
Could turn your
whole life around.

33
00:01:23,415 --> 00:01:26,034
Guy like you might not be
able to understand that.

34
00:01:27,506 --> 00:01:29,101
I understand.

35
00:01:29,125 --> 00:01:30,937
So it's a done deal?

36
00:01:30,961 --> 00:01:32,523
Might take a few
days to finalize,

37
00:01:32,547 --> 00:01:34,242
but yeah.

38
00:01:34,266 --> 00:01:35,945
It's happening.

39
00:01:35,970 --> 00:01:37,972
You have my word.

40
00:01:38,107 --> 00:01:39,390
You're all right, Mr. Ross.

41
00:01:45,569 --> 00:01:47,932
Harvey, you know the only
times you've been here at night

42
00:01:47,957 --> 00:01:49,277
were the god-awful
dinner party...

43
00:01:49,409 --> 00:01:50,409
And the other time.

44
00:01:50,411 --> 00:01:51,879
Well, this isn't that.

45
00:01:51,997 --> 00:01:53,247
I want to know why Liberty Rail

46
00:01:53,383 --> 00:01:55,278
has a video of you
in their file room.

47
00:01:55,302 --> 00:01:56,469
What are you talking about?

48
00:01:56,588 --> 00:01:58,189
I'm talking the fact
that our smoking gun

49
00:01:58,307 --> 00:01:59,424
just became inadmissible.

50
00:01:59,593 --> 00:02:01,314
- Harvey...
- How'd you get those documents?

51
00:02:01,396 --> 00:02:03,148
Are you asking
if I did something illegal?

52
00:02:03,265 --> 00:02:04,409
Because I didn't.

53
00:02:04,434 --> 00:02:05,554
Well, they went to the D.A.,

54
00:02:05,570 --> 00:02:07,132
which means they think you did,

55
00:02:07,156 --> 00:02:08,857
so I'm gonna ask you
one more time,

56
00:02:08,992 --> 00:02:10,587
how did you get
in their file room?

57
00:02:10,611 --> 00:02:12,530
By walking through the
door they buzzed open.

58
00:02:12,665 --> 00:02:14,009
And why would they do that?

59
00:02:14,034 --> 00:02:15,117
Because I'm me.

60
00:02:15,253 --> 00:02:16,955
What the hell does that mean?

61
00:02:17,089 --> 00:02:19,101
It means that I led
the woman to believe

62
00:02:19,125 --> 00:02:20,646
that I was an official
from Washington.

63
00:02:20,762 --> 00:02:22,129
Led them to believe it,

64
00:02:22,298 --> 00:02:23,632
or flat out told them?

65
00:02:23,767 --> 00:02:25,436
Because one kills our case

66
00:02:25,554 --> 00:02:29,954
and the other puts you
in a world of shit.

67
00:02:29,978 --> 00:02:31,172
Harvey, I'm not an idiot,

68
00:02:31,197 --> 00:02:33,009
and I don't appreciate
being treated like one.

69
00:02:33,033 --> 00:02:35,202
I told you I didn't do
anything illegal, and I didn't.

70
00:02:35,320 --> 00:02:36,537
Not an idiot?

71
00:02:36,656 --> 00:02:38,777
What the hell were you doing
there in the first place?

72
00:02:38,792 --> 00:02:40,438
- Harvey.
- It was Mike's idea, wasn't it?

73
00:02:40,462 --> 00:02:44,000
No, he didn't even
know about it.

74
00:02:44,135 --> 00:02:45,670
- Where are you going?
- To see Mike.

75
00:02:45,804 --> 00:02:47,733
I told you, he didn't even
know I was going to do it.

76
00:02:47,757 --> 00:02:50,404
I don't care, because he
sure as hell knew after.

77
00:02:50,429 --> 00:02:51,596
Let's go.

78
00:03:01,998 --> 00:03:05,536
I am so proud of you.

79
00:03:05,705 --> 00:03:08,401
I've done that before.

80
00:03:08,425 --> 00:03:11,607
I'm not talking about that.

81
00:03:11,632 --> 00:03:13,100
I'm talking about your case.

82
00:03:13,217 --> 00:03:14,361
Ah.

83
00:03:14,386 --> 00:03:16,032
You believed in it,
and you fought for it,

84
00:03:16,056 --> 00:03:19,226
and I... I love that about you.

85
00:03:19,361 --> 00:03:23,543
And I love that you
love that about me.

86
00:03:23,568 --> 00:03:26,071
When a person gives you
a compliment like that,

87
00:03:26,206 --> 00:03:28,075
you're supposed
to give one back.

88
00:03:28,242 --> 00:03:29,459
But I just did.

89
00:03:29,578 --> 00:03:31,474
I said that you love
that I love that about me.

90
00:03:31,498 --> 00:03:32,725
And what if I said I love
that you love that I love that

91
00:03:32,750 --> 00:03:34,395
about you?

92
00:03:34,419 --> 00:03:35,586
How would that make you feel?

93
00:03:35,755 --> 00:03:38,141
So tired.

94
00:03:38,259 --> 00:03:41,430
Well, we both know
why you're so tired.

95
00:03:41,565 --> 00:03:43,066
Yeah, because I'm so good.

96
00:03:43,185 --> 00:03:44,602
Don't you love that about me?

97
00:03:52,701 --> 00:03:54,763
You knew Donna bullshitted
her way into that company

98
00:03:54,788 --> 00:03:57,351
and you let us use
those work orders?

99
00:03:57,375 --> 00:03:58,508
How did you find out?

100
00:03:58,627 --> 00:03:59,961
It doesn't matter
how I found out.

101
00:04:00,130 --> 00:04:01,324
Answer my question.

102
00:04:01,349 --> 00:04:03,077
Yes, I knew, but what
difference does it make? We won.

103
00:04:03,101 --> 00:04:04,362
We didn't win,

104
00:04:04,387 --> 00:04:07,190
because Evan Smith has video
of Donna in their offices.

105
00:04:07,308 --> 00:04:08,586
- What?
- She know about this too?

106
00:04:08,611 --> 00:04:10,340
Harvey, she's just
trying to strong-arm us.

107
00:04:10,364 --> 00:04:11,480
Are you listening to me?

108
00:04:11,649 --> 00:04:13,317
They have the opposing
counsel's secretary

109
00:04:13,452 --> 00:04:15,320
poking around
in their goddamn file room.

110
00:04:15,489 --> 00:04:17,458
If I were the D.A.,
I'd sure as hell look into it.

111
00:04:17,576 --> 00:04:19,355
- The D.A.?
- Yeah, the D.A.

112
00:04:19,380 --> 00:04:20,663
Harvey, they let her in.

113
00:04:20,799 --> 00:04:22,644
According to you,
but they're gonna claim fraud

114
00:04:22,668 --> 00:04:24,387
or theft
or any number of things.

115
00:04:24,504 --> 00:04:26,139
What are you gonna do?

116
00:04:26,257 --> 00:04:28,620
I'm making a deal to drop this
case, that's what I'm gonna do,

117
00:04:28,645 --> 00:04:30,123
and you're gonna file
the paperwork as soon as I do.

118
00:04:30,147 --> 00:04:31,507
So you're just gonna
let this woman

119
00:04:31,516 --> 00:04:32,744
blackmail you without a fight?

120
00:04:32,769 --> 00:04:34,079
You're damn right I am.

121
00:04:34,104 --> 00:04:35,298
Harvey, we can still
win this case and clear...

122
00:04:35,323 --> 00:04:36,584
There is no case,

123
00:04:36,608 --> 00:04:38,420
and I wouldn't give a shit
about it if there was.

124
00:04:38,445 --> 00:04:39,695
I care about Donna.

125
00:04:39,831 --> 00:04:40,758
And you think I don't?

126
00:04:40,782 --> 00:04:41,809
You care so much for her?

127
00:04:41,834 --> 00:04:43,034
Then draw up those papers,

128
00:04:43,169 --> 00:04:45,371
because I'm letting
Evan know it's over.

129
00:04:47,677 --> 00:04:51,348
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪

130
00:04:51,467 --> 00:04:54,638
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪

131
00:04:54,772 --> 00:04:58,060
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪

132
00:04:58,194 --> 00:05:01,315
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪

133
00:05:01,451 --> 00:05:04,455
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪

134
00:05:04,572 --> 00:05:08,494
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪

135
00:05:08,629 --> 00:05:09,963
♪ All right ♪

136
00:05:09,965 --> 00:05:11,502
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪

137
00:05:11,503 --> 00:05:15,505
♪ Suits 4x15 ♪ Intent Original
Air Date on February 25, 2015

138
00:05:15,507 --> 00:05:16,757
♪ The greenback boogie ♪

139
00:05:16,782 --> 00:05:23,286
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man.

140
00:05:28,158 --> 00:05:29,586
What are you doing here?

141
00:05:29,611 --> 00:05:30,944
We have a situation.

142
00:05:31,113 --> 00:05:33,249
Is the fate of the firm
hanging in the balance?

143
00:05:33,367 --> 00:05:35,620
- No...
- Then I don't give a shit.

144
00:05:36,756 --> 00:05:38,090
You told Malone, didn't you?

145
00:05:41,130 --> 00:05:43,266
I didn't get a chance
to tell him,

146
00:05:43,384 --> 00:05:44,852
because he had already
figured out

147
00:05:44,970 --> 00:05:46,855
that I had been lying to him
this whole time.

148
00:05:48,192 --> 00:05:51,146
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, you're sorry.

149
00:05:51,281 --> 00:05:53,162
This morning I thought
I was going away with him

150
00:05:53,285 --> 00:05:54,679
for two weeks.

151
00:05:54,704 --> 00:05:56,131
Now I don't know if I'm ever
gonna see him again.

152
00:05:56,156 --> 00:05:57,573
He quit?

153
00:05:57,692 --> 00:06:00,128
He didn't get around
to giving me his career plans.

154
00:06:00,229 --> 00:06:02,058
You want me to talk to him
for you?

155
00:06:02,083 --> 00:06:05,003
No, this is my mess.

156
00:06:05,138 --> 00:06:06,866
And I will take care
of it myself.

157
00:06:06,890 --> 00:06:08,170
You can take care of it
tomorrow.

158
00:06:08,176 --> 00:06:10,178
Right now,
I'm making you a drink.

159
00:06:16,824 --> 00:06:19,170
Zipadeedoodah or Grab My Sack?

160
00:06:19,194 --> 00:06:20,673
- What?
- Messenger service.

161
00:06:20,698 --> 00:06:21,725
Which one do we use?

162
00:06:21,749 --> 00:06:22,865
- I-I...
- You know what?

163
00:06:23,001 --> 00:06:24,596
Use whoever you want.
Just take care of it.

164
00:06:24,620 --> 00:06:26,221
Louis, don't you have
your own secretary?

165
00:06:26,340 --> 00:06:28,208
Oh, you mean Norma,
who I can't find anywhere,

166
00:06:28,344 --> 00:06:29,905
who is probably taking
the day off again?

167
00:06:29,929 --> 00:06:32,048
Last year, she tried to get
Arbor Day off,

168
00:06:32,183 --> 00:06:34,624
and I told her to blow a goddamn
tree and get her ass in here.

169
00:06:34,637 --> 00:06:35,721
You know what, Louis?

170
00:06:35,856 --> 00:06:38,559
Norma has taken 4 days off
in the last 36 years.

171
00:06:38,694 --> 00:06:40,215
Why don't you back
the hell off of her.

172
00:06:40,230 --> 00:06:41,732
What the hell is the matter
with you?

173
00:06:41,866 --> 00:06:43,901
You usually jump on
the Norma bashing train

174
00:06:44,070 --> 00:06:45,989
like a hobo in a 1940s
action movie.

175
00:06:46,123 --> 00:06:48,125
- I'm sorry; I just...
- What?

176
00:06:50,748 --> 00:06:52,583
I bullshitted my way
into Liberty Rail

177
00:06:52,718 --> 00:06:53,812
to get some documents.

178
00:06:53,836 --> 00:06:54,919
They caught me on video,

179
00:06:55,055 --> 00:06:56,816
and now they're threatening
to press charges.

180
00:07:01,098 --> 00:07:02,209
You're not saying anything.

181
00:07:02,234 --> 00:07:04,102
It's nothing. It's fine.

182
00:07:05,239 --> 00:07:06,917
Then why did you look
so concerned?

183
00:07:06,941 --> 00:07:09,194
I was concerned,
but they're threatening charges,

184
00:07:09,329 --> 00:07:10,746
which means they want something,

185
00:07:10,865 --> 00:07:12,977
and I know Harvey,
and whatever it is they want,

186
00:07:13,002 --> 00:07:14,598
he'll find a way
to give it to him.

187
00:07:14,622 --> 00:07:16,173
Okay.

188
00:07:16,291 --> 00:07:18,320
Thanks, Louis.

189
00:07:18,344 --> 00:07:19,511
I'll take care of your stuff.

190
00:07:19,630 --> 00:07:21,074
No, no.
You have enough on your mind.

191
00:07:21,099 --> 00:07:23,551
I'll take care of it myself.

192
00:07:27,310 --> 00:07:30,675
Mr. Specter, don't tell me.

193
00:07:30,699 --> 00:07:33,068
You're here to talk
about Ms. Paulsen.

194
00:07:33,203 --> 00:07:35,122
I'm here to tell you
you made your point.

195
00:07:35,240 --> 00:07:36,852
And what point is that?

196
00:07:36,876 --> 00:07:38,688
If you drop any charges
against Donna,

197
00:07:38,712 --> 00:07:40,139
we'll drop the lawsuit
against you.

198
00:07:40,164 --> 00:07:42,216
Well, that's not
a very even trade.

199
00:07:42,335 --> 00:07:45,817
I'm giving your client the
chance to get away with murder.

200
00:07:45,841 --> 00:07:48,176
Last I checked, my client wasn't
being charged with murder,

201
00:07:48,312 --> 00:07:49,847
and I don't need you
to drop your suit,

202
00:07:49,981 --> 00:07:51,064
because you have no case.

203
00:07:51,183 --> 00:07:52,233
No case?

204
00:07:52,352 --> 00:07:54,915
Your client put a faulty train
on those tracks,

205
00:07:54,940 --> 00:07:57,222
people died, and they knew
it could happen the whole time.

206
00:07:57,243 --> 00:07:58,304
And you have no proof.

207
00:07:58,329 --> 00:07:59,673
And where I come from,

208
00:07:59,698 --> 00:08:01,750
you cut a deal with me
to make sure I stop looking.

209
00:08:01,868 --> 00:08:04,597
Then I guess we come
from different places,

210
00:08:04,622 --> 00:08:06,863
because I didn't give that video
to the district attorney

211
00:08:06,877 --> 00:08:08,906
to leverage you into a deal.

212
00:08:08,930 --> 00:08:11,776
I did it to blow you out
of the water.

213
00:08:11,801 --> 00:08:14,053
This is a person's life.

214
00:08:14,222 --> 00:08:16,057
Maybe you should have
thought of that

215
00:08:16,192 --> 00:08:18,644
before you sent her
to rob my client.

216
00:08:18,780 --> 00:08:22,762
Evan, I care about this woman.

217
00:08:22,787 --> 00:08:24,097
Look, I understand.

218
00:08:24,122 --> 00:08:26,719
She's probably worked for you
for a long time.

219
00:08:26,744 --> 00:08:28,389
Maybe you sleep together
once in a while.

220
00:08:28,413 --> 00:08:30,749
But my job is to defend
my client

221
00:08:30,884 --> 00:08:33,063
to the best of my abilities,

222
00:08:33,087 --> 00:08:36,008
and that's exactly what
I'm going to do.

223
00:08:49,783 --> 00:08:51,762
Holy shit.

224
00:08:51,786 --> 00:08:54,840
You can't possible have
a check already.

225
00:08:54,958 --> 00:08:58,796
I don't have a check, Joe.

226
00:08:58,965 --> 00:09:00,325
We have to drop the case.

227
00:09:00,350 --> 00:09:01,778
What the hell are you
talking about?

228
00:09:01,803 --> 00:09:02,803
We had drinks last night.

229
00:09:02,938 --> 00:09:04,607
Yeah, we also had proof
last night,

230
00:09:04,724 --> 00:09:05,808
and now we don't.

231
00:09:05,943 --> 00:09:07,310
- Why not?
- It's complicated.

232
00:09:07,446 --> 00:09:09,114
You know,
it's a lot of legal rigmarole...

233
00:09:09,232 --> 00:09:10,760
- Hey, don't talk down to me.
- I'm not talking down to you.

234
00:09:10,784 --> 00:09:12,064
But I'm also
not gonna stand here

235
00:09:12,070 --> 00:09:13,347
and explain civil procedure.

236
00:09:13,372 --> 00:09:15,157
Maybe I don't understand
civil procedure,

237
00:09:15,292 --> 00:09:18,329
but I know enough to understand
when something doesn't add up.

238
00:09:18,464 --> 00:09:20,332
We got the evidence
the wrong way.

239
00:09:20,468 --> 00:09:21,812
Well, get it the right way.

240
00:09:21,837 --> 00:09:22,837
Subpoena it or something.

241
00:09:22,839 --> 00:09:24,149
I can't.

242
00:09:24,173 --> 00:09:25,725
What do you mean, you can't?

243
00:09:25,844 --> 00:09:27,244
That money was gonna
change my life.

244
00:09:27,263 --> 00:09:28,992
And if you want to go to
a different law firm,

245
00:09:29,016 --> 00:09:30,376
I understand.

246
00:09:30,401 --> 00:09:33,237
You know as well as I do nobody
else is gonna take this case.

247
00:09:33,356 --> 00:09:35,886
You told me you cared
about these people.

248
00:09:35,911 --> 00:09:37,255
You gave me your word.

249
00:09:37,280 --> 00:09:40,033
Yeah, and I wish I could
keep it.

250
00:09:40,201 --> 00:09:42,347
I want those bastards
as much as you want this money,

251
00:09:42,371 --> 00:09:43,371
but I've got no proof,

252
00:09:43,507 --> 00:09:44,901
and you're not
a credible witness.

253
00:09:44,926 --> 00:09:46,738
- Oh, that bullshit again.
- That's not bullshit.

254
00:09:46,762 --> 00:09:48,681
If you had been straight with me
from day one,

255
00:09:48,798 --> 00:09:50,350
we wouldn't even be in
this mess.

256
00:09:52,388 --> 00:09:54,691
How much did they give you
to dump the case?

257
00:09:55,810 --> 00:09:56,871
Had to be something.

258
00:09:56,896 --> 00:09:58,781
Otherwise,
you wouldn't sell me out.

259
00:10:03,123 --> 00:10:04,718
I'm sorry, Joe. It's over.

260
00:10:04,743 --> 00:10:09,249
You're sorry?

261
00:10:16,145 --> 00:10:19,065
Jessica.

262
00:10:19,183 --> 00:10:20,183
Do you need something?

263
00:10:20,185 --> 00:10:22,437
I came by earlier,
and you weren't in.

264
00:10:22,573 --> 00:10:24,585
I had a meeting, and I
really didn't think you wanted

265
00:10:24,609 --> 00:10:26,088
to be looped in on my schedule.

266
00:10:26,112 --> 00:10:27,863
I don't,
and I'm not checking up on you.

267
00:10:27,999 --> 00:10:30,451
I just didn't know if you
were coming in.

268
00:10:30,586 --> 00:10:33,149
You mean you weren't sure
if I was ever coming in again.

269
00:10:33,174 --> 00:10:35,376
You wouldn't be the first person
to leave a job

270
00:10:35,511 --> 00:10:36,795
for personal reasons.

271
00:10:36,930 --> 00:10:38,799
It sounds to me like you have
an agenda.

272
00:10:40,436 --> 00:10:42,271
- I don't.
- Well, that's a first.

273
00:10:44,026 --> 00:10:46,361
Are you saying that I came here
to push you out?

274
00:10:46,479 --> 00:10:49,042
I'm saying that I've never known
you not to know what you want.

275
00:10:49,067 --> 00:10:50,819
What I want is to talk about us,

276
00:10:50,953 --> 00:10:52,347
but you don't seem to want
to do that,

277
00:10:52,372 --> 00:10:56,244
so I'm focusing on this.

278
00:10:56,379 --> 00:10:57,998
I'm not resigning
my senior partnership

279
00:10:58,132 --> 00:10:59,967
the day after
what happened happened,

280
00:11:00,086 --> 00:11:01,386
if that's what you're asking.

281
00:11:01,505 --> 00:11:04,976
I'm asking if you plan
to resign it at all.

282
00:11:05,094 --> 00:11:07,376
And I can't tell you that
right now, because I don't know.

283
00:11:07,482 --> 00:11:08,682
Well, when will you know?

284
00:11:08,851 --> 00:11:10,853
Look, Jessica,
you're the managing partner,

285
00:11:11,021 --> 00:11:13,273
so if you want to push me out,
push me out,

286
00:11:13,408 --> 00:11:15,244
but if you're asking me
what I want to do,

287
00:11:15,361 --> 00:11:17,747
I'm telling you
that I haven't decided.

288
00:11:28,885 --> 00:11:29,945
How did it go?

289
00:11:29,969 --> 00:11:31,804
Never mind how it went.

290
00:11:31,940 --> 00:11:33,725
Where's Mike.
Did he file those papers?

291
00:11:33,860 --> 00:11:35,381
I-I-I don't know.
He's not even in yet.

292
00:11:35,395 --> 00:11:37,007
Well, you tell him
not to file anything,

293
00:11:37,031 --> 00:11:38,867
and you tell him to do
whatever he has to

294
00:11:38,985 --> 00:11:40,046
to stick it to that woman.

295
00:11:40,070 --> 00:11:41,214
Why?

296
00:11:41,239 --> 00:11:42,874
Because it didn't work.

297
00:11:43,993 --> 00:11:45,244
What didn't work?

298
00:11:45,379 --> 00:11:48,383
I tried to make a deal with Evan
to trade the case.

299
00:11:48,501 --> 00:11:50,920
You mean you offered to drop
the case in exchange for me.

300
00:11:51,089 --> 00:11:52,172
Yes.

301
00:11:54,060 --> 00:11:55,071
And now what are we gonna do?

302
00:11:55,096 --> 00:11:56,290
You're not gonna do anything.

303
00:11:56,315 --> 00:11:57,793
I'm gonna do whatever I have to

304
00:11:57,817 --> 00:11:59,412
to get Terrance Wolf
to back off.

305
00:11:59,436 --> 00:12:02,834
Harvey, there's no way the D.A.
handles a case like this himself

306
00:12:02,858 --> 00:12:04,192
just because I work for you.

307
00:12:04,328 --> 00:12:06,340
Whether he handles it himself
or not doesn't matter,

308
00:12:06,365 --> 00:12:08,784
because this case won't even
exist in another hour.

309
00:12:16,339 --> 00:12:17,540
How did it go?

310
00:12:17,707 --> 00:12:19,041
I just told a man
that everything

311
00:12:19,178 --> 00:12:20,188
I promised him was bullshit.

312
00:12:20,212 --> 00:12:21,272
How do you think it went?

313
00:12:21,297 --> 00:12:22,441
Oh, Mike, I'm sorry.

314
00:12:22,466 --> 00:12:25,387
Oh, you should have seen
his face.

315
00:12:25,521 --> 00:12:27,116
That money was gonna change
his life,

316
00:12:27,140 --> 00:12:29,381
and then I dangled it in front
of him and ripped it away.

317
00:12:29,395 --> 00:12:30,622
Yeah, but it's not your fault.

318
00:12:30,646 --> 00:12:32,448
You did everything you could.

319
00:12:32,567 --> 00:12:34,035
He accused me of selling out.

320
00:12:34,152 --> 00:12:35,232
You know you didn't do that.

321
00:12:35,238 --> 00:12:36,382
Didn't I?

322
00:12:36,406 --> 00:12:37,433
We gave up because...

323
00:12:37,458 --> 00:12:38,993
Of me?

324
00:12:42,082 --> 00:12:43,276
That's not what I was gonna say.

325
00:12:43,301 --> 00:12:44,301
Yeah, it was.

326
00:12:44,420 --> 00:12:45,901
No, I was gonna say
because of Harvey.

327
00:12:45,922 --> 00:12:47,033
What are you talking about?

328
00:12:47,058 --> 00:12:48,570
Harvey never wanted
to take this case,

329
00:12:48,594 --> 00:12:50,122
so he put a clock on it
to get me to drop it.

330
00:12:50,146 --> 00:12:51,658
That's why we're where we are
right now.

331
00:12:51,682 --> 00:12:53,434
Listen to me;
Harvey is out there right now

332
00:12:53,568 --> 00:12:55,070
busting his ass
to fix everything.

333
00:12:55,187 --> 00:12:56,498
No, Donna.

334
00:12:56,523 --> 00:12:58,419
He doesn't give a shit about
this case, and he never did.

335
00:12:58,444 --> 00:13:00,089
Then why did he send me here
to tell you to do

336
00:13:00,113 --> 00:13:02,198
everything you can to stick it
to Evan Smith?

337
00:13:02,333 --> 00:13:04,262
She didn't take the deal,
did she?

338
00:13:04,287 --> 00:13:06,289
No, she didn't.

339
00:13:06,423 --> 00:13:07,484
Donna, I'm sorry.

340
00:13:07,509 --> 00:13:09,154
I didn't realize
that you were still...

341
00:13:09,178 --> 00:13:10,295
On the hot seat?

342
00:13:10,430 --> 00:13:13,495
Like I said, Harvey's
busting his ass to fix it,

343
00:13:13,519 --> 00:13:15,387
which means he's gonna fix it.

344
00:13:16,641 --> 00:13:18,976
Now, finish what we started
and figure out a way

345
00:13:19,112 --> 00:13:22,316
to win this case.

346
00:13:27,993 --> 00:13:30,162
Harvey Specter.

347
00:13:30,298 --> 00:13:31,976
I was wondering when you
would show up.

348
00:13:32,000 --> 00:13:33,311
That's funny;
I was wondering why

349
00:13:33,336 --> 00:13:34,730
you never sent me
a Christmas card.

350
00:13:34,755 --> 00:13:36,367
Ha-ha.

351
00:13:36,391 --> 00:13:37,892
You don't seem
the least bit worried

352
00:13:38,010 --> 00:13:40,229
about the pending charges
against your secretary.

353
00:13:40,348 --> 00:13:42,183
I'm not,
because she did nothing wrong.

354
00:13:42,318 --> 00:13:43,518
Well, you know what I think?

355
00:13:43,653 --> 00:13:46,189
I think you wouldn't be here
if she did nothing wrong.

356
00:13:46,325 --> 00:13:48,443
Listen to me.
She didn't steal anything.

357
00:13:48,578 --> 00:13:51,224
She got those documents by
convincing them to let her in,

358
00:13:51,249 --> 00:13:52,249
and that is not a crime.

359
00:13:52,251 --> 00:13:54,063
And the last time
you were in my office,

360
00:13:54,087 --> 00:13:57,102
you told me you hadn't committed
a crime to get the job done.

361
00:13:57,126 --> 00:13:59,011
After I told you
you had an innocent man,

362
00:13:59,130 --> 00:14:02,277
and all you cared about
was procedure.

363
00:14:02,301 --> 00:14:04,270
All I cared about was the law.

364
00:14:04,388 --> 00:14:06,890
Well, if you're so concerned
with people breaking the law,

365
00:14:07,026 --> 00:14:08,755
why don't you take a look
at those documents?

366
00:14:08,779 --> 00:14:11,565
Because they prove Liberty Rail
actually committed a crime,

367
00:14:11,700 --> 00:14:13,621
unlike Donna, whose only crime
is working for me.

368
00:14:13,738 --> 00:14:15,717
I'm not investigating her
for working for you.

369
00:14:15,741 --> 00:14:18,076
I'm investigating her
for felony fraud.

370
00:14:18,212 --> 00:14:20,214
What the hell are you
talking about?

371
00:14:22,669 --> 00:14:26,424
The woman that let her in
swears your secretary told her

372
00:14:26,559 --> 00:14:29,490
she was with the National
Transportation Safety Board.

373
00:14:29,514 --> 00:14:31,600
That's a federal agency,

374
00:14:31,734 --> 00:14:34,938
which makes what she did
not a trick.

375
00:14:35,107 --> 00:14:37,660
It makes it felony fraud.

376
00:14:42,286 --> 00:14:44,171
My office. Now.

377
00:14:47,177 --> 00:14:49,546
Close the door.

378
00:14:49,682 --> 00:14:50,609
Harvey, what happened?

379
00:14:50,633 --> 00:14:52,050
What happened is,
you lied to me.

380
00:14:52,185 --> 00:14:53,329
What are you talking about?

381
00:14:53,354 --> 00:14:55,356
You told their secretary
you were with the NTSB?

382
00:14:55,475 --> 00:14:58,311
- That's not what I said.
- Bullshit.

383
00:14:58,447 --> 00:14:59,313
I know when I've been lied to.

384
00:14:59,448 --> 00:15:00,481
Come clean right now.

385
00:15:00,616 --> 00:15:01,983
I...

386
00:15:02,119 --> 00:15:04,655
- Right the hell now.
- I never said I was with them.

387
00:15:04,790 --> 00:15:06,070
I said, "Have you ever heard of"

388
00:15:06,159 --> 00:15:08,161
the National Transportation
Safety Board?

389
00:15:08,297 --> 00:15:09,524
How is that any different?

390
00:15:09,548 --> 00:15:11,383
- I'm sorry, I...
- You're sorry?

391
00:15:11,502 --> 00:15:13,703
Harvey, I swear I didn't know
that that made it a crime.

392
00:15:13,805 --> 00:15:15,367
You knew when I point-blank
asked you,

393
00:15:15,391 --> 00:15:17,009
and you lied to me about it.

394
00:15:17,145 --> 00:15:19,574
Well, I thought that you
would take care of it.

395
00:15:19,598 --> 00:15:22,128
How can I take care of it if you
don't tell me the goddamn truth?

396
00:15:22,153 --> 00:15:24,165
Do you think that I didn't want
to tell you the truth?

397
00:15:24,190 --> 00:15:26,659
- Then why didn't you?
- Because I was ashamed.

398
00:15:28,413 --> 00:15:30,532
I know that it sounds stupid,

399
00:15:30,701 --> 00:15:33,203
but you and Mike and everyone
pull these rabbits

400
00:15:33,372 --> 00:15:35,401
out of your hats all the time,
and I just sit outside,

401
00:15:35,425 --> 00:15:37,544
and I answer the phones.

402
00:15:37,713 --> 00:15:41,184
And then I got those documents,
and people said I saved the day.

403
00:15:41,302 --> 00:15:43,521
And the next thing I knew,
you were on my doorstep

404
00:15:43,639 --> 00:15:45,525
coming at me like I was
some sort of criminal,

405
00:15:45,642 --> 00:15:49,982
and I panicked, and I lied.

406
00:15:50,116 --> 00:15:52,462
- Donna...
- I'm sorry, Harvey.

407
00:15:52,487 --> 00:15:54,907
I know you are,
but this just got

408
00:15:55,042 --> 00:15:57,127
1,000 times harder for me
to get out of.

409
00:15:58,714 --> 00:16:00,276
You mean for you
to get me out of.

410
00:16:00,300 --> 00:16:02,780
Donna, you of all people
should understand by now

411
00:16:02,805 --> 00:16:04,256
that to me
they're the same thing.

412
00:16:14,241 --> 00:16:15,943
What are you doing here?

413
00:16:16,110 --> 00:16:18,139
I went to see you at work.
They said you called in sick.

414
00:16:18,164 --> 00:16:19,810
I said, what are you doing here?

415
00:16:19,834 --> 00:16:22,003
I wanted to tell you
the good news.

416
00:16:22,121 --> 00:16:23,600
I'm not dropping your case
after all.

417
00:16:23,624 --> 00:16:25,519
Good for you.

418
00:16:25,543 --> 00:16:27,462
Hey, Joe.

419
00:16:27,597 --> 00:16:29,158
I know you've been
jerked around,

420
00:16:29,182 --> 00:16:31,468
but things are gonna change.

421
00:16:31,604 --> 00:16:32,971
Gonna change? Really?

422
00:16:33,139 --> 00:16:35,692
I thought you said you got
the evidence in the wrong way.

423
00:16:35,811 --> 00:16:38,173
Well, and you said we should
get it in the right way,

424
00:16:38,198 --> 00:16:39,984
so that's exactly
what we're gonna do.

425
00:16:40,118 --> 00:16:42,654
Like I said, good for you, but
you're not gonna do it with me.

426
00:16:42,823 --> 00:16:44,458
Hey, Joe.

427
00:16:44,575 --> 00:16:47,412
I can't subpoena those records
without the legitimate client.

428
00:16:47,547 --> 00:16:50,561
I have no basis and no standing
to move forward if I did.

429
00:16:50,585 --> 00:16:54,057
Oh, now you have time to explain
procedure to me, right?

430
00:16:54,175 --> 00:16:56,594
Okay, fine. I deserved that.

431
00:16:56,730 --> 00:16:59,566
But, Joe, this case cannot
move forward without you.

432
00:16:59,685 --> 00:17:03,523
You should have thought of that
before you cut me loose.

433
00:17:03,658 --> 00:17:05,025
They got to you, didn't they?

434
00:17:06,779 --> 00:17:08,558
They gave you a few dollars
to shut you up,

435
00:17:08,583 --> 00:17:10,085
and then they sealed
the agreement

436
00:17:10,202 --> 00:17:11,396
with no admission of guilt.

437
00:17:11,421 --> 00:17:12,565
You know what?

438
00:17:12,590 --> 00:17:14,736
I can't comment on that,
and you know why,

439
00:17:14,760 --> 00:17:16,712
but let's get
one thing straight.

440
00:17:16,846 --> 00:17:19,265
They didn't shut me up; You did.

441
00:17:19,384 --> 00:17:20,528
And if I took anything,

442
00:17:20,553 --> 00:17:22,221
it was because I had
no other choice.

443
00:17:22,356 --> 00:17:23,700
Joe, listen to me.

444
00:17:23,725 --> 00:17:25,871
If the check hasn't cleared,
we can still get out of it.

445
00:17:25,896 --> 00:17:27,397
Don't come by here anymore.

446
00:17:28,784 --> 00:17:31,036
So much for really caring
about those people.

447
00:17:33,575 --> 00:17:35,077
Go to hell.

448
00:17:43,338 --> 00:17:45,100
I thought nobody puts baby
in the corner.

449
00:17:45,124 --> 00:17:46,291
Since when am I "baby"?

450
00:17:46,426 --> 00:17:47,843
Since you're sitting
in the corner.

451
00:17:47,962 --> 00:17:49,774
You're usually a power table
kind of girl.

452
00:17:49,798 --> 00:17:52,101
Well, I'm not tonight.

453
00:17:53,355 --> 00:17:55,190
Jessica, what's going on?

454
00:17:56,560 --> 00:17:58,979
It's over between me and Jeff.

455
00:17:59,148 --> 00:18:00,700
What? What happened?

456
00:18:00,817 --> 00:18:02,452
It's not important.

457
00:18:02,570 --> 00:18:04,989
One day the man is calling me
about taking you to Paris,

458
00:18:05,158 --> 00:18:06,292
and the next it's over,

459
00:18:06,410 --> 00:18:08,139
and the reason for all that
isn't important?

460
00:18:08,163 --> 00:18:09,474
No, it isn't, because right now,

461
00:18:09,499 --> 00:18:11,540
I have to decide whether
he should stay at the firm.

462
00:18:11,552 --> 00:18:13,364
Well, then I'd say the reason
that you broke up is important.

463
00:18:13,389 --> 00:18:14,984
And I don't want to get into it
right now,

464
00:18:15,008 --> 00:18:16,870
because it's not going
to change.

465
00:18:16,894 --> 00:18:20,349
Wow, heard that before.

466
00:18:20,483 --> 00:18:24,438
Leah, I'm not like Dad,
and I'm tired of hearing it.

467
00:18:24,574 --> 00:18:26,442
I know you always say
you're not like him,

468
00:18:26,595 --> 00:18:29,030
but here you are scrubbing up
for the next surgery

469
00:18:29,165 --> 00:18:31,060
instead of fighting for the man
that you love.

470
00:18:31,085 --> 00:18:33,037
You know what?

471
00:18:33,172 --> 00:18:36,770
Most sisters would say,
"I'm sorry, Jessica,"

472
00:18:36,795 --> 00:18:38,012
and then give me a hug.

473
00:18:38,131 --> 00:18:40,216
Jessica, I am sorry
that you're hurting,

474
00:18:40,384 --> 00:18:41,865
and if you want something
sugarcoated,

475
00:18:41,886 --> 00:18:44,940
I'll order you dessert, but that
is not how we show support.

476
00:18:45,058 --> 00:18:47,277
You're right.

477
00:18:47,396 --> 00:18:52,430
We show it by telling each other
what we think, so...

478
00:18:52,455 --> 00:18:55,074
And what I think is,

479
00:18:55,210 --> 00:18:57,996
two days ago,
this man loved you.

480
00:18:58,131 --> 00:19:00,417
So unless you cheated on him,
stole from him,

481
00:19:00,551 --> 00:19:04,139
or killed somebody,
it seems to me the two of you

482
00:19:04,258 --> 00:19:06,394
should be able to get past
whatever it is you did do.

483
00:19:13,940 --> 00:19:16,026
Joe Henderson backed out.

484
00:19:18,114 --> 00:19:21,285
Harvey, did you hear me?

485
00:19:21,421 --> 00:19:23,122
They paid him off.
We have no case anymore.

486
00:19:23,290 --> 00:19:25,376
And right now,
I have a bigger problem.

487
00:19:25,510 --> 00:19:26,437
Donna lied.

488
00:19:26,462 --> 00:19:28,047
What do you mean, she lied?

489
00:19:28,181 --> 00:19:30,801
I mean she didn't just bullshit
her way into that file room.

490
00:19:30,936 --> 00:19:33,272
She used the words "National
Transportation Safety Board."

491
00:19:33,374 --> 00:19:34,808
In what context?

492
00:19:34,943 --> 00:19:37,539
In the context of committing
a crime to help you.

493
00:19:37,564 --> 00:19:40,177
Are you accusing me of knowing
that she did that?

494
00:19:40,202 --> 00:19:42,382
If you didn't know, it's because
you didn't want to know.

495
00:19:42,406 --> 00:19:44,051
Harvey, she told me
she didn't steal those things.

496
00:19:44,075 --> 00:19:45,637
I believed her
the same way you did.

497
00:19:45,661 --> 00:19:47,044
And you lied just like she did.

498
00:19:47,163 --> 00:19:48,497
I did not lie.

499
00:19:48,632 --> 00:19:51,218
Then how come when I asked you
where those documents came from,

500
00:19:51,337 --> 00:19:52,889
you didn't say one word
about Donna?

501
00:19:53,006 --> 00:19:55,152
Because you wouldn't have
listened to another word

502
00:19:55,177 --> 00:19:57,290
I said after that, and I was
trying to get the job done.

503
00:19:57,314 --> 00:19:58,992
Well, you got the job done
by risking her.

504
00:19:59,017 --> 00:20:01,338
And how is that different than
all the times you risked me?

505
00:20:01,354 --> 00:20:03,106
Because she's different.

506
00:20:10,704 --> 00:20:15,344
Harvey, I swear I didn't know.

507
00:20:15,462 --> 00:20:18,024
Well, like I said, right now,
I've got a bigger problem.

508
00:20:18,049 --> 00:20:20,435
Donna's gonna be charged
with felony fraud,

509
00:20:20,554 --> 00:20:22,556
and she's guilty.

510
00:20:27,950 --> 00:20:29,401
- Five elements.
- What?

511
00:20:29,536 --> 00:20:31,287
Proving fraud consists
of five elements.

512
00:20:31,405 --> 00:20:33,457
Okay, I'm aware of that,
and they have all of them.

513
00:20:33,576 --> 00:20:35,271
What about injury?

514
00:20:35,295 --> 00:20:37,581
How did Donna injure
Liberty Rail?

515
00:20:37,715 --> 00:20:40,278
- You know how.
- I know, and you know.

516
00:20:40,303 --> 00:20:42,115
But Evan Smith isn't gonna sit
in front of a jury

517
00:20:42,139 --> 00:20:44,285
and explain why
those documents have value

518
00:20:44,310 --> 00:20:47,073
without exposing her client
to criminal charges.

519
00:20:47,098 --> 00:20:48,232
And without damages,

520
00:20:48,351 --> 00:20:50,853
what Donna did is trespassing
at the worst.

521
00:20:50,989 --> 00:20:52,249
What do you want me to do?

522
00:20:52,273 --> 00:20:53,717
I want you to stay
on the civil case.

523
00:20:53,743 --> 00:20:54,994
Harvey, the lawsuit is dead.

524
00:20:55,111 --> 00:20:56,278
We don't have a plaintiff.

525
00:20:56,447 --> 00:20:58,226
Then get another one,
because I'm not letting

526
00:20:58,251 --> 00:21:03,041
this woman get away
with a goddamn thing.

527
00:21:05,012 --> 00:21:06,295
All right,

528
00:21:06,431 --> 00:21:07,993
I'm paying you the courtesy
of a meeting.

529
00:21:08,017 --> 00:21:09,444
What's on your mind?

530
00:21:09,469 --> 00:21:11,164
Well, based on his reputation,
I would say that

531
00:21:11,189 --> 00:21:13,035
he's going to try to weasel
his way out of this.

532
00:21:13,059 --> 00:21:15,311
What I'm going to do
is save Mr. Wolf

533
00:21:15,447 --> 00:21:17,282
from being embarrassed
in open court.

534
00:21:17,400 --> 00:21:19,796
And I'm sure there's no side
benefit to you in the process.

535
00:21:19,821 --> 00:21:20,965
You do know you're gonna have
to put Ms. Smith

536
00:21:20,989 --> 00:21:22,289
on the stand, right?

537
00:21:22,408 --> 00:21:24,303
So do you; That's why you
had her come down here.

538
00:21:24,328 --> 00:21:26,524
And did she tell you
what Donna actually took?

539
00:21:26,548 --> 00:21:28,967
You told me what Donna took.

540
00:21:29,086 --> 00:21:32,367
And I also told you that it
proves they committed a crime,

541
00:21:32,391 --> 00:21:36,040
but she can't say that,
which means all Donna stole

542
00:21:36,065 --> 00:21:37,660
was a meaningless stack
of papers,

543
00:21:37,684 --> 00:21:39,269
and without actual damages...

544
00:21:39,403 --> 00:21:40,497
I know the law.

545
00:21:40,522 --> 00:21:42,163
Then you know you've got
a shitty witness.

546
00:21:46,666 --> 00:21:48,284
Well?

547
00:21:48,418 --> 00:21:50,347
I can't get into the details
of those documents,

548
00:21:50,372 --> 00:21:52,234
but that doesn't mean
that they don't have value.

549
00:21:52,258 --> 00:21:54,177
Of course they have value.
The saved you ass.

550
00:21:54,295 --> 00:21:56,547
They're confidential.
They have trade secrets.

551
00:21:56,683 --> 00:21:58,361
The only secret that is in there

552
00:21:58,385 --> 00:21:59,696
is that your trains kill people.

553
00:21:59,721 --> 00:22:01,389
All right, enough.

554
00:22:01,557 --> 00:22:06,364
Ms. Smith,
if you can't show damages,

555
00:22:06,483 --> 00:22:07,951
I have no case.

556
00:22:08,069 --> 00:22:09,069
You don't need damages.

557
00:22:09,204 --> 00:22:10,264
You have intent.

558
00:22:10,288 --> 00:22:12,217
And if you really knew
my reputation,

559
00:22:12,242 --> 00:22:14,055
you'd also know
that I used to work here.

560
00:22:14,079 --> 00:22:17,276
And I can tell you they've never
gone after anyone for intent

561
00:22:17,300 --> 00:22:18,779
in the history
of the D.A.'s office,

562
00:22:18,803 --> 00:22:20,398
and they're not gonna start now.

563
00:22:20,422 --> 00:22:22,063
It was good doing business
with you, Evan.

564
00:22:33,277 --> 00:22:34,277
Hey.

565
00:22:34,279 --> 00:22:36,281
Hey. How are things?

566
00:22:36,417 --> 00:22:38,146
You mean the things
that you said that Harvey

567
00:22:38,170 --> 00:22:39,203
would take care of?

568
00:22:39,338 --> 00:22:41,101
Yes, those are exactly
the things I mean.

569
00:22:41,125 --> 00:22:42,653
Well,
those are exactly the things

570
00:22:42,677 --> 00:22:44,462
that Harvey just took care of.

571
00:22:44,597 --> 00:22:45,607
He did?

572
00:22:45,632 --> 00:22:50,689
He did.

573
00:22:53,478 --> 00:22:56,148
Louis, what's wrong?

574
00:22:56,283 --> 00:22:57,533
Nothing's wrong.

575
00:22:57,652 --> 00:23:00,656
It's just...
I know it wasn't gonna happen,

576
00:23:00,824 --> 00:23:05,664
but when you first told me
they might press charges,

577
00:23:05,800 --> 00:23:08,052
the thought of you
behind bars...

578
00:23:09,505 --> 00:23:11,174
Oh, come on.

579
00:23:11,342 --> 00:23:14,179
It just would have been
some cushy, white-collar resort.

580
00:23:14,347 --> 00:23:16,348
I could have finally gotten
my yoga certification...

581
00:23:16,350 --> 00:23:19,548
It wouldn't have been.

582
00:23:19,572 --> 00:23:21,357
But it doesn't matter,
because I was right.

583
00:23:21,493 --> 00:23:23,495
Harvey did whatever it took.

584
00:23:26,284 --> 00:23:27,534
Thanks, Louis.

585
00:23:27,670 --> 00:23:30,372
God, he doesn't even know
how lucky he is to have you.

586
00:23:32,177 --> 00:23:33,461
Norma's still out, isn't she?

587
00:23:33,596 --> 00:23:35,408
Her goddamn sister tripped
and fell in the tub,

588
00:23:35,432 --> 00:23:36,683
and she went to help.

589
00:23:36,802 --> 00:23:39,221
It's like she doesn't even care
about me at all.

590
00:23:52,912 --> 00:23:54,022
I know you don't work
in maintenance,

591
00:23:54,047 --> 00:23:55,999
but you do have access
to accounts payable,

592
00:23:56,135 --> 00:23:57,302
so if you could...

593
00:23:57,420 --> 00:24:00,641
look... no... hey, please,
just hear me...

594
00:24:00,759 --> 00:24:03,657
God damn it.

595
00:24:03,681 --> 00:24:06,183
Another one wouldn't take
your call?

596
00:24:06,319 --> 00:24:07,402
No, none of them will.

597
00:24:07,521 --> 00:24:09,273
I've been through
this entire directory.

598
00:24:09,407 --> 00:24:11,253
As soon as I use the words
"crash," "heat," or "sensors,"

599
00:24:11,277 --> 00:24:12,304
they all stop talking.

600
00:24:12,329 --> 00:24:13,472
Mike, people died.

601
00:24:13,497 --> 00:24:15,333
Somebody's got to want to do
the right thing.

602
00:24:15,450 --> 00:24:17,263
Well, if somebody does,
I can't find them.

603
00:24:17,287 --> 00:24:18,849
Okay what about
the victims' families?

604
00:24:18,873 --> 00:24:20,313
Oh, you mean
the original plaintiffs.

605
00:24:20,459 --> 00:24:23,179
Yeah, the problem is,
they already have a settlement.

606
00:24:23,297 --> 00:24:24,297
Go on. Look at it.

607
00:24:24,432 --> 00:24:25,632
They weren't stupid.

608
00:24:25,768 --> 00:24:27,162
It prevents them from ever
going after them again.

609
00:24:27,187 --> 00:24:30,441
Mike,
I'm just trying to help you.

610
00:24:30,560 --> 00:24:31,787
I know you are. I'm sorry.

611
00:24:31,811 --> 00:24:33,540
I'm just frustrated.

612
00:24:33,565 --> 00:24:36,128
If I can't find a new plaintiff,
I can't keep this case alive.

613
00:24:36,152 --> 00:24:38,348
Wait a second.

614
00:24:38,373 --> 00:24:41,460
You said no one at the company
will talk to you.

615
00:24:41,578 --> 00:24:44,057
They won't, because they're all
afraid they'll lose their job.

616
00:24:44,082 --> 00:24:46,585
All right, so what about someone
who has nothing left to lose?

617
00:24:48,423 --> 00:24:50,759
What are you talking about?

618
00:24:50,894 --> 00:24:53,647
I'm talking about him.

619
00:24:56,821 --> 00:24:59,657
So I rescheduled the meeting
that you missed with Latham

620
00:24:59,776 --> 00:25:01,159
for 3:00 tomorrow.

621
00:25:01,278 --> 00:25:02,505
Here are the newest contracts.

622
00:25:02,530 --> 00:25:04,783
Also, Kathy Finn called
about the takeover,

623
00:25:04,917 --> 00:25:07,536
so I sent her the latest specs,
and I told her to sit tight.

624
00:25:07,672 --> 00:25:09,851
And I noticed the left pen on
your desk set was out of ink,

625
00:25:09,876 --> 00:25:11,260
so I had the cartridge replaced.

626
00:25:11,379 --> 00:25:13,658
You could have done all of this
while I was out of the office.

627
00:25:13,682 --> 00:25:15,861
I know, but then I wouldn't have
had a chance to thank you.

628
00:25:15,886 --> 00:25:17,388
Donna.

629
00:25:17,555 --> 00:25:19,785
Thank you, Harvey.

630
00:25:19,810 --> 00:25:21,561
You're welcome.

631
00:25:21,729 --> 00:25:24,232
Ms. Paulsen, Mr. Specter.

632
00:25:24,367 --> 00:25:27,265
Terrance, you better be here
to give Donna a formal apology

633
00:25:27,289 --> 00:25:28,406
from the D.A.'s office.

634
00:25:28,541 --> 00:25:30,270
No.

635
00:25:30,294 --> 00:25:32,997
I'm here to give
her lawyer this.

636
00:25:36,554 --> 00:25:37,481
Harvey, what is that?

637
00:25:37,506 --> 00:25:38,650
Donna, leave the room.

638
00:25:38,675 --> 00:25:39,808
You can tell her to leave.

639
00:25:39,927 --> 00:25:41,489
Don't forget to tell her
her arraignment's

640
00:25:41,513 --> 00:25:42,573
at 9:00 a.m. tomorrow morning.

641
00:25:42,597 --> 00:25:43,647
Arraignment? For what?

642
00:25:43,766 --> 00:25:44,766
You son of a bitch.

643
00:25:44,768 --> 00:25:46,487
You amended the charges
to intent?

644
00:25:46,604 --> 00:25:48,022
You said it's never been done

645
00:25:48,157 --> 00:25:49,608
in the history
of the D.A.'s office.

646
00:25:49,743 --> 00:25:51,338
I decided to make history.

647
00:25:51,362 --> 00:25:53,531
By going after someone
for stealing nothing.

648
00:25:53,666 --> 00:25:55,535
She went in there to find
the Hope Diamond.

649
00:25:55,669 --> 00:25:57,815
Just because she came out
with a piece of glass

650
00:25:57,840 --> 00:25:59,319
doesn't mean it wasn't fraud.

651
00:25:59,343 --> 00:26:00,593
That's exactly what it means.

652
00:26:00,712 --> 00:26:02,441
Every time I run into you,

653
00:26:02,465 --> 00:26:05,469
you tell me whatever shady thing
just went down

654
00:26:05,636 --> 00:26:08,701
was about the greater good
or that it didn't happen

655
00:26:08,725 --> 00:26:12,196
or this, that, or the other,
but a crime was committed here,

656
00:26:12,315 --> 00:26:13,459
and I'm going after her for it.

657
00:26:13,484 --> 00:26:15,369
Bullshit. You're going after me.

658
00:26:15,487 --> 00:26:17,849
Oh, you're telling me
you didn't order her to do it.

659
00:26:17,874 --> 00:26:19,158
No, I didn't.

660
00:26:19,293 --> 00:26:21,523
Well, we'll find out...

661
00:26:21,547 --> 00:26:23,832
when she's about to be convicted

662
00:26:24,001 --> 00:26:28,558
and I offer her a deal.

663
00:26:33,529 --> 00:26:36,008
What happens now?

664
00:26:36,032 --> 00:26:38,478
What happens now is,
we go in there tomorrow

665
00:26:38,503 --> 00:26:40,933
and enter a plea of not guilty.

666
00:26:40,958 --> 00:26:42,208
But I am guilty.

667
00:26:42,343 --> 00:26:44,996
Donna, intent to commit fraud
is a bullshit charge,

668
00:26:45,132 --> 00:26:46,910
and he's just using you
to try to scare you.

669
00:26:46,934 --> 00:26:48,803
Well, it's working. I'm scared.

670
00:26:48,937 --> 00:26:50,639
- Donna...
- What's the punishment?

671
00:26:50,775 --> 00:26:52,936
It doesn't matter, because
I'm gonna get you out of it.

672
00:26:52,944 --> 00:26:55,147
Harvey, what's the punishment?

673
00:26:56,316 --> 00:26:57,343
Three to five years.

674
00:26:57,368 --> 00:26:59,320
Oh, my God.

675
00:26:59,456 --> 00:27:01,435
- Three to five years for what?
- Not now, Louis.

676
00:27:01,459 --> 00:27:03,161
I just saw Terrance Wolf
at the elevator.

677
00:27:03,328 --> 00:27:05,357
Three to five years for what?

678
00:27:05,382 --> 00:27:08,169
He's charging her with intent
to commit fraud.

679
00:27:08,304 --> 00:27:09,231
Holy shit.

680
00:27:09,255 --> 00:27:10,973
Louis, I don't want to hear it.

681
00:27:11,092 --> 00:27:12,286
Well, you're going to,
because you were supposed to

682
00:27:12,310 --> 00:27:13,320
get her out of this.

683
00:27:13,345 --> 00:27:14,372
This isn't helping.

684
00:27:14,397 --> 00:27:16,078
What the hell do you think
I've been doing?

685
00:27:16,100 --> 00:27:17,327
I don't know, but whatever
it is, it didn't do a thing.

686
00:27:17,352 --> 00:27:18,831
You have no idea
what you're talking about.

687
00:27:18,855 --> 00:27:21,051
I told her that you were never
gonna let her get in trouble.

688
00:27:21,075 --> 00:27:22,085
It's not so simple.

689
00:27:22,110 --> 00:27:23,270
What the hell isn't so simple?

690
00:27:23,279 --> 00:27:25,198
She's guilty.

691
00:27:25,332 --> 00:27:27,178
Wolf is trying to use her
to turn on me,

692
00:27:27,203 --> 00:27:28,737
because he thinks
I put her up to it.

693
00:27:28,839 --> 00:27:30,039
Did you?

694
00:27:30,174 --> 00:27:31,518
Harvey didn't even know
I did it.

695
00:27:31,543 --> 00:27:32,904
You know what?
It doesn't even matter.

696
00:27:32,929 --> 00:27:34,714
- Because I'm taking over.
- No, you're not.

697
00:27:34,849 --> 00:27:36,276
He's trying to get her
to turn on you.

698
00:27:36,301 --> 00:27:37,745
You cannot be her lawyer.

699
00:27:37,770 --> 00:27:39,889
She's not going to,
so what difference does it make?

700
00:27:40,024 --> 00:27:42,777
The difference is, if you're out
of the picture, Wolf backs down.

701
00:27:42,896 --> 00:27:45,125
From where he's standing,
I'm in the picture,

702
00:27:45,149 --> 00:27:46,449
and he's never gonna back down.

703
00:27:46,568 --> 00:27:48,369
You don't know that,
and this is Donna's life.

704
00:27:48,371 --> 00:27:49,811
And I'm not putting it
in your hands.

705
00:27:49,823 --> 00:27:51,184
And it's not your decision
to make.

706
00:27:51,209 --> 00:27:53,055
No, it's not. It's Donna's.

707
00:27:53,080 --> 00:27:54,882
And she's sticking with me.

708
00:28:00,057 --> 00:28:02,727
Louis, please,
I know that you want to help,

709
00:28:02,845 --> 00:28:03,845
but just go.

710
00:28:21,878 --> 00:28:23,680
- Mr. Jaworski.
- Yeah.

711
00:28:23,798 --> 00:28:25,860
My name is Mike Ross.
I'm with Pearson Specter Litt.

712
00:28:25,884 --> 00:28:27,018
This is Rachel Zane.

713
00:28:27,137 --> 00:28:28,855
She's one of our associates.

714
00:28:28,973 --> 00:28:31,014
Sir, we'd like to speak with you
about the accident.

715
00:28:31,027 --> 00:28:33,696
Look, I was already deposed
for that lawsuit.

716
00:28:33,815 --> 00:28:34,865
The victims got paid.

717
00:28:34,984 --> 00:28:36,462
I said everything
I had to say, okay?

718
00:28:36,486 --> 00:28:38,705
We're not here
to come after you.

719
00:28:38,823 --> 00:28:40,217
We want you to sue Liberty Rail.

720
00:28:40,242 --> 00:28:41,553
Oh, yeah?
And why would I sue them?

721
00:28:41,578 --> 00:28:43,857
'Cause while you might have been
driving the train,

722
00:28:43,882 --> 00:28:45,166
that accident wasn't your fault.

723
00:28:45,301 --> 00:28:47,003
Is this some kind of a joke?

724
00:28:47,137 --> 00:28:48,221
No, sir. It isn't.

725
00:28:48,340 --> 00:28:49,841
They made you the fall guy.

726
00:28:51,428 --> 00:28:53,263
Bullshit.
Why would they do that?

727
00:28:53,398 --> 00:28:55,016
Because they needed
to blame someone,

728
00:28:55,151 --> 00:28:56,903
and not only were you
at the wheel,

729
00:28:57,021 --> 00:28:58,405
you had no memory
of what happened.

730
00:28:58,523 --> 00:29:01,170
Nah, I don't believe it.

731
00:29:01,195 --> 00:29:03,163
They're a good company.
They wouldn't do this.

732
00:29:03,281 --> 00:29:04,415
Mr. Jaworski...

733
00:29:04,533 --> 00:29:05,750
Look, I killed those people.

734
00:29:06,871 --> 00:29:08,433
And they still gave me
early retirement

735
00:29:08,457 --> 00:29:09,851
and let me keep my pension.

736
00:29:09,876 --> 00:29:11,928
The reason they did that
was to keep you quiet.

737
00:29:15,602 --> 00:29:17,448
I need you to get off
my property,

738
00:29:17,472 --> 00:29:19,107
both of you.

739
00:29:21,396 --> 00:29:23,208
Sir, you know that we're telling
the truth.

740
00:29:23,232 --> 00:29:25,177
Yeah, well, is the truth
gonna support the family

741
00:29:25,201 --> 00:29:27,431
of a guy who can't get another
job for the rest of his life?

742
00:29:27,456 --> 00:29:29,124
If we win,
you'll be set up for life.

743
00:29:29,242 --> 00:29:30,242
Ah, take a look at me.

744
00:29:30,411 --> 00:29:32,496
I ain't the guy who wins.

745
00:29:32,630 --> 00:29:34,549
I'm the guy who loses.

746
00:29:34,668 --> 00:29:37,137
What if I can guarantee
to take care of all of that

747
00:29:37,256 --> 00:29:38,473
no matter what happens.

748
00:29:42,731 --> 00:29:44,933
What would you need me to do?

749
00:29:46,104 --> 00:29:47,104
All rise.

750
00:29:51,947 --> 00:29:53,030
You okay?

751
00:29:53,166 --> 00:29:55,168
Mm-hmm.

752
00:29:55,286 --> 00:29:56,503
Am I gonna have to talk?

753
00:29:56,621 --> 00:29:58,021
Just be polite
and say "Your Honor."

754
00:29:58,124 --> 00:30:00,103
It will be over
before you know it.

755
00:30:00,128 --> 00:30:02,324
State versus Donna Paulsen.

756
00:30:02,348 --> 00:30:05,969
Is the defense counsel prepared
to proceed with the arraignment?

757
00:30:06,105 --> 00:30:07,031
We are, Your Honor.

758
00:30:07,055 --> 00:30:08,524
Ms. Paulsen,
you have been charged

759
00:30:08,641 --> 00:30:10,620
with felony intent
to commit fraud.

760
00:30:10,645 --> 00:30:13,616
This carries a maximum sentence
of up to five years in prison.

761
00:30:13,734 --> 00:30:15,819
Do you understand the charges
against you today?

762
00:30:15,954 --> 00:30:17,237
Yes, Your Honor.

763
00:30:17,373 --> 00:30:18,373
How do you plead?

764
00:30:20,161 --> 00:30:21,378
Not guilty, Your Honor.

765
00:30:21,497 --> 00:30:22,547
Very well.

766
00:30:22,665 --> 00:30:24,884
Mr. Wolf, is the state ready
to go to trial?

767
00:30:25,003 --> 00:30:26,003
We are, Your Honor.

768
00:30:26,004 --> 00:30:27,556
Trial is set to begin Monday.

769
00:30:27,674 --> 00:30:29,403
Next case.

770
00:30:29,427 --> 00:30:31,012
All right, you made your point.

771
00:30:31,147 --> 00:30:32,658
Let's plead this down
to a misdemeanor

772
00:30:32,682 --> 00:30:34,234
and both go back
to our real jobs.

773
00:30:34,352 --> 00:30:36,020
This is my real job.

774
00:30:36,188 --> 00:30:37,917
Maybe if you had
a little more respect

775
00:30:37,942 --> 00:30:40,923
for what it stands for,
you wouldn't be standing here.

776
00:30:40,947 --> 00:30:44,061
Listen, I'm gonna wipe that look
off your smug face.

777
00:30:44,085 --> 00:30:45,513
You give it a try, Harvey,

778
00:30:45,538 --> 00:30:47,506
but I've got all the evidence
I need.

779
00:30:54,302 --> 00:30:58,057
You're gonna have to go
find yourself a new secretary.

780
00:31:17,725 --> 00:31:21,313
I see you're back
to not knocking.

781
00:31:21,432 --> 00:31:23,484
I take it that means
you've made up your mind.

782
00:31:23,602 --> 00:31:25,153
I have.

783
00:31:25,271 --> 00:31:26,271
And?

784
00:31:26,273 --> 00:31:28,969
And what I've decided

785
00:31:28,994 --> 00:31:31,280
is that you shut the door
on me the other night,

786
00:31:31,415 --> 00:31:35,203
and it's not fair you to dictate
what I do and don't get to say.

787
00:31:35,338 --> 00:31:37,123
I told you.

788
00:31:37,259 --> 00:31:38,780
It doesn't matter
what you have to say,

789
00:31:38,794 --> 00:31:40,513
because whatever it is,
I won't believe it.

790
00:31:40,631 --> 00:31:45,354
Well, what if I was here
to tell you that I love you?

791
00:31:50,364 --> 00:31:54,680
Jessica,
you lied to me for months...

792
00:31:54,705 --> 00:31:57,017
Jeff, please.

793
00:31:57,041 --> 00:32:00,306
Just listen.

794
00:32:00,331 --> 00:32:02,477
I know I hurt you,

795
00:32:02,501 --> 00:32:05,003
but you were the one

796
00:32:05,139 --> 00:32:08,654
who wanted us to work together
and be in a relationship.

797
00:32:08,678 --> 00:32:11,240
And you were the one who thought
it was a mistake.

798
00:32:11,265 --> 00:32:13,234
Because I was scared.

799
00:32:13,353 --> 00:32:16,166
But I changed my mind,

800
00:32:16,191 --> 00:32:20,079
because you refused to give up.

801
00:32:20,197 --> 00:32:23,418
And now I'm refusing to give up.

802
00:32:23,537 --> 00:32:26,434
I want you to stay here.

803
00:32:26,458 --> 00:32:29,044
I want us to have both.

804
00:32:32,051 --> 00:32:33,051
Jessica...

805
00:32:33,052 --> 00:32:37,442
You wanted me to let
my walls down.

806
00:32:37,560 --> 00:32:40,229
Well, they're down.

807
00:33:06,610 --> 00:33:08,091
Donna, why don't you go home?

808
00:33:08,112 --> 00:33:10,475
You know I like to be alone when
I'm getting ready for a trial.

809
00:33:10,499 --> 00:33:12,418
I need to talk to you.

810
00:33:12,520 --> 00:33:13,520
What is it?

811
00:33:13,621 --> 00:33:15,956
I think maybe Louis was right.

812
00:33:16,092 --> 00:33:18,961
You think Louis was right
about what?

813
00:33:19,130 --> 00:33:20,547
Maybe he should be
handling my case.

814
00:33:25,023 --> 00:33:27,609
Okay, well,
if that's how you feel.

815
00:33:27,728 --> 00:33:29,791
I knew it; I knew you would
take this as an insult.

816
00:33:29,816 --> 00:33:31,544
How exactly would you like me
to take it?

817
00:33:31,568 --> 00:33:33,047
I would like you
to take it seriously

818
00:33:33,071 --> 00:33:34,381
and talk about it with me.

819
00:33:34,406 --> 00:33:38,161
Okay, Donna, why exactly would
you prefer Louis to handle this?

820
00:33:38,329 --> 00:33:40,164
Because I sat
in that arraignment today,

821
00:33:40,333 --> 00:33:42,001
and it hit me for the first time

822
00:33:42,136 --> 00:33:45,507
that I might actually go
to prison.

823
00:33:45,676 --> 00:33:48,011
And you were more concerned
with attacking Terrance Wolf

824
00:33:48,179 --> 00:33:49,240
than you were with me.

825
00:33:49,265 --> 00:33:50,459
So you think Louis is right.

826
00:33:50,484 --> 00:33:51,985
I piss off the D.A. too much.

827
00:33:52,119 --> 00:33:54,249
- Well, you sure did today.
- Because he's coming at us.

828
00:33:54,274 --> 00:33:55,718
And you're pouring gas
on the fire.

829
00:33:55,743 --> 00:33:57,672
Because that's what I do,
and I don't need you

830
00:33:57,696 --> 00:34:00,248
coming in here second-guessing
how I do my job.

831
00:34:00,367 --> 00:34:02,119
Harvey,
why are you attacking me?

832
00:34:02,253 --> 00:34:03,180
I'm not the enemy.

833
00:34:03,205 --> 00:34:04,399
You sure as hell are right now.

834
00:34:04,424 --> 00:34:05,735
What? Why am I the...

835
00:34:05,759 --> 00:34:07,260
Because I'm getting ready
for a fight,

836
00:34:07,379 --> 00:34:08,523
and you're telling me
you don't think I can win.

837
00:34:08,547 --> 00:34:09,858
I'm not telling you that.

838
00:34:09,883 --> 00:34:11,361
I'm telling you
that I'm petrified.

839
00:34:11,385 --> 00:34:14,081
And I understand, but I
don't have time to comfort you.

840
00:34:14,106 --> 00:34:16,252
- Well, I need you to make time.
- And I can't, because...

841
00:34:16,277 --> 00:34:18,396
Harvey, this is my life!

842
00:34:20,818 --> 00:34:24,289
When I told Louis how you
got me out of this thing,

843
00:34:24,407 --> 00:34:26,459
he told me how scared he was
at the thought

844
00:34:26,578 --> 00:34:31,168
of me going to prison,
and I just... need...

845
00:34:31,302 --> 00:34:34,483
you... to...

846
00:34:34,507 --> 00:34:37,455
Donna, the thought of you
going to prison

847
00:34:37,479 --> 00:34:39,658
makes me want to drop
to my knees.

848
00:34:39,683 --> 00:34:41,127
You want to hear me say it?

849
00:34:41,152 --> 00:34:42,798
There it is.

850
00:34:42,822 --> 00:34:44,082
But that's not gonna happen,

851
00:34:44,107 --> 00:34:45,586
because I'm not gonna
let it happen.

852
00:34:45,610 --> 00:34:49,582
But in order to do that,
you need to let me do what I do.

853
00:34:49,700 --> 00:34:51,262
- Harvey...
- That's enough.

854
00:34:51,286 --> 00:34:52,670
You want someone
to give you a hug?

855
00:34:52,789 --> 00:34:54,006
Go to Louis.

856
00:34:54,124 --> 00:34:55,853
You want someone to get you out
of this thing,

857
00:34:55,877 --> 00:34:57,127
you need to leave me alone.

858
00:35:09,678 --> 00:35:11,158
I need to know everything
you have,

859
00:35:11,159 --> 00:35:12,123
and I need to know right now.

860
00:35:12,124 --> 00:35:14,133
We got the conductor to sign on,
but we have to give him...

861
00:35:14,135 --> 00:35:15,195
I don't care what
I have to give him.

862
00:35:15,220 --> 00:35:16,304
What does that give us?

863
00:35:16,438 --> 00:35:18,107
What do you mean?
It gives us standing.

864
00:35:18,225 --> 00:35:19,693
Now we can subpoena
those records.

865
00:35:19,811 --> 00:35:21,005
Well, that's not enough.

866
00:35:21,030 --> 00:35:22,458
- It's a start.
- I don't need a start.

867
00:35:22,483 --> 00:35:23,843
I need a finish,
and I need it now.

868
00:35:27,040 --> 00:35:28,658
They're charging Donna,
aren't they?

869
00:35:28,793 --> 00:35:30,472
She was arraigned this morning.

870
00:35:30,496 --> 00:35:34,000
If this thing goes to trial,
I can't guarantee a win.

871
00:35:34,136 --> 00:35:35,814
So we're back to trading
the case for Donna.

872
00:35:35,838 --> 00:35:37,367
Yeah, and I don't want to hear
your moral objections

873
00:35:37,391 --> 00:35:39,309
about those people getting away
with murder.

874
00:35:39,427 --> 00:35:40,310
I'm not talking about that,
Harvey,

875
00:35:40,429 --> 00:35:41,540
but if Donna was arraigned,

876
00:35:41,565 --> 00:35:43,126
it's not up to them
to drop the charges.

877
00:35:43,234 --> 00:35:45,246
It's up to Wolf, and you know
he's never gonna do that.

878
00:35:45,270 --> 00:35:46,999
I'm not talking about
dropping the charges.

879
00:35:47,024 --> 00:35:49,185
I'm talking about making
this whole damn thing go away.

880
00:35:49,194 --> 00:35:51,306
Harvey, if you're saying
what I think you're saying,

881
00:35:51,330 --> 00:35:52,758
that's obstruction of justice.

882
00:35:52,784 --> 00:35:54,201
The way I see it, it's justice.

883
00:35:54,336 --> 00:35:55,263
You know what I mean.

884
00:35:55,287 --> 00:35:56,481
I do, and I don't give a shit.

885
00:35:56,506 --> 00:35:58,375
- This is Donna.
- All right, I get it.

886
00:35:58,509 --> 00:36:00,094
But what if what I have
isn't enough?

887
00:36:00,213 --> 00:36:01,357
Like you said, it's a start.

888
00:36:01,381 --> 00:36:03,883
Have an official complaint
on my desk by the morning.

889
00:36:04,052 --> 00:36:06,213
- And what are you gonna do?
- I'm gonna get us enough.

890
00:36:17,876 --> 00:36:20,078
All right, I hear you.
I hear you.

891
00:36:23,252 --> 00:36:24,419
Do you know who I am?

892
00:36:24,588 --> 00:36:25,421
No.

893
00:36:25,555 --> 00:36:27,784
Yeah, Mike Ross works for me.

894
00:36:27,809 --> 00:36:29,093
Hey, I don't give a shit.

895
00:36:29,229 --> 00:36:31,241
I told him not to take your case
in the first place,

896
00:36:31,265 --> 00:36:33,794
because I knew you were
a goddamn shakedown artist,

897
00:36:33,819 --> 00:36:35,548
but now someone I care about
is in trouble,

898
00:36:35,572 --> 00:36:36,833
because you took a payout.

899
00:36:36,858 --> 00:36:38,108
Get out of my face.

900
00:36:38,277 --> 00:36:39,327
Listen to me.

901
00:36:39,445 --> 00:36:42,760
If you don't do
what we need you to do,

902
00:36:42,784 --> 00:36:43,784
I will hurt you.

903
00:36:43,786 --> 00:36:45,315
You better be prepared
to kill me,

904
00:36:45,339 --> 00:36:47,207
because I'm not gonna give
that money back.

905
00:36:48,961 --> 00:36:50,281
Well, if this is just
about money,

906
00:36:50,297 --> 00:36:53,801
then we don't need to fight
at all.

907
00:36:55,806 --> 00:36:58,119
Harvey,
this is becoming a habit.

908
00:36:58,144 --> 00:37:00,090
I've seen you more than
my last three boyfriends.

909
00:37:00,114 --> 00:37:02,043
Somehow that doesn't
surprise me.

910
00:37:02,067 --> 00:37:03,702
You're funny.

911
00:37:03,820 --> 00:37:05,204
I like you.

912
00:37:05,323 --> 00:37:07,801
But I know you're not here
to mock my relationship,

913
00:37:07,825 --> 00:37:09,042
so what's on your mind?

914
00:37:09,162 --> 00:37:10,306
We wanted to give you this.

915
00:37:10,331 --> 00:37:11,882
What's this?

916
00:37:12,000 --> 00:37:14,481
It's the lawsuit we filed
on behalf of Michael Jaworski.

917
00:37:14,505 --> 00:37:17,234
You know, the man you let
take the fall for the accident.

918
00:37:17,259 --> 00:37:18,403
Michael Jaworski can't sue...

919
00:37:18,428 --> 00:37:19,896
What?

920
00:37:20,014 --> 00:37:20,897
Sue you,
because you were smart enough

921
00:37:21,016 --> 00:37:22,685
to take care of his expenses?

922
00:37:22,852 --> 00:37:24,831
Well, now I'm taking care
of his expenses.

923
00:37:24,855 --> 00:37:26,083
And now we have standing,

924
00:37:26,108 --> 00:37:28,193
and we are going to subpoena
those documents.

925
00:37:28,329 --> 00:37:30,748
Am I supposed to start quaking
in my boots?

926
00:37:30,865 --> 00:37:33,345
Nope, we know
if you can doctor a report,

927
00:37:33,370 --> 00:37:35,015
you can alter
those maintenance records.

928
00:37:35,039 --> 00:37:36,089
I didn't alter anything.

929
00:37:36,208 --> 00:37:37,926
Well, that's not what
Joe Henderson said.

930
00:37:38,044 --> 00:37:40,022
He said you came to him,
admitted everything,

931
00:37:40,047 --> 00:37:42,016
and offered him a settlement
to keep quiet.

932
00:37:42,135 --> 00:37:44,948
We didn't admit anything,
and that settlement is sealed.

933
00:37:44,973 --> 00:37:47,442
Oh, you mean this settlement?

934
00:37:49,397 --> 00:37:50,948
We had an agreement.

935
00:37:51,066 --> 00:37:53,546
Well, here's the thing
about paying people off, Evan.

936
00:37:53,571 --> 00:37:55,539
Someone can always
pay them more.

937
00:37:57,244 --> 00:37:59,940
His word won't hold up
against Richard McIntyre's.

938
00:37:59,964 --> 00:38:02,811
Oh, he's not saying that Richard
McIntyre put him up to it.

939
00:38:02,836 --> 00:38:03,863
He's saying you did.

940
00:38:03,888 --> 00:38:05,282
That's bullshit.

941
00:38:05,307 --> 00:38:06,809
And does that really matter?

942
00:38:09,264 --> 00:38:10,291
What do you want?

943
00:38:10,316 --> 00:38:12,318
You made the author
of that report disappear.

944
00:38:12,436 --> 00:38:14,938
You made Joe Henderson
disappear.

945
00:38:15,074 --> 00:38:17,159
Figure out a way to make
the witness against Donna

946
00:38:17,277 --> 00:38:18,277
change her tune.

947
00:38:18,446 --> 00:38:20,164
That's obstruction of justice.

948
00:38:20,283 --> 00:38:21,450
That's not my problem.

949
00:38:21,583 --> 00:38:23,502
You son of a bitch.

950
00:38:23,622 --> 00:38:24,982
It's your call.

951
00:38:25,007 --> 00:38:28,011
Maybe people will believe Joe,
maybe they won't,

952
00:38:28,129 --> 00:38:29,323
but instead of making money,

953
00:38:29,348 --> 00:38:31,277
you're gonna be
defending yourself in court

954
00:38:31,301 --> 00:38:33,437
for the next five years.

955
00:38:33,555 --> 00:38:36,308
You're so sure we did this,
you're really gonna let us

956
00:38:36,444 --> 00:38:38,529
get away with murder
for your secretary?

957
00:38:38,647 --> 00:38:41,048
You're damn right I am,
and if I had to do it again,

958
00:38:41,151 --> 00:38:44,037
I'd do it 100 times.

959
00:38:55,926 --> 00:38:57,059
What's that?

960
00:38:58,314 --> 00:38:59,314
You know what it is.

961
00:39:03,572 --> 00:39:07,003
- Jeff...
- Jessica, you were right.

962
00:39:07,028 --> 00:39:09,581
We either need to have both,
or it's not going to work.

963
00:39:11,035 --> 00:39:13,431
And you don't want both?

964
00:39:13,455 --> 00:39:17,879
Effective immediately,
I'm tendering my resignation.

965
00:39:21,303 --> 00:39:22,553
Then I wish you luck.

966
00:39:24,224 --> 00:39:27,110
Good luck, Jessica.

967
00:39:49,350 --> 00:39:50,470
Do you remember?

968
00:39:50,602 --> 00:39:53,522
Yes, of course I remember.
It happened right there.

969
00:39:56,328 --> 00:39:57,389
Well, it was your fault,

970
00:39:57,414 --> 00:39:59,199
'cause you made me
burst out laughing.

971
00:39:59,333 --> 00:40:00,450
You didn't just burst.

972
00:40:00,586 --> 00:40:02,454
You spat a piece of shrimp
across the room

973
00:40:02,589 --> 00:40:04,070
and into the back
of my mother's hair.

974
00:40:06,295 --> 00:40:08,491
And she didn't even feel it
because of all the hair spray,

975
00:40:08,515 --> 00:40:10,217
and it stuck in there
like a tick.

976
00:40:10,352 --> 00:40:11,436
Oh, my God.

977
00:40:11,554 --> 00:40:13,250
I could hardly look at her
or that boyfriend

978
00:40:13,274 --> 00:40:14,284
for the next two hours.

979
00:40:14,308 --> 00:40:15,308
What was his name again?

980
00:40:15,310 --> 00:40:16,979
Who cares? He was such a loser.

981
00:40:17,113 --> 00:40:18,507
Oh, come on;
He was the reason you had

982
00:40:18,532 --> 00:40:20,093
that god-awful party
in the first place.

983
00:40:28,749 --> 00:40:30,027
Thank you, Harvey.

984
00:40:30,052 --> 00:40:32,170
You don't need to thank me.
You already thanked me.

985
00:40:32,339 --> 00:40:34,892
No, I thanked you for fixing it.

986
00:40:35,011 --> 00:40:38,993
Now I'm thanking you for not
bringing it up all night.

987
00:40:39,018 --> 00:40:40,663
I just figured if you wanted
it brought up,

988
00:40:40,687 --> 00:40:44,442
you'd bring it up,
and now you have, so...

989
00:40:48,366 --> 00:40:51,731
I told you I'd never let
anything happen to you,

990
00:40:51,755 --> 00:40:55,353
and I wont ever,

991
00:40:55,378 --> 00:40:59,885
so you don't ever have to
feel scared like that again.

992
00:41:03,191 --> 00:41:06,456
I thought you said you didn't do
the comfort thing.

993
00:41:06,481 --> 00:41:07,949
I didn't say I didn't do it.

994
00:41:08,067 --> 00:41:09,568
I said I didn't have time,

995
00:41:09,703 --> 00:41:13,624
because I was so busy
saving your ass.

996
00:41:18,000 --> 00:41:20,469
I'm sorry I doubted you.

997
00:41:23,759 --> 00:41:25,594
I'm sorry I snapped at you.

998
00:41:32,357 --> 00:41:35,137
Anyone else every loses faith
in me,

999
00:41:35,162 --> 00:41:40,262
it doesn't matter.

1000
00:41:40,287 --> 00:41:42,957
But with you, it's different.

1001
00:41:51,139 --> 00:41:53,474
I should go.

1002
00:42:01,156 --> 00:42:02,624
Why?

1003
00:42:02,741 --> 00:42:05,211
You know why.

1004
00:42:10,472 --> 00:42:13,008
You know I love you, Donna.

1005
00:42:23,905 --> 00:42:30,409
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man

