Avery mckernon
was the first client
I ever brought into the firm.
I have stacked my engines
up against bronson
And everyone else's
in the world, and mine win,
Because I make sure
they're designed
Better than anyone else's.
And that's the speech
you're gonna give.
I said I was giving you
50% of mckernon.
I didn't say I was keeping
the other 50%.
You finally realized they need
an upgrade in representation?
It's up to you, jack.
Stand by provision c-35
Or pack up your shit.
I want you to tell me
The worst mistake
you ever made as a therapist?
That wasn't part of the deal.
- I killed someone.
- What?
A client needed someone
to get his son out of rehab
So that he could attend
his mother's funeral.
I knew deep down inside
he wasn't ready,
But I gave the go-ahead anyway,
And the night of the funeral...
He overdosed and died.
I'm surprised you called
for another appointment.
What can I say? You telling
me that story got to me.
So you're ready
to tell the truth?
I am. The woman
in my dream was donna.
[gentle pop music]
♪ ♪
(agard) I don't think the woman
in your dream was actually donna.
I think it was your mother.
(harvey) I don't believe it.
I tell you the thing that's
been eating at me for days,
And you call me a liar?
No, I'm not calling you a liar.
Your dream was a representation
of unresolved issues.
The only unresolved issue
is I told you the truth,
And you're turning on me.
Bringing up your mother
isn't turning on you.
You have no idea what
bringing up my mother is to me.
No, I don't. That's the whole
point of what we're doing here.
Well, it doesn't matter
what we're doing here,
'cause I'm not staying.
Harvey, I don't care
how much money you make
Or how many women
you sleep with.
You have issues in your life
That are going to keep you
from having real relationships.
Now, you can tell yourself
It has nothing to do
with your mother all you want,
But it's a lie, and you know it.
(harvey) and I said we're done.
♪ ♪
Louis, we need to talk.
Oh, if it's about
the summer associate with b.O.,
That is out of my control.
It's about jack soloff.
What?
So help me, if that asshole
Is backing out
of his agreement, i...
No one's backing out
of anything.
Well, then what's the problem?
Right now there is no problem.
We beat him.
He's been neutralized.
But that's not where
I want him to stay.
What do you mean?
I mean we've won,
But the man's shown himself
to be a force.
And if he's ever gonna come
around to being on our side,
We have to give him time
to lick his wounds.
I don't care what you say,
But that weasel is never
gonna be on our side.
And that's exactly
the kind of petty thinking
That led to your feuds
with scottie, hardman,
Harvey, me, just to name a few.
Jessica, this is different,
and you know it.
Jack started this whole thing.
Louis, last night you asked
When were you going to learn
to listen to me.
The time is now.
- And you said...
- I don't care what I said.
If you let your pettiness
Get the better of you with jack,
So help me god,
You will not be
the one left standing.
You have my word.
Louis, I need to talk to you,
And I don't want you
to be upset.
What is it?
Dominic barone called.
He wants to come in
for a meeting.
Now, I know he called me...
Excellent. Pick a time.
But you're not mad that
he called me instead of you?
Why would I be mad?
Am I in the right office?
Mike, you're thinking
of the old louis.
The new louis is not petty,
And he definitely
does not get upset
About things like
who called who.
And may I ask where
the new louis came from?
From inside.
I took a look at the man
in the mirror,
And I decided
it was time to make a change.
Well, I'm glad you did.
And I don't know
what dominic wants,
But whatever it is,
I'm looking forward
to working with you on it.
- Did you just hear that?
- Yes.
Then you know once mike
and dominic agree to a time,
You need to reschedule it.
Louis.
Dominic needs to learn
that I'm the man in charge.
But you're not
the man in charge,
Because harvey gave you and mike
mckernon motors to share.
But dominic doesn't know that,
And mike and I gave him
a card at the same time.
And mike's says "associate,"
And mine says
"pearson specter litt,"
And I crossed out the "pearson
specter" like I always do.
Louis, did you not hear
what jessica said
About stopping
all the pettiness?
Yeah, that was
about jack soloff.
No, it was about pettiness.
Donna, I'm sorry,
but I only have
A certain amount
of non-pettiness in me,
And the real louis litt
needs to come out somewhere.
Okay, louis, you want dominic
to think you're the man?
Mm-hmm.
Then you need to stop worrying
about who he called
And start worrying
about what he needs,
Which is for you to be
a great lawyer.
[elevator bell dings]
Good, you're here.
Did you file the johnson brief?
- Not yet.
- Then do it this morning.
I want to drop the hammer
on those guys this afternoon.
Well, before you do, there's
a sam tull waiting to see you.
Who the hell is sam tull?
Tall, handsome,
steely blue eyes?
Not ringing any bells.
Well, maybe this
will knock the cobwebs out.
He said the last time
you saw him,
He was
with morello asset management
And you threatened
to kick his ass.
You let him in my office?
Do I look
like I was born yesterday?
He's in the conference room
Under the supervision
of one rachel zane.
I told him if he didn't
behave himself,
I'd kick his ass myself.
You'd do that, wouldn't you?
I sure as hell would.
And if you don't get
in there this second,
I'll kick yours.
Don't tell me you're here
To take me up on that offer
to step outside.
I'm not.
Good, then we've established
That you're smarter than
the last time I saw you.
Now get the hell
out of our offices.
Harvey, the man came to see us.
Rachel, this man is an asshole,
And he was willing to let
an innocent person go to jail.
And now I'm an innocent person
who could go to jail.
What?
I'm being accused of making
unauthorized trades.
- By morello?
- I don't work there anymore.
I work at butler trading.
Good for you.
Were they authorized or not?
I swear to god
I didn't do one thing
They don't know about.
And let me guess,
you don't have any proof?
No, I don't...
Because that's the way
things work.
What does that mean?
It means he's saying
they checked his trades
Enough to decide
it was okay with the risk
But not enough
to put it in writing.
Okay, but why wouldn't
they put it in writing?
Because they would rather
say I went rogue
Than pay a $2 million fine.
Here's the problem, sam.
Why should I believe you,
when the last time we met
You were the one
who was willing to put
An innocent person away?
Because I didn't know
she was innocent.
And the truth is...
I didn't care.
But you did.
I'm telling you...
I didn't do this.
Please, I need your help.
If I find out
you're lying to me,
This time I won't
just threaten you.
I will beat the shit out of you.
(man) ♪ see the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
.
Donna, could I talk to you
for a minute?
Yeah, if you can tell me
where the honey is hiding.
Hey, hey, hey.
Oh, sneaky little bear.
So what's on your mind?
Okay, so I'm trying to plan
Something special
for our wedding.
What? We're getting married?
Mike, this is so sudden. I'm
gonna have to think about it.
And what about rachel?
Oh, who cares about rachel?
- I love you.
- Are you finished?
- Do I have to be?
- Donna, I'm serious.
Okay, what do you need?
Rachel told me
it was her fantasy
To get married on her birthday
at the plaza hotel.
So I called to arrange it,
but then...
They're booked
for the next five years.
How did you know that?
Same reason you came to me
for help... i know what I know.
Well, I need someplace
just as good.
There is no place just as good.
So what am I supposed to do?
You already did
what you're supposed to do.
You came to me.
Now, put brody back
and don't hide him this time.
You named the bear?
You want me to help you or not?
Paul gilroy.
Yes. And you are?
I'm the guy who's gonna
keep sam tull out of jail.
And how are you
gonna do that, mister...
Specter.
Harvey specter.
You're gonna pay that fine
and admit what you did.
Well, I'm sorry
to disappoint you, mr. Specter,
But there's no way I'm admitting
to something I didn't do.
Whether you admit it or not,
You're gonna write a check
either way.
It's up to you whether it's
for $2 million or $30 million.
My associate seems
to be running late,
So go ahead, take me for
a walk down bullshit lane.
We're suing you for $30 million.
Well, I must have fired
five other people,
Because wrongful termination's
capped at $5 million.
We're not suing you
for wrongful termination.
We're suing you
for malicious prosecution.
You can't do that.
I'm not a prosecutor.
No, you're not,
but you're framing my client
For a crime he didn't commit.
So it's up to you, paul.
Write the little check
or the big check.
Ball's in your court.
Dominic, you're here early.
How are you?
Good.
In fact, I was just thinking
about the last time I was here.
You were helping me become ceo.
Oh, come on, you pretty much
became ceo all on your own.
Well, it doesn't matter
how I got there.
You're gonna help me stay there.
What's that?
The future
of battery-powered engines.
We need it, or we don't survive.
I'm guessing there's a catch.
The catch is it costs a fortune.
But I have a handshake deal
with the ceo of range tech.
We started
as mechanics together,
And if I can close in two weeks,
He'll sell me the whole company
at a price I can afford.
If I can't,
he puts it on the market.
We'll be out of business
in ten years.
(louis) what's going on?
You guys starting
the meeting without me?
No, dominic just got here early,
But the headline is he wants us
To close a handshake deal
to buy range tech
Within the next two weeks,
And I was about to tell him
that we could.
Well, I'm sorry, but we can't.
What do you mean you can't?
I mean there's no way that
we can close a deal like this
In two weeks without skipping
due diligence.
No, louis, he's known
the ceo for 30 years.
So we don't have to skip it,
But we can do
a streamlined version.
Okay, well, then we might
as well not do it at all.
We don't get it done
in that time,
I can lose this deal.
They put a clock on it.
And why would they do that?
I'll tell you why,
Because they know
you won't pay attention
To whatever it is that they're
trying to slide by you.
Slide something by me?
This is my friend.
We have a handshake deal.
A handshake deal
doesn't mean shit.
- Louis!
- It's okay, mike.
Obviously louis doesn't get me.
Because to me, a handshake deal
means everything.
So you do whatever due diligence
you can in the next week,
Because if you mess up my deal,
I'll be looking
for a new law firm.
[elevator bell dings]
Paul gilroy's lawyer called.
That was fast.
Want the bad news
or the worse news?
Why don't you give me both
And let me decide
what kind of news it is.
Not only are they not
paying the fine.
They also filed a motion
to have our suit dismissed.
- Man, I should've known.
- Should've known what?
That you were full of shit
when you said dominic calling me
To set up that meeting
didn't bother you.
I don't care who he called.
I did what I did in there
because the client comes first.
Bullshit, you antagonized me
and then dominic.
Oh, what meeting were you in?
I wasn't antagonizing him.
I was protecting him.
Oh, really?
By shitting all over his idea
and then pissing him off?
I don't care
if we pissed him off.
He doesn't need a friend.
What he needs is for us
to be great lawyers.
Louis, you have a history
of getting bent out of shape
Over hierarchy, so don't tell me
That has nothing to do
with this.
Okay, fine, mike.
You know what, you're right.
I did get bent out of shape.
Did.
But then I got over it,
because as I said,
The client comes first.
You really expect me
to believe that?
Mike, a few years ago,
dominic spent 90% of his time
Under the hood.
He is rushing into this
Because he feels it's his only
chance, and you know it.
You think harvey would sign off
on this without due diligence?
[sighs]
And let me guess, you expect me
to do all the work?
No, you take half, I take half.
We do the work together.
.
(donna)
oh, you're not hearing me.
- Oh, I'm hearing you.
- No, you're not.
I'm calling on behalf
of michael jordan.
I don't care who
you're calling for.
We're booked on that date.
Oh, but your assistant,
ginny, said that the smiths
Might be willing to, um...
First of all,
it's patricia, not ginny.
And it's the mcmillans,
not the smiths.
So, if you don't have
anything else, then...
You know what?
That was a legitimate question,
And it would be nice
if you weren't so rude.
So the least you can do
is messenger over a brochure,
Because if you don't,
Mr. Jordan is gonna call
the manager of the plaza
And get your ass fired.
Louis, I need to talk to you.
I was just on my way to see you.
About the pending
epa investigation?
- Shit.
- I thought you'd be gloating.
You're the one who wanted this.
I didn't want this.
I feared this.
If dominic buys range tech,
he's in huge trouble.
And if we tell him that
without having a solution,
He'll fire us.
That's the thing.
I have a solution.
I found a company
that has a battery division
That we can buy.
Now, we just have
to approach them and...
No. Did you not just
hear what I said?
We cannot jeopardize his deal.
We won't be jeopardizing it
If we can get them to sign
a nondisclosure agreement.
And the only way we'll be able
to get them to do that
Is if they're our client.
Well, then it's
a good thing they are.
You found one
of our own clients?
You're a genius.
Yeah, there's only one problem.
They're jack soloff's client.
Forget it, we need to find
another company.
There is no other company.
Mike, there is no way
that soloff
Will work with us on this.
He hates me.
Then we have to find a way
to make him un-hate you,
Because I'm telling you,
this deal is good for jack,
And it is good for us.
There has to be a way.
Well, then you talk to him.
Are you... are you saying
you want me
To negotiate with soloff
on my own?
I'm saying we're a team,
and there's a better chance
Of soloff saying yes
to you than to me.
- Oh, hey.
- Hey.
What are you doing here?
I was just getting an nda.
I am actually here for you.
I'm making copies of a brochure
from the plaza hotel.
Wait, so you got it done?
No, I called them,
and they were dicks,
And they got pissed at me.
So you failed?
Okay.
If by "failed,"
You mean I got the name
Of the wedding planner,
her assistant,
The couple getting married,
And a brochure
with their letterhead on it,
Then, yeah, mike,
yeah, I failed.
Whoa, donna, are you sure
you can handle this?
Do you ask a chef who's cooking
If the meal's gonna
turn out okay?
No, you sit back,
you behave yourself
Until you get the best
duck à I'orange
You've ever tasted.
Yeah, I don't really like duck
with orange stuff.
- Get out.
- Gone.
[sighs]
I like the way you operate.
Excuse me?
Never let them see you sweat.
What makes you think
I'm sweating?
My eyes.
You may have fooled opie
with that metaphor,
But we both know you got
duck à la shit.
Okay, new girl, I don't know
who you think you're talking to,
But this is what I do.
What you do.
I've been doing shit like this
Since you was an itch
in your daddy's pants.
Hang on, did you just
quote lethal weapon to me?
You got that?
Maybe you do have something.
Good luck with your duck, red.
Mr. Tull, how long have you
been working at butler trading?
Almost three years.
And how much money have you made
For their clients
over that time?
Approximately $150 million.
So let me get this straight.
You made a trade, lost money,
they did nothing.
But the day they find out
that they have to pay a fine,
They said you were acting alone
And they're letting you
go to jail?
Exactly.
And how do you know
they signed off on your trade?
Because everyone knows that
they sign off on every trade.
And, ultimately,
who would be responsible
For stopping a trade
that violated regulations?
Paul gilroy.
So it couldn't possibly be that
you knew what you were doing,
You kept it secret, and that
all of this is your fault?
It could be, but it isn't.
Well, that's interesting,
Because we have somebody
who says it is.
And who the hell is that?
- Mr. Tull's therapist.
- What?
A therapist can't testify
against their own patient.
She can if we paid for it
and he signed a waiver,
Which he did.
Mr. Tull, your therapist's
testimony is coming,
And when it does, your ability
to cut a deal goes away.
Drop this matter,
And no one ever knows
you saw a therapist at all.
You went to see
a company-provided therapist,
And you never told me?
I didn't think it mattered.
Well, it goddamn does.
Did you tell this woman
you did this?
No, because I didn't do this.
Well, they're not bringing her
in to testify to that.
I told her that I felt guilty,
As if the whole thing
was my fault.
I never said it was.
Well, you might as well have,
Because that's what
it's gonna sound like.
- Harvey...
- How could you be so stupid
To confide your feelings
to a stranger?
Because I needed help.
And if you're not gonna talk
about your feelings,
You might as well
not see a therapist at all.
You better hope
there are therapists in prison,
Because if I can't
stop her from testifying,
That's where
you're gonna end up.
[knock at door]
Mike ross, what brings you
down to my office?
I'm here with a proposal
from louis.
You're here because
louis wants something from me,
But he's too afraid to ask.
He's not afraid.
He just sent me here
because he figured
You might hear it better
coming from me.
Well...
Mckernon motors wants
to make an investment
In battery technology.
We'd like to quietly negotiate
with tanaka,
And we need your help
getting them to sign this.
And why would I do that?
Because it's huge money,
And now that
contingent compensation
Is back at the firm,
it's huge money for you.
And the last time louis came
to me with an offer like this,
It was bullshit.
Well, I'm not louis,
and this isn't bullshit.
Then I guess I just
have one question.
How much of the deal are you
authorized to give away?
50%, and that's more than fair.
Maybe it is,
but I want all of it.
You know this helps
your client, right?
I don't give a shit.
All of it or none of it.
It's gonna be none of it,
And you're just taking money
out of your own pocket.
I don't care,
because this isn't about money.
It's about getting even,
so run along.
Go tell louis I'm not
lifting a finger to help him
Unless I get everything.
Wow, you really are a dick.
I take it that means
you know where I stand.
.
Jessica, hi.
What can I do for you?
How's the wedding
planning going?
Oh, well, we're still
looking for a venue,
But things are moving along.
I hear a lot of couples fight
during this time.
Well, I happen to have
a fiancé who's smart enough
To leave everything to me.
But that is not why you're here.
I want to know
how harvey's doing.
With our case?
No, I just want to know
how he's doing.
He's doing fine.
Keep an eye on him.
I will.
[keys clacking]
[door opens]
What are you doing here?
You're coming
to my offices tomorrow
To testify against my client
and you didn't tell me?
I didn't tell you
because this is the first
I'm hearing about it.
Bullshit, I saw it.
You got subpoenaed to testify
against sam tull.
And until you just
burst in here,
I had no idea
he was your client.
Well, it doesn't matter
because you're not showing up.
And you're going to stop them
from arresting me, are you?
Because that's what
will happen if I don't.
Then get yourself someone
like me and get out of it.
For your information,
I have been to three
different men like you,
Because I care about sam,
And you know better than I do
That once he signed that
release, I have no choice.
Well, I have a way
to get you out of it,
And you're gonna do it.
They ask you something
that's gonna send him to jail,
You lie.
I can't do that.
You can, and you will,
and they'll never know.
I'll know.
And even if I didn't,
I have notes,
And if they found those,
I'd be going to jail.
Then destroy them,
because he's innocent,
And he trusted you
with everything.
And if that doesn't
mean something to you,
Then why the hell should anyone
ever trust you with anything?
Harvey, this isn't about us.
No one can ever make me
do that to you.
I'm sure sam tull
thought the same thing.
(louis) well?
It's not gonna work.
He said no?
He said he wants
100% of the deal.
- Piece of shit.
- I know.
So...
I don't know. We're gonna have
to think of something else.
[sighs]
Give it to him.
- What?
- I said give it to him.
Louis, hey,
I know we're under the gun
With this dominic thing,
but I really don't think
It's a good idea to let him
push you around like that.
I'm not letting him
push me around.
I'm listening to my leader.
What are you talking about?
Remember when you asked me where
the new louis was coming from
And I told you from me?
It wasn't from me.
It was from jessica.
She asked me to stop
the pettiness once and for all.
And if I can't do that now,
I'll never be able to do it.
Okay, then I guess
all we have to do
Is figure out a way
to sell the idea to tanaka.
Oh, trust me.
If I can do this,
I definitely can do that.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
Louis, what the hell
have you done?
What? I'm setting up
for our meeting with tanaka.
Are you kidding me?
This isn't gung ho.
Louis, they're gonna
take one look at you,
They're gonna run out the door.
No, they're not.
Mike, tanaka's a japanese
company steeped in tradition.
I don't care
what you think they are.
This is offensive.
There's absolutely
nothing offensive
About showing respect
for another culture.
And what do you know
about their culture?
Mike, trust me.
When I was in junior high,
We had an exchange student
stay with us.
Ooh, suki.
Here we go.
She was far from home
And proud of her culture,
And she set up
everything in this room
To make herself
feel comfortable,
Right down to giving
my father this very kimono
And laying out a map
of her hometown.
Louis, I want you
to listen to me.
They are gonna be here
in 45 minutes,
And if you are still
dressed like that
And this room
still looks like this,
Dominic is going to fire us.
They're not gonna be here
in 45 minutes,
'cause they're here right now.
Mr. Tanaka-san.
(tanaka) who did this?
I did.
That is a map of shikoku.
My family is from there.
I know.
How?
Because we do our homework, sir,
Just like we did
our homework on this deal.
I think we are going
to get along very nicely.
[upbeat music]
Please.
What are you doing?
Get the tea.
- You want...
- Yeah, get the tea.
Okay.
♪ ♪
[french accent] oh, you must
be the future mcmillans.
I would say sorry I'm late,
but I am not sorry.
So let us begin
discussing the details
Of your first wedding.
I'm sorry. You are?
Oh, my name
is of no consequence.
What is, is that my company
has taken over
The planning service
of the plaza hotel.
Here's our brochure.
Mm, I can see by the look
on your faces
That bitch patricia,
she did not tell you.
Bitch?
We love patricia.
Well, she's no longer with us.
As I was saying, the menu
will no longer be optional.
We'll be serving
duck à I'orange, escargot,
And foie gras.
But we're vegan.
What is that?
- It's...
- It doesn't matter.
We are french.
You eat what we serve,
or you do not eat.
Can we taste it?
Oh, would you like me to just
show you my naked body
Before we go out to dinner
and you want to sleep with me?
I need to go to the restroom.
[normal voice] okay, so
here's what's gonna happen.
She's gonna want to drop me,
And you're gonna drop
the plaza hotel.
- What?
- Cut the shit, john.
I did that so you could
have some cover.
I did some checking,
And you either need to change
the location of your wedding,
Or I'm gonna tell her
about your mistress.
Yeah.
Dr. Agard, when did sam tull
start seeing you as a patient?
Approximately six months ago.
And why did he start seeing you?
He said his job involved
taking risks,
And it was causing him stress.
So he wanted
to stop taking risks?
No, he wanted to continue.
Oh, I get it.
He wanted to continue
with the risks,
He just wanted
to feel better about it.
Yes.
And were you able
to help him feel better
About taking these risks?
Um, uh, we made progress.
- Yes or no?
- Yes.
And after you helped him
feel good about taking risks,
Did he reveal that he then lost
$50 million on one trade?
Dr. Agard, you are under oath.
And if you will not answer,
I will have a judge
compel you to answer.
Yes.
And how did he say he felt
about losing $50 million
On one trade?
He said he felt guilty about it.
So he came to you
to continue taking risks
Until he finally
lost $50 million
And then admitted
to being guilty.
That is not what she said.
I'm sorry, he just felt guilty.
You want to drop this now,
Or do you want us to hand
this tape over to the sec?
Dr. Agard, did you want to give
the testimony you just gave?
- Of course not.
- And why is that?
Because I care about my clients.
Is it possible that
you didn't want to give it
Because it's not true?
No, it's not possible.
You couldn't possibly
have been pressured
To give false testimony
against your wishes?
No, I couldn't have.
Have you ever been
pressured to do something
You didn't want to do
by a client before?
Let me rephrase.
Isn't it true that you released
a client that you cared about
From rehab for no reason
Other than you felt pressure
from a different client
Who was actually paying
the bills?
Dr. Agard, you're under oath,
And if you will not answer,
I will have a judge
compel you to answer.
Yes.
And did this person die
of an overdose
Less than 24 hours later?
Yes.
So if you let yourself
be pressured
When someone's life is at risk,
What's to make us think
you're not doing
The exact same thing right now?
.
You arrogant piece of shit.
Watch yourself.
This is my office.
Well, I don't care what it is.
How dare you betray me
like that?
- I tried to warn you.
- You didn't warn me.
You asked me to lie for you,
and I told you I wouldn't.
I asked you to lie
for sam tull...
This isn't about sam tull,
and you know it.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I opened up to you
so that we could build trust,
Not so that you could
humiliate me.
I humiliated you to help a man
You say you care about.
And our fighting
about your mother
Had nothing to do with that?
- Excuse me?
- You walked out of our session
Because you didn't want
to talk about your mother.
And the second
you had the chance
To permanently damage
our relationship, you took it.
You're insane.
And you're
a self-serving narcissist
Who will do or say anything
to get what he wants.
I did what I did in there
to protect my client.
And I don't give a shit
if it hurt your feelings or not,
Because you betrayed him
Just as much
as I'm betraying you.
And you may be the one
who's crying about it,
But he's the one who's been
accused of committing a crime.
If you're lucky,
someday you're gonna realize
What's really going on here,
and when that day comes,
I hope you find someone
to help you,
Because it isn't going to be me.
Mike, put that coffee down
and check this out.
It's a map of scarsdale...
Where I grew up.
Tanaka returned the favor.
Actually, louis,
I got that for you.
You did? Why?
Because you were right
and I was wrong,
And as crazy as it seems,
You and I actually make
a pretty good team.
Now all that's left
Is calling dominic
to set up a meeting.
Why don't you do it?
I can't.
I got to go hang my map.
Dominic, what are you
doing here?
I was just about to call you.
To say what,
that you blew up my deal?
- Because I already know.
- What?
That's right. Range tech
called me after they heard
That I was negotiating
with another company.
Problem is, I wasn't negotiating
My lawyers were
without my consent.
Okay, calm down, dominic.
There was a problem
with range tech.
I told you that I didn't want
there to be any problems!
Well, if you'd bought them,
Their problems were gonna
become your problems.
But just calm down
and take a second,
Because we brought you
a solution.
Which is what?
Mike, don't call dominic.
Tanaka pulled out.
Pulled out of what?
It doesn't matter.
You're both fired.
- Harvey, I need to talk to you.
- Not now, rachel.
- Sam tull's been arrested.
- What?
Gilroy's lawyer gave
formal notice to the sec.
They won't pay the fine
under any circumstance.
God damn it.
Gretchen, get paul gilroy
on the phone.
Harvey, what are you gonna do?
Tull can't go to prison
for this.
- No one's going to prison.
- But how do you now that?
We didn't think he'd be
arrested in the first place.
I don't care what we thought.
It's not gonna happen because
I'm not letting it happen.
I've got mr. Gilroy on line one.
Are you out of your mind?
You contacted the sec?
(gilroy) they contacted me.
And I'm not the one who filed
a malicious prosecution lawsuit.
No, you're the one
who got his ass kicked
In a deposition then turned
around and asked for more.
I didn't get my ass kicked,
mr. Specter.
That idiot therapist did,
and she no longer works for us.
But you still
don't have any proof
That I authorized those trades,
and you never will.
So I suggest
you stop harassing me
And focus on getting
your client out of jail.
You heard the man.
We're dropping the lawsuit?
No, we're doubling the damages.
Get it done.
You son of a bitch.
You set us up.
I'm sorry, louis, I have no
idea what you're talking about.
Oh, bullshit. You told
tanaka not to make a deal.
Yes, I did.
At first, it looked like
a good idea,
But then I did my due diligence,
And lo and behold, it didn't.
Was that before or after
You leaked our meeting
to range tech?
I have to say, I'm appalled.
I mean, after you've been
so aboveboard
In all your dealings with me,
To think that I would
go behind your back
And leak news of that meeting
with no possible chance
Of it being linked back to me,
that's really offensive.
It is linked back to you,
plain as day.
Then I guess you two
must have some sort of proof,
Because if you don't,
You can walk yourselves
the hell out of my office.
It's one thing for you
to have your feud with me,
But you just cost your firm
a huge piece of business.
Let me explain to you
what I already told him.
This isn't about business.
It's about getting even.
Harvey, do you have a minute?
If you're here to tell me
to drop that countersuit...
I'm not telling you
to drop anything.
I'm just saying in addition
to attacking gilroy,
We should be getting proof
that sam got the authorization
For those trades.
We don't have any proof.
We can if we get
some of the other traders
To come forward
and say how it went.
They'll never testify to that.
Harvey, that therapist
was the company therapist.
Those traders saw her
on a regular basis
To keep their shit together.
So, if sam opened up to her
about work,
Then some of the other traders
must have too.
She can't speak to that.
Of course she can.
If tull waived privilege,
then they all did.
You know that.
It doesn't matter.
You saw what I did to her.
She's not gonna want to help us.
It's not about helping us.
It's about helping her client.
I can't ask her to do that.
- Why not?
- Because I can't.
- Harvey, what's going on?
- Nothing's going on.
How did you know those things
about her in that deposition?
Because I did.
Does it have something
to do with the fact
That you've been having
panic attacks
And that she's your therapist?
- Because if it does...
- This conversation is over.
Look, I am not trying
to butt into things
That don't concern me,
but this isn't about you.
This is about keeping
sam tull out of prison.
.
What the hell
are you doing here?
You two don't work
for me anymore.
Just give us a minute
to explain.
There's nothing to explain.
You blew up my deal
and ruined a friendship
Because you thought
you knew better than me.
We do know better than you.
You're an arrogant
son of a bitch.
Dominic, this is a draft
of a class-action lawsuit
Headed range tech's way
The second
the epa's report comes out.
That's the same report
that your friend kept buried.
And if you'd bought them,
That suit would have
been headed your way.
So, yes, we blew up the deal,
But that man
was never your friend.
You lied to me,
and worse than that,
You didn't respect me.
I am sorry. I shouldn't
have antagonized you.
And I shouldn't have said
that rushing through this deal
Without doing due diligence
was feasible.
You see, the bottom line is,
is that we were both right
When we tried to do
this deal with tanaka.
And now that we've got
nothing to hide from you,
There is nothing to stop us
from finding you someone else.
So, instead of standing here
kissing my ass,
Why don't you get to work
doing that?
If you're here to apologize,
I'm not interested.
I'm not here to apologize.
I'm here because I need
to look at your files.
There really is no end
to your arrogance.
I wouldn't ask if this wasn't
The only way to keep sam
out of prison.
I'm not giving you
sam tull's file.
And I'm not asking for it.
I want to see all the files
of the other traders you saw.
Are you out of your mind?
No, I'm not. They all signed
the same waiver sam did.
Some of them must have admitted
the way it works at butler,
And it's in your notes.
Let me see
if I have my facts straight.
You eviscerate me, justify it,
And then waltz back here
as if nothing happened.
I know something happened,
but now is not the time.
You mean now is not the time
as long as you need a favor.
Oh, god damn it,
you're not doing me a favor.
You're helping your patient,
the one you said
You went to see three different
lawyers to keep from betraying.
And if you hadn't betrayed me,
You wouldn't be
in this position right now.
What do you want me to say...
I'm sorry?
As a matter of fact, I do.
You think I wanted
to depose you like that?
It made me sick.
I hated every
goddamn second of it,
Because I know all you've
been trying to do is help me,
And the only reason
I didn't apologize before
Is because if I knew
it kept sam out of prison,
I'd do it all again.
Now, are you gonna help me?
Harvey, even if
I wanted to help you,
It... it doesn't say
those things in my files.
I need them anyway.
I just told you they
don't have what you need.
I know that, and you know that,
But they don't know that.
You're gonna try and bluff them?
It won't work.
You saw what I did
in there to you,
And that was something
I didn't want to do.
Trust me,
they won't know what hit 'em.
[elevator bell dings]
We get fired by mckernon motors,
And you didn't tell me
and you didn't tell harvey?
- Wait, jessica...
- God damn it.
We didn't tell anyone
because we were fired
For less than a day,
and then we fixed it.
Oh, you fixed it?
Yes, it was all
a misunderstanding.
Now dominic's back on board.
I don't give a shit
that dominic is back on board
And neither does
fletcher engines.
- Fletcher engines?
- That's right.
In the less than a day that
you were fired by mckernon,
Jack soloff signed
fletcher as a client,
And now I have
to let mckernon go.
That son of a bitch.
Jessica, he set
this whole thing up.
Oh, and I'm sure you did
nothing to antagonize him.
I did do nothing.
I swear, I wasn't petty.
I trusted him,
and then he used that trust
To stab us in the back.
Jessica, you have no idea.
Louis has never been
more right in his life.
You can't dump mckernon.
It'll kill harvey.
Well, we can't goddamn
represent them now,
And you know it.
We can if you tell jack
he has to drop fletcher.
Do you realize the position
you're putting me in?
Fletcher is worth three times
what mckernon is.
I'm sorry you're in
this position right now,
But for once, I'm not
the one who put you in it.
Jack soloff is.
(donna) dinner is served.
I guess that means you got opie
his bridal gift after all.
I did.
And I shouldn't have been
so standoffish with you
In the file room.
Well, maybe I shouldn't
have had that be
Our first interaction.
No, that's not on you.
That's on me.
I never welcomed you
to the firm, and I should have.
You know, when I was
a young mother,
First week of school, every day
I dropped my little girl off.
When I left, she cried.
Friday came, I left,
she didn't cry.
So I did.
What are you saying?
You didn't welcome me
to the firm
Because you weren't ready to see
your little girl move on.
Are you saying harvey
is my little girl?
I'm saying you weren't
ready to move on.
You're all right, gretchen.
Hope you like french.
Hi.
You know, you didn't have
to schedule an appointment
Just to tell me
how it turned out.
I scheduled an appointment
to give you these.
Thank you very much.
They're from sam tull.
Did you get me anything?
I did.
I'm ready to talk
about my mother.
[gentle folk music]
[groans]
♪ ♪
This is beautiful.
Why did...
I wanted to celebrate
a special occasion.
What's the special occasion?
I got us the plaza hotel
On your birthday.
For our wedding?
Yeah.
Oh.
[giggles]
Oh, that is the sweetest
thing you've done
Since you asked me to marry you.
No, it's the sweetest
thing I've done
Until the next thing I do.
- Oh, mike.
- Mm.
I mean, how did you do it?
That must have been impossible.
No, it was a piece of cake.
You went to donna, didn't you?
That's why it was
a piece of cake.
[chuckles]
♪ ♪
[clears throat]
Jessica, what are you
doing here so late?
I didn't get a chance
to congratulate you
On signing fletcher engines.
Hey, good news travels fast.
Yes, it does, and you're going
to drop them even faster.
I take it this has
something to do
With our long-standing
relationship
With mckernon motors.
You know damn well
what this has to do with.
I know that my client
Is the fourth-largest
engine manufacturer
In the country.
And if you had
landed them like a man,
I'd be the first one in here
with a bottle of champagne.
But you did it by putting
a shiv in your fellow attorneys.
So this...
It's how it's gonna be.
And by "fellow attorneys,"
don't you really mean "harvey"?
Watch yourself, jack,
And drop fletcher engines
by morning.
If you don't, I will.
By morning it is.
And by afternoon,
the entire firm's gonna know
That you chose a mid-size client
over fletcher
Because harvey specter
has an attachment to them...
And you have
an attachment to him.
I admire people
who challenge me, jack.
But there's a limit to that,
and you are on the very edge.
So let me be clear.
This is your last chance
to work with me.
Take it, and you have a future.
Don't, and you can go ask
daniel hardman for a job,
Because we both know
that's how you got the idea
For fletcher engines
in the first place.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪