1
00:00:00,060 --> 00:00:01,239
Previously on Suits...

2
00:00:01,263 --> 00:00:03,457
Walter, I can't guarantee you
we'll win,

3
00:00:03,459 --> 00:00:06,893
but I can guarantee you
that I will never sell you out.

4
00:00:06,917 --> 00:00:08,839
Well, you told me that
Mike Ross wasn't a threat,

5
00:00:08,855 --> 00:00:10,377
and then he handcuffed us
with a T.R.O.

6
00:00:10,392 --> 00:00:12,540
I want proof that
he's giving up his bid,

7
00:00:12,564 --> 00:00:13,927
and if I don't get it
by the morning,

8
00:00:13,951 --> 00:00:15,597
I'm gonna call
my private investigators,

9
00:00:15,621 --> 00:00:16,599
and I'm gonna finish
what I started.

10
00:00:16,624 --> 00:00:18,254
What did Harvey tell you?

11
00:00:18,278 --> 00:00:19,724
Looks like he told me the truth.

12
00:00:19,748 --> 00:00:21,093
We're done.

13
00:00:21,119 --> 00:00:23,367
I want you to stop
the personal attacks on Mike.

14
00:00:23,391 --> 00:00:25,073
You told me this
wasn't gonna be a problem.

15
00:00:25,095 --> 00:00:28,579
You don't have to stop this
because you're some changed man.

16
00:00:28,604 --> 00:00:30,652
You have to stop this
because you owe me.

17
00:00:30,676 --> 00:00:31,677
Mr. Ross.

18
00:00:31,678 --> 00:00:32,639
Eric Woodall.

19
00:00:32,664 --> 00:00:34,127
I'm the U.S. attorney for...

20
00:00:34,151 --> 00:00:35,564
The southern district
of New York.

21
00:00:35,588 --> 00:00:36,733
I know who you are.

22
00:00:36,758 --> 00:00:38,404
Since when does the S.E.C.
go around

23
00:00:38,428 --> 00:00:40,976
intimidating law firms
by going after their clients?

24
00:00:41,001 --> 00:00:42,163
They don't, but they will

25
00:00:42,188 --> 00:00:43,791
when Eric Woodall starts there
next week.

26
00:00:43,808 --> 00:00:44,809
It started.

27
00:00:44,810 --> 00:00:47,659
Seven clients, seven subpoenas,

28
00:00:47,684 --> 00:00:49,204
all coming tomorrow.

29
00:01:07,584 --> 00:01:09,815
Uh, excuse me,
you don't have an appointment.

30
00:01:09,839 --> 00:01:10,934
I don't need an appointment.

31
00:01:10,959 --> 00:01:12,722
Sit down, shut up, and listen.

32
00:01:12,747 --> 00:01:15,630
Harvey might forgive you because
you returned those recordings,

33
00:01:15,654 --> 00:01:16,598
but I don't.

34
00:01:16,622 --> 00:01:17,934
- Donna.
- Not done.

35
00:01:17,959 --> 00:01:20,140
What Harvey did with Gillis,
it was harsh,

36
00:01:20,164 --> 00:01:23,080
but using what I told you
in a private conversation...

37
00:01:23,105 --> 00:01:25,220
That crosses a line
that even Harvey never would.

38
00:01:25,244 --> 00:01:26,940
- Donna.
- Still not done.

39
00:01:26,964 --> 00:01:30,030
When you left our firm,
you left me too,

40
00:01:30,055 --> 00:01:32,520
but I honestly thought
that we'd always be friends.

41
00:01:32,545 --> 00:01:35,528
Now I'm not so sure.

42
00:01:35,552 --> 00:01:37,449
Amy, did you send Donna
the package?

43
00:01:37,474 --> 00:01:39,004
Guilt gift. Didn't open it.

44
00:01:39,028 --> 00:01:41,326
It was a balenciaga
classic town bag.

45
00:01:41,351 --> 00:01:42,395
Ivory?

46
00:01:42,419 --> 00:01:43,748
Anthracite
with an outside pocket.

47
00:01:43,773 --> 00:01:44,867
His idea or yours?

48
00:01:44,892 --> 00:01:46,171
Don't answer that.

49
00:01:46,196 --> 00:01:49,546
It was yours.

50
00:01:49,571 --> 00:01:50,782
I'm sorry, Donna.

51
00:01:50,807 --> 00:01:52,487
You and Harvey want to
knock each other out,

52
00:01:52,511 --> 00:01:54,491
you go right ahead.

53
00:01:54,516 --> 00:01:56,620
But don't ever betray me again.

54
00:01:59,211 --> 00:02:00,212
Nice shoes.

55
00:02:04,190 --> 00:02:05,642
She's even better
than I imagined.

56
00:02:18,108 --> 00:02:21,091
Looking for this?

57
00:02:21,115 --> 00:02:23,463
Harvey Specter.

58
00:02:23,488 --> 00:02:25,969
What brings you to Montclair
at 7:00 in the morning?

59
00:02:25,993 --> 00:02:27,857
Oh, you know
what brings me here.

60
00:02:27,882 --> 00:02:30,681
I woke up to find these
on my welcome mat.

61
00:02:30,705 --> 00:02:33,270
Well, as much as I'd love
to have been responsible

62
00:02:33,295 --> 00:02:36,412
for subpoenaing seven
of your firm's top clients,

63
00:02:36,437 --> 00:02:38,701
I didn't even know about this
till just now.

64
00:02:38,725 --> 00:02:40,848
You didn't even have the balls
to come at me directly.

65
00:02:40,864 --> 00:02:42,543
Get off my property.

66
00:02:42,568 --> 00:02:43,813
What's the matter, Eric?

67
00:02:43,838 --> 00:02:46,420
You're afraid
I'll get you fired again?

68
00:02:46,445 --> 00:02:48,375
I get it.

69
00:02:48,399 --> 00:02:51,148
You want to hear me say
I'm using my new position

70
00:02:51,172 --> 00:02:53,019
to destroy your business,

71
00:02:53,044 --> 00:02:55,575
'cause you're the piece
of garbage that got me fired.

72
00:02:55,600 --> 00:02:57,113
Isn't that what you
want to hear me say?

73
00:02:57,137 --> 00:02:59,602
Oh, I know
you'll never say that,

74
00:02:59,627 --> 00:03:01,357
but I do want you to admit
that you sent

75
00:03:01,382 --> 00:03:03,412
an agent Brian Harris
after my firm.

76
00:03:03,437 --> 00:03:05,333
Sorry.
I don't even have jurisdiction

77
00:03:05,357 --> 00:03:06,837
over that department.

78
00:03:06,862 --> 00:03:09,510
That department's run by a man
name Sean Cahill.

79
00:03:09,535 --> 00:03:10,763
So all on his own,

80
00:03:10,787 --> 00:03:13,352
Sean Cahill just happened
to target my firm?

81
00:03:13,377 --> 00:03:15,425
Well, he is a killer attorney

82
00:03:15,449 --> 00:03:18,299
with a nose for sleazy lawyers,

83
00:03:18,323 --> 00:03:19,584
and I should know.

84
00:03:19,609 --> 00:03:21,539
We came up together
at the Justice Department.

85
00:03:21,564 --> 00:03:23,729
You know, that little
governmental agency

86
00:03:23,753 --> 00:03:25,182
that protects their own?

87
00:03:25,207 --> 00:03:27,220
Well, Eric, your big brother
couldn't protect you

88
00:03:27,245 --> 00:03:28,557
from getting fired before,

89
00:03:28,582 --> 00:03:31,230
and I don't see how this is
gonna be any different,

90
00:03:31,255 --> 00:03:34,362
and by the way,
that's yesterday's paper.

91
00:03:35,816 --> 00:03:37,429
You wanted to see me?

92
00:03:37,454 --> 00:03:38,455
Sure did.

93
00:03:38,456 --> 00:03:40,637
Have a seat.

94
00:03:40,661 --> 00:03:42,641
I was going over
our trade sheets.

95
00:03:42,666 --> 00:03:44,363
Couldn't help but notice

96
00:03:44,388 --> 00:03:46,619
you bought another 100,000
shares of Gillis Industries.

97
00:03:46,643 --> 00:03:47,871
It's gonna be fine.

98
00:03:47,896 --> 00:03:49,576
Do I look like an asshole
to you?

99
00:03:49,601 --> 00:03:50,997
Where the hell
did you get the money?

100
00:03:51,021 --> 00:03:53,469
You know where I got the money.

101
00:03:53,493 --> 00:03:54,889
I bought those shares on margin.

102
00:03:54,913 --> 00:03:55,957
And leveraged my company.

103
00:03:55,982 --> 00:03:57,061
The bylaws said I can do it.

104
00:03:57,086 --> 00:03:58,632
I don't care
what the bylaws say,

105
00:03:58,656 --> 00:04:00,269
you did this without asking.

106
00:04:00,293 --> 00:04:01,375
Look, I know you're pissed.

107
00:04:01,380 --> 00:04:02,441
Oh, I'm not pissed.

108
00:04:02,465 --> 00:04:03,977
I've been waiting for you

109
00:04:04,002 --> 00:04:05,649
to have the balls
to do something like this

110
00:04:05,673 --> 00:04:06,674
since you got here.

111
00:04:06,693 --> 00:04:08,256
You raised my risk,

112
00:04:08,280 --> 00:04:10,162
but you also raised my reward,
and on top of it,

113
00:04:10,184 --> 00:04:12,833
you did it like
an investment banker,

114
00:04:12,858 --> 00:04:14,494
without permission.

115
00:04:18,171 --> 00:04:20,369
Well, thank you, Jon.

116
00:04:20,393 --> 00:04:22,764
Go get 'em.

117
00:04:24,820 --> 00:04:26,500
One more thing. Yeah?

118
00:04:26,525 --> 00:04:29,206
You have a week
to de-leverage my company.

119
00:04:29,231 --> 00:04:31,336
If you don't,
you're out of a job.

120
00:04:35,380 --> 00:04:36,608
You want to explain to me why

121
00:04:36,633 --> 00:04:38,447
you went to Eric Woodall's house
this morning?

122
00:04:38,471 --> 00:04:40,000
I understand
you're bent out of shape

123
00:04:40,025 --> 00:04:41,538
because I stepped on
your territory...

124
00:04:41,562 --> 00:04:43,408
You think I give a shit
about my territory?

125
00:04:43,433 --> 00:04:44,880
What the hell are you doing
in here?

126
00:04:44,904 --> 00:04:45,986
Listen, I really don't care

127
00:04:45,990 --> 00:04:47,553
if you work this thing or I do,

128
00:04:47,577 --> 00:04:49,691
but whoever it is has to
not be an idiot.

129
00:04:49,715 --> 00:04:51,445
And how, exactly, am I an idiot?

130
00:04:51,470 --> 00:04:53,952
- You poked the bear.
- Eric Woodall isn't the bear.

131
00:04:53,976 --> 00:04:55,872
No. I am.

132
00:04:55,897 --> 00:04:58,830
And whatever you were
about to say, don't say it.

133
00:04:58,854 --> 00:05:01,136
Harvey, this is his case.

134
00:05:01,161 --> 00:05:02,557
It's why we brought him in,

135
00:05:02,581 --> 00:05:03,809
and I don't want you involved.

136
00:05:03,834 --> 00:05:04,835
Me?

137
00:05:04,836 --> 00:05:05,981
I'm the one who found out

138
00:05:06,006 --> 00:05:07,184
it's not Woodall
coming after us, it's...

139
00:05:07,209 --> 00:05:08,939
Sean Cahill.

140
00:05:08,963 --> 00:05:10,307
You think I didn't know that?

141
00:05:10,332 --> 00:05:12,781
These are my clients,
and when they call in a panic,

142
00:05:12,806 --> 00:05:14,786
I need to be the voice
on the other end of the line.

143
00:05:14,811 --> 00:05:17,059
Then be the voice
on the other end of the line,

144
00:05:17,083 --> 00:05:18,829
but you're not
handling the S.E.C.

145
00:05:18,854 --> 00:05:20,667
I'm the reason
they're coming after us.

146
00:05:20,692 --> 00:05:22,840
Which is why you wanted to
hire Jeff in the first place.

147
00:05:22,864 --> 00:05:24,644
That was before
all this became real.

148
00:05:24,669 --> 00:05:25,864
Now that it's happening,

149
00:05:25,888 --> 00:05:27,066
he doesn't want to
sit on the sidelines.

150
00:05:27,091 --> 00:05:28,520
Damn right I don't.

151
00:05:28,544 --> 00:05:30,709
Well, then find yourself
a comfortable spot on the bench,

152
00:05:30,733 --> 00:05:33,021
because like it or not,
Jeff's in charge.

153
00:05:35,579 --> 00:05:38,896
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪

154
00:05:38,921 --> 00:05:42,355
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪

155
00:05:42,379 --> 00:05:45,696
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪

156
00:05:45,721 --> 00:05:49,038
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪

157
00:05:49,062 --> 00:05:51,755
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪

158
00:05:51,757 --> 00:05:55,762
♪ Suits 4x04 ♪ Leveraged
Original Air Date on July 9, 2014

159
00:05:56,080 --> 00:05:57,693
♪ all right ♪

160
00:05:57,717 --> 00:06:02,955
♪ All that time imagine this ♪

161
00:06:02,980 --> 00:06:04,649
♪ The greenback boogie ♪

162
00:06:04,673 --> 00:06:06,675
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man.

163
00:06:10,615 --> 00:06:12,044
So it go just like
you said it would?

164
00:06:12,068 --> 00:06:13,413
Exactly, except for the part

165
00:06:13,438 --> 00:06:15,185
where if I don't find
a new investor in a week,

166
00:06:15,210 --> 00:06:16,388
I'm out of a job.

167
00:06:16,413 --> 00:06:18,059
I'm surprised
he gave you a week.

168
00:06:18,083 --> 00:06:20,231
- Amy, it's not funny.
- I know it isn't.

169
00:06:20,255 --> 00:06:22,820
I was just trying to make
the best of the situation.

170
00:06:22,845 --> 00:06:24,825
Well, if you want to make
the best of the situation,

171
00:06:24,850 --> 00:06:26,580
get me a meeting
with Tony Gianopolous,

172
00:06:26,605 --> 00:06:29,972
because if I can't get
in there...

173
00:06:29,997 --> 00:06:31,225
I'm in trouble.

174
00:06:31,250 --> 00:06:33,398
We're in trouble.

175
00:06:33,422 --> 00:06:35,151
You really mean that?

176
00:06:35,175 --> 00:06:38,943
You think I'm staying here
if you leave?

177
00:06:38,968 --> 00:06:40,247
Thank you, Amy.

178
00:06:40,272 --> 00:06:41,483
I'm just kidding.

179
00:06:41,508 --> 00:06:42,820
Epstein's been trying
to poach me

180
00:06:42,845 --> 00:06:44,458
since the day I got here.
Mmm. Tch.

181
00:06:44,482 --> 00:06:46,462
Yeah, you think those flowers
bought themselves?

182
00:06:46,487 --> 00:06:48,267
Mm-mm.

183
00:06:48,292 --> 00:06:51,415
You... wow.

184
00:06:57,481 --> 00:06:59,294
Can I talk to you a second?

185
00:06:59,319 --> 00:07:01,232
If you want an update
on the takeover,

186
00:07:01,257 --> 00:07:02,937
you should talk to Harvey.

187
00:07:02,961 --> 00:07:05,275
That's not why I'm here.

188
00:07:05,300 --> 00:07:06,913
Look, Logan, I-I know that you...

189
00:07:06,937 --> 00:07:09,519
I have five companies here

190
00:07:09,544 --> 00:07:11,057
that I'm looking at
for my next deal,

191
00:07:11,081 --> 00:07:13,162
and I need someone
to evaluate them

192
00:07:13,186 --> 00:07:16,035
from a legal standpoint.

193
00:07:16,060 --> 00:07:18,575
- Your next deal.
- Yeah, my next deal.

194
00:07:18,599 --> 00:07:21,031
Harvey told me
not to hurt my future

195
00:07:21,056 --> 00:07:22,451
by going below the belt
with Mike,

196
00:07:22,475 --> 00:07:23,889
so instead of not
hurting my future,

197
00:07:23,913 --> 00:07:25,726
I thought I'd start
planning for it.

198
00:07:25,751 --> 00:07:28,567
So then maybe Harvey is who
you should be planning it with.

199
00:07:28,591 --> 00:07:30,271
Well, Harvey's got stuff to do,

200
00:07:30,296 --> 00:07:32,477
and he's not the one who
convinced me to back off Mike.

201
00:07:32,501 --> 00:07:34,615
Are you saying that I owe you?

202
00:07:34,639 --> 00:07:35,751
No, I'm not saying that,

203
00:07:35,776 --> 00:07:37,189
but that is what you said to me.

204
00:07:37,213 --> 00:07:39,460
So we're just gonna go
back and forth, trading favors?

205
00:07:39,484 --> 00:07:40,796
Rachel, this isn't a favor.

206
00:07:40,821 --> 00:07:42,534
I have a board meeting
on Friday.

207
00:07:42,559 --> 00:07:43,904
I need to be prepared.

208
00:07:43,929 --> 00:07:46,234
So are you my lawyer or not?

209
00:07:48,239 --> 00:07:49,484
I will get right on it.

210
00:07:49,509 --> 00:07:51,429
Thank you.

211
00:07:55,491 --> 00:07:57,404
Louis, I need your help.
We're gonna need to...

212
00:07:57,428 --> 00:07:58,596
Don't speak.

213
00:08:01,856 --> 00:08:03,636
You may speak.

214
00:08:03,661 --> 00:08:04,756
What were you doing?

215
00:08:04,780 --> 00:08:07,796
Just thanking
the lord God almighty.

216
00:08:07,821 --> 00:08:09,601
We taking down Jessica?
We firing Malone?

217
00:08:09,625 --> 00:08:10,670
I am tingling.

218
00:08:10,695 --> 00:08:12,007
What, Harvey? Just tell me what.

219
00:08:12,032 --> 00:08:14,981
Mike Ross just bought another
2% of Gillis Industries.

220
00:08:15,005 --> 00:08:16,969
He must be leveraged up
to his scrawny little neck.

221
00:08:16,994 --> 00:08:19,158
Exactly, and he's gonna be
scrambling for funding.

222
00:08:19,182 --> 00:08:21,195
You want me
to get your T.R.O. removed.

223
00:08:21,220 --> 00:08:22,265
How do you know that?

224
00:08:22,290 --> 00:08:24,236
Because you pissed off
judge Ramos

225
00:08:24,261 --> 00:08:25,607
and now she can't stand you.

226
00:08:25,632 --> 00:08:26,810
How do you know that?

227
00:08:26,835 --> 00:08:28,030
Oh, because I keep
a list of your enemies.

228
00:08:28,055 --> 00:08:29,350
You want to see it?
Just get it done.

229
00:08:29,375 --> 00:08:30,486
Oh, I'm gonna get it done.

230
00:08:30,510 --> 00:08:32,156
It's like taking candy
from a baby.

231
00:08:32,181 --> 00:08:33,695
Louis, we're splitting
Mike's focus.

232
00:08:33,719 --> 00:08:35,565
That doesn't mean
he won't be prepared.

233
00:08:35,590 --> 00:08:36,868
Oh, he can prepare all he wants,

234
00:08:36,893 --> 00:08:39,158
but the student is about to meet
the master,

235
00:08:39,182 --> 00:08:41,212
because Ralph Macchio
doesn't stand a chance

236
00:08:41,237 --> 00:08:42,817
against Mr. Miyagi.

237
00:08:42,841 --> 00:08:45,680
You know The Karate Kid?

238
00:08:53,534 --> 00:08:54,819
That's not cool, Harvey.

239
00:08:57,878 --> 00:09:01,111
Oh, let me see
if I can guess why you're here.

240
00:09:01,136 --> 00:09:02,932
You came to tell me
the way I handled Harvey

241
00:09:02,957 --> 00:09:05,506
this morning was sexy.

242
00:09:05,531 --> 00:09:07,477
Oh, you mean when I told him
to leave you alone?

243
00:09:07,502 --> 00:09:11,371
And the way that I allowed you
to do that was very sexy.

244
00:09:11,395 --> 00:09:13,157
Uh-huh.

245
00:09:13,182 --> 00:09:15,630
And this is...

246
00:09:15,655 --> 00:09:17,335
The Griffen Cosmetics subpoena.

247
00:09:17,359 --> 00:09:18,438
I looked them all over.

248
00:09:18,463 --> 00:09:19,641
This is the weakest one.

249
00:09:19,666 --> 00:09:21,646
- The weakest one?
- Exactly.

250
00:09:21,671 --> 00:09:24,720
Once this one goes down,
the others fall like dominos.

251
00:09:24,744 --> 00:09:26,758
First of all, if I were gonna
take that strategy,

252
00:09:26,783 --> 00:09:28,229
I would go for the hardest one.

253
00:09:28,253 --> 00:09:29,999
Second of all,
why don't you walk yourself

254
00:09:30,024 --> 00:09:31,737
back to your office
and let me do my job?

255
00:09:31,761 --> 00:09:33,976
Excuse me?

256
00:09:34,001 --> 00:09:37,619
You told Harvey you
brought me in to handle this.

257
00:09:37,643 --> 00:09:41,545
Your job isn't to worry about
what I told Harvey.

258
00:09:41,570 --> 00:09:44,352
Your job is to worry about
what I'm telling you.

259
00:09:44,376 --> 00:09:46,023
And what I'm telling you

260
00:09:46,047 --> 00:09:48,495
is that I'm not walking
into an S.E.C. negotiation

261
00:09:48,520 --> 00:09:49,481
with a babysitter.

262
00:09:49,506 --> 00:09:51,002
Negotiation?

263
00:09:51,026 --> 00:09:52,422
This is going to be a war.

264
00:09:52,446 --> 00:09:54,627
I know that, and I'm gonna
win it with one shot.

265
00:09:54,651 --> 00:09:56,131
Then I suggest you
warm up to this.

266
00:09:56,155 --> 00:09:59,071
You're not walking into
the S.E.C. with a babysitter.

267
00:09:59,096 --> 00:10:01,969
You're walking in there
with a bazooka.

268
00:10:04,860 --> 00:10:06,423
Hey, Mike,
you need to see something.

269
00:10:06,447 --> 00:10:08,210
No, I don't have time.

270
00:10:08,235 --> 00:10:09,882
I'm working on
the Gianopolous proposal.

271
00:10:09,907 --> 00:10:12,127
Yeah, that proposal isn't
gonna matter if they win this.

272
00:10:18,043 --> 00:10:20,491
Goddamn it.

273
00:10:20,515 --> 00:10:22,212
Harvey's trying to roll back
the T.R.O.?

274
00:10:22,237 --> 00:10:23,238
No, it's not Harvey.

275
00:10:23,239 --> 00:10:24,240
Check the docket.

276
00:10:24,242 --> 00:10:27,425
It's some woman named Lois Litt.

277
00:10:30,507 --> 00:10:32,554
Yeah.

278
00:10:32,578 --> 00:10:33,579
I know how to handle her.

279
00:10:33,580 --> 00:10:35,077
Um, here.

280
00:10:35,102 --> 00:10:36,615
This is 90% done. Check it over.

281
00:10:36,639 --> 00:10:38,619
Make sure there's not
one comma out of place.

282
00:10:38,644 --> 00:10:40,792
Mike, come on,
you know I can do more than...

283
00:10:40,816 --> 00:10:42,429
I don't have time, Amy.
Just do it.

284
00:10:42,453 --> 00:10:43,955
Okay.

285
00:10:46,964 --> 00:10:49,262
How long did you work
in this shit hole?

286
00:10:49,287 --> 00:10:51,935
Sorry I'm late.
Been up to my neck in work.

287
00:10:51,959 --> 00:10:54,041
Just filed seven huge subpoenas.

288
00:10:54,066 --> 00:10:55,445
- Yeah, we know what you filed.
- Oh.

289
00:10:55,469 --> 00:10:56,932
I see you brought the missus.

290
00:10:56,956 --> 00:11:00,741
Jessica, whatever you're
about to say, don't say it.

291
00:11:00,765 --> 00:11:02,795
How about I say it with this?

292
00:11:02,820 --> 00:11:04,098
Ooh, a subpoena?

293
00:11:05,126 --> 00:11:06,388
Smells fresh. It is.

294
00:11:06,413 --> 00:11:08,209
And you'll be answering it
in court tomorrow.

295
00:11:08,233 --> 00:11:09,528
Oh, well then I better see

296
00:11:09,553 --> 00:11:12,586
what flavor bullshit
you're serving up.

297
00:11:14,566 --> 00:11:16,196
Ah, ah, now, this is a good one.

298
00:11:16,220 --> 00:11:20,606
"Malicious prosecution
of Pearson Specter clients,"

299
00:11:20,631 --> 00:11:21,959
and how exactly
are we doing that?

300
00:11:21,984 --> 00:11:22,985
I'll tell you how.

301
00:11:22,986 --> 00:11:24,349
You come at our clients.

302
00:11:24,373 --> 00:11:25,718
Our clients leave us.

303
00:11:25,743 --> 00:11:27,021
You drop their cases.

304
00:11:27,046 --> 00:11:28,559
Well, I certainly
wouldn't tell them

305
00:11:28,583 --> 00:11:30,263
that's how to avoid
S.E.C. scrutiny,

306
00:11:30,288 --> 00:11:33,565
but it's not my fault
if dropping Pearson Specter

307
00:11:33,590 --> 00:11:34,591
starts catching on.

308
00:11:34,615 --> 00:11:35,626
Enough bullshit.

309
00:11:35,651 --> 00:11:37,348
You're targeting my clients

310
00:11:37,372 --> 00:11:39,470
on behalf of Eric Woodall,
and you know it.

311
00:11:39,494 --> 00:11:41,390
That is a lovely theory,
but if you had any proof,

312
00:11:41,415 --> 00:11:42,978
you wouldn't be standing here
right now.

313
00:11:43,003 --> 00:11:44,899
I have proof, Sean.

314
00:11:44,923 --> 00:11:46,119
I have proof you filed

315
00:11:46,144 --> 00:11:47,757
seven cases in one day
against our clients,

316
00:11:47,782 --> 00:11:49,244
which we both know
has never happened

317
00:11:49,268 --> 00:11:50,765
in the history of the S.E.C.

318
00:11:50,789 --> 00:11:52,218
It has now.

319
00:11:52,242 --> 00:11:55,091
We've filed nine cases
against clients of Weil Gotshal,

320
00:11:55,115 --> 00:11:56,260
eight against Skaaden,

321
00:11:56,285 --> 00:11:58,867
and six against Cravath.

322
00:11:58,892 --> 00:12:00,705
Welcome to the new S.E.C.

323
00:12:00,730 --> 00:12:02,410
We target law firms.

324
00:12:02,434 --> 00:12:04,414
And as long as we're not
only targeting yours,

325
00:12:04,439 --> 00:12:07,137
the only way to shut this down
is to shut us down.

326
00:12:07,162 --> 00:12:08,257
You and I both know

327
00:12:08,282 --> 00:12:10,847
what's really
going on here, Sean,

328
00:12:10,872 --> 00:12:12,017
and I'm gonna prove it.

329
00:12:12,041 --> 00:12:13,970
Well, good luck,
but how do you think

330
00:12:13,995 --> 00:12:16,327
judge Hopkins is gonna respond
to your allegations

331
00:12:16,352 --> 00:12:17,915
when I tell him
they're coming from a man

332
00:12:17,939 --> 00:12:21,841
who is about to be fired?

333
00:12:21,866 --> 00:12:23,896
Oh, you... you didn't tell her.

334
00:12:23,921 --> 00:12:27,355
Ooh, that's awkward.

335
00:12:27,379 --> 00:12:28,748
I'll see you in court.

336
00:12:31,272 --> 00:12:33,286
- Jessica!
- I don't want to hear it.

337
00:12:33,311 --> 00:12:35,040
- Well, you need to hear it.
- What?

338
00:12:35,064 --> 00:12:36,494
That you lied to me?

339
00:12:36,518 --> 00:12:38,081
You know, I didn't
actually lie to you.

340
00:12:38,106 --> 00:12:40,086
Oh, no, no, no.
You tell me that you didn't lie

341
00:12:40,111 --> 00:12:41,974
because we never directly
asked you the question,

342
00:12:41,999 --> 00:12:43,200
and I will knock your head off.

343
00:12:43,201 --> 00:12:44,202
All right, fine.

344
00:12:44,204 --> 00:12:45,516
I lied.

345
00:12:45,541 --> 00:12:47,104
I lied
because it doesn't matter.

346
00:12:47,128 --> 00:12:49,359
I want to fight for you,
and I'm the best man to do it.

347
00:12:49,383 --> 00:12:51,163
Well, the new part
of the equation

348
00:12:51,188 --> 00:12:53,067
is that you just made me
look like a fool.

349
00:12:53,092 --> 00:12:54,455
- Jess.
- Don't pull that Jess shit

350
00:12:54,479 --> 00:12:56,242
with me... I want to know what
it says in your file.

351
00:12:56,267 --> 00:12:58,432
- I don't know what it says.
- How the hell do you not know?

352
00:12:58,456 --> 00:12:59,634
'Cause whatever it is
is bullshit.

353
00:12:59,659 --> 00:13:01,606
Because the reason
they were gonna fire me

354
00:13:01,630 --> 00:13:03,092
is that I refused
to go after you.

355
00:13:03,117 --> 00:13:05,733
Then why didn't you tell me that

356
00:13:05,758 --> 00:13:07,537
when you came at us
demanding a job?

357
00:13:07,561 --> 00:13:09,458
Because good lawyers negotiate

358
00:13:09,483 --> 00:13:12,783
from a position of strength,
not weakness.

359
00:13:12,808 --> 00:13:15,390
Well, the position
you just put us in

360
00:13:15,415 --> 00:13:17,117
is pretty goddamn weak.

361
00:13:25,854 --> 00:13:27,331
Oh well if it isn't
the boy wonder.

362
00:13:27,332 --> 00:13:29,278
- Louis, hey.
- Don't Louis me.

363
00:13:29,303 --> 00:13:30,648
You left without even
the courtesy

364
00:13:30,673 --> 00:13:33,054
of a "how's your father?"
What does that mean?

365
00:13:33,079 --> 00:13:35,572
It means that I'm not here
to exchange pleasantries.

366
00:13:35,573 --> 00:13:37,202
I'm here to get
that T.R.O. lifted.

367
00:13:37,227 --> 00:13:38,372
Well, I'm sorry
you feel that way.

368
00:13:38,397 --> 00:13:40,160
I'm also sorry
to hear about Sheila.

369
00:13:40,184 --> 00:13:42,416
Bullshit you're sorry
to hear about she...

370
00:13:42,441 --> 00:13:43,552
What are you talking about?

371
00:13:43,576 --> 00:13:44,854
Come on, you have to have heard.

372
00:13:44,879 --> 00:13:46,392
Heard what?

373
00:13:46,416 --> 00:13:48,229
She's engaged.

374
00:13:48,254 --> 00:13:50,325
It's all over Harvard's
Facebook page.

375
00:13:56,252 --> 00:13:57,753
Oh, my God,
how could she do this?

376
00:13:57,754 --> 00:14:00,235
She said she could never be
attracted to a handsome man.

377
00:14:00,260 --> 00:14:02,140
And that picture doesn't
even do him justice,

378
00:14:02,165 --> 00:14:03,110
but this one, however...

379
00:14:03,134 --> 00:14:04,780
- A thong?
- Yeah.

380
00:14:04,804 --> 00:14:06,919
That... What the-

381
00:14:06,944 --> 00:14:09,592
Yeah, it's a whole, like,
beach thing, I guess.

382
00:14:09,617 --> 00:14:11,948
Long weekend.

383
00:14:11,972 --> 00:14:13,819
You're a son of a bitch, Mike.

384
00:14:13,844 --> 00:14:15,039
You're not even sorry at all.

385
00:14:15,064 --> 00:14:16,443
You're using this
to get into my head.

386
00:14:16,467 --> 00:14:17,913
Louis, come on,
I can't believe you.

387
00:14:17,937 --> 00:14:19,584
You think I would use
Sheila's engagement

388
00:14:19,608 --> 00:14:20,769
just to get you off your game?

389
00:14:20,777 --> 00:14:21,889
Never gonna work.

390
00:14:21,914 --> 00:14:23,159
That I would
stick it in your face

391
00:14:23,184 --> 00:14:24,747
that she's all up
in this guy's business

392
00:14:24,754 --> 00:14:26,066
in a way that you've
never seen before?

393
00:14:26,091 --> 00:14:27,269
Water off a duck's back.

394
00:14:27,294 --> 00:14:29,074
That right now
she's probably scrapbooking

395
00:14:29,098 --> 00:14:30,527
the first day
of their relationship,

396
00:14:30,551 --> 00:14:32,081
which apparently happened
just weeks

397
00:14:32,106 --> 00:14:34,820
after you broke her heart?

398
00:14:34,845 --> 00:14:36,259
You're the devil.

399
00:14:36,283 --> 00:14:37,628
Next up on the docket,

400
00:14:37,653 --> 00:14:40,017
Sidwell Investment group
versus Sanders International.

401
00:14:40,041 --> 00:14:41,336
Looks like that's us.

402
00:14:41,361 --> 00:14:42,443
I'll see you in there.

403
00:14:45,706 --> 00:14:46,867
Louis, I can't believe it.

404
00:14:46,891 --> 00:14:49,123
I give you one
goddamn job to do,

405
00:14:49,148 --> 00:14:50,560
and you...
What are you doing up there?

406
00:14:50,584 --> 00:14:52,164
Harvey, please, I can explain.

407
00:14:52,188 --> 00:14:56,424
Oh, explain why you stood in
front of the judge like a moron?

408
00:14:56,449 --> 00:14:57,611
What possible explanation...

409
00:14:57,635 --> 00:15:00,350
Sheila got engaged.

410
00:15:00,375 --> 00:15:02,038
What?

411
00:15:02,063 --> 00:15:03,064
When?

412
00:15:03,082 --> 00:15:04,283
This morning.

413
00:15:05,538 --> 00:15:06,622
Louis, I'm sorry.

414
00:15:07,760 --> 00:15:09,473
I was so sure
that she would just come around

415
00:15:09,498 --> 00:15:11,011
about having children, you know?

416
00:15:11,035 --> 00:15:13,450
That's why I've been
turning down

417
00:15:13,475 --> 00:15:15,088
all those J-date requests.

418
00:15:15,112 --> 00:15:16,457
We'll get Mike another way.

419
00:15:16,482 --> 00:15:18,295
Oh, you're goddamn right
we're gonna get him.

420
00:15:18,320 --> 00:15:19,498
I'm gonna get
that son of a bitch

421
00:15:19,522 --> 00:15:20,550
if it's the last thing I do.

422
00:15:20,575 --> 00:15:22,472
What are you talking about?

423
00:15:22,497 --> 00:15:25,680
He used the Sheila news
to get into my head, Harvey.

424
00:15:25,705 --> 00:15:30,392
Used the news
or gave you the news?

425
00:15:30,417 --> 00:15:32,046
Oh, please,
what difference does it make?

426
00:15:32,070 --> 00:15:33,248
What difference does it make?

427
00:15:33,273 --> 00:15:34,870
It makes all the difference.

428
00:15:34,894 --> 00:15:36,507
Like on the one hand,
I feel for you,

429
00:15:36,532 --> 00:15:38,534
and on the other, you're
the world's biggest idiot.

430
00:15:38,553 --> 00:15:39,615
Look at my computer.

431
00:15:39,639 --> 00:15:40,777
I've been staring at it
for three hours.

432
00:15:40,802 --> 00:15:41,803
It's real.

433
00:15:41,827 --> 00:15:43,357
I don't believe it.

434
00:15:43,382 --> 00:15:45,062
Yeah, that adonis on that yacht,

435
00:15:45,086 --> 00:15:46,280
Sheila's fiance.

436
00:15:46,305 --> 00:15:48,620
That adonis
is a photoshopped picture

437
00:15:48,644 --> 00:15:51,410
of Lorenzo Lamas from 1998!

438
00:15:51,434 --> 00:15:52,814
Who the hell is Lorenzo Lamas?

439
00:15:52,839 --> 00:15:54,218
Well, I can tell you
who he isn't.

440
00:15:54,242 --> 00:15:56,212
He isn't Sheila's fiance!

441
00:16:01,626 --> 00:16:03,106
Oh, thank God.

442
00:16:03,131 --> 00:16:05,278
Are you even listening?

443
00:16:05,302 --> 00:16:07,584
It was bad enough
that Nigel rattled you

444
00:16:07,608 --> 00:16:09,154
with your unread cat letters.

445
00:16:09,179 --> 00:16:10,457
Now you're letting Mike do this?

446
00:16:10,482 --> 00:16:12,495
- Harvey, please.
- Shut the hell up!

447
00:16:12,520 --> 00:16:14,017
Look, I tried to warn you,

448
00:16:14,041 --> 00:16:16,824
and you stood there with your
stupid leg up in the air,

449
00:16:16,848 --> 00:16:19,647
telling me that the student
was no match for the master

450
00:16:19,671 --> 00:16:23,874
and all it took
was one doctored picture

451
00:16:23,898 --> 00:16:25,210
for you to shit the bed!

452
00:16:25,235 --> 00:16:28,802
- I didn't mean to...
- Shut the hell up!

453
00:16:28,827 --> 00:16:29,962
God.

454
00:16:36,061 --> 00:16:38,326
Well, fancy meeting you here.

455
00:16:38,351 --> 00:16:41,084
Rachel, get out of here.

456
00:16:41,108 --> 00:16:45,059
I was just coming to
make some copy...

457
00:16:45,083 --> 00:16:46,479
Louis, what's wrong?

458
00:16:46,504 --> 00:16:48,451
I don't want to talk about it;
Nothing is wrong.

459
00:16:48,475 --> 00:16:50,222
Well, obviously
something's wrong.

460
00:16:50,247 --> 00:16:51,809
You know what,
if you're so curious,

461
00:16:51,833 --> 00:16:53,363
why don't you just go ask
the man of your dreams?

462
00:16:53,388 --> 00:16:55,603
I'm sure the two of you will
have a big laugh about it later.

463
00:16:55,627 --> 00:16:57,440
Okay, I don't know
what you're talking about,

464
00:16:57,465 --> 00:16:58,643
but seeing you like this,

465
00:16:58,667 --> 00:17:00,413
there's no way
that I would laugh at you.

466
00:17:00,438 --> 00:17:01,617
What is it?

467
00:17:01,642 --> 00:17:03,789
Mike convinced me
that Sheila was engaged

468
00:17:03,813 --> 00:17:05,459
to throw me off my game.

469
00:17:05,484 --> 00:17:07,481
I'm so sorry, Louis.

470
00:17:07,505 --> 00:17:09,269
Yeah, well, he sure wasn't.

471
00:17:09,294 --> 00:17:11,090
Stuck a knife in me, twisted it

472
00:17:11,115 --> 00:17:12,978
with the thought of her
and another man.

473
00:17:13,003 --> 00:17:16,421
It felt like
a drill in my skull all day,

474
00:17:16,445 --> 00:17:17,623
and then to top it all off,

475
00:17:17,647 --> 00:17:22,625
it cost me the respect
of my best friend.

476
00:17:24,464 --> 00:17:25,542
Maybe...

477
00:17:25,567 --> 00:17:27,982
Oh, don't you even try
to defend him.

478
00:17:28,007 --> 00:17:29,486
No, I wasn't going to.

479
00:17:29,510 --> 00:17:31,157
I was going to say,

480
00:17:31,181 --> 00:17:33,729
maybe this is what you needed

481
00:17:33,754 --> 00:17:36,737
to decide to reconnect
with Sheila.

482
00:17:36,762 --> 00:17:38,208
And what about Harvey?

483
00:17:38,232 --> 00:17:40,268
How do I repair that?

484
00:17:42,007 --> 00:17:43,754
I'm really sorry
for what happened, Louis.

485
00:17:43,779 --> 00:17:44,780
I am.

486
00:17:58,314 --> 00:17:59,994
- Hey.
- Hey.

487
00:18:00,019 --> 00:18:01,297
Did you eat?

488
00:18:01,322 --> 00:18:03,252
Are you asking because
you're concerned about me

489
00:18:03,277 --> 00:18:07,312
or because you want to know
if I left you any food?

490
00:18:07,337 --> 00:18:10,254
Whoa.

491
00:18:10,278 --> 00:18:11,757
Tough day? I'm sorry.

492
00:18:11,781 --> 00:18:13,794
I've just been working
16-hour days,

493
00:18:13,819 --> 00:18:17,069
and I'm really... stressed.

494
00:18:17,094 --> 00:18:18,273
Yeah, I know the feeling.

495
00:18:18,298 --> 00:18:19,643
Really?

496
00:18:19,668 --> 00:18:23,821
'Cause I heard that you had
a pretty big win today.

497
00:18:23,845 --> 00:18:24,846
You talked to Harvey.

498
00:18:24,847 --> 00:18:26,911
I talked to Louis.

499
00:18:26,935 --> 00:18:28,331
Mike, I know you want to win,

500
00:18:28,356 --> 00:18:31,205
but do you have any idea
what your lie did to him?

501
00:18:31,229 --> 00:18:32,258
It wasn't a lie.

502
00:18:32,282 --> 00:18:33,711
It was a strategy.

503
00:18:33,735 --> 00:18:36,918
It was both, and it ended up
with him near tears.

504
00:18:36,943 --> 00:18:38,288
Come on, Rachel.

505
00:18:38,313 --> 00:18:40,293
It just seems like all
that matters to you is winning

506
00:18:40,318 --> 00:18:42,533
and that you don't care about
what it does to your friends.

507
00:18:42,557 --> 00:18:44,437
You know what?

508
00:18:44,462 --> 00:18:46,275
I'm sorry that I hurt Louis,

509
00:18:46,300 --> 00:18:47,622
but he was going to
that courtroom

510
00:18:47,637 --> 00:18:49,416
so they could put their
tender offer to a vote.

511
00:18:49,441 --> 00:18:51,171
I know.

512
00:18:51,195 --> 00:18:53,727
You also know because we've
had this discussion before

513
00:18:53,752 --> 00:18:55,565
that if he got his way,

514
00:18:55,590 --> 00:18:58,238
they would rip that company
to shreds.

515
00:18:58,263 --> 00:19:00,912
So instead of coming down on me
for what I did to Louis,

516
00:19:00,937 --> 00:19:03,084
why don't you start worrying
about all the lives

517
00:19:03,108 --> 00:19:05,613
that Logan Sanders is
gonna destroy if that happens?

518
00:19:16,024 --> 00:19:17,318
You know, it's funny.

519
00:19:17,343 --> 00:19:19,425
You told me you didn't care
who was in charge.

520
00:19:19,449 --> 00:19:21,697
You just wanted whoever it was
to not be an idiot.

521
00:19:21,721 --> 00:19:23,634
Are you saying
that I was an idiot?

522
00:19:23,659 --> 00:19:25,072
I'm saying we both were.

523
00:19:25,096 --> 00:19:27,026
I shouldn't have gone
to Woodall,

524
00:19:27,051 --> 00:19:29,983
and you shouldn't have
lied to us.

525
00:19:30,007 --> 00:19:32,089
You don't seem pissed.

526
00:19:32,113 --> 00:19:34,879
I've had enough happen
already today.

527
00:19:34,904 --> 00:19:37,235
Besides, lying to me was wrong,

528
00:19:37,259 --> 00:19:39,524
but lying to the woman
you're in a relationship with

529
00:19:39,548 --> 00:19:41,310
is a whole other level.

530
00:19:41,335 --> 00:19:43,500
When do you think
she's gonna get past it?

531
00:19:43,524 --> 00:19:45,655
From personal experience,
that could take a while.

532
00:19:45,679 --> 00:19:47,092
That's not my problem.

533
00:19:47,117 --> 00:19:48,496
That's yours.

534
00:19:48,520 --> 00:19:50,217
Then what are you doing here,
Harvey?

535
00:19:50,241 --> 00:19:54,059
I'm here to tell you
what you're gonna do about it.

536
00:19:54,084 --> 00:19:56,031
No.

537
00:19:56,056 --> 00:19:57,201
No way.

538
00:19:57,225 --> 00:19:58,904
I'm not taking the stand.

539
00:19:58,929 --> 00:20:00,241
Then what are you doing here?

540
00:20:00,266 --> 00:20:02,296
Because Woodall telling you
to go after our clients

541
00:20:02,321 --> 00:20:04,168
is how you got this job
in the first place

542
00:20:04,193 --> 00:20:05,672
and happens to make our case.

543
00:20:05,696 --> 00:20:07,176
He didn't outright tell me
to do it,

544
00:20:07,200 --> 00:20:08,201
and you know it.

545
00:20:08,203 --> 00:20:09,264
You had to find out somehow.

546
00:20:09,288 --> 00:20:10,901
I found out from Brian Harris.

547
00:20:10,926 --> 00:20:13,524
He told me he had
this funny feeling

548
00:20:13,548 --> 00:20:14,944
that the day after
Woodall arrived,

549
00:20:14,969 --> 00:20:16,866
that I was gonna
start issuing subpoenas

550
00:20:16,890 --> 00:20:19,371
to Pearson Specter clients.

551
00:20:19,396 --> 00:20:22,798
When I asked him why,
he said, "you know why."

552
00:20:22,822 --> 00:20:24,268
Then you're gonna
get up on the stand

553
00:20:24,292 --> 00:20:26,640
and tell them that.
I can't. I have no proof.

554
00:20:26,665 --> 00:20:28,929
It was vague, and it's
a third party conversation.

555
00:20:28,953 --> 00:20:31,068
Which makes it hearsay,
and I don't give a shit.

556
00:20:31,092 --> 00:20:33,540
Well, I do, 'cause it opens
me up to slander at best

557
00:20:33,565 --> 00:20:35,111
and perjury charges at worst.

558
00:20:35,135 --> 00:20:36,715
Well, Jeff, you used that story

559
00:20:36,740 --> 00:20:38,051
to get your ass in here.

560
00:20:38,076 --> 00:20:40,949
Now use it to get the job done.

561
00:20:48,183 --> 00:20:49,184
Amy!

562
00:20:50,552 --> 00:20:51,553
I thought I asked you

563
00:20:51,554 --> 00:20:53,533
to leave the Gianopolous
proposal on my desk.

564
00:20:53,558 --> 00:20:55,588
And I did, 20 minutes ago.

565
00:20:55,613 --> 00:20:56,976
What? Okay.

566
00:20:57,000 --> 00:20:58,913
Did you proof it? No.

567
00:20:58,938 --> 00:21:00,301
I thought you'd have
a better chance

568
00:21:00,325 --> 00:21:01,854
if the document
was riddled with typos.

569
00:21:01,879 --> 00:21:03,325
- This is important.
- I know it is,

570
00:21:03,349 --> 00:21:04,812
which is why I read it
backwards and forwards.

571
00:21:04,836 --> 00:21:06,199
Okay, did you add the part

572
00:21:06,223 --> 00:21:07,568
about the leveraged recap
like I asked?

573
00:21:07,593 --> 00:21:10,409
I did, but your figures
on the non-voting stock

574
00:21:10,433 --> 00:21:12,748
didn't add up,
so I proposed a staggered board

575
00:21:12,773 --> 00:21:14,252
to make up for the imbalance.

576
00:21:14,276 --> 00:21:15,689
Staggered board?

577
00:21:15,713 --> 00:21:17,126
Yeah, don't act so surprised.

578
00:21:17,150 --> 00:21:18,663
I'm sorry,
I just thought that you...

579
00:21:18,687 --> 00:21:20,416
You just thought
that I didn't know anything

580
00:21:20,441 --> 00:21:21,838
about what goes on here?

581
00:21:21,862 --> 00:21:23,140
Listen up, T. Boone Pickens,

582
00:21:23,165 --> 00:21:25,363
I actually know a lot
about this business.

583
00:21:25,387 --> 00:21:26,482
Okay, I said I'm sorry...

584
00:21:26,507 --> 00:21:27,886
And I know more than enough
to know

585
00:21:27,910 --> 00:21:29,690
that that looks like
every other proposal

586
00:21:29,715 --> 00:21:31,026
that's comes across my desk.

587
00:21:31,051 --> 00:21:32,813
Well, that gives me
a shit load of confidence

588
00:21:32,821 --> 00:21:33,983
going into this meeting.

589
00:21:34,008 --> 00:21:35,404
I'm not trying to
destroy your confidence.

590
00:21:35,428 --> 00:21:36,740
That's the one thing you have
going for you.

591
00:21:36,765 --> 00:21:38,010
Then what are you trying to do?

592
00:21:38,035 --> 00:21:39,247
Mike, you're not here

593
00:21:39,272 --> 00:21:40,885
because you crunched
Sidwell some numbers.

594
00:21:40,909 --> 00:21:43,013
You're here because
you solved a problem for him.

595
00:21:46,439 --> 00:21:47,440
All right.

596
00:21:47,442 --> 00:21:48,871
Get rid of this, and bring...

597
00:21:48,895 --> 00:21:51,099
And bring you everything
I can find on Tony Gianopolous.

598
00:21:51,100 --> 00:21:53,432
On it.

599
00:21:53,457 --> 00:21:54,458
Amy.

600
00:21:56,280 --> 00:21:57,281
Why aren't you...

601
00:21:57,282 --> 00:21:58,283
Why am I an assistant

602
00:21:58,285 --> 00:21:59,982
and not an investment banker?

603
00:22:00,006 --> 00:22:01,935
I'm getting my PhD
in psychology.

604
00:22:01,960 --> 00:22:04,827
Money bores me.

605
00:22:04,851 --> 00:22:06,915
I don't know why you needed
to talk to me in chambers,

606
00:22:06,939 --> 00:22:08,134
Mr. Malone.

607
00:22:08,159 --> 00:22:09,387
I was clear on my ruling.

608
00:22:09,412 --> 00:22:11,225
Well, with all due respect,
Your Honor,

609
00:22:11,250 --> 00:22:13,197
your ruling didn't cover
the fact that the S.E.C.

610
00:22:13,222 --> 00:22:15,135
has a vendetta
against Pearson Specter.

611
00:22:15,160 --> 00:22:16,540
That's a serious accusation.

612
00:22:16,564 --> 00:22:17,775
And if it were the truth,

613
00:22:17,799 --> 00:22:19,412
he would have said it
out there, not in here.

614
00:22:19,437 --> 00:22:20,749
I'm doing it in private, Sean,

615
00:22:20,774 --> 00:22:22,554
because I don't want to slander
an entire department

616
00:22:22,578 --> 00:22:23,756
based on the actions of two men.

617
00:22:23,781 --> 00:22:24,993
Translation?

618
00:22:25,018 --> 00:22:26,564
He doesn't want to be
charged with perjury

619
00:22:26,588 --> 00:22:28,067
because he's lying,
and this is a joke.

620
00:22:28,092 --> 00:22:29,455
It wasn't a joke
when I was asked

621
00:22:29,479 --> 00:22:31,610
to do the exact same thing
that he's doing right now.

622
00:22:31,634 --> 00:22:33,036
What the hell
are you talking about?

623
00:22:33,054 --> 00:22:34,450
Before I left the S.E.C.,

624
00:22:34,474 --> 00:22:36,622
I was told to target
Pearson Specter clients.

625
00:22:36,646 --> 00:22:38,259
- And who exactly told you?
- Brian Harris.

626
00:22:38,284 --> 00:22:39,496
Then go after him,

627
00:22:39,520 --> 00:22:40,999
'cause all you've got on me
is hearsay,

628
00:22:41,024 --> 00:22:42,804
and might I point this is
the accusation of a man

629
00:22:42,828 --> 00:22:44,876
who is about to be fired,
which I'd say should be taken

630
00:22:44,900 --> 00:22:46,228
with a cubic meter of salt.

631
00:22:46,253 --> 00:22:48,216
Well, that cubic meter of salt

632
00:22:48,241 --> 00:22:49,763
might actually
get a little bit smaller

633
00:22:49,779 --> 00:22:51,559
if Sean here were to, say,
open up his files

634
00:22:51,583 --> 00:22:53,029
and show us his paper trail.

635
00:22:53,053 --> 00:22:55,702
Our work product is covered
under federal regulation,

636
00:22:55,727 --> 00:22:57,004
and he knows that.

637
00:22:57,029 --> 00:22:58,751
I also know you're hiding
behind your office

638
00:22:58,768 --> 00:22:59,846
and using his court to do it.

639
00:22:59,870 --> 00:23:01,383
All right, all right,
that's enough.

640
00:23:01,408 --> 00:23:02,787
Mr. Malone,
I don't appreciate you

641
00:23:02,811 --> 00:23:03,806
using my chambers to testify,

642
00:23:03,830 --> 00:23:05,226
and he may not have proof,

643
00:23:05,250 --> 00:23:08,350
but if one client
leaves his firm

644
00:23:08,375 --> 00:23:10,161
and their charges
miraculously disappear,

645
00:23:10,598 --> 00:23:12,161
you're looking at more
than sanctions.

646
00:23:12,186 --> 00:23:14,524
You're looking at jail time.

647
00:23:18,835 --> 00:23:20,899
Thank you.

648
00:23:20,923 --> 00:23:22,403
Rachel?

649
00:23:22,428 --> 00:23:23,656
It's only been a day.

650
00:23:23,680 --> 00:23:25,410
You already have a suggestion
for my new deal?

651
00:23:25,435 --> 00:23:26,864
- I do.
- Good.

652
00:23:26,888 --> 00:23:28,868
Then which of those five
companies should I go after?

653
00:23:28,893 --> 00:23:30,306
None of them.

654
00:23:30,330 --> 00:23:31,876
So you brought me nothing?

655
00:23:31,901 --> 00:23:34,115
No, I brought you
five better options.

656
00:23:34,139 --> 00:23:36,061
- What's wrong with the op...
- Just take a look.

657
00:23:42,160 --> 00:23:44,173
These companies
have no disposable assets.

658
00:23:44,198 --> 00:23:46,463
No, they don't.
They have underperforming assets

659
00:23:46,487 --> 00:23:48,489
that can be turned around
and built into something.

660
00:23:48,492 --> 00:23:50,088
Did you even look into
the companies I gave you?

661
00:23:50,112 --> 00:23:51,858
- Yes, I did, but I...
- But what?

662
00:23:51,883 --> 00:23:53,330
Sounds like someone's
been drinking

663
00:23:53,354 --> 00:23:55,200
her boyfriend's kool-aid.
Maybe if more people did,

664
00:23:55,225 --> 00:23:57,005
there just might be...
God damn it, Rachel,

665
00:23:57,030 --> 00:23:58,909
I'm not in business
to save the world.

666
00:23:58,933 --> 00:24:00,480
I asked for
a professional opinion.

667
00:24:00,505 --> 00:24:02,418
And I gave you
a professional opinion.

668
00:24:02,443 --> 00:24:04,273
You just don't like it.
No, I don't.

669
00:24:04,297 --> 00:24:06,194
And now we're gonna have to work
all day tomorrow

670
00:24:06,219 --> 00:24:07,949
to do what I asked you to do
in the first place.

671
00:24:07,974 --> 00:24:09,285
You mean spend all day together.

672
00:24:09,310 --> 00:24:10,712
- If that's what it takes.
- Mm-hmm.

673
00:24:10,730 --> 00:24:12,293
Did you call this board meeting

674
00:24:12,317 --> 00:24:13,964
just so we could
spend more time together?

675
00:24:13,989 --> 00:24:15,635
Did you bring me deals
you knew I'd reject

676
00:24:15,659 --> 00:24:16,777
just to avoid it?

677
00:24:18,750 --> 00:24:21,182
Look, like I said,

678
00:24:21,206 --> 00:24:22,852
I have a meeting on Friday,

679
00:24:22,877 --> 00:24:24,189
and I need to be
prepared for it,

680
00:24:24,214 --> 00:24:25,860
so maybe you should
go back to your office,

681
00:24:25,884 --> 00:24:27,079
get cracking,

682
00:24:27,104 --> 00:24:29,225
and just give me a call
when you have something.

683
00:24:32,033 --> 00:24:33,367
Okay.

684
00:24:37,529 --> 00:24:40,345
You're kidding me.

685
00:24:40,369 --> 00:24:41,949
So this is all mine?

686
00:24:41,974 --> 00:24:43,854
Yup.

687
00:24:43,879 --> 00:24:45,692
In 20 days, the public access
will be gone,

688
00:24:45,716 --> 00:24:49,100
and you will have yourself
1/4 mile of private beach.

689
00:24:49,125 --> 00:24:50,804
What about
the Southampton city council?

690
00:24:50,829 --> 00:24:52,209
What about them?

691
00:24:52,233 --> 00:24:54,982
They're a bunch of
public-access loving assholes.

692
00:24:55,006 --> 00:24:59,911
Like I said, what about them?

693
00:24:59,935 --> 00:25:01,948
How'd you do this, Mike?

694
00:25:01,973 --> 00:25:03,703
Well, the question isn't
how I did it,

695
00:25:03,728 --> 00:25:05,240
it's why I did it.

696
00:25:05,264 --> 00:25:07,746
Oh. You want something from me.

697
00:25:07,771 --> 00:25:09,751
Just your consideration.

698
00:25:09,776 --> 00:25:12,131
Well, you've earned it.
Go ahead.

699
00:25:20,435 --> 00:25:21,938
Not interested.

700
00:25:24,278 --> 00:25:25,791
You didn't even look at it.

701
00:25:25,815 --> 00:25:27,685
Oh, I don't have to.

702
00:25:29,090 --> 00:25:31,103
You just said that I earned
your consideration.

703
00:25:31,128 --> 00:25:33,131
Mm-hmm, and you just got it.

704
00:25:34,554 --> 00:25:37,587
Gillis industries
is ripe for a turnaround,

705
00:25:37,612 --> 00:25:40,159
and I already own 7%.
Congratulations.

706
00:25:40,183 --> 00:25:42,265
Now go beg someone else
for money,

707
00:25:42,290 --> 00:25:43,686
because you're not getting mine.

708
00:25:43,710 --> 00:25:45,306
I don't understand.

709
00:25:45,330 --> 00:25:46,442
You don't have to.

710
00:25:46,467 --> 00:25:48,113
Now get the hell
out of my office.

711
00:25:48,137 --> 00:25:50,140
- Mr. Gianopolous.
- I said get the hell out.

712
00:25:59,415 --> 00:26:00,510
Hey, Mike. How's it going?

713
00:26:00,534 --> 00:26:01,752
Fancy meeting you here.

714
00:26:06,182 --> 00:26:07,695
It was you.

715
00:26:07,719 --> 00:26:09,783
What was me?

716
00:26:09,807 --> 00:26:13,876
I'm just here to thank you
for the advice you once gave me.

717
00:26:13,901 --> 00:26:15,570
You know,
back when we were friends.

718
00:26:17,827 --> 00:26:18,828
- Louis.
- No, no, no.

719
00:26:18,829 --> 00:26:20,192
No, no, no.

720
00:26:20,216 --> 00:26:22,281
You once told me that
my actions had consequences.

721
00:26:22,305 --> 00:26:23,599
Remember?

722
00:26:23,624 --> 00:26:25,621
Your actions yesterday
have consequences too.

723
00:26:25,646 --> 00:26:27,911
What did you say to Gianopolous?

724
00:26:27,936 --> 00:26:29,131
Not much.

725
00:26:29,156 --> 00:26:31,002
Just that you were
the person responsible

726
00:26:31,026 --> 00:26:32,004
for his number two leaving him.

727
00:26:32,029 --> 00:26:33,030
I was responsible?

728
00:26:33,031 --> 00:26:34,176
He agreed to it.

729
00:26:34,201 --> 00:26:35,597
But what he didn't know
was is that

730
00:26:35,621 --> 00:26:37,651
it was his own lawyer
who came up with the idea.

731
00:26:37,676 --> 00:26:38,938
Now he does.

732
00:26:38,963 --> 00:26:40,826
- And what does that...
- Have to do with it?

733
00:26:40,851 --> 00:26:42,614
He may have agreed to it,

734
00:26:42,638 --> 00:26:44,201
but it was a betrayal by you.

735
00:26:44,226 --> 00:26:45,622
And here's a little something

736
00:26:45,646 --> 00:26:48,662
you obviously do not know
about investment banking.

737
00:26:48,686 --> 00:26:51,770
The only thing more satisfying
to these guys than money

738
00:26:51,795 --> 00:26:54,967
is sticking it to someone
who stuck it to them.

739
00:27:01,736 --> 00:27:02,771
Louis.

740
00:27:05,745 --> 00:27:07,341
I'm sorry for hurting you
with Sheila.

741
00:27:07,366 --> 00:27:10,048
Don't you ever mention
her name to me again.

742
00:27:10,073 --> 00:27:13,240
Okay, but it was a move,

743
00:27:13,265 --> 00:27:14,266
like you just did.

744
00:27:14,267 --> 00:27:16,564
So can we move on?

745
00:27:16,588 --> 00:27:19,672
Move on?

746
00:27:19,697 --> 00:27:23,883
You used the woman I love
to extend your goddamn T.R.O.

747
00:27:23,907 --> 00:27:28,227
You knew how I felt about her,
and you did it anyway.

748
00:27:28,252 --> 00:27:31,268
I will never, ever forget it
until the day I die.

749
00:27:31,292 --> 00:27:33,396
Good luck beating Harvey
without money.

750
00:27:39,454 --> 00:27:40,542
I have good news.

751
00:27:41,116 --> 00:27:42,896
James Dolan died
and left me the Knicks?

752
00:27:42,920 --> 00:27:45,135
Louis stopped Mike
from getting Gianopolous.

753
00:27:45,159 --> 00:27:46,504
He blocked his funding.

754
00:27:46,530 --> 00:27:47,531
Good.

755
00:27:53,245 --> 00:27:54,858
You went to Louis
with a problem,

756
00:27:54,883 --> 00:27:55,928
he fixed it,

757
00:27:55,952 --> 00:27:57,532
and all you're gonna say
is "good"?

758
00:27:57,557 --> 00:27:59,036
Donna, I'm glad
he fixed the problem,

759
00:27:59,060 --> 00:28:00,907
but it was a problem he created.

760
00:28:00,932 --> 00:28:01,960
He created it because

761
00:28:01,984 --> 00:28:03,413
when it comes to people
he cares about,

762
00:28:03,437 --> 00:28:05,134
Louis has a blind spot.

763
00:28:05,159 --> 00:28:07,891
Yeah, for people and cats
and who knows what else?

764
00:28:07,915 --> 00:28:09,662
I'll tell you what else.

765
00:28:09,687 --> 00:28:11,523
He cares about you.

766
00:28:13,596 --> 00:28:15,042
What do you want from me, Donna?

767
00:28:15,067 --> 00:28:17,715
I want you to tell him
he did a good job.

768
00:28:17,739 --> 00:28:20,020
I'll tell him
when we come out on top.

769
00:28:20,045 --> 00:28:21,223
Okay, Harvey.

770
00:28:21,248 --> 00:28:23,195
You do what you're gonna do,

771
00:28:23,220 --> 00:28:24,298
but just remember,

772
00:28:24,322 --> 00:28:26,169
when Louis asked Sheila
to marry him,

773
00:28:26,194 --> 00:28:28,442
you were the one he picked
to be his best man,

774
00:28:28,466 --> 00:28:31,104
and you said yes.

775
00:28:41,782 --> 00:28:44,114
I'm sorry,
but we're not hiring today.

776
00:28:44,138 --> 00:28:45,399
I think you'd be
looking for a job

777
00:28:45,424 --> 00:28:46,871
given the beat-down
you took in chambers.

778
00:28:46,895 --> 00:28:48,073
I'm not sure what

779
00:28:48,098 --> 00:28:49,661
Jeff disgruntled employee here
told you,

780
00:28:49,685 --> 00:28:50,814
but I'm still standing.

781
00:28:50,838 --> 00:28:53,135
Well, what I told her
is that you lost.

782
00:28:53,160 --> 00:28:54,205
Then why are you here?

783
00:28:54,229 --> 00:28:55,709
We're here to make you an offer.

784
00:28:55,733 --> 00:28:57,129
You drop all seven cases,

785
00:28:57,154 --> 00:28:58,984
we drop the malicious
prosecution claim.

786
00:28:59,008 --> 00:29:00,487
No deal.

787
00:29:00,511 --> 00:29:03,244
Judge Hopkins is going to be
waiting for you to take action.

788
00:29:03,269 --> 00:29:05,049
Too much time goes by,

789
00:29:05,073 --> 00:29:06,552
he's gonna think
you're full of shit.

790
00:29:06,576 --> 00:29:07,855
But if you fold right now,

791
00:29:07,880 --> 00:29:09,208
he's only gonna sanction you

792
00:29:09,233 --> 00:29:10,996
for the exact claim
that we're willing to drop.

793
00:29:11,021 --> 00:29:12,551
Which is why
we'll tell the judge

794
00:29:12,575 --> 00:29:14,421
that in exchange for those
cases being dropped,

795
00:29:14,446 --> 00:29:16,476
we'll give the S.E.C.
unprecedented access

796
00:29:16,501 --> 00:29:17,864
to our clients' books.

797
00:29:17,888 --> 00:29:21,055
Which, of course,
you won't be doing.

798
00:29:21,080 --> 00:29:22,341
No, we won't.

799
00:29:22,366 --> 00:29:24,179
So what exactly
am I getting out of this?

800
00:29:24,203 --> 00:29:25,365
You get to save face.

801
00:29:25,390 --> 00:29:26,391
I do like my face.

802
00:29:26,393 --> 00:29:27,789
However, I also like my ass,

803
00:29:27,813 --> 00:29:29,826
which will be on the line
if I take this deal.

804
00:29:29,851 --> 00:29:33,191
Then you have 24 hours to
decide which one you like more.

805
00:29:39,908 --> 00:29:41,655
Mr. Forstman, Mike Ross.

806
00:29:41,680 --> 00:29:43,577
No.

807
00:29:43,602 --> 00:29:45,248
Sir, I think that
if you hear me out...

808
00:29:45,272 --> 00:29:48,338
How the hell
did you find me here?

809
00:29:48,363 --> 00:29:50,027
The article in Forbes said

810
00:29:50,051 --> 00:29:51,480
you can't go more
than three hours

811
00:29:51,505 --> 00:29:53,502
without Rosa's cafe cubanos.

812
00:29:53,527 --> 00:29:55,975
That article in Forbes
was six years ago.

813
00:29:55,999 --> 00:29:57,928
It also said you never change.

814
00:29:57,953 --> 00:29:59,265
Did you also read where I have

815
00:29:59,290 --> 00:30:01,371
every Bud Fox wannabe dumped
in a local landfill?

816
00:30:01,395 --> 00:30:02,875
If you do that,

817
00:30:02,899 --> 00:30:06,172
you'll miss the opportunity
to get back at Harvey Specter.

818
00:30:09,114 --> 00:30:10,516
And what does
a little shit like you

819
00:30:10,535 --> 00:30:12,148
know about Harvey Specter?

820
00:30:12,172 --> 00:30:14,186
I know that he bought that
'63 Aston Martin

821
00:30:14,211 --> 00:30:16,207
out from under you,
and you've hated him ever since.

822
00:30:16,232 --> 00:30:17,962
You know he keeps it
in a garage?

823
00:30:17,987 --> 00:30:19,099
Doesn't even drive it.

824
00:30:19,123 --> 00:30:20,124
What do you want?

825
00:30:24,236 --> 00:30:25,497
Gillis Industries.

826
00:30:25,522 --> 00:30:27,302
Gillis Industries...

827
00:30:27,326 --> 00:30:29,858
Is a black hole
of distressed debt.

828
00:30:29,883 --> 00:30:30,944
I want nothing to do with it.

829
00:30:30,969 --> 00:30:31,914
No, it isn't.

830
00:30:31,938 --> 00:30:34,075
It's a '63 Aston Martin.

831
00:30:37,451 --> 00:30:38,462
Who do you work for?

832
00:30:38,487 --> 00:30:40,034
Who says I work for anyone?

833
00:30:40,058 --> 00:30:41,236
Because a young kid like you

834
00:30:41,261 --> 00:30:44,227
with enough clout
to go after Gillis...

835
00:30:44,251 --> 00:30:45,614
I'd know you.

836
00:30:45,638 --> 00:30:47,585
I work for Jonathan Sidwell.

837
00:30:47,610 --> 00:30:51,251
Okay. You've got my 230 mil.

838
00:30:52,873 --> 00:30:55,288
I only need 80.

839
00:30:55,313 --> 00:30:57,600
You don't know what you need.

840
00:30:59,957 --> 00:31:01,686
What happens to the company
is my call.

841
00:31:01,711 --> 00:31:03,164
Done.

842
00:31:08,228 --> 00:31:10,766
Oh, one more thing,
when you get those papers.

843
00:31:12,738 --> 00:31:14,886
I have a feeling there'll be
a provision buried in there

844
00:31:14,910 --> 00:31:17,475
that says that
once the deal closes,

845
00:31:17,500 --> 00:31:19,513
you cut Sidwell out.

846
00:31:19,538 --> 00:31:21,134
I'm sorry, what?

847
00:31:21,159 --> 00:31:22,488
I don't know him,

848
00:31:22,513 --> 00:31:24,360
and I want need him
sucking a chunk out of a deal

849
00:31:24,384 --> 00:31:26,471
that can't happen without me.

850
00:31:39,672 --> 00:31:41,017
Well?

851
00:31:41,042 --> 00:31:42,521
He went for it.

852
00:31:42,545 --> 00:31:43,657
That is great.

853
00:31:43,682 --> 00:31:45,695
No, it's not all great.

854
00:31:45,720 --> 00:31:49,087
He'll only give me the money
if I agree to cut out Sidwell.

855
00:31:49,112 --> 00:31:50,173
What?

856
00:31:50,197 --> 00:31:52,712
What does cut him out even mean?

857
00:31:52,737 --> 00:31:54,082
It means make sure Sidwell

858
00:31:54,107 --> 00:31:55,953
doesn't get a penny
from this deal.

859
00:31:55,978 --> 00:31:59,463
Mike, the second he finds
that out, you're gone.

860
00:31:59,487 --> 00:32:01,769
He's not gonna find out
until the deal closes,

861
00:32:01,793 --> 00:32:04,241
and if I don't find the money,
I'm out of a job anyway.

862
00:32:04,266 --> 00:32:07,449
Oh, I get it.

863
00:32:07,474 --> 00:32:09,678
At least this way, you get to
leave on the winning side.

864
00:32:09,679 --> 00:32:12,752
- We leave on the winning side.
- Who says I'm gonna do that?

865
00:32:14,608 --> 00:32:16,806
What happened to, "you think
I'm staying if you leave"?

866
00:32:16,831 --> 00:32:17,875
Yeah, that was before I knew

867
00:32:17,899 --> 00:32:19,111
you were gonna screw over
Sidwell.

868
00:32:19,136 --> 00:32:20,899
- Amy, I...
- No, he may be

869
00:32:20,924 --> 00:32:22,537
a dick sometimes,
but he's the reason you're here.

870
00:32:22,561 --> 00:32:25,461
You think I want this?

871
00:32:25,485 --> 00:32:26,847
I have to make a choice between

872
00:32:26,871 --> 00:32:28,401
the promise I made
to Walter Gillis

873
00:32:28,426 --> 00:32:29,637
and what I owe Jonathan.

874
00:32:29,661 --> 00:32:31,441
Mike, Walter Gillis
doesn't give a shit

875
00:32:31,466 --> 00:32:32,548
about that promise anymore.

876
00:32:32,569 --> 00:32:33,914
Yeah, but I do,

877
00:32:33,939 --> 00:32:35,842
and so do all the people
that work for him.

878
00:32:38,383 --> 00:32:40,888
So you're gonna do it.

879
00:32:42,945 --> 00:32:44,624
I don't know.

880
00:32:44,649 --> 00:32:47,816
But I do know that I keep
having to do shity things

881
00:32:47,840 --> 00:32:49,403
just to win this thing,

882
00:32:49,428 --> 00:32:51,430
but I'm gonna go make up
for one of them right now.

883
00:32:57,297 --> 00:33:00,547
I'm sorry I didn't do
what you asked me to do.

884
00:33:00,572 --> 00:33:02,351
I should have evaluated
your ideas.

885
00:33:02,376 --> 00:33:04,190
You should have,

886
00:33:04,214 --> 00:33:05,525
but I should have remembered

887
00:33:05,550 --> 00:33:08,199
that you don't always do
what people expect of you.

888
00:33:08,224 --> 00:33:10,455
You mean what people
tell me to do.

889
00:33:10,480 --> 00:33:12,426
I chose the nicer version.

890
00:33:12,450 --> 00:33:14,130
Well, I, um...

891
00:33:14,155 --> 00:33:16,185
I finished what I should
have done in the first place.

892
00:33:16,210 --> 00:33:18,107
- And?
- And let's go through them.

893
00:33:20,287 --> 00:33:22,217
- What are you doing here?
- Waiting for you.

894
00:33:22,242 --> 00:33:23,554
I figured if I tried
to go upstairs,

895
00:33:23,579 --> 00:33:24,890
you'd have me killed.

896
00:33:24,915 --> 00:33:26,428
Oh, is that a joke,
'cause I'm not laughing.

897
00:33:26,452 --> 00:33:27,982
Louis, I didn't say it
right the first time.

898
00:33:28,006 --> 00:33:30,009
I want to say it again.
I'm sorry.

899
00:33:31,949 --> 00:33:33,962
You think "I'm sorry"
makes up for what you did?

900
00:33:33,987 --> 00:33:36,319
No, but I'm hoping
that we can move past it

901
00:33:36,344 --> 00:33:38,240
and be friends again.

902
00:33:38,264 --> 00:33:40,077
Well, the only problem
with that is,

903
00:33:40,102 --> 00:33:41,915
is that you and I both know
that you're only here

904
00:33:41,940 --> 00:33:43,382
because I took away
your sugar daddy,

905
00:33:43,394 --> 00:33:44,923
and now you want me
to take it easy on you.

906
00:33:44,947 --> 00:33:47,529
Louis, if you don't want to
accept my apology, that's fine,

907
00:33:47,554 --> 00:33:49,267
but I'm not here
from a position of weakness.

908
00:33:49,292 --> 00:33:50,738
I'm here from
a position of strength.

909
00:33:50,762 --> 00:33:52,125
Bullshit. Where'd you get money?

910
00:33:52,149 --> 00:33:53,377
You don't have any friends
out there.

911
00:33:53,402 --> 00:33:55,734
No, but Harvey has enemies.

912
00:33:55,758 --> 00:33:57,487
What's that supposed to mean?

913
00:33:57,512 --> 00:33:58,914
You told me
these guys hold grudges.

914
00:33:58,932 --> 00:34:01,297
I just found a guy
with one against Harvey.

915
00:34:01,321 --> 00:34:02,383
You son of a bitch.

916
00:34:02,408 --> 00:34:03,804
You didn't come here
to apologize.

917
00:34:03,828 --> 00:34:05,191
You came here
to rub it in my face.

918
00:34:05,198 --> 00:34:06,977
Oh, and I bet you just
can't wait to tell Harvey

919
00:34:07,002 --> 00:34:08,582
that I'm the one
who gave you the idea.

920
00:34:08,606 --> 00:34:10,002
Louis, I wasn't even
gonna tell you

921
00:34:10,026 --> 00:34:11,004
how I got the idea at all.

922
00:34:11,029 --> 00:34:12,207
I'm still not gonna tell Harvey.

923
00:34:12,231 --> 00:34:13,493
Because you want me to owe you?

924
00:34:13,518 --> 00:34:14,964
Because I'm not
as much of an asshole

925
00:34:14,989 --> 00:34:16,652
as you think I am.

926
00:34:16,676 --> 00:34:19,241
- What about a buyout?
- Never gonna happen.

927
00:34:19,266 --> 00:34:20,962
He's got a golden parachute.

928
00:34:20,986 --> 00:34:22,883
Well, then I've got two people
on the board.

929
00:34:22,908 --> 00:34:24,253
I can force a vote.

930
00:34:24,278 --> 00:34:26,191
You do that,
it triggers a stock split.

931
00:34:26,216 --> 00:34:27,561
His shares double
in voting power.

932
00:34:27,586 --> 00:34:29,566
Yours don't.
I mean, that's all five.

933
00:34:29,591 --> 00:34:32,424
None of them work.
No, they don't.

934
00:34:32,448 --> 00:34:34,145
So when you told me
you should have

935
00:34:34,170 --> 00:34:35,431
evaluated my ideas first,

936
00:34:35,456 --> 00:34:37,052
you weren't saying
that they were good.

937
00:34:37,076 --> 00:34:39,324
I was saying
I wasn't doing my job.

938
00:34:39,348 --> 00:34:41,680
Which was to let me
figure out for myself

939
00:34:41,705 --> 00:34:43,167
that my ideas weren't good.

940
00:34:43,191 --> 00:34:45,908
I chose the nicer version.

941
00:34:45,932 --> 00:34:50,753
Logan, there are plenty
of other companies out there.

942
00:34:50,777 --> 00:34:52,156
None that we're gonna find
in time

943
00:34:52,180 --> 00:34:53,381
for my board meeting tomorrow.

944
00:34:53,383 --> 00:34:54,384
- So push it.
- I can't.

945
00:34:54,386 --> 00:34:57,603
I didn't call it.

946
00:34:57,627 --> 00:34:59,273
- And I thought...
- Yeah, I know.

947
00:34:59,298 --> 00:35:01,980
That I only even arranged it
to spend time with you?

948
00:35:02,005 --> 00:35:03,183
You really didn't.

949
00:35:03,208 --> 00:35:05,723
No, and now they're gonna
ask me tomorrow

950
00:35:05,747 --> 00:35:07,058
how Gillis is going,

951
00:35:07,083 --> 00:35:09,063
and I'm gonna have to tell them
we might lose,

952
00:35:09,088 --> 00:35:10,802
and then they're gonna ask me
what else I have,

953
00:35:10,827 --> 00:35:13,341
and I'm gonna have to
tell them nothing.

954
00:35:13,366 --> 00:35:14,695
Or maybe you won't.

955
00:35:14,720 --> 00:35:16,918
I told you,
I'm not in that business.

956
00:35:16,942 --> 00:35:19,423
Then convince the board
that you should be.

957
00:35:19,447 --> 00:35:20,448
Okay.

958
00:35:20,450 --> 00:35:21,451
Go back to your office.

959
00:35:21,452 --> 00:35:22,453
Get your files.

960
00:35:22,455 --> 00:35:23,734
Like you said,

961
00:35:23,759 --> 00:35:27,199
I don't always do
what people expect me to do.

962
00:35:37,676 --> 00:35:39,506
Louis, can I talk to you
for a minute?

963
00:35:39,531 --> 00:35:41,177
Of course.

964
00:35:41,202 --> 00:35:44,820
I heard about what you did
with Gianopolous.

965
00:35:44,844 --> 00:35:46,313
Good job.

966
00:35:49,021 --> 00:35:50,099
I appreciate that, Harvey.

967
00:35:50,124 --> 00:35:51,837
I do.

968
00:35:51,861 --> 00:35:53,808
Um...

969
00:35:53,833 --> 00:35:55,512
But it doesn't matter.

970
00:35:55,537 --> 00:35:58,410
You know,
he went somewhere else.

971
00:35:59,513 --> 00:36:00,825
I know.

972
00:36:00,850 --> 00:36:02,813
He went to Forstman.

973
00:36:02,838 --> 00:36:05,638
I just wanted to tell you
you did a good job anyway.

974
00:36:05,663 --> 00:36:08,367
See, that's the thing.

975
00:36:11,376 --> 00:36:13,356
I didn't.

976
00:36:13,381 --> 00:36:15,886
What are you talking about?

977
00:36:19,697 --> 00:36:21,166
Mike got the idea from me.

978
00:36:23,339 --> 00:36:25,887
What?

979
00:36:25,911 --> 00:36:27,180
How?

980
00:36:28,685 --> 00:36:29,997
When I cut him off
from Gianopolous,

981
00:36:30,022 --> 00:36:31,367
I stuck it in his face,

982
00:36:31,392 --> 00:36:36,146
and I told him that
people hold grudges, and I...

983
00:36:36,170 --> 00:36:37,983
He must have known
your history with Forstman,

984
00:36:38,008 --> 00:36:39,628
and that's why he went to him,
so...

985
00:36:44,925 --> 00:36:46,204
I'm sorry.

986
00:36:46,229 --> 00:36:47,975
God damn it, Louis.

987
00:36:48,000 --> 00:36:51,016
I don't want to keep
being mad at you,

988
00:36:51,040 --> 00:36:53,322
but you keep doing
the same shit.

989
00:36:53,347 --> 00:36:55,193
But, see, this wasn't me
being duped.

990
00:36:55,217 --> 00:36:59,086
No, it was you
letting your emotions

991
00:36:59,111 --> 00:37:01,893
lead you into
doing something stupid.

992
00:37:01,917 --> 00:37:04,182
Again.

993
00:37:04,207 --> 00:37:07,390
You just had to
stick it in his face.

994
00:37:07,414 --> 00:37:10,664
You know what?

995
00:37:10,689 --> 00:37:12,692
I'm done.

996
00:37:14,365 --> 00:37:15,951
It's not fair, you know.

997
00:37:18,709 --> 00:37:24,616
I'm emotional. You're cold.

998
00:37:24,641 --> 00:37:27,907
You're loved,

999
00:37:27,932 --> 00:37:29,435
and I'm hated.

1000
00:37:30,772 --> 00:37:34,307
Louis, if I was so cold,

1001
00:37:34,331 --> 00:37:37,621
I wouldn't have come here
in the first place.

1002
00:37:49,217 --> 00:37:50,410
What are you doing?

1003
00:37:50,435 --> 00:37:53,039
Pouring us a drink.

1004
00:37:53,840 --> 00:37:54,841
Cahill took the deal.

1005
00:37:54,842 --> 00:37:56,885
All seven cases
are officially dead.

1006
00:37:59,476 --> 00:38:03,200
Jessica, I'm sorry that I didn't
come clean with you before.

1007
00:38:04,028 --> 00:38:06,176
Me too.

1008
00:38:06,200 --> 00:38:08,798
Lying to you
was a business decision,

1009
00:38:08,823 --> 00:38:11,071
and it was wrong,

1010
00:38:11,095 --> 00:38:12,340
but I want you to know

1011
00:38:12,365 --> 00:38:14,436
that I would never lie to you,
man to woman.

1012
00:38:16,108 --> 00:38:17,711
I appreciate that.

1013
00:38:20,937 --> 00:38:22,500
We have a problem.

1014
00:38:22,524 --> 00:38:24,470
I just got off the phone
with Richard Coleman.

1015
00:38:24,495 --> 00:38:26,392
Last week, Sean Cahill asked him

1016
00:38:26,417 --> 00:38:28,314
if I'd ever crossed any lines
in his presence.

1017
00:38:28,339 --> 00:38:29,600
Son of a bitch.

1018
00:38:29,625 --> 00:38:31,188
He doesn't want our clients
to leave us.

1019
00:38:31,212 --> 00:38:33,427
He wants them
to cough up dirt on me.

1020
00:38:33,451 --> 00:38:35,632
At least none of them did,
or we'd be in trouble right now.

1021
00:38:35,656 --> 00:38:37,970
- How do you want to handle it?
- Let's talk about it tomorrow.

1022
00:38:37,995 --> 00:38:40,243
Right now, I've got
something else to do.

1023
00:38:40,267 --> 00:38:41,914
Shit.

1024
00:38:41,939 --> 00:38:44,304
They wouldn't turn on Harvey.

1025
00:38:44,328 --> 00:38:46,559
Cahill wanted us
to drop those cases anyway,

1026
00:38:46,583 --> 00:38:48,062
and I just did him a big favor.

1027
00:38:48,087 --> 00:38:49,967
You couldn't have known that.

1028
00:38:49,992 --> 00:38:52,180
It was my job to know that.

1029
00:38:57,443 --> 00:38:58,989
Hey, Mike?

1030
00:38:59,014 --> 00:39:01,412
- Yeah.
- Harvey Specter's here to...

1031
00:39:01,436 --> 00:39:03,724
Harvey, what can I do for you?

1032
00:39:06,700 --> 00:39:08,346
I wanted to thank you
for the recordings.

1033
00:39:08,371 --> 00:39:11,254
Is that why you came
all the way down here?

1034
00:39:11,278 --> 00:39:13,592
I came to tell you I think
you're making a big mistake

1035
00:39:13,616 --> 00:39:15,814
getting into bed with Forstman.
I knew it.

1036
00:39:15,839 --> 00:39:17,319
Mike, you don't know this guy.

1037
00:39:17,343 --> 00:39:19,457
You could have thanked me
for those recordings days ago,

1038
00:39:19,481 --> 00:39:21,445
but instead you picked
the exact day

1039
00:39:21,470 --> 00:39:22,798
that I find a new investor
to show up

1040
00:39:22,823 --> 00:39:24,636
with your thank-you
and your friendly advice.

1041
00:39:24,661 --> 00:39:26,157
This isn't some move.

1042
00:39:26,181 --> 00:39:27,911
- You only make moves.
- Mike.

1043
00:39:27,935 --> 00:39:29,030
Hey, tell me right now

1044
00:39:29,055 --> 00:39:30,418
that you wouldn't do
the same thing

1045
00:39:30,425 --> 00:39:31,386
if you were in my position.

1046
00:39:31,411 --> 00:39:34,093
I was.

1047
00:39:34,117 --> 00:39:35,145
And I did.

1048
00:39:35,170 --> 00:39:36,733
What?

1049
00:39:36,757 --> 00:39:38,821
You think our grudge
is about some car?

1050
00:39:38,845 --> 00:39:40,625
What the hell
are you talking about?

1051
00:39:40,650 --> 00:39:43,198
When I was younger,
I made a shady deal with him,

1052
00:39:43,223 --> 00:39:45,103
and I paid for it.
Who says that I'm making-

1053
00:39:45,128 --> 00:39:46,323
If you haven't, you will,

1054
00:39:46,348 --> 00:39:48,445
because Forstman
doesn't throw money around

1055
00:39:48,469 --> 00:39:50,049
without getting something
in return.

1056
00:39:50,073 --> 00:39:51,686
He's gonna get money in return.

1057
00:39:51,710 --> 00:39:53,107
Money is third on his list.

1058
00:39:53,131 --> 00:39:54,944
The first two
are getting back at people

1059
00:39:54,969 --> 00:39:56,130
and getting control of people.

1060
00:39:56,155 --> 00:39:57,450
Maybe you should have
thought of that

1061
00:39:57,475 --> 00:39:59,455
before you had Louis
cut me off from Gianopolous,

1062
00:39:59,480 --> 00:40:01,801
because now I have
no other choice!

1063
00:40:09,539 --> 00:40:10,958
You always have a choice.

1064
00:40:18,810 --> 00:40:22,117
Here's to turning around
Piedmont Avionics.

1065
00:40:24,692 --> 00:40:25,693
What?

1066
00:40:25,694 --> 00:40:28,076
Nothing.

1067
00:40:28,101 --> 00:40:29,547
What time is it?

1068
00:40:29,571 --> 00:40:33,239
Too late for you
to change your mind.

1069
00:40:33,264 --> 00:40:36,363
Logan, the board
is going to be wowed.

1070
00:40:36,387 --> 00:40:38,251
Well, I wish I had
your confidence.

1071
00:40:38,276 --> 00:40:41,810
You are not short
in the confidence department.

1072
00:40:41,834 --> 00:40:44,032
Oh, you don't have to
pay me compliments.

1073
00:40:44,056 --> 00:40:46,588
I meant it as an insult.

1074
00:40:46,613 --> 00:40:48,827
You know, if this law thing
doesn't work out...

1075
00:40:48,852 --> 00:40:50,984
Then I could have a career
in venture capital?

1076
00:40:51,008 --> 00:40:53,974
No, I was gonna say
you could be my assistant.

1077
00:40:53,998 --> 00:40:56,112
Hilarious.

1078
00:40:56,136 --> 00:40:58,685
Seriously, Rachel, I...

1079
00:40:58,710 --> 00:41:00,723
I couldn't have done it
without you.

1080
00:41:00,748 --> 00:41:03,531
Yes, you could have.

1081
00:41:03,555 --> 00:41:05,101
It just wouldn't have been
as good.

1082
00:41:05,126 --> 00:41:07,741
Humility.

1083
00:41:07,765 --> 00:41:09,484
Another thing I love about you.

1084
00:41:26,411 --> 00:41:29,428
Logan, I should go.

1085
00:41:29,452 --> 00:41:30,663
Rachel, I...

1086
00:41:30,688 --> 00:41:32,358
Um...

1087
00:41:35,000 --> 00:41:36,736
Good luck tomorrow.

1088
00:41:36,760 --> 00:41:42,768
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man

