Previously on Suits...
Katrina Bennett.
She comes in,
she takes over,
She acts like everything
is her idea.
This wasn't
about a job for me.
It was about having a life,
But I guess
you wouldn't understand that.
So you're gonna punish me
by giving me to Louis?
Because you and I are done.
You make me want
to be a better man.
I can't let you do this.
I regret where we are,
And I've been trying to get us
back to where we were.
You're suggesting
bribing a man
to get you out
of your bribery charge.
"In for a penny, in for
a pound," mother always said.
Ava Hessington
doesn't plead no contest.
She pleads guilty.
And you get
to call it a win.
I can beat you, and I did.
You put me
in that position again,
and I'll do
whatever I have to do to win.
Are you saying screw this
deal, let's kick his ass?
I'm saying take the deal.
We already did.
I win, you back me
for managing partner.
You want
to take down Jessica.
I do.
What time
are you coming over?
Um, I thought
we were doing my place.
No, because whenever
I'm at your place,
all I can see is Tess
in a bed sheet.
I'll be there at 9:00.
Bran bars are forbidden
to first years.
- Since when?
- Since two seconds ago.
Order of the quartermaster,
who is no longer
speaking with you.
Rachel.
Hmm?
Can you please instruct
the associate to your right
to pass
the nondairy creamer?
Louis, as I have been trying
to tell you in person,
and in the note I left,
and in your voice mail,
I'm sorry.
Do you know what
nondairy creamer is, Rachel?
- Uh--
- It's a metaphor.
The first sip, you think
it's real, you know?
After all,
it wants you to believe
that it's genuine
and it's good,
and it's gonna deliver
on its promise.
But then with time,
you realize that it's
just a concoction of chemicals
that's designed
to disguise the truth
that it's actually
full of shit.
Then why
are you drinking it?
I'm lactose intolerant.
I don't accept.
Don't accept what?
Whatever bullshit apology
you're here to give me.
You gave me your word,
and the second
you found out that Mike
was actually gonna say yes,
you couldn't stand it.
You sold me out.
I'm not here
to give you an apology.
I'm here to give you a case.
Those are
the Hessington oil files.
Yeah, you know what, Harvey?
I don't want
your sloppy seconds.
That takeover attempt's
gonna be dead in the water
the second that Ava Hessington's
settlement goes public.
Tony Gianopolous isn't
going to just sell his shares
and go away.
You're right.
You know what he's gonna do?
He's gonna
leverage his position,
and he's gonna get
as much greenmail as he can.
Which is exactly
why I'm here.
You're better suited
to beat him back than I am.
You think I don't know that?
I know you know it.
I want you to know I know it.
Leave the box.
Louis,
have you given any thought
to a rebound associate?
Harvey, come on, you know
I'm not that kind of guy.
Come on, you have him
file a few interrogatories,
maybe pick up your dry cleaning,
and then you cut him loose.
With no strings attached?
Better men than you
have done it.
No.
- Yep.
- Who, Baird?
A week-long fling
I ended six days too late.
Yeah, but Harvey,
I don't just want a superficial
relationship, you know?
I want a true mentee.
Someone I can take
to the gun club or mudding
or to the origami festival.
Louis, you're gonna find
the right one.
Origami festival?
Oh, my God.
Well, this is a surprise.
What?
I just never thought I'd see
the great Harriet Specter
making her own copies.
Is that
what this thing does?
You've never made a copy
in your life before, have you?
Of course not,
I'm too busy being a badass
and worrying about my hair.
And your brilliant associate,
Michelle Ross,
does all the hard work
for you anyway.
You're goddamn right
she does.
I'm really sorry
for what I said
about having a life.
I know.
So we're good?
We're good.
And you and Mike,
you're good?
Do you really think
that Harvey
had an emotional epiphany
on his own?
So you did forgive him?
Yes.
Well, he doesn't know that.
Which is why I have
a triple-whip, double-fat,
extra shot mocha latte
with caramel.
Fair enough.
But maybe it's time
you told him.
So you decided
not to go back to London?
Well, we have some
unfinished business to discuss,
and I thought it best
to do it in person.
The takeover attempt.
Tony Gianopolous.
Well, I've assigned it
to another attorney,
but before you express
any concern, he's excellent.
Well, not only
do I not have concerns,
I'm glad
you've handed it off.
And why is that?
Because that way I know you'll
trust the man you're overseeing
when you come and work for me.
I have to say,
I'm flattered.
I don't want you
to be flattered.
I want you to say yes.
As much success as I've had
with that line myself,
I'm afraid
I'm not an oilman.
The oil business
is about oil
as much as you being
a lawyer is about the law.
Every day is a knife fight
in a prison yard,
and something tells me
you like a good knife fight.
No rules in a knife fight.
Harvey, I've just lost
my number two.
I can't think of anyone better
to replace him.
Ava
I'm a woman
who gets what I want,
and I am willing
to pay for it.
Don't get me wrong,
I'm happy to whore myself out.
I just prefer to have
more than one client.
Harvey, what a coincidence.
Cameron, I'm surprised
you can afford this place
now that
you're unemployed again.
Well, my temporary gig
isn't over just yet.
You may think
you have them fooled, Cameron,
but they'll figure you out
eventually.
You didn't.
What are you talking about?
Ava Hessington,
you're under arrest.
- What?
- On what charge?
Conspiracy
to commit murder.
This is bullshit, Cameron.
We had a deal.
A deal where your client
admitted to bribing
a foreign official.
That Colonel
that she paid off?
After that, six people
were killed by his troops.
I give my driver a tip,
and then he runs over someone.
Doesn't mean I had
anything to do with it.
But if the person
he hit was me,
sure would look like that.
What the hell
are you talking about?
All six people
did whatever they could
to stop your client
from getting her pipeline.
If that's all you got,
you don't have shit.
She did this, Harvey.
You don't know her.
Yeah, but I know you,
and you don't give a damn
about murder
in some foreign country.
You took this case
to stick it to me.
And I did.
She admitted that was a bribe
because she never thought we
would tie her to those deaths,
and now I got her.
And you didn't
see it coming,
and there's nothing
you can do about it.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ Suits 3x03 ♪
Unfinished Business
Original Air Date on July 30, 2013
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ the greenback boogie
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
What do you need me to do?
Whatever you have to
to get Ava out,
because Cameron's gonna
try and keep her in.
You really think he's gonna
try and deny her bail?
- I know it.
- Harvey, one thing.
Hey, look, if you have
a problem defending someone
who's accused of murder,
I don't want to hear it.
Look, you won't, 'cause I'm
willing to do whatever it takes
to win
whether she's innocent or not.
Then come with me.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm going to see Ava with you?
- Yep.
- Yeah, baby!
Butch and Sundance are back.
Ooh, no go.
What do--what do--
what do you mean, "no go"?
I mean, you're not
butch or Sundance.
Why not?
'Cause Butch was the leader,
and Sundance was the gunslinger,
and I'm both.
Okay, but Sundance
couldn't swim,
and Butch never shot anyone,
so that makes you a loser.
Better than a fraud.
I think it's time
for some new material.
You write
Midnight Train to Georgia,
you don't just
sing it once.
And speaking of Butch Cassidy,
let's go start a knife fight.
Uh, Norma,
I just want you, from now on,
to just try to wear socks,
because if you--
there isn't--
and what is that?
Hessington oil's earnings
per share
and market cap growth
over the last 11.2 years.
Somebody ask you
to do this?
I didn't do it because
somebody asked me to, Louis.
I did it
because I want in on the case.
You know, you realize
something like this
would entail
working hand in glove
and possibly even
a trip or two to the mud club.
I'm in.
And what makes you think
you're good enough
to be my personal associate?
I don't want to be
your personal associate.
- What?
- I'm a fifth year.
I don't want to be
anyone's personal associate,
but I know how good you are,
you know how good I am.
We can use each other.
Hmm.
Like a symbiotic relationship.
Like between a phytoplankton
and a whale.
I'm not familiar
with their specific dynamic,
but, yes, exactly.
Well, Katrina, I kind of
had enough of being used
by associates looking to move
one rung up the ladder,
so I suggest you get
the hell out of my office
and find yourself
another whale.
Did you know
about these murders?
I knew there was
a demonstration,
it turned ugly,
and that people died.
Did you know those people
were the leaders
of the demonstration?
No.
Did you know the military
was responsible?
All I know about these deaths
is that they happened.
On your land.
We own thousands of acres.
It's a volatile country.
People kill each other
on a regular basis.
So you just chalk it up
to coincidence
that the six leaders
of this demonstration,
against
your company's policies,
on your company's
private property, were murdered?
It was reported as
a combat incident, not a murder.
You just said all you know
about these deaths
is that they happened.
Now you know
it was a combat incident.
Which one is it?
Harvey,
what the hell is this,
and who the hell
does he think he is?
Mike's just doing his job.
Well, Mike,
every death in that country is
reported as a combat incident,
and for your information,
there were thousands of people
opposed to our pipeline.
That's all we need
right now.
Would you
please excuse us?
How exactly did you manage
to get your head
so far up your own ass?
You told me
to take this deal.
I did,
and now here I am.
I didn't know
about these murders.
What you don't seem to believe
is neither did I.
We were doing our job.
Cameron Dennis
will come at you with worse.
Do you think
I did this?
That's irrelevant.
I just want to make sure I know
all the evidence against you.
I have no idea
what the evidence is,
because I had
nothing to do with it,
and you say it's irrelevant,
but it's not irrelevant to me.
Do you think I did this?
Do you want a lawyer
who thinks
you're innocent and loses
or a lawyer who doesn't
want to know and wins?
You know
the answer to that.
Then don't ask me
that question again,
'cause after I win
and you're free,
what I think won't matter.
So what did she want
to talk to you about?
She wanted to know
if you were single.
Listen, when you
get back to the office--
Wait, what do you mean?
What do you mean,
what do I mean?
I mean, I thought we were
gonna go back together.
I don't know, I thought we could
get some lunch or something.
Like what?
I don't know.
Like, maybe steak or something.
It's the middle of the day.
Yeah, Harvey, that's when
people usually eat lunch.
This is about Louis,
isn't it?
What? No.
Maybe.
So I'm supposed to
take you mudding now?
That's not the point.
Look, let's just concentrate
on winning this thing,
and when it's over,
we can talk
about lunch, dinner,
or anything else.
Whoa, whoa,
you really mean that?
No.
Butch and Sundance are back.
What are you doing?
Dropping off
something for Harvey.
You don't have
any cases with Harvey.
I will when he sees
what's in here.
No.
You're not taking credit
for my ideas again.
Harvey's gonna know
I built this airplane.
Harvey's not gonna
know anything.
You're a little late
to the party.
He and I
are working together again.
I'm not looking
to take your place.
Oh, really?
You just happened to prepare
a document for him,
thinking he didn't
have an associate?
He's working a case
that I'm right for.
That's not how it works
around here.
I handle all of his cases.
Does Harvey know that?
What Harvey knows
is that I'm the "A" team,
and you're the "B" team,
so you can leave the folder,
or you can take it
with you,
but if you're looking to ride
some partner's coattails,
you're gonna have
to look somewhere else.
Well, the "B" team
worked at the D.A.'s office
and came up
with a defense strategy
based on a specific knowledge
of Cameron Dennis.
The "A" team
quotes him movies.
We'll see who Harvey does
and doesn't value.
Katrina,
Mike is Harvey's guy.
When he tells you
he's speaking for Harvey,
he's speaking for Harvey.
And please don't
come into this office
when I'm away
from my desk again.
Boy, am I glad I never
snuck into Harvey's office
when you
weren't around before.
Thanks, Donna.
I still expect
free, exotic,
caffeinated beverages
for the foreseeable future.
Cameron Dennis.
Son of a bitch.
He played us.
He slid that guilty plea
right by.
I should've seen it coming.
We should've seen it coming.
I'm the one that convinced you
to take that deal.
What's done is done.
Question is,
what's being done?
I'm working on getting Ava
off these charges,
and I got Mike working
on getting her out on bail.
So you're back with him.
What's the point
of having a right arm
without a right hand?
- Good.
- Is it?
- What do you mean?
- I mean, he threatened you.
I've never known you
to be forgiving
with someone
who threatened you.
I've never known you to be
particularly forgiving either.
Um, I'm sorry,
I'll come back.
It's okay.
We're all good.
We're good?
When you work with tigers,
once in a while, they're gonna
take a swipe at you.
I like working with tigers.
Of course, when they get out of
hand, you have to put them down.
Now, where are we on the prep
for Ava's bail hearing?
Well, I was thinking,
since Cameron used the
settlement to double-cross us,
why don't we use the bail
hearing to double-cross him?
Your Honor,
this is not
a Ponzi scheme
or insider trading,
this is cold-blooded murder.
Prosecution moves
that bail be denied.
That's ridiculous.
My client's not going anywhere.
She's got a business to run.
Let's look
at how she does business.
Less than 48 hours ago,
she admitted to bribery.
You want to talk
about how she does business?
Let's talk
about how you do business.
Your Honor,
I have a list of 87 murder cases
that Cameron Dennis
tried as a D.A.
In each instance, he allowed
reasonable bail to be set.
I allowed bail
because gangbangers
don't have a fraction
of Ms. Hessington's resources.
You allowed bail
because you didn't give a damn
about those guys,
and this is personal.
It's why you took the case,
it's why you hid a witness,
and it's why you negotiated
a settlement in bad faith.
My chambers now.
You bring an accusation
like that into my courtroom,
you better be able
to back it up.
Your Honor,
when I told him
he took this case
to stick it to me,
he said, quote, "I did,
and now I got her,
and you didn't see it coming."
You know what, Your Honor?
He's right.
I am sticking it to him.
Guilty as charged,
just like his client.
- Okay, let me--
- That's enough.
I am not a washing machine.
You two are not here
to air your dirty laundry.
She admitted to bribing
a Colonel in the army,
and that same army
killed these people.
Three environmentalists
died in the polar ice cap.
You think she killed them also?
Maybe I'll look into that.
You gonna leak it
to a corporate raider too?
What's he talking about?
I'm talking about the fact
that he leaked
this whole thing
to Tony Gianopolous.
This is a personal vendetta,
and he has no concrete evidence
against my client.
Not only do I want no bail,
I want you to throw
this case out right now.
Well, I'm not gonna do that.
But I'll tell you something,
Mr. Dennis,
I am setting bail at $1.
And if you don't
have any evidence,
I'm gonna hear his motion
for summary judgment,
rule in his favor,
and this trial is going to be
over before it even starts.
Bloody hell.
Um, excuse me, do you not
see me sitting here?
Yeah, I saw you.
I just chose to ignore you.
You must like
living dangerously.
I do, and that's
why stopping here,
doing this with you,
well, that's playing with fire.
There's nothing wrong with
a little casual conversation.
What happens
when casual conversation
becomes serious fun?
Oh, you're good.
I can promise you,
I'm better than good.
Stephen Huntley,
senior partner, London office.
Donna.
Just Donna?
Yeah, it's like a name
and a title in one.
You'll see.
I've heard.
Secretarial pool's
been buzzing
about some new, feisty ginger
for a fortnight.
Look, if you're trying
to charm your way
into Harvey's office,
it's not gonna happen.
Mm, no, I'm not trying
to charm my way
into Harvey's office.
Oh, what were you
trying for?
Well, actually,
I was gonna try for--
Donna, I need you
to send Louis
everything we have
on Tony Gianopolous.
He's running point.
Harvey, a pleasure.
I'm Stephen.
I know who you are,
and I know why you're here.
You're Darby's fixer, and you're
here to hijack my case.
Did you text him
whilst we were--
You said you're good?
I'm good too.
This isn't over.
Is that a threat?
Mm, you take it
in whatever tone
pleases you the most.
You're right.
I am Darby's fixer, but I'm not
here to hijack anything.
When I got on a plane
at Heathrow,
this was still
merely bribery.
I've only just learned
of the murder charges now
as I touched down.
It just means the timing
changed, not the motive.
Forget the bombshell
the prosecution's just dropped.
Let's talk about the bombshell
outside your office.
Donna?
She's got a body
like Elizabeth Hurley
and the sass
of Maggie Thatcher.
I went out with Liz.
Don't sell her short
in the sass department.
Oh, I'm well aware
of her sass.
'99.
'98.
Really?
Well, you're obviously
a better man than I am.
Don't beat yourself up.
You got plenty of company.
By the way,
before you say anything else,
she can hear
every word we say.
Now, I've got
a murder charge to defend,
so why don't you tell me
why the hell you're really here?
Well, I'm here to oversee
cultural integration.
Cultural integration.
Standard part of the merger,
been on the books for two weeks.
And why do you need me?
Well, smoothing over
these transitional periods
is never easy.
It's not child's play.
You're an influencer here.
People listen to you.
I want you to help them
listen to me.
I get it.
You want me
to pave the way for you.
Here's the thing.
I don't pave the way
for people.
People pave the way for me.
Mm.
I get it.
Steer clear of you,
and you and I
will get along
just fine.
Welcome to New York.
So, have you met
Stephen Huntley yet.
- I did.
- What'd you think?
Turns out we have
some things in common.
Turns out he didn't
show up empty-handed.
That's $1/2 million.
Mmhmm, first dividend check
of the merger.
That was my buy-in amount.
Maybe it wasn't
such a bad idea after all.
Wait a second.
What was your check for?
More than that.
1.2?
I'm not telling.
1.5?
You're three times
more valuable than me?
Oh, I don't think that.
The check thinks that.
Does the check think
the only thing
that guy's here for
is cultural integration?
The check
wasn't born yesterday.
He is to Darby
what you are to me,
and I wouldn't send you
to do that.
No, you wouldn't.
So what'd you tell him?
I told him as long
as he steers clear of me,
he'll be fine.
You told him wrong.
I want you to find out
what the hell that guy's up to.
She's right, you know.
Cultural integration's
scheduled for a week.
Stephen Huntley booked a room
at the Peninsula for a month.
Is it a room or a suite?
It's important.
- A suite.
- Good work.
- It's what I do.
- There's only one problem.
Jessica just told me
to look into him one second ago.
- I anticipated her needs.
- No, you didn't.
I anticipated your needs?
You anticipated your needs.
And by "your needs," I mean--
Okay, my needs are not
the topic of this conversation.
All I'm saying is,
you went to the trouble
of specifically finding out
he booked a suite.
- W--
- Save it.
Can I talk to you
for a second?
Not if it's about working
with Harvey on this case.
Look, this isn't easy for me
to do, but for some reason,
you and I keep locking horns,
and now I'm out in the cold.
I know how I got here, but
I don't know how to get back.
What do you want, Katrina?
I want to figure out a way
we can coexist in this firm.
You want to know a way?
When you see me coming,
give me a wide berth.
You know what?
I'm apologizing to you.
You don't have to be a dick.
I'm a dick?
You have treated
everyone at this firm
below your station
like shit.
Now all of a sudden
you want to be my best friend?
Oh, I get it.
This isn't about me and you.
This is about me
and your little girlfriend.
Rachel
is not my girlfriend.
This has nothing to do with her,
and this conversation is over.
Funny how you know exactly
who I was talking about.
Thank you.
Harvey, to what do I owe
the pleasure of this lunch?
I wanted to thank you
for the check.
Oh, I thought
that'd change your attitude.
It did.
In fact,
you gave something to me,
I want to give
something to you.
What is it?
It's a hotel bill.
I paid it.
Then I checked you out.
Hope you left housekeeping
a hefty gratuity.
You're not here
to deliver checks
or make
smooth transitions,
and if you're not
gonna tell me the truth,
you don't need
to be here at all.
Well, that's gonna make it
extremely difficult
for me to help you
take over the firm
from Jessica.
I know about your deal
with Edward.
He sent me here to help.
Why didn't you
tell me this before?
Well, you told me
Miss Moneypenny was listening.
I didn't know
whether you wanted her to hear.
So you're here to help me
take over the firm from Jessica?
What exactly does that mean?
You know what it means.
I don't need you
baby-sitting me on this case.
I'm not a baby-sitter.
I'm a fixer.
I'm here to help you.
Now why would you
turn that down?
What's to stop you
from using this
to take over
the firm from me?
I'm not like you.
I don't care to have
my name on the door.
So you're here
just to help me.
You don't need
anything in return.
Your car club has a pair
of mint 1956
Porsche speedsters.
You want to drive one?
I want to race you.
Harvey,
fancy meeting you here.
Cameron,
you keep showing up unannounced,
and I'm not sure why.
I can meet you
anytime, anywhere,
because I'm not afraid
of you.
Well, you should be.
I've got five witnesses
who place the Colonel
that your client bribed
at the scene
of those murders.
You want evidence?
Here it is.
See you in court.
We can schedule it
for anytime, anywhere.
You still
don't want my help?
No, I don't.
I don't trust you.
I'm not telling you
to trust me.
I'm telling you
that this is what Darby wants.
Well, Darby isn't here.
Hey, you wanted to talk to me?
Hey, yes.
So I know you don't want me
fighting your battles for you,
and I didn't.
Uhoh.
I just don't want you
to get upset with me.
What?
I went to talk to Donna
about her and me,
and you came up.
What about me?
That it's time for you
to be accepted back.
- That's why she did it.
- Did what?
I caught Katrina
trying to horn in on my case.
- Again?
- Yeah, I know.
Donna walked in
in the middle,
and she took her
to the woodshed.
So you're okay
with what I did?
I'm more than okay.
Not only did Katrina
slink away,
but she came back later
with her tail between her legs,
looking to be my friend.
Well, she is not your friend.
She's definitely not
my friend.
She most certainly isn't.
What are you talking about?
Um...
After I told her that she
could take her friendship
and shove it up her ass,
she said that this whole thing
was about you
and that I was just trying
to protect my girlfriend.
She called me
your girl--girlfriend?
Mmhmm.
And what did you say?
I mean, what--
what could I say?
We're keeping it a secret.
I-I said you weren't.
Good.
Yeah.
Am I?
Don't you know?
Well, we never really
talked about it.
You mean,
I've never really asked.
Nobody asks
anybody anymore.
Whoops.
Sorry.
Are you okay?
Rachel Elizabeth Zane,
will you be my girlfriend?
Yes.
What the hell is this?
What?
I'm working with Harvey,
my best friend.
Harvey gave birth to me.
When you see me coming,
give me a wide berth,
because I'm a dick.
I'm a dick, dick, dick.
I'm working with Harvey,
my best friend...
Oh, my God.
You're not the fool anymore,
Louis.
Mike Ross is.
And I can't take it back.
I put myself
out on a limb for you,
so if you say no to me,
I won't just be a fool.
I'll be done.
Ugh, this means war.
And I am not taking
any prisoners.
If you think I'm staying
out of it, you're crazy.
I don't want you out of it.
I want you in it.
So what are we gonna do?
Nothing right now.
I need to help Harvey.
I don't believe it.
It's a setback,
but it's going away.
And what exactly
does that mean?
I looked into three
of the witnesses,
and all three were affiliated
with a guerilla faction
within the last five years.
We're gonna paint
the entire incident
as a firefight between
the government and armed rebels.
Which, as you pointed out,
is exactly how it was reported
in the first place.
They're still placing
the Colonel at these murders.
I don't think
you understand.
This is what I found
in two hours.
In another day--
I understand perfectly.
You want to tear
these people down in court.
Well, I'm suggesting
they never get there.
We find out how to get to them,
and we pay them off.
Bribery is what got you
into this situation.
Now you think
that's your way out?
That's what you said
when I suggested that with Nick,
and I listened to you.
And I was able to
neutralize him without a payoff.
You were able
to get Cameron Dennis
to offer me a deal that's
now being used against me.
And even if you can
impugn these five witnesses,
your way still
goes to a verdict.
Mine doesn't.
It doesn't
if we don't get caught.
Then don't get caught.
We're not
going to get caught,
because we're not doing this.
You told me you'd do
anything it takes to win.
Remember that?
You'll steal
the rival pitcher's girlfriend
the night
before the big game.
This is the night
Ms. Hessington, what
you're proposing is a crime.
A crime to get me
out of a crime I didn't commit.
You said it doesn't matter
whether you believe me or not.
It doesn't.
But it does,
because if you thought
I was innocent, you'd do this.
I won't.
Then you're fired.
And I'll find
someone who will.
Where did you get
this picture?
- I friended her on Facebook.
- She accepted?
Not as me.
I found an intern
at the D.A.'s office
that she worked with
two years ago
who doesn't have
a Facebook account.
Mm. See?
You're not the only one
who can away with fraud.
Okay, step aside.
Aha.
Holy shit.
Yeah, you do not want
to get on my bad side.
I can see that.
What are you working on?
Oh, let me rephrase.
Why the hell aren't you
working on Ava's defense?
Uh, because we got fired.
That's no reason
not to work on her defense.
Look, Harvey,
I know we're just getting back
on the same team and all,
and I don't want
to disagree with you,
but it's actually
a very excellent reason.
Wrong.
Odds are Cameron's
expecting her to do this,
and we get a call tomorrow
to get her
out of a new bribery charge.
And then whatever lawyer
she replaces us with
can't stand up
to Cameron in court.
'Cause he's not gonna
stop working on this.
And neither are we.
One more thing.
Don't.
Don't what?
You think I don't know
what you were doing
in there with Rachel?
You saw it too?
I did,
and I need you to let it go.
Wait, so you're saying
she threw a punch,
and you don't want me
to throw a punch back?
I'm saying we're
in the middle of a murder trial,
and I need you
to let it go.
Harvey, is there something
you'd like to tell me about Ava?
Yeah, some clients can be
a pain in the ass.
Some ex-clients too.
- Temporary situation.
- Good, good.
'Cause I just wanted to make
sure you were still all over it.
Did you want to make sure
the sun was still shining
and the sky
was still blue?
I'd be humble
after I got fired.
If I ever got fired.
I don't know what it's like
in the D.A.'s office now,
but if I did
what you did
to someone who was with me
in the trenches,
I'd be done,
like you are now.
You have no idea what the
story is between me and Mike.
I don't care
what the story is.
You hired me,
and then you hung me out to dry.
You don't give me cases.
You don't give me a word.
What am I supposed to do?
We both know
how you got here.
You expect more from me?
That's not my problem.
I do know how I got here,
which is how I know
you're not gonna fire me.
So keep your empty threats
to yourself.
When I said, "you're done,"
I meant your future
at this firm is over,
because you will
never be anything
more than you are
right now.
And if you ever do
anything like that
to Mike Ross again,
I don't give a shit
what our deal was.
You'll be gone.
Hey.
Remember that thing
we were gonna do to Katrina?
We don't need
to do it anymore.
- What are you talking about?
- Harvey just did it.
He went to talk to her?
He laid her out.
Yeah, you don't want to be
on his bad side either.
You know, we could still
send her that thing.
Really?
No, actually,
Harvey told me not to.
So?
He's not so tough.
Yeah,
but we could take him.
What's he gonna do?
Talk to us with his words?
Wag a finger at us.
Maybe give us a time-out.
Maybe even slap us
with a lawsuit.
High five.
- Okay.
We don't need to bribe
the witnesses.
We need them to sue us,
right?
The alien tort statute
allows foreign nationals
to bring civil claims
in U.S. court.
And then we settle.
Might be a payoff,
but it's a legal payoff.
And the witnesses
aren't Americans,
so Cameron
can't subpoena them.
Exactly.
Good, but they need
a legitimate claim,
or we could be on the hook
for bribery ourselves.
What are they suing us for?
Harvey, they witnessed
multiple murders.
That would be
emotionally distressing.
Might even
suffer from P.T.S.D.
Which would prevent them
from getting on the plane
and testifying
in our case.
Get it going.
You got a lawyer
to take the other side?
I have someone in mind,
but we need a way to get
those witnesses to go for it.
No, right now our problem
isn't getting them to go for it.
It's getting to Ava before she
gets someone to bribe them.
Hey, Harvey.
I heard about what you did
with Katrina.
I know I asked you not to,
and I wasn't going to,
but I saw her,
and I couldn't help it.
I get it.
She brings that out
in people,
but listen,
just don't let it happen again.
Son of a bitch.
I'd call you
a lying son of a bitch,
but you were
true to your word.
- Yeah, what word's that?
- You're not like me.
I didn't hijack
your client, Harvey.
Oh, no, you waited
for her to fire me,
and then you swooped in
with an illegal fix.
You're wrong.
You gonna look me in the eye
and tell me
you didn't just meet with her
about bribing those witnesses?
That's exactly
what I met with her about.
She asked me if I was willing,
and I said I was.
I also told her that
in this particular situation,
it'd be counterproductive.
You looked
into Cameron Dennis.
She bribes those witnesses,
he'll be lying in wait.
And that's what
you told her?
Yeah, amongst other things.
You told her
to stick with the lawyer
she picked
in the first place?
More or less.
Harvey, listen,
I told you,
you don't have
to trust me, okay?
But Darby does.
And Darby wants this win.
Therefore, so do I.
I'm guessing you think
that means that I owe you.
No, I think it means
you're gonna pay me.
You look happy.
Dodged a bullet.
You got Ava back.
Stephen got Ava back.
Turns out he's here to help.
And you believe that?
He got Ava back.
Mike's on his way over there
as we speak.
Mike?
He made the call.
Why not let him
score the touchdown?
And you must have
someplace else to be.
Blonde or brunette?
Neither.
I have to go repay a debt.
So once this is all
taken care of, I wire the money.
And Cameron's witnesses
never take the stand.
Harvey told me
this maneuver was your idea.
I'm not one to take credit,
but, yes, it was.
He trusts you,
doesn't he?
I like to think so.
So you know
how he thinks?
What I know
about how Harvey thinks
is that you can never be sure
what Harvey's gonna think.
What do you think
he thinks?
I think
that he's not really interested
in whether
you did it or not.
He's interested
in what the evidence is
and what we can
make it say.
I want to know.
- Then you should ask him.
- I'm asking you.
I have no idea
whether Harvey thinks
you had those people
murdered or not,
but even if I did,
I would never say anything
because he wouldn't
want me to.
He's picked
a good number two.
I like to think so.
What do you think?
I think it's my job
to represent you
to the best
of my ability.
To say anything else would be
as big a betrayal to Harvey
as discussing
what he thinks.
Let me guess,
you won the Testosterone 500,
and you're here to brag.
Actually,
Harvey took the checkered flag,
and I'm here for you.
Why would I go out
with a loser?
Well, losing
has its benefits.
If he thinks
he's a better man than me,
then he won't get jealous.
Oh, Harvey's got
nothing to be jealous of.
Not yet.
He will be
if you take a ride with me.
That could be dangerous.
Yeah.
Look,
if you think
a fancy car
and some smooth talk
is all it takes
to get to me...
Okay, I understand.
I'm sure I can find another
connoisseur of the theater
to take to MacBeth.
Oh, your research
came up short.
I've already seen MacBeth.
Not with me,
not in the front row,
and certainly
not with Daniel Day-Lewis.
I'm in trouble.
This is everything
I have on Tony Gianopolous.
Read it, summarize it,
and make it your life.
I won't let you down.
Welcome to team Litt.
Louis.
Thank you.
Here it is.
Fully executed settlement.
Signed, sealed, delivered.
Who'd you get
to represent the other side?
Harold Gunderson.
Louis' whipping boy?
Yeah, he works
for Allison Holt now,
which is actually
kind of perfect,
'cause everyone
knows she would
never do anything
to help us.
But I got Harold the job,
so--
He owes you one.
Not anymore.
What'd you say?
What?
When Ava asked
if I thought she was guilty.
I told her that I had no idea
what you thought
and it was none of her business
what I thought.
Good answer.
What about you?
You want to know
what I think?
I know what you think,
and I think it too.
She did it.
We, uh...
We never had drinks before.
I know.
Harvey,
we just admitted to each other
that we're defending
a murderer.
Doesn't really seem like
cause for celebration.
It's not a celebration.
Remember when you said
Butch and Sundance were back?
They weren't.
What do you mean?
I mean
it's time I told you
I made a deal with Darby to
take over the firm from Jessica.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man