You're the most amazing woman
I have ever met.
Are you doing what I think
you're doing?
Rachel Elizabeth Zane,
will you marry me?
- Yes.
- Yes?
You want my permission
to take Mike
and force him
to be your associate?
Speak now or forever
hold your peace.
I got us something.
It's the perfect way
to consummate our relationship.
So just wait right here.
It's in the kitchen.
- Sure.
- I can't let you do this.
You're going back
where you belong.
You never cared about me.
All you care about is yourself.
Louis, I'm not Norma.
I told you I'd never let
anything happen to you.
And I won't ever.
I should go.
Why?
You know I love you, Donna.
You ran away but not before
you told me you love me.
I did that because I wanted
to make you feel better.
I don't want your pity.
You need to start thinking about
a new secretary.
Harvey has no idea
how lucky he is to have you.
[tense music]
I'm leaving you, Harvey.
You can't just quit.
I'm not quitting.
I'm going to work for Louis.
♪ ♪
So I told him I'll cave
on the billables,
but if he wants someone
to kiss his ass all day,
he'll have to settle for Louis.
[laughs]
And what did he say?
I don't know, but we got paid
and I haven't heard
from him in a week.
I have to say Harvey,
all things considered,
you're taking this whole
Donna-Louis thing in stride.
Well, I may have my issues,
but they only make me stronger.
Good, because we're about to
walk into a room
packed with people who think
they've got us by the balls.
Well, I don't care what they
think, cause I'm gonna kill it.
[dramatic music]
What the hell's going on?
What's going on is
I left you five messages
and you never called me back.
The meeting was over an hour ago
and you weren't here.
Five messages?
Please, you have to understand,
I lost my secretary.
I don't give a shit.
I lost my company.
No, you haven't.
We can get them back.
I can take care of it.
Bullshit.
You can't even
take care of yourself.
Sorry, Harvey.
You're on your own.
♪ ♪
And then what happens?
And then I get up.
And how do you feel
when you get up?
I told you I don't wanna talk
about how I feel.
Then what are you doing here?
You know what I'm doing here.
I told you, your sleepless
nights aren't going to stop
until you accept the fact
that your secretary
isn't coming back.
And I told you they'll stop
when she does.
So just write me
another prescription
and let me get some sleep
in the meantime.
It doesn't work that way.
Then how does it work?
Why don't we start
with you taking me
through the whole story again?
What the hell good
is that gonna do?
You want the truth?
I think you might have
left some things out.
Well, I didn't,
and I'm not about to
go through this whole
damn thing again.
Then go and find yourself
another doctor.
Because I'm not writing
a prescription for anything
without you talking to me.
♪ ♪
[Mike sighs]
[Mike chuckles]
[laughs softly]
I...I can't stop
staring at it.
Oh, I noticed.
Yeah.
So will everyone else.
Well, I mean, yeah,
that's the point.
For everyone to realize
that you're my property.
[laughs]
Okay.
Are you saying you own me now?
Oh, hell yeah, and this here
is just like a little collar
for your finger.
[chuckles]
- Mm.
- Mike, seriously...
- Hmm?
I know we told my parents
last night,
but I was thinking that,
in terms of work,
maybe we should keep it
to ourselves for a bit.
I understand.
- You do?
- Sure.
You know, it's like
there's this bubble around us,
and you just don't want it
to burst yet.
And you're okay with that?
Rachel, you just agreed to spend
the rest of your life with me.
Right now I'm pretty okay
with everything.
Mm.
- Then it's settled.
- Mm.
We'll tell Donna and that's it.
What?
What about the bubble?
There's no Donna in the bubble.
Oh, come on, there's room
for Donna in the bubble.
You realize I get to sleep with
whoever's in the bubble, right?
So long as you realize
that my dad's in the bubble.
Donna it is.
[laughs]
Come here.
All right.
Remember that thing online?
- [laughs]
- We're doing it.
Donna, what the hell
are you doing?
What does it look like
I'm doing?
I'm getting rid
of these résumés.
No, no. Oh, my God, woman,
are you crazy?
I have interviews with Norma's
replacements in ten minutes.
Oh, that's gonna be hard
considering the fact
that I canceled
all your interviews.
Damn it, Donna, those were
the best candidates in the city.
No, Louis, the best candidate
in the city
is standing right
in front of you.
But you told me no.
And now I'm saying yes.
This is the most amazing moment
in my entire life.
Good.
I'll get you a temp
for a couple of weeks
and then we'll get started.
Wait, I'm sorry, wait.
You haven't told Harvey yet?
I told him. I just...
I have to give him two weeks.
Okay, you know what,
on second thought,
as much as I appreciate
the gesture,
I think you should just stay
with Harvey.
What are you talking about?
This isn't a gesture.
No, look, you just...
Do you remember
Mike almost became my associate?
(Louis) What am I talking about?
Of course you do.
Well then, you'll also remember
that just as Mike had said yes,
Harvey swoops in
and he takes him back from me
at the last second.
That isn't gonna happen.
What you don't know
is that I left the room.
I went to get Mike this cake
that said,
"Welcome to Team Litt."
Two minutes later, I come back
and there they are,
high-fiving, laughing,
and then they leave.
[somber music]
I threw the cake out.
♪ ♪
I cannot have that happen again
with you.
Louis, I told you
that isn't gonna happen.
Did you not just hear me?
It took Harvey two minutes
to steal Mike back from me.
With you, he has two weeks.
♪ ♪
So no thank you.
Donna, I need to get in touch
with Henderson before lunch,
and I need to get
Braxton a bottle of wine.
I took care of all that.
Good.
Thanks.
Is there anything else
you want to talk about?
Not that I can think of.
Did you really think
that if you just acted
like I changed my mind
that I'd change my mind?
Oh, come on, Donna, Louis?
I mean, how long do you think
that's going to last?
It's gonna last however long
I want it to last.
- Donna...
- Harvey, this is happening.
This is my formal notice.
But I have no intention
of leaving you high and dry,
so let's talk about finding you
someone in the next two weeks.
- Finding me someone?
- Yes.
I already have a list of the top
legal secretaries in the city.
You mean you made a list
for Louis
before you decided
to abandon me?
I'm not abandoning you, Harvey.
I'm doing what's best for me.
Well, as long as we're doing
what's best for ourselves,
you know what's best for me?
Ripping the Band-Aid off.
- Harvey...
- So why don't you clean out
your desk,
walk yourself over to Louis,
and take that with you?
[somber music]
This isn't how two adults who
care about each other move on.
As far as I'm concerned,
two adults
who care about each other
don't move on at all.
So, if you're gonna go, just go.
♪ ♪
♪ Suits 5x01 ♪
Denial
Original Air Date on June 24, 2015
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(sighs)
What the hell are you doing
in here?
Kevin Slattery's been
waiting 20 minutes.
- What?
- Kevin Slattery.
Didn't Donna tell you?
No, she, um...
Harvey, what's going on?
Nothing's going on.
Why is Kevin Slattery here?
He's looking for a new lawyer,
and I'm looking for you
to close him.
- Why me?
- Why not you?
Because everybody
and their mother knows
they're going bankrupt
in two weeks
and I'm not a bankruptcy expert.
Aren't you listening to me?
He doesn't want to
declare bankruptcy.
He wants you to fight for him.
Then he's come to me
on the right day.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
Kevin, I hear you're looking
for a fight
and I understand
we don't have much time.
We don't, and I just wasted
half an hour waiting for you.
So, before we get to anything,
you're gonna convince me
why I should go with you
in the first place.
Okay, we're done.
Don't let the door hit you
on the way out.
- What?
- You heard me.
Only one of us is facing
bankruptcy and it isn't me.
So instead of scolding me
for being late,
you needed to be convincing me
why I should save
your dying company.
So, nice to meet you.
Loyalty.
What did you just say?
I have a game-changing contract
that's guaranteed
to come my way in six weeks
if we can show solvency.
Guaranteed by who?
My college roommate.
And you tell that
to your bankers,
word gets out it's up for bid,
your competitors undercut you,
and your roommate won't be able
to help you anymore.
But if we make it six weeks,
we're back in business.
And I guarantee
we'll never leave you.
Here's the thing, Kevin.
I don't give a shit about
a regional trucking company
that's only going to increase
our billings 1%.
I get you out of this,
your stock's gonna go
through the roof.
- You want a piece.
- I want 20%
No way.
You're the one coming to me.
Okay?
80% of something is a whole lot
better than 100% of nothing.
[stirring music]
You gonna fight out there
like you just did in here?
This is the preseason, Kevin.
I haven't even broken a sweat.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
Do you have a second?
Yeah, sure.
What's going on?
- Donna, are you shaking?
- I never should have
- expected him to...
- What's going on?
You know what?
Never mind. Sorry.
Um...
What did you want to talk about?
You never should've expected
who to what?
What happened?
I'm leaving Harvey.
Oh, my God.
Why?
You remember when I told you
you could never go back,
and then I said
I lied about that?
Uh-huh.
Turns out I was lying
when I said I lied.
So you're just gonna leave?
No, I'm going to work for Louis.
What? When?
[laughs softly]
Today.
I'm sorry, Rachel.
You didn't come in here
to talk about this.
- What did you wanna talk...
- No.
It's nothing.
It can wait.
- You got something for me?
- When don't I?
I redid your shitty motion to
dismiss on Colter.
My shitty motion?
Yeah, your precedents
might as well have been
Flintstone v. Rubble.
Listen to me, The Flintstones
is an iconic classic
that clearly conveys the fact...
- That you're old?
- Hey, you're the one
who came up with the reference.
Which conveys the fact
that I'm smart.
Wow, somebody took their
confidence booster shot
- this morning.
- Actually, I took it
last night.
And by took it,
I mean I asked Rachel
to marry me.
Oh shit, I wasn't supposed to
tell you that, but I just did.
Then I won't say
congratulations yet.
Oh, no, you can still say it.
I can also say I need a list
of every one
of Slattery Corp's creditors,
and I need it yesterday.
Now, why would you say that
instead of congratulations?
Because we have less
than two weeks
to keep them out of bankruptcy
and we can't do that
without knowing every person
Kevin Slattery owes a nickel to.
Harvey, that list is gonna be
over 50 names long.
There's no way we can get to
all of them in two weeks.
You know what? Instead of
telling me what we can't do
and asking me for a copy
of Brides Magazine,
why don't you just get the damn
list together?
You told him we're engaged?
I couldn't help myself.
But I wish I hadn't told him.
Harvey, what's going on
with you?
Nothing's going on.
Congratulations.
There, I said it.
Where the hell is my calendar?
You know, I had it
right here yesterday.
I don't know.
I'll go get Donna.
No, don't get Donna.
I'll take care of it.
What do you mean
don't get Donna?
I said I'll take care of it.
I've got it right here.
Thanks, Rachel.
[phone rings]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
Harvey Specter's office.
No, he's not available
right now.
Can I take a message?
Why didn't you tell him
about Donna?
Because I knew Rachel knew,
and she'd tell him,
and then I wouldn't have to
waste my time with it.
Waste time or feel something?
You think I wasn't feeling
something anyway?
And what were you feeling?
Right now,
I'm feeling this deposition
- is never going to end.
- This isn't a deposition,
and you're not getting out
of this that easily.
You know what, I'm getting a
little tired of your attitude.
And what attitude is that?
The attitude where
I'm not gonna supply
prescription narcotics
to someone
who won't tell me the truth?
The attitude that says you know
me better than I know myself.
I never said I know you better
than you know yourself.
You said I'm keeping things
from you.
And that's something you know
just as much as I do.
Oh, bullshit.
I've been telling the truth
this whole time and I haven't
left out a goddamn word.
Okay, Harvey,
if that's how you wanna play it.
I do know you
better than you know yourself.
I had you pegged about
four seconds after you walked in
my door, which is why I know
you weren't just
washing your face
when Jessica walked in.
You were washing your
face because you threw up.
And you told yourself that you
were coming down with something
or you had some bad clams.
But I'll tell you
what really happened.
You threw up because
you had a panic attack.
And you're not coming to me
because you're having trouble
sleeping.
You're coming to me
because you're scared to death
that it'll happen again.
[dramatic music]
Mike, can I talk to you
for a minute?
What do you wanna talk about?
Captain Dickhead back there?
Look, I think maybe we should
cut him a little slack.
No, I cut him some slack
when he barely acknowledged
our engagement.
Then I tried to get Donna
to help him
and he bites my head off.
What are you doing?
Donna's leaving him.
And she's going to
work for Louis.
What the hell happened?
They've been through everything
together.
What could possibly...
Oh, my God,
they crossed the line.
It's more complicated than that.
What does that mean?
They crossed the line years ago.
You know what?
It doesn't matter.
I don't need to no anymore.
Of course...
we'll cut Harvey all the slack
in the world.
Okay, I am going to stay late
and help him
get everything in order.
Hey, just keep in mind
that cutting him some slack
is one thing.
Doing Donna's job is another.
It's just one day.
It's not gonna last forever.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
[clears throat]
- How'd you find me here?
- Easy.
I knew after this morning,
you'd come in here
and your standard sandwich
of commiseration.
I don't have a sandwich
of commiseration...
Rueben on rye, with bacon
instead of Russian dressing.
Well-done bacon.
And if it's all the same to you,
I would prefer to eat by myself.
Fine.
I just came in here
to give you this.
You mean...
Today is the day I work for you.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe it.
This is really happening?
What do we do first?
I mean, I'm so goddamn
turned on right now.
I don't know.
Maybe we could get a jump on
some of the things that have
been piling up since Norma.
Well, my Dictaphone's at full
capacity, it's about to burst.
Well, I could help you
with that.
- Would you?
- Of course.
That's my job.
Relieving the pressure
on your Dictaphone.
Okay, you know what?
Maybe we're, um...
moving too quickly.
Okay.
Well, how about
I just redo your calendar,
and index every live case you
have, and then get to know
every single inch
of your filing system.
I don't think that's moving
less quickly.
Culminating in that
inevitable moment
when your phone finally rings
and I say those
three magic words.
Oh, good sweet Jesus.
"Louis Litt's office."
[hissing]
God damn it, woman,
we're going back right now.
Take care of the bill.
10% tip.
Well-done bacon, my ass.
He's totally not thinking
about sex right now.
[lively music]
Tell me you found
all 50 creditors.
Not just all 50.
I found the one.
How do you know
you found the right one?
Because I know exactly
what you're gonna do.
Then let me show you how
I'm gonna do it.
[clears throat]
[laughs softly]
You're really gonna make them
do that?
- Sure am.
- All of them?
Doesn't work with some of them.
North or South?
Take your pick.
Well, Harvey, that's brilliant.
There's only one problem.
It's illegal.
Let 'em sue us.
It's civil, not criminal.
Besides, we're bluffing anyway.
What if I told you I have a way
to make it legal anyway?
I'd say your idea
better work fast
because we're going over there
in an hour.
[lively music]
(Harvey)
Vince Sanfillipo?
[imitating Hannibal Lecter]
Yes.
Is there a reason
you're not turning around?
[imitating Hannibal Lector] I like to play
a little game with some of my visitors.
For example,
you use Evian skin cream
and sometimes you wear
L'Air Du Temps.
- But not today.
- Of course I do.
[as Clarice Starling] I'm just one
generation away from poor white trash.
And I could only dream
of getting out.
Getting anywhere.
[imitating Hannibal Lector]
Getting all the way to the FBI.
A census taker tried to
test me once.
I ate his liver
with some fava beans
and a nice Chianti.
You see a lot, Doctor.
But are you strong enough
- to point that high-powered...
- Quid pro quo, Clarice...
All right.
That's enough.
We didn't come here
for a quote-off.
No, you didn't.
You came here to get me
to give Kevin Slattery
more time, and that's never
going to happen.
Actually, we're here to get you
to buy up every piece of debt
associated with Slattery Freight
and then get you to give him
more time.
And why would I do that?
Why? Because you're the biggest
debtholder,
and if any of the others
makes a claim,
it'll trigger bankruptcy,
and you get 50 cents
on the dollar five years
from tomorrow.
You think I'm gonna
double down on a loser,
because you can quote
Silence of the Lambs?
No, you're gonna do it because
the day we file bankruptcy,
every truck in that fleet's
going straight to Canada.
And that 50 cents on the dollar
just hit 25.
But that's illegal
and I will sue you
and your client into the ground.
Well, it would be illegal if we
hadn't just a bought a defunct
Canadian trucking company
for a dollar.
Bullshit!
Your covenants prohibits you
from doing that.
Not if we do it before anyone
calls in our debt.
Which we did.
You're a son of a bitch.
That's exactly what
I thought of myself
when I came up with the idea.
To be fair, I was the one
that came up with
the defunct Canadian
trucking company thingy.
- So...
- Oh, yeah, you're right.
You're a son of a bitch, too.
Oh, thanks, Harvey.
I appreciate that.
Well, now that we agree
what we are,
the question is, what are you
gonna do about it?
[stirring music]
♪ ♪
What's so funny?
I was just thinking
about that nutbag.
Who starts a meeting off
like that?
Yeah, you got to
give him credit, though.
It was pretty fun.
You think he's gonna do that bit
with the creditors?
I don't care if he makes them
put the lotion in the basket,
as long as he buys up
their debt.
[as Buffalo Bill]
Or else it gets the hose again.
(both) Wait, was she a great big
fat person?
[laughs softly]
Good job today, Mike.
Thanks.
Does this mean
I've earned the right
for us to talk about
the Donna situation?
There is no Donna situation.
Harvey, come on, I know
you're not touchy-feely, but...
Look, there's nothing
to talk about,
because it isn't gonna last.
[tense music]
Okay.
[door closes]
- Hey.
- Hi.
I got some Georgio's
reheating in the oven.
Oh, you are my hero.
Oh, I know.
I mean, who says
that men can't cook?
I think Georgio's does.
- That's a fair point.
- Mm-hmm.
So how was your test?
Mmm...
Whoa, it was that bad?
You studied like crazy.
No, it's not that
it was that bad.
I just...
I didn't take it.
What do you mean
you didn't take it?
I decided to stay late
and help Harvey.
Help Harvey what?
Never mind.
I know what.
Something that would've been
done by Donna
and should've been done by
his new secretary
except he hasn't hired one yet.
You're the one who said
we should cut him as much slack
as he needs.
I meant tolerating him
being a dick.
Not you flunking out of school.
The last time I asked Harvey
for time off,
he told me
work is my law school,
and he was right.
I'm not gonna ask him for time
when he needs me the most.
[laughs softly]
What?
- What?
- I was just thinking about
when I asked you to marry me,
I said how tenacious you are.
Well, I know.
It's like you should know what
you're getting yourself into.
But you see what happens
when you don't wear that collar
- on your finger?
- Stop it.
[stirring music]
I can't believe
you're really mine.
Now, where would be
the perfect place to...
Good morning, Louis.
Holy shit. You just scared
the shit out of me.
What are you doing here
so early?
It's 8:15.
Well, yeah, but we worked
late last night,
and I told you to
take the morning.
Louis, it's day two,
I'm not taking anything.
Oh, shoot.
I get it.
You came in early
because you bought me
an expensive gift
and you wanted to
surprise me by putting it
on my desk.
Something like that.
Do you want me to go?
You can still surprise me.
Never mind.
Uh...
Being that you're here,
I have a prospective client
coming in at 9:00.
No, you don't.
What do you mean?
The asshole canceled?
No, the asshole intentionally
showed up an hour early
and I sent him home,
telling him he was an hour late.
What, are you crazy?
That was Carl Fields, Donna.
$12 million in billings
you let walk out the door.
No, that's 12 million in
billings that's coming your way
because now he knows you're not
someone to be trifled with.
No, you can't know that.
Really?
Because I just got off the phone
with his secretary, and they're
expecting you to come by
with an engagement letter
in an hour.
Holy shit!
- Oh, shit.
- What?
What's the problem?
I'm still printing
to my old printer.
What, for the engagement letter?
Donna, please,
you've done enough.
Let me take care of it.
[lively music]
Like I wouldn't notice.
♪ ♪
There you go, little fella.
Hey.
I was...
I was just...
It's fine, Louis.
Whatever you were doing,
- it's fine.
- Hey, Harvey,
if there are
any hard feelings with Donna...
No, Louis.
No hard feelings.
Okay, but I just want to say,
if there was...
I said there's no hard feelings.
As a matter of fact,
why don't you tell Donna
I want her to have this?
[dramatic rumbling]
[poignant music]
[in slow motion]
She's leaving you.
[people laughing]
♪ ♪
You wanted to see me?
That was an hour ago.
Well, I just heard.
And I just heard the results
of your little strong-arm tactic
with Mike.
You mean you heard
that it worked.
Oh, I know you got them
to do what you wanted.
They bullied
all the other creditors,
bought off all their debt,
and they're going to back off
for eight weeks.
Why do you seem pissed?
Because you left a creditor
off the list.
What?
How could that happen?
I don't know how it happened,
but I know what it means.
We're gonna get held hostage.
I'll take care of it.
And if you can't take care of it
and Slattery goes bankrupt,
you better figure out
a way to keep him here.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means Jack Soloff's been
going around the firm
saying you're never gonna
save that company
and we don't have a plan
to retain their business
when you don't.
Since when do you care
about what Jack Soloff says?
Since he's a senior partner
with ambition
and you dropped the ball
twice in the two days.
If you're so afraid of him,
why don't you just fire him?
[laughs]
I'm not afraid of anybody,
and I never said ambition
was a bad thing.
- Jessica...
- Harvey,
I don't know what's going on
between you and Donna,
but I do know you chose
not to let me in on it,
so I'm gonna let you in on this.
If you can't figure out
how to get shit done
without her, I will.
[dramatic music]
How'd it go
with Mr. Fields?
Fine, but before you
dislocate your arm
patting yourself on the back,
I need you to file those
before you leave today.
All of them?
Yes, all of them.
That's what "those" means.
And then I want you to update
my Word Perfect by the morning.
Louis, I have tickets
to the theater at 8:00.
Second day and you're already
taking banking hours?
Okay, I hardly think
8:00 constitutes...
Norma worked till midnight
eight days a week
and never bunted an eye.
- Bunted?
- Yes, bunted.
You have a problem
with my words now?
Okay, Louis, I don't know if you
skipped your afternoon prunie
or what,
but you're making me
feel uncomfortable.
(Louis) Well, let's get
something straight.
I'm not here to
make your life comfortable.
You're here to do that for me.
And the next time you print
something to the wrong copier,
get it yourself.
♪ ♪
I gave you one job...
To find every single one
of Slattery's creditors,
and you screwed it up.
- What are you talking about?
- You left one off the list,
and as soon as they realize that
we bought out everyone else,
they'll know we have a deal
and they'll call in their debt
and the whole thing
will blow up.
Wait a second, they haven't
even called it in yet?
No, they haven't
called it in yet,
because they're gonna wait
till the last second
so they can hold us
over a barrel
because you didn't do your job.
And now I gotta find some
leverage on Katzen Financial.
I didn't miss Katzen Financial.
Then why weren't they
on the list?
I don't know, they were
on the list when I sent it...
Goddamn Rachel.
Harvey!
Katzen was the last name
on that list
and the only name on that page,
all right?
The printer must have just
run out of paper.
This isn't Rachel's fault.
What am I supposed to tell
Kevin Slattery?
"The reason you're losing
your company
is because my associate
didn't load the printer"?
I don't know, how about
you tell him the truth?
That the reason he may
lose his company
is because you didn't hire
a secretary.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
You know what it means.
Rachel has been killing herself
to take care of you,
and we haven't said anything
because we both agreed
to cut you some slack.
- We?
- Yeah, we,
but I'm not gonna let you
come down on her
for screwing up something
that wasn't her job.
Her job is to do what I say,
and you better wrap your head
around that.
No, Harvey you better wrap
your head around the fact
that Donna is gone and
she is not coming back.
And I told you, it's not
gonna last with her and Louis.
You keep saying that,
but all I see is Donna
outside Louis's office
and no one outside yours.
So you better swallow your pride
and ask her for help,
or hire a new secretary,
but either way,
you're done taking it out
on Rachel.
[tense music]
- [sighs]
- Hey, there, you got a minute?
Barely.
I need those two weeks
you offered me before.
I'm afraid
it's too late for that.
Donna, I'm drowning.
This whole thing
with the Slattery deal is...
I'm sorry about your deal,
Harvey, but you should have
thought about that
before you turned me down.
So you're punishing me?
I'm not punishing you.
But I have a mountain of work,
and even if I didn't,
how do you think Louis
would feel if I suddenly
started working for you again?
I don't give a shit
how Louis feels.
Well, what about how I feel?
Which is that you're trying
to undermine my decision.
How the hell am I trying
to undermine your decision?
What do you call this?
That... that was before...
Before what?
Before you ran into Louis?
Before you needed my help?
What?
Donna...
Do you know where I found this?
Louis put it right on top
of the list of secretaries
that I have been keeping for you
because I still care about you,
and you know what they both did?
They fed right into
his nightmare
that I'm gonna leave him,
which is exactly
what you wanted.
Do you know how hard it is
for me
to swallow my pride
and come over here?
Do you know how hard it is
for me to say no to you?
(Harvey)
Then don't.
I am asking you
for one little thing.
No, Harvey, it's not
one little thing.
Today it's the Slattery deal,
tomorrow's the Weiss merger,
and then the day after that,
it will be
a million other things
until you think everything is
back to normal.
(Donna) Well, it's not.
This is the new normal.
This is my desk now, and I wish
I could help you, but I can't.
Donna, please.
I'm sorry, Harvey,
you're on your own.
[heartbeat thumping]
(Dr. Agard) And that's when it happened,
isn't it?
You had another one.
[heartbeat thumping]
[sighs]
I don't... I don't want
to talk about it.
Step one to making them stop
is talking about it.
[heartbeat thumping]
I couldn't think,
I couldn't see, I c...
I couldn't breath.
(Dr. Agard)
And what did you do?
(Harvey)
You know what I did.
(Dr. Agard) No, I know.
I need you to say it.
Why?
'Cause the more you say it,
the less power it has over you.
[heartbeat thumping]
(Harvey) I made my way
into the bathroom,
and my heart was p-pounding,
and my chest cracked open.
[laughs]
It was... it was like
I was under water.
I looked at the stall,
and there was... two shoes there,
a piece-of-shit brown shoe,
untied, two guys laugh...
Yeah, and then?
[heartbeat accelerating]
(Harvey) [sighs]
I ran to the stall, I threw up,
and I just waited
until it was over.
[toilet flushing]
(Dr. Agard) And that's the night
you came to see me.
Yeah.
And you made up a story
about having trouble sleeping
to get antianxiety medication,
and you've been taking
a pill a day since.
Yes.
[heartbeat pounding]
Busy.
Louis...
I'm not leaving you.
It says,
"Replacements for Louis"
Right here on top,
"replacements for Louis."
That's because that's the list
I made after Norma died.
Then why do you still have it?
Because I was saving it
for Harvey.
This is for Harvey?
Yes, Louis, because I work
for you now,
and I'd like to tell you
to stop questioning
whether I'm gonna
change my mind,
but we both know
that's never gonna happen,
so instead, I'll say...
you need to talk to me about it
when it does.
But I did talk to you, Donna.
First, I loaded you up
with work, then I yelled at you,
and then I put the can-opener
on top of that list.
I mean, I can't be
more direct than that.
Yes, you can, Louis.
Because I don't want that kind
of relationship anymore.
What's it for?
What's what for?
(Louis)
The can opener.
It's just a can opener, Louis.
No, it's not.
Harvey was sending me a message
when he gave it to me.
That message wasn't meant
for you.
It was meant for me.
Donna, you want me
to talk to you,
but now you're not
talking to me.
It was a ritual
that Harvey and I would do
before we went to trial.
So the message was,
Donna, you'll never have
something like that with me.
No, Louis, that's not what...
We should have a ritual.
Let's worry about that
after we win our first big case.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
I was just about to offer you
one of those.
Jessica, if you're here
to yell at me again...
I'm not here to yell at you.
I'm here to apologize to you.
Then you can have a drink.
The truth is,
there's a time for yelling
and there is a time
for understanding,
and a good partner
knows the difference.
You mean
a good managing partner.
No, I mean a good partner.
The night you found out
Donna was in trouble,
the first thing you did
was take the time...
to have a drink with me
about Jeff.
So the least I could do
is take the time
and understand your situation.
You mean, the fact
that I don't have a secretary.
I mean that after 12 years,
the woman you wouldn't
come work here without
is now working for someone else.
And you want to know why.
I don't need to know why.
I need to know if you want me
to undo it.
What?
I know you and Donna
aren't me and Jeff,
but you are as close
as two people can be
without being that.
Shit, Harvey, Scottie leaving
didn't throw you off your game
this much.
I appreciate the offer.
But as long as Donna wants
to work for Louis,
I am not gonna force her
to work for me.
Okay.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
Harvey, have you thought about
what's going to happen
if she doesn't come back?
She will.
♪ ♪
(Dr. Agard)
Wow.
Wow what?
This Jessica sounds like
a hell of a woman.
What does that have to do
with anything?
No, it doesn't.
I-I was just...
Look, I don't care
what you were doing.
We've been here long enough.
Hmm, we have.
But I'm not gonna give you
another prescription.
You said if I opened up...
I said if you didn't,
I wouldn't.
I didn't say if you did,
I would.
They're not the same thing.
Goddamn it.
Hold on, you didn't
let me finish.
I'm not gonna write you
another prescription.
I'm gonna give you these.
That's enough for another week.
You want me to come
in here again.
Mm, I sure do.
Or you can roll the dice
and spread them out,
but you're not getting anymore
without seeing me again.
[moody pop music]
♪ ♪
One more thing.
These episodes are gonna
keep happening
until you accept the fact
that Donna may never come back.
♪ ♪
Where the hell have you been
all morning?
What are you, my mother?
I was at a meeting.
Why?
Remember when you said
Katzen was gonna
wait till the last second
to hold us over a barrel?
Well, they didn't.
They sold all of their debt
to Kevin Slattery's
biggest competitor.
They're gonna want to put us
in the ground for good.
Well, then it's a good thing
I figured out a way
to convince 'em not to.
What the hell are we still
doing here?
You tell me.
♪ ♪
What the hell happened?
Atlantic Freight
is my chief rival.
If they call in the debt,
they'll force me
into bankruptcy.
If they call in the debt.
What is he talking about?
He's talking about the fact
that we just came from
a meeting with them,
and you're right.
They'd love nothing more
than to put you down
once and for all.
Goddamn it.
But lucky for you, we told them
that if they force you
into bankruptcy,
that doesn't necessarily
kill your company,
but buying your name does.
So they own me?
That's your brilliant solution?
No, they own
the Slattery trademark,
which they think
effectively puts you under,
but they don't know
what we know.
And what is that?
That you have another contract
that doesn't care
about the name of your company.
They only care
about the name of the owner.
How the hell did Katzen
even know to sell their debt?
Because I made a mistake.
You sure as hell did!
After asking for 20%
of my company
and bragging that
you could save it.
Well, it turns out it, you're
just an arrogant mouthpiece
that thinks he can
save anything.
But you can't.
Kevin, nobody hates change
more than I do,
but it's coming
whether we like it or not.
And if I could save
both your company and your name,
I would,
but you're right, I can't.
So take the deal, wake up
tomorrow, and go to work.
[stirring music]
♪ ♪
Hey, Harvey?
Yeah.
I just want to say thanks...
for not throwing us
under the bus back there.
What do you mean?
Well, I mean, you could have
told Slattery the truth.
That mistake was
mine and Rachel's.
No it wasn't.
You were right,
that mistake was mine.
[poignant music]
♪ ♪
Hey. What are you
doing here so late?
You didn't hear?
We closed the Davis brothers.
- That's huge.
- It is.
So I thought maybe
this was the perfect time
to start our ritual.
Oh, Donna, listen,
I've been thinking.
I don't think we don't need
to have a ritual.
Come on.
It's our first big win.
That's the same exact cake
I got Mike.
I know.
How did you know?
I'm Donna.
[laughs softly]
You sure are.
What flavor is it?
Well, I called Esther,
and she said
German Chocolate was
your favorite.
I hate German Chocolate.
Which is why I got you
Mocha Fudge.
It's perfect.
[sniffs]
What can I do for you, Harvey?
I just wanted to see
if you still had that list.
Of course I do.
[heartbeat thumping]
[door opens]
[rousing pop music]
♪ ♪
What's this?
Your engagement present.
Come on, Rachel,
how long did you think
you could keep
that glow a secret?
I'm glowing?
Like Times Square
on New Year's Eve.
To me.
The rest of the world
can't even see you
under that pile of work
you took on to help Harvey.
You knew about that too?
Of course I did,
which is why
you're getting this.
Donna, you didn't have to...
I didn't, but Harvey did.
And he won't think
to get you two a gift,
'cause I was always the one
who took care of things
like that, so...
I don't know what to say.
Say thank you.
Thank you.
And promise me,
no matter what is going on
in my life,
you won't feel bad about telling
me all the good things in yours.
I promise.
[stirring music]
♪ ♪
What is this?
(Harvey)
A copy of Brides Magazine.
Why is it on my desk?
How else are you gonna
pick your colors?
Colors?
What are colors?
How do you know what they are?
Because I'm a grown man.
Really? 'Cause you sound
more like a grown woman.
That's very hurtful.
I looked everywhere
for that issue.
Thanks, Harvey.
Thank me on the way.
Where are we going?
To do what we should have done
the day you got engaged.
Nets game.
Are you kidding?
Front row.
Holy shit.
Is Jay-Z gonna be there?
Yeah, right next to me.
Next to you?
Wait, this my gift, hey.
I don't care whose gift it is.
I'm not doing that to Jay-Z.
Oh, you know what,
I'll just sit next to Beyoncé.
We'll call it a draw.
You know what, never mind.
I'm taking Rachel.
Yeah, well, why don't you just
give it to both of us?
Oh, wait, then who would
stay here and do all your work?
Shit.
Was that too soon?
Oh, I'm so sorry, bud.
Let's go!
[rousing pop music]
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man