1
00:00:01,034 --> 00:00:02,227
Previously on Suits...

2
00:00:02,472 --> 00:00:04,191
That's not
Woodall coming after us.

3
00:00:04,309 --> 00:00:05,325
It's Sean Cahill.

4
00:00:05,444 --> 00:00:07,864
If your hands weren't full
with Eric,

5
00:00:08,000 --> 00:00:09,918
they will be full with me.

6
00:00:10,053 --> 00:00:12,533
What happened to "You think
I'm staying if you leave?"

7
00:00:12,557 --> 00:00:13,584
Yeah, that was before I knew

8
00:00:13,609 --> 00:00:15,004
you were gonna screw
over Sidwell.

9
00:00:15,029 --> 00:00:16,814
Forstman doesn't throw
money around

10
00:00:16,982 --> 00:00:17,882
without getting something
in return.

11
00:00:18,001 --> 00:00:19,836
I have no other choice!

12
00:00:19,955 --> 00:00:21,800
You two are on opposite sides
of a takeover battle,

13
00:00:21,825 --> 00:00:24,011
and your girlfriend
is your associate.

14
00:00:24,129 --> 00:00:25,742
Are you trying to say
that we're colluding?

15
00:00:25,766 --> 00:00:27,047
You went right there,
didn't you?

16
00:00:31,259 --> 00:00:33,796
So we're just gonna go back
and forth trading favors?

17
00:00:33,931 --> 00:00:35,349
Are you my lawyer or not?

18
00:00:35,517 --> 00:00:38,020
Seriously, Rachel, I couldn't
have done it without you.

19
00:00:38,189 --> 00:00:40,074
Logan, I should go.

20
00:00:43,382 --> 00:00:45,217
Damn right.
You get one, Huntley.

21
00:00:45,352 --> 00:00:47,304
Eisenheim, you
silly son of a bitch.

22
00:00:47,440 --> 00:00:49,025
You think I'd leave you
out of the fun?

23
00:00:49,175 --> 00:00:51,061
Riceman, after you killed
the singer depo.

24
00:00:52,198 --> 00:00:53,416
Out of my way, Johnson.

25
00:00:53,551 --> 00:00:54,996
Coffee's for closers.
You don't get a mug.

26
00:00:55,020 --> 00:00:57,205
Am I to assume I'm getting
my own personal Litt-up mug?

27
00:00:57,207 --> 00:00:58,207
Absolutely not.

28
00:00:58,209 --> 00:01:00,295
Those are mere mugs.

29
00:01:00,430 --> 00:01:03,969
This, My Lady, is a chalice.

30
00:01:04,070 --> 00:01:05,070
Okay.

31
00:01:05,206 --> 00:01:06,624
It looks like
all the other ones.

32
00:01:06,776 --> 00:01:07,820
No, Donna.

33
00:01:07,844 --> 00:01:10,681
What makes this a chalice
is not the mug.

34
00:01:10,800 --> 00:01:13,018
It's what's inside.

35
00:01:13,187 --> 00:01:14,856
Wait a second. Is that...

36
00:01:14,991 --> 00:01:16,353
Mm-hmm, an exact replica
of the one.

37
00:01:16,360 --> 00:01:19,414
Dame Judi Dench wore as Ophelia.

38
00:01:19,550 --> 00:01:21,863
Louis, this must
have cost a fortune.

39
00:01:21,887 --> 00:01:22,887
Donna, please.

40
00:01:23,006 --> 00:01:24,527
You helped me overcome
my stage fright.

41
00:01:24,642 --> 00:01:27,496
You can't put a price on that.

42
00:01:29,751 --> 00:01:30,751
I don't know what to say.

43
00:01:30,887 --> 00:01:34,809
That's all you have to say.

44
00:01:34,945 --> 00:01:36,061
I got one for Harvey too.

45
00:01:36,197 --> 00:01:37,509
You know, Louis,
I don't think that...

46
00:01:37,533 --> 00:01:39,201
I know he is still upset with me

47
00:01:39,370 --> 00:01:40,805
for leading Mike to Forstman,

48
00:01:40,906 --> 00:01:42,734
but I just thought maybe
if he could...

49
00:01:42,759 --> 00:01:43,759
Give it to me.

50
00:01:43,761 --> 00:01:46,532
I will take care of it.

51
00:01:46,683 --> 00:01:49,704
Thank you, Donna.

52
00:01:51,325 --> 00:01:53,160
Hey, Mike,
Sidwell wants to see you.

53
00:01:53,296 --> 00:01:55,492
Shit.

54
00:01:55,517 --> 00:01:56,633
What?

55
00:01:56,769 --> 00:01:58,888
He took Forstman's money
last night.

56
00:01:59,006 --> 00:02:01,058
Do you think he knows
you're gonna cut him

57
00:02:01,177 --> 00:02:02,194
out of the deal?

58
00:02:02,346 --> 00:02:05,200
There's only one way
to find out.

59
00:02:29,897 --> 00:02:31,165
You wanted to see me?

60
00:02:31,283 --> 00:02:35,840
Damn right I did.

61
00:02:35,959 --> 00:02:40,215
Something you want to tell me?

62
00:02:40,350 --> 00:02:43,471
Jonathan,
I don't know what to say.

63
00:02:43,607 --> 00:02:45,118
Well, you better
think of something

64
00:02:45,142 --> 00:02:46,737
'cause I just got off the phone
with some asshole

65
00:02:46,761 --> 00:02:48,564
from the SEC who accused you

66
00:02:48,699 --> 00:02:52,103
of colluding
with Harvey Specter.

67
00:02:52,239 --> 00:02:54,401
That's bullshit.

68
00:02:54,426 --> 00:02:56,355
Then why the hell were the two
of you sharing a porterhouse

69
00:02:56,380 --> 00:02:57,692
when you were supposed
to be buying stock

70
00:02:57,716 --> 00:02:58,934
from me two nights ago?

71
00:02:59,085 --> 00:03:00,880
- It's not what you think.
- What I think is

72
00:03:00,905 --> 00:03:03,135
you better start telling me
what's going on around here.

73
00:03:03,160 --> 00:03:04,277
There's nothing going on.

74
00:03:04,412 --> 00:03:05,757
Look, I know that guy.
He's full of shit.

75
00:03:05,781 --> 00:03:07,093
Well, I don't know him
from a hole in the ground,

76
00:03:07,117 --> 00:03:08,712
but I know that
you're keeping stuff from me.

77
00:03:08,736 --> 00:03:09,920
Jonathan, I...

78
00:03:10,056 --> 00:03:11,200
First you don't transfer
Forstman's money.

79
00:03:11,225 --> 00:03:12,703
Then you blow
a straight-up stock purchase

80
00:03:12,727 --> 00:03:14,656
that any first-year trader
could do in his sleep.

81
00:03:14,681 --> 00:03:15,742
It wasn't straight-up.

82
00:03:15,766 --> 00:03:16,859
I had to set up an auction,

83
00:03:16,884 --> 00:03:18,353
which happened to get postponed.

84
00:03:18,455 --> 00:03:19,465
Yeah, 'cause you were
sipping wine

85
00:03:19,490 --> 00:03:20,852
with Harvey Specter behind
my back.

86
00:03:20,993 --> 00:03:22,354
It got postponed
because my girlfriend

87
00:03:22,378 --> 00:03:23,723
was in the hospital.

88
00:03:23,747 --> 00:03:26,418
What?

89
00:03:26,536 --> 00:03:27,971
Rachel passed out at school.

90
00:03:28,089 --> 00:03:29,350
Harvey and I went
to the hospital,

91
00:03:29,374 --> 00:03:30,569
so we pushed the sale.

92
00:03:30,593 --> 00:03:33,264
- Then you should have told me.
- You're right.

93
00:03:33,399 --> 00:03:34,684
I should have. I'm sorry.

94
00:03:34,852 --> 00:03:37,522
But that's what happened.

95
00:03:37,691 --> 00:03:39,359
That's it?

96
00:03:39,527 --> 00:03:41,864
That's it.

97
00:03:41,998 --> 00:03:45,419
Fine.

98
00:03:45,571 --> 00:03:49,094
But if there is anything else
that you're not telling me,

99
00:03:49,212 --> 00:03:51,098
now is the time.

100
00:03:54,922 --> 00:03:58,444
There isn't.

101
00:04:21,856 --> 00:04:22,906
Well?

102
00:04:23,025 --> 00:04:24,637
Allison is at dinner
with some friends,

103
00:04:24,661 --> 00:04:26,196
but she'll be home soon.

104
00:04:26,331 --> 00:04:28,000
I have to go.

105
00:04:28,151 --> 00:04:29,953
Come on, we're working.

106
00:04:31,674 --> 00:04:33,426
We're not working.

107
00:04:33,545 --> 00:04:36,659
I am sneaking around,
pretending to work

108
00:04:36,684 --> 00:04:38,469
so that I can spend time
with you.

109
00:04:38,604 --> 00:04:41,224
Sneaking around?

110
00:04:41,359 --> 00:04:43,145
That's what I'd call it,
wouldn't you?

111
00:04:43,279 --> 00:04:45,732
I don't know.

112
00:04:45,851 --> 00:04:50,408
I just don't really want
to think of it like that.

113
00:04:50,526 --> 00:04:52,328
I have to go.

114
00:04:54,834 --> 00:04:57,254
Well, she's with her friends.

115
00:04:57,372 --> 00:04:59,341
Aren't you allowed to be
with your friends?

116
00:04:59,510 --> 00:05:03,566
Is that what we are,
we're friends?

117
00:05:06,940 --> 00:05:12,699
I was actually hoping
that we're more than that.

118
00:05:15,256 --> 00:05:18,376
Mm, we shouldn't be
having this conversation.

119
00:05:20,249 --> 00:05:22,134
You wouldn't be here

120
00:05:22,252 --> 00:05:25,389
if you didn't want to be
having this conversation.

121
00:05:27,312 --> 00:05:28,757
Rachel.

122
00:05:28,781 --> 00:05:34,708
We have had chemistry
from the second we met.

123
00:05:34,825 --> 00:05:39,299
You know it.

124
00:05:39,450 --> 00:05:43,423
And I know it.

125
00:06:14,984 --> 00:06:16,869
Rachel. Hey.

126
00:06:17,021 --> 00:06:18,206
Hi.

127
00:06:18,357 --> 00:06:20,961
What are you doing here?

128
00:06:21,078 --> 00:06:23,164
I am here because I wanted
to talk to you

129
00:06:23,299 --> 00:06:25,145
before you came in
to see Harvey this morning.

130
00:06:25,170 --> 00:06:27,472
Do you want some coffee?

131
00:06:27,591 --> 00:06:29,403
No, I won't be here
long enough for that.

132
00:06:29,428 --> 00:06:31,563
Are you sure?

133
00:06:31,715 --> 00:06:33,684
Look, Logan.

134
00:06:33,852 --> 00:06:35,270
I know why you're here.

135
00:06:35,406 --> 00:06:37,742
If you knew why I was here,

136
00:06:37,893 --> 00:06:39,945
then I wouldn't need to be here.

137
00:06:40,064 --> 00:06:41,760
I think you're here to tell me
that what's happening

138
00:06:41,784 --> 00:06:46,290
isn't really happening,
but it is.

139
00:06:48,931 --> 00:06:51,077
I have a boyfriend that I love,

140
00:06:51,101 --> 00:06:53,748
so I need you to
stop pursuing me.

141
00:06:53,773 --> 00:06:56,527
No more flowers, no more looks,

142
00:06:56,645 --> 00:06:58,480
no more attempted kisses,

143
00:06:58,598 --> 00:07:00,094
no more anything, okay?

144
00:07:00,118 --> 00:07:03,122
Look, you said that if
I knew why you were here,

145
00:07:03,274 --> 00:07:06,128
you wouldn't need to be here.

146
00:07:06,280 --> 00:07:08,082
I think you do need to be here,

147
00:07:08,216 --> 00:07:10,920
and we both know why.

148
00:07:11,056 --> 00:07:13,592
You're wrong.

149
00:07:13,760 --> 00:07:18,651
I don't think I am.

150
00:07:18,769 --> 00:07:20,654
You once told me
we had chemistry

151
00:07:20,773 --> 00:07:23,076
the second that we met.

152
00:07:27,486 --> 00:07:30,006
Logan, please.

153
00:07:30,157 --> 00:07:34,097
Tell me to stop, and I'll stop.

154
00:07:49,877 --> 00:07:50,877
I can't.

155
00:07:50,879 --> 00:07:52,331
Rachel. Rachel.

156
00:07:55,371 --> 00:07:58,927
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪

157
00:07:59,061 --> 00:08:02,265
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪

158
00:08:02,401 --> 00:08:05,438
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪

159
00:08:05,574 --> 00:08:09,163
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪

160
00:08:09,280 --> 00:08:12,117
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪

161
00:08:12,236 --> 00:08:16,125
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪

162
00:08:16,260 --> 00:08:17,595
♪ All right ♪

163
00:08:17,713 --> 00:08:21,716
♪ Suits 4x06 ♪ Litt the Hell Up
Original Air Date on July 23, 2014

164
00:08:23,223 --> 00:08:24,273
♪ the greenback boogie ♪

165
00:08:24,298 --> 00:08:28,301
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man

166
00:08:28,503 --> 00:08:29,671
Harvey, I need to...

167
00:08:29,788 --> 00:08:31,257
What the hell is this?

168
00:08:31,391 --> 00:08:33,143
It's from Louis.
He wanted you to have it.

169
00:08:33,261 --> 00:08:36,199
What do you mean he wanted me
to have it?

170
00:08:36,368 --> 00:08:38,563
You haven't talked to him
since Mike landed Forstman.

171
00:08:38,588 --> 00:08:39,756
It's a gesture.

172
00:08:39,891 --> 00:08:41,119
Now, can I please
get back to what...

173
00:08:41,143 --> 00:08:42,928
Oh, why didn't you say
it was a gesture?

174
00:08:43,064 --> 00:08:46,068
Mike has access to Forstman
and his $4 billion.

175
00:08:46,185 --> 00:08:47,887
Logan's on his way over
to discuss

176
00:08:48,006 --> 00:08:50,509
our next move, which we can't
make for two more weeks

177
00:08:50,660 --> 00:08:52,929
because Louis thought Sheila
was marrying Lorenzo Lamas,

178
00:08:53,098 --> 00:08:54,767
but I just got a mug
with something stupid

179
00:08:54,902 --> 00:08:57,121
printed on it,
so now everything's okay.

180
00:08:57,240 --> 00:08:58,708
Great.

181
00:08:58,826 --> 00:08:59,919
Are you done being a dick?

182
00:08:59,944 --> 00:09:01,279
Because everything's not okay.

183
00:09:01,380 --> 00:09:02,742
- What did Louis do now?
- Nothing.

184
00:09:02,850 --> 00:09:04,986
And Logan Sanders isn't
on his way here

185
00:09:05,121 --> 00:09:09,027
because he just got
brought down to the SEC.

186
00:09:12,301 --> 00:09:13,412
What the hell do you think
you're doing

187
00:09:13,437 --> 00:09:14,815
talking to my client
without me present?

188
00:09:14,839 --> 00:09:16,107
Oh, he hasn't said a word yet.

189
00:09:16,225 --> 00:09:17,369
We're waiting for you
to get the party started.

190
00:09:17,394 --> 00:09:18,537
And what gives you the right

191
00:09:18,562 --> 00:09:19,824
to bring him here
in the first place?

192
00:09:19,849 --> 00:09:21,695
The United States government
gives me the right,

193
00:09:21,719 --> 00:09:22,729
so if you don't mind,
I have a few questions

194
00:09:22,754 --> 00:09:23,837
I would like to ask him.

195
00:09:23,989 --> 00:09:25,591
You got questions for him,
you ask me.

196
00:09:25,710 --> 00:09:26,737
Okay, here's one.

197
00:09:26,762 --> 00:09:28,174
What makes you think
you can get away

198
00:09:28,198 --> 00:09:29,516
with collusion on my watch?

199
00:09:29,650 --> 00:09:31,171
I already told you
we're not colluding,

200
00:09:31,302 --> 00:09:33,522
and you harassing my client
won't change that.

201
00:09:33,658 --> 00:09:34,953
Will me telling him
about your date

202
00:09:34,977 --> 00:09:36,846
the other night
with Mike Ross change that?

203
00:09:36,947 --> 00:09:38,308
What?

204
00:09:38,333 --> 00:09:39,477
See, I think he and Mike Ross
are colluding

205
00:09:39,502 --> 00:09:41,671
to allow you to purchase
Gillis Industry stock

206
00:09:41,807 --> 00:09:42,807
at a cut rate price.

207
00:09:42,808 --> 00:09:43,924
That's bullshit.

208
00:09:44,061 --> 00:09:45,239
Then why would you set up
a private auction

209
00:09:45,263 --> 00:09:47,148
while neither one
of you ended up bidding?

210
00:09:47,283 --> 00:09:49,262
And Logan here mysteriously
bought the stock

211
00:09:49,287 --> 00:09:50,932
without any competition.

212
00:09:50,957 --> 00:09:53,109
That's it. We're done.

213
00:09:53,245 --> 00:09:55,223
You didn't bring us in here
to ask him questions.

214
00:09:55,247 --> 00:09:57,885
You brought us in here to ask me
questions in front of him.

215
00:09:58,053 --> 00:09:59,305
Am I smart enough to do that?

216
00:09:59,439 --> 00:10:01,391
You're dumb enough to try,
and we're leaving.

217
00:10:01,527 --> 00:10:02,688
I have not dismissed you yet.

218
00:10:02,695 --> 00:10:05,332
Then arrest us on the way out.

219
00:10:05,450 --> 00:10:08,087
Gentlemen.

220
00:10:13,932 --> 00:10:15,901
Hey, what's going on?

221
00:10:16,020 --> 00:10:17,655
You look upset.

222
00:10:17,773 --> 00:10:18,924
No, it's nothing.

223
00:10:19,026 --> 00:10:21,496
I just found out
I have to go to Columbia,

224
00:10:21,630 --> 00:10:23,142
so could you just tell Harvey
that I won't be able

225
00:10:23,166 --> 00:10:24,206
to make the Logan meeting?

226
00:10:24,335 --> 00:10:25,720
Rachel, there is no meeting.

227
00:10:25,872 --> 00:10:27,807
Logan got hauled down
to the SEC.

228
00:10:27,943 --> 00:10:29,227
What?

229
00:10:29,362 --> 00:10:30,823
I just saw him this morning.
That doesn't make...

230
00:10:30,847 --> 00:10:33,651
Well, it must have been...
Wait a second.

231
00:10:33,787 --> 00:10:35,956
They picked him up at his condo.

232
00:10:36,091 --> 00:10:39,462
Why were you at Logan's condo?

233
00:10:39,598 --> 00:10:42,101
Donna, please don't
do your thing on me.

234
00:10:42,219 --> 00:10:44,939
Rachel, what is going on?

235
00:10:47,579 --> 00:10:49,331
The other night
I was working with Logan,

236
00:10:49,449 --> 00:10:53,622
and things got intense,
and he tried to kiss me.

237
00:10:53,757 --> 00:10:55,425
Okay, so what did you do?

238
00:10:55,561 --> 00:10:58,148
Nothing. I didn't do anything.

239
00:10:58,299 --> 00:11:00,518
Then why were you at
his condo this morning?

240
00:11:00,653 --> 00:11:03,707
I went to tell him
that I didn't want him

241
00:11:03,826 --> 00:11:04,910
to get the wrong idea.

242
00:11:05,078 --> 00:11:06,359
Rachel, if you went
to his place,

243
00:11:06,381 --> 00:11:08,082
you were giving him
the wrong idea.

244
00:11:11,256 --> 00:11:13,392
Something happened, didn't it?

245
00:11:15,448 --> 00:11:16,649
I kissed him.

246
00:11:16,783 --> 00:11:19,069
How long?

247
00:11:19,204 --> 00:11:20,204
Too long.

248
00:11:20,373 --> 00:11:21,708
God, I feel horrible.

249
00:11:21,876 --> 00:11:22,886
I'm a horrible person.

250
00:11:22,911 --> 00:11:24,379
No, you're not.

251
00:11:24,515 --> 00:11:28,521
You are a great person
who had a not-so-great moment.

252
00:11:28,655 --> 00:11:30,607
Donna, please, you can't
say a word to anyone.

253
00:11:30,726 --> 00:11:31,994
Of course not.

254
00:11:32,112 --> 00:11:35,116
But Rachel, you can't say
a word to anyone either.

255
00:11:41,512 --> 00:11:43,231
Go ahead,
say what you're gonna say.

256
00:11:43,350 --> 00:11:44,360
You know what I'm gonna say.

257
00:11:44,385 --> 00:11:45,435
Is what he said true?

258
00:11:45,570 --> 00:11:47,356
Logan, I am not
colluding with Mike Ross.

259
00:11:47,524 --> 00:11:48,534
Well, if I thought that,

260
00:11:48,559 --> 00:11:49,755
I wouldn't even
be standing here.

261
00:11:49,779 --> 00:11:52,359
I'm talking about you
buying that stock.

262
00:11:52,383 --> 00:11:54,335
- Look, I can't talk about that.
- Why not?

263
00:11:54,504 --> 00:11:56,723
Because telling you about it
would make it parking,

264
00:11:56,842 --> 00:11:57,852
but that doesn't matter anymore

265
00:11:57,877 --> 00:11:59,762
because now that
that guy hauled you in,

266
00:11:59,897 --> 00:12:01,692
we can't do a thing
with those shares anyway.

267
00:12:01,717 --> 00:12:04,237
Well, what can we do?

268
00:12:04,388 --> 00:12:06,658
You and Mike Ross can get
in a room together,

269
00:12:06,776 --> 00:12:09,447
and put this thing to bed
once and for all.

270
00:12:09,565 --> 00:12:11,250
No, that's a bad idea.

271
00:12:11,401 --> 00:12:13,620
Logan, if we don't finish
this now,

272
00:12:13,756 --> 00:12:14,924
you're gonna have the SEC

273
00:12:15,076 --> 00:12:16,544
crawling up your ass
day and night.

274
00:12:16,712 --> 00:12:18,024
Look, you can try
to scare me all you want,

275
00:12:18,048 --> 00:12:19,382
but I did nothing wrong,

276
00:12:19,517 --> 00:12:21,228
and the last guy I'm getting
in a room with

277
00:12:21,253 --> 00:12:23,473
is Mike goddamn Ross.

278
00:12:28,868 --> 00:12:30,236
Don't you ever knock?

279
00:12:30,404 --> 00:12:32,874
Logan Sanders got taken
downtown this morning.

280
00:12:32,992 --> 00:12:34,160
Sean Cahill.

281
00:12:34,294 --> 00:12:35,305
Son of a bitch is throwing shit

282
00:12:35,330 --> 00:12:36,390
at the wall to see what sticks.

283
00:12:36,415 --> 00:12:38,501
- And what stuck?
- Wexler.

284
00:12:38,619 --> 00:12:40,115
Logan found out
we bought that stock.

285
00:12:40,139 --> 00:12:41,924
Did you tell him
why we kept it from him?

286
00:12:42,059 --> 00:12:43,788
- He didn't seem to care.
- All right.

287
00:12:43,813 --> 00:12:45,041
Well, it doesn't matter
because you're going to end

288
00:12:45,065 --> 00:12:46,567
this takeover battle now.

289
00:12:46,684 --> 00:12:48,937
What do you think I've been
doing for the past month?

290
00:12:49,106 --> 00:12:51,218
Harvey, I don't think you
understand what I'm saying.

291
00:12:51,243 --> 00:12:53,840
This guy's already looking
at us for collusion.

292
00:12:53,864 --> 00:12:55,199
The longer this thing drags on,

293
00:12:55,334 --> 00:12:56,815
the more likely he is
to come after us

294
00:12:56,820 --> 00:12:57,820
for buying that stock.

295
00:12:57,956 --> 00:13:00,626
In other words, end this thing?

296
00:13:00,794 --> 00:13:02,229
Not in other words.

297
00:13:02,364 --> 00:13:04,684
In those exact words.

298
00:13:10,486 --> 00:13:12,990
So I guess Jonathan didn't
know you sold him out.

299
00:13:14,137 --> 00:13:15,244
How'd you know that?

300
00:13:15,246 --> 00:13:16,614
Because if he knew,

301
00:13:16,749 --> 00:13:17,615
he'd have come by your office

302
00:13:17,751 --> 00:13:18,952
and ripped you to pieces.

303
00:13:19,069 --> 00:13:20,671
Instead, you're out here
enjoying a bagel

304
00:13:20,673 --> 00:13:21,985
without the courtesy
of coming by

305
00:13:22,009 --> 00:13:23,677
to tell me that he didn't know.
My bad.

306
00:13:23,812 --> 00:13:25,931
So now what are we gonna do?

307
00:13:26,066 --> 00:13:27,361
Well, we're gonna kick some ass.

308
00:13:27,385 --> 00:13:30,389
Wait.
What are you talking about?

309
00:13:30,525 --> 00:13:32,160
The SEC called Sidwell,

310
00:13:32,328 --> 00:13:34,491
and I guarantee you
they also called Logan Sanders,

311
00:13:34,516 --> 00:13:36,818
which means Harvey can't
use those shares,

312
00:13:36,970 --> 00:13:38,238
and I'm in the driver's seat.

313
00:13:38,356 --> 00:13:40,241
- Well, that explains it.
- Explains what?

314
00:13:40,410 --> 00:13:42,880
Harvey just called.
He wants to have a meeting.

315
00:13:47,055 --> 00:13:49,024
- Jeff.
- Hey.

316
00:13:49,159 --> 00:13:50,671
Did you hear what
Sean Cahill did this morning?

317
00:13:50,696 --> 00:13:52,665
I did. Yeah.

318
00:13:52,799 --> 00:13:54,645
Then you know he's poking
around the Wexler purchase.

319
00:13:54,670 --> 00:13:55,680
Ah, let him.

320
00:13:55,705 --> 00:13:56,973
You don't seem very concerned.

321
00:13:57,107 --> 00:13:59,193
I'm not concerned
because I did a damn good job

322
00:13:59,345 --> 00:14:01,197
protecting this firm
from any liability.

323
00:14:01,349 --> 00:14:02,711
Yeah, well, the question is
did you protect us

324
00:14:02,735 --> 00:14:05,155
from all liability?

325
00:14:05,323 --> 00:14:09,646
Is there something that
you want to ask me, Jessica?

326
00:14:09,797 --> 00:14:11,566
I want you to go
back over your work

327
00:14:11,668 --> 00:14:15,274
with a fine-tooth comb,
and make sure it's airtight.

328
00:14:15,408 --> 00:14:17,878
Jessica, you're the one
who asked me to buy that stock,

329
00:14:18,046 --> 00:14:21,902
and I made it questionable,
like you asked,

330
00:14:22,054 --> 00:14:25,208
but if Sean Cahill comes at
us for attempting to park it,

331
00:14:25,327 --> 00:14:27,379
that is on you, not my work.

332
00:14:27,531 --> 00:14:30,669
Jeff, just go back over
everything like I said.

333
00:14:30,803 --> 00:14:31,830
There's nothing to go back over.

334
00:14:31,855 --> 00:14:33,440
We're as protected as we can be.

335
00:14:33,576 --> 00:14:34,817
Okay, maybe you didn't hear me.

336
00:14:34,911 --> 00:14:36,747
Every partner at this firm

337
00:14:36,882 --> 00:14:38,467
goes over their work
if I say so.

338
00:14:38,618 --> 00:14:39,699
And you know what, Jessica?

339
00:14:39,720 --> 00:14:43,192
I'm not every goddamn partner.

340
00:14:43,310 --> 00:14:46,698
So either you trust me
or you don't.

341
00:14:54,315 --> 00:14:56,183
Hey, look what the cat
dragged in.

342
00:14:56,352 --> 00:14:58,654
Such a serious expression.

343
00:14:58,790 --> 00:15:01,343
It's because we need to have
a serious conversation.

344
00:15:01,461 --> 00:15:02,696
Well, let's get to it.

345
00:15:02,797 --> 00:15:04,125
I want you to come up
with a number

346
00:15:04,149 --> 00:15:06,936
that we can pay you
to end this thing.

347
00:15:07,072 --> 00:15:09,709
And why would I do that?

348
00:15:09,826 --> 00:15:12,213
Because Sean Cahill
hauled Logan into the SEC.

349
00:15:12,348 --> 00:15:14,383
Well, all that means is
that you can't vote

350
00:15:14,518 --> 00:15:16,387
the shares that
you stole from me,

351
00:15:16,556 --> 00:15:18,424
and that is a "you" problem.

352
00:15:18,560 --> 00:15:21,747
Mike, it takes two people
to make a case for collusion.

353
00:15:21,866 --> 00:15:24,135
So if he's coming at us,
he's coming at you,

354
00:15:24,270 --> 00:15:26,306
which means it's a "we" problem.

355
00:15:26,441 --> 00:15:28,287
Yeah, you can try
and spin it any way you want,

356
00:15:28,311 --> 00:15:30,446
but I'm happy right where I am.

357
00:15:30,615 --> 00:15:31,893
I guess you agreed
to this meeting

358
00:15:31,917 --> 00:15:32,997
just to waste my time, huh?

359
00:15:33,086 --> 00:15:34,147
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.

360
00:15:34,172 --> 00:15:37,253
Who said I don't want to deal?

361
00:15:37,278 --> 00:15:38,696
Don't play me.

362
00:15:38,814 --> 00:15:40,132
Here's the new deal.

363
00:15:40,267 --> 00:15:43,037
You don't buy me out.
I buy you out.

364
00:15:43,139 --> 00:15:44,790
- What?
- We tried it Logan's way.

365
00:15:44,926 --> 00:15:46,371
Now we're gonna try it mine...
Mike.

366
00:15:46,395 --> 00:15:48,324
'Cause the only way I'd get
in a room with that guy

367
00:15:48,349 --> 00:15:51,720
is if you guarantee that
I leave with Gillis Industries.

368
00:15:51,822 --> 00:15:53,184
He's not gonna agree to that.

369
00:15:53,208 --> 00:15:57,714
That's another "you" problem.

370
00:16:02,641 --> 00:16:04,544
Rachel, I need to
know what's going on

371
00:16:04,662 --> 00:16:07,216
with Logan Sanders. What?

372
00:16:07,350 --> 00:16:10,448
You spent an extra 20 hours
with him last week.

373
00:16:10,473 --> 00:16:11,891
It wasn't billed
to the takeover,

374
00:16:12,059 --> 00:16:13,694
and I need to know
what it's about.

375
00:16:13,830 --> 00:16:16,834
We were looking at future deals.

376
00:16:16,936 --> 00:16:18,437
- "We"?
- Yes, we.

377
00:16:18,538 --> 00:16:22,845
He asked me if I could help him
put together some ideas...

378
00:16:23,013 --> 00:16:25,199
- Why?
- What are you getting at?

379
00:16:25,351 --> 00:16:27,330
I don't know if you've been
paying attention around here,

380
00:16:27,355 --> 00:16:29,157
but we need to wrap
this thing up,

381
00:16:29,291 --> 00:16:32,189
so I need to know if whatever
you and Logan were up to

382
00:16:32,214 --> 00:16:35,134
can force him to end this thing
with Mike once and for all.

383
00:16:35,269 --> 00:16:37,772
It can.

384
00:16:37,891 --> 00:16:40,194
How?

385
00:16:40,345 --> 00:16:43,868
Logan is under pressure
from his board,

386
00:16:44,002 --> 00:16:47,675
and if he doesn't
close this deal soon,

387
00:16:47,825 --> 00:16:50,229
he might lose control
of his company.

388
00:16:50,348 --> 00:16:52,350
Jessica, I must say
your impromptu lunch

389
00:16:52,467 --> 00:16:53,936
in the middle of the day
is exactly

390
00:16:54,071 --> 00:16:55,616
what the doctor ordered.
Thank you, Louis.

391
00:16:55,640 --> 00:16:58,111
Now, I must admit
that I brought you here

392
00:16:58,245 --> 00:16:59,891
because I have something
that I didn't want

393
00:16:59,916 --> 00:17:01,634
to discuss at the office.

394
00:17:01,785 --> 00:17:03,280
If you're firing Harvey,
I can't be in on it.

395
00:17:03,305 --> 00:17:04,586
I just bought him
an amazing mug,

396
00:17:04,591 --> 00:17:05,953
and we're in
a really good place right now.

397
00:17:05,977 --> 00:17:08,564
And I'm happy for you,
but this isn't about Harvey.

398
00:17:08,732 --> 00:17:09,816
It's about the firm.

399
00:17:09,951 --> 00:17:11,953
We recently purchased
a large block of stock

400
00:17:12,104 --> 00:17:13,466
without realizing
that we represent

401
00:17:13,575 --> 00:17:15,303
a client
with the same interests.

402
00:17:15,327 --> 00:17:16,689
You're worried
about the appearance

403
00:17:16,814 --> 00:17:18,109
of parking the stock? Exactly.

404
00:17:18,133 --> 00:17:19,728
And I just want
to make sure that we are

405
00:17:19,752 --> 00:17:22,723
as protected as possible.

406
00:17:25,830 --> 00:17:27,332
Sure, I can do it.

407
00:17:27,450 --> 00:17:29,452
- You seem upset.
- No, I'm not upset.

408
00:17:29,588 --> 00:17:30,882
I mean, why would
I be upset, Jessica?

409
00:17:30,906 --> 00:17:32,352
You take me to
an amazing restaurant,

410
00:17:32,376 --> 00:17:33,844
then you give me some
bullshit story

411
00:17:34,012 --> 00:17:36,064
about a stock purchase
with a fabricated company,

412
00:17:36,216 --> 00:17:38,078
and when it's clear as day
this is Gillis Industries.

413
00:17:38,103 --> 00:17:40,105
- Louis.
- The very same stock purchase

414
00:17:40,224 --> 00:17:41,686
that you went to Malone
to structure,

415
00:17:41,710 --> 00:17:42,576
and now you want me
to double check his work

416
00:17:42,712 --> 00:17:43,772
because you don't trust him.

417
00:17:43,797 --> 00:17:45,499
Oh, question is can I trust you?

418
00:17:45,601 --> 00:17:48,071
- What?
- This lunch isn't about him.

419
00:17:48,172 --> 00:17:49,567
It's about you.

420
00:17:49,591 --> 00:17:52,312
You knew I'd figure this out.

421
00:17:52,446 --> 00:17:53,898
Just like I know
you'll figure out

422
00:17:54,016 --> 00:17:56,285
whether or not we have exposure.

423
00:17:56,404 --> 00:17:57,956
Now, the question is
can you do it

424
00:17:58,074 --> 00:17:59,542
without telling Jeff Malone?

425
00:17:59,677 --> 00:18:05,136
I can, and I will.

426
00:18:10,163 --> 00:18:11,592
If you're gonna discuss
what happened,

427
00:18:11,616 --> 00:18:12,938
you can just forget it
because I...

428
00:18:12,951 --> 00:18:15,622
I am not here to talk
about that, and you know it.

429
00:18:15,757 --> 00:18:17,019
What?

430
00:18:17,043 --> 00:18:19,596
You told Harvey about
my problems with the board.

431
00:18:19,714 --> 00:18:21,466
I told your attorney
about a situation

432
00:18:21,635 --> 00:18:23,186
you discussed
with your other attorney.

433
00:18:23,304 --> 00:18:25,056
And now he's using it
to strong-arm me

434
00:18:25,191 --> 00:18:26,191
into caving to Mike.

435
00:18:26,310 --> 00:18:27,387
No, now he's using it
to give you

436
00:18:27,412 --> 00:18:29,081
the opportunity
to impress your board.

437
00:18:29,198 --> 00:18:30,844
Did you bring Harvey that
information to get rid of me?

438
00:18:30,869 --> 00:18:32,954
Logan, I didn't bring
Harvey that information,

439
00:18:33,123 --> 00:18:34,156
he asked me for it.

440
00:18:34,292 --> 00:18:35,927
And I don't need to get rid
of you

441
00:18:36,061 --> 00:18:38,147
because what happened
this morning is

442
00:18:38,282 --> 00:18:39,784
never gonna happen again.

443
00:18:39,902 --> 00:18:42,456
Okay, Rachel,
you got what you wanted.

444
00:18:42,574 --> 00:18:43,908
I'm gonna get in
a room with Mike

445
00:18:44,076 --> 00:18:45,878
and come to an agreement.

446
00:18:46,013 --> 00:18:49,435
What do you mean you're
gonna get in a room with him?

447
00:18:49,586 --> 00:18:51,165
Well, how else did
you see this happening?

448
00:18:51,189 --> 00:18:53,559
Did you think I was gonna
let Harvey take care of it?

449
00:18:53,695 --> 00:18:57,032
Look, please, you can't
tell him what happened.

450
00:18:57,201 --> 00:19:01,591
Rachel, I would never do that.

451
00:19:01,743 --> 00:19:03,128
Thank you.

452
00:19:03,279 --> 00:19:04,881
Just to be clear,
it's not for him.

453
00:19:05,015 --> 00:19:06,850
It's for me...

454
00:19:06,969 --> 00:19:08,164
'Cause you say
what happened this morning

455
00:19:08,188 --> 00:19:09,221
will never happen again,

456
00:19:09,390 --> 00:19:12,227
and I'm still hoping
that it will.

457
00:19:12,396 --> 00:19:14,625
But I don't want it to happen
because you two are fighting.

458
00:19:14,650 --> 00:19:18,990
I want it to happen
because you want it to.

459
00:19:32,517 --> 00:19:36,072
- Hey.
- Hey.

460
00:19:36,174 --> 00:19:38,326
Do you want me to heat
some of this up or you?

461
00:19:38,478 --> 00:19:40,163
Mike, I need to talk to you.

462
00:19:40,281 --> 00:19:42,450
Are you upset about something?

463
00:19:42,619 --> 00:19:44,287
No.

464
00:19:44,423 --> 00:19:47,260
I heard you might be
making a deal.

465
00:19:49,932 --> 00:19:52,184
And you're worried because
you're on the losing side?

466
00:19:52,304 --> 00:19:55,642
No, I'm actually happy
that this thing will be over.

467
00:19:55,777 --> 00:19:56,777
But?

468
00:19:56,895 --> 00:19:58,146
I think that you should have

469
00:19:58,315 --> 00:20:00,117
Jonathan Sidwell put this
to bed for you.

470
00:20:00,235 --> 00:20:02,203
Rachel...

471
00:20:02,322 --> 00:20:03,717
You and Harvey
have so much bad blood.

472
00:20:03,741 --> 00:20:05,220
Yeah, and this is our
chance to patch it up.

473
00:20:05,245 --> 00:20:06,847
- And what about Logan?
- What about him?

474
00:20:06,964 --> 00:20:09,585
I'm not gonna let him get to me.

475
00:20:09,720 --> 00:20:10,982
That's what you said
the last time

476
00:20:11,006 --> 00:20:12,016
you two got in a room together.
This is different.

477
00:20:12,041 --> 00:20:13,236
- Mike.
- Rachel, stop it.

478
00:20:13,260 --> 00:20:14,511
Look, we're at the finish line.

479
00:20:14,646 --> 00:20:16,291
I'm not gonna pass the baton
to somebody else,

480
00:20:16,315 --> 00:20:19,653
and I'm not gonna blow it
because this time

481
00:20:19,771 --> 00:20:24,779
I've got all the leverage.

482
00:20:24,915 --> 00:20:28,420
Well, if you have
all the leverage, then...

483
00:20:28,538 --> 00:20:31,425
Maybe you should
ask for one more thing.

484
00:20:35,106 --> 00:20:37,186
You're a halfhour late.

485
00:20:37,187 --> 00:20:38,522
I got stuck in traffic.

486
00:20:38,657 --> 00:20:39,969
I was starting to think
you didn't want this company.

487
00:20:39,993 --> 00:20:41,036
Harvey, I wouldn't be
getting in a room

488
00:20:41,061 --> 00:20:42,379
with that guy if I didn't.

489
00:20:42,530 --> 00:20:44,633
Good. So we're not gonna
have trouble in there?

490
00:20:44,802 --> 00:20:45,829
Not from me.

491
00:20:45,854 --> 00:20:46,980
Then let's get
this thing over with

492
00:20:47,005 --> 00:20:48,005
and get back to normal.

493
00:20:48,775 --> 00:20:51,796
Keep that in mind.

494
00:20:51,947 --> 00:20:53,609
Logan, sorry I'm late.

495
00:20:53,634 --> 00:20:57,940
Let's get to it.

496
00:20:58,076 --> 00:21:00,863
All right, just so we're clear,

497
00:21:00,997 --> 00:21:03,561
we're agreeing to have
you buy us out.

498
00:21:03,585 --> 00:21:04,719
Good.

499
00:21:04,871 --> 00:21:07,073
I think you'll find
this more than generous.

500
00:21:10,649 --> 00:21:11,951
It is.

501
00:21:12,085 --> 00:21:14,589
You gonna try and spread
this over 1,000 payments?

502
00:21:14,723 --> 00:21:16,558
All up front.

503
00:21:19,782 --> 00:21:20,649
Then all that's left is for you

504
00:21:20,784 --> 00:21:21,911
to pull out your checkbook.

505
00:21:21,936 --> 00:21:24,306
Well, actually,
there is one more thing.

506
00:21:24,441 --> 00:21:25,909
You said it, Harvey.

507
00:21:26,011 --> 00:21:28,348
Let's get things back to normal.

508
00:21:28,516 --> 00:21:29,543
What are you talking about?

509
00:21:29,568 --> 00:21:30,684
Once this deal is done,

510
00:21:30,820 --> 00:21:33,072
you go back to being my lawyer,
and he's out.

511
00:21:33,191 --> 00:21:34,241
What?

512
00:21:34,360 --> 00:21:36,295
You sign that,
I'm Harvey's client,

513
00:21:36,430 --> 00:21:38,216
and you're looking
for new representation.

514
00:21:38,351 --> 00:21:40,938
That's... this is bullshit.

515
00:21:41,056 --> 00:21:42,206
It's not bullshit.

516
00:21:42,341 --> 00:21:44,102
Apple and Dell don't
have the same attorneys,

517
00:21:44,112 --> 00:21:45,313
and neither will you and I.

518
00:21:45,414 --> 00:21:46,916
Mike, you two aren't those two,

519
00:21:47,050 --> 00:21:48,518
and I can represent you both.

520
00:21:48,636 --> 00:21:49,729
Yeah, but it doesn't matter

521
00:21:49,754 --> 00:21:51,440
because it's not
about who you represent.

522
00:21:51,592 --> 00:21:52,910
It's about
who Rachel represents.

523
00:21:53,061 --> 00:21:54,061
All right, enough.

524
00:21:54,063 --> 00:21:55,163
We agreed to a number.

525
00:21:55,282 --> 00:21:57,334
We can work this out
another time.

526
00:21:57,469 --> 00:21:58,731
No, we're gonna
work it out right now.

527
00:21:58,755 --> 00:22:00,284
- No, we're not.
- Then you don't have a deal.

528
00:22:00,309 --> 00:22:01,643
God damn it, Mike.

529
00:22:01,744 --> 00:22:02,985
This isn't the time to do this.

530
00:22:03,147 --> 00:22:04,224
This is exactly
the time to do it

531
00:22:04,249 --> 00:22:05,410
because this is the last time

532
00:22:05,501 --> 00:22:07,503
I'm ever gonna be
in a room with him.

533
00:22:07,622 --> 00:22:09,234
Well, finally,
something we can agree on.

534
00:22:09,258 --> 00:22:10,486
Then let's agree
to something else.

535
00:22:10,510 --> 00:22:11,911
We let Harvey choose
which one of us

536
00:22:11,930 --> 00:22:13,292
he wants to represent
after today.

537
00:22:13,316 --> 00:22:17,172
- Mike, do not put me in that...
- Done.

538
00:22:17,306 --> 00:22:19,051
And now that we've agreed
to let Harvey decide,

539
00:22:19,076 --> 00:22:21,346
I'm gonna let you in
on a little secret.

540
00:22:21,481 --> 00:22:23,767
The way he got me into this
room in the first place

541
00:22:23,902 --> 00:22:26,181
was he knows that I've got
ten deals lined up after this.

542
00:22:26,206 --> 00:22:27,206
Logan.

543
00:22:27,325 --> 00:22:30,162
Decide.

544
00:22:40,449 --> 00:22:41,978
I'm going with Mike.

545
00:22:42,003 --> 00:22:43,605
- What?
- Mike's my guy.

546
00:22:43,722 --> 00:22:45,774
You knew that going in.
I don't give a shit,

547
00:22:45,926 --> 00:22:47,478
and I don't think
Jessica Pearson

548
00:22:47,614 --> 00:22:49,565
is going to let you
pick him over me.

549
00:22:49,700 --> 00:22:51,201
Jessica has nothing to do
with this.

550
00:22:51,304 --> 00:22:52,672
You just agreed to those terms.

551
00:22:52,839 --> 00:22:53,923
Those were bullshit terms.

552
00:22:54,058 --> 00:22:55,202
So you're going back
on your word?

553
00:22:55,227 --> 00:22:56,277
What does it look like?

554
00:22:56,396 --> 00:22:59,283
Looks like there's
no deal on Gillis.

555
00:23:06,048 --> 00:23:08,551
Mike, you didn't have
to blow up the deal like that.

556
00:23:08,686 --> 00:23:10,021
Your client blew up the deal.

557
00:23:10,171 --> 00:23:12,201
- Because you blindsided him.
- Fine.

558
00:23:12,226 --> 00:23:14,061
Then once he's had time
to think about it,

559
00:23:14,196 --> 00:23:16,082
you go back and convince him.
Convince him?

560
00:23:16,217 --> 00:23:17,529
You should have come to me first

561
00:23:17,553 --> 00:23:19,065
instead of looking to rub it
in his face.

562
00:23:19,089 --> 00:23:20,534
I wasn't rubbing anything
in anyone's face.

563
00:23:20,558 --> 00:23:21,753
Oh, bullshit. You have leverage,

564
00:23:21,777 --> 00:23:23,172
and you want to make
sure he knew it.

565
00:23:23,197 --> 00:23:24,809
And when he had leverage,
he made sure I knew it,

566
00:23:24,833 --> 00:23:26,084
and I didn't agree to a deal,

567
00:23:26,235 --> 00:23:28,304
and then break my word
ten seconds later.

568
00:23:28,439 --> 00:23:30,368
And I'm giving you my word.

569
00:23:30,393 --> 00:23:32,713
Close this deal,
and as soon as it's wrapped up,

570
00:23:32,847 --> 00:23:34,066
he's out.

571
00:23:34,200 --> 00:23:36,179
And what about Jessica?
Is she gonna agree to it?

572
00:23:36,204 --> 00:23:37,455
Let me deal with Jessica.

573
00:23:37,590 --> 00:23:38,995
Oh, just like you did on wexler.

574
00:23:39,019 --> 00:23:40,019
That was a different thing,

575
00:23:40,044 --> 00:23:41,696
and you know it. Do I?

576
00:23:43,350 --> 00:23:46,956
Get him to agree up front,
or we don't have a deal.

577
00:23:51,132 --> 00:23:54,080
Louis, I don't usually
get summoned to people.

578
00:23:54,104 --> 00:23:55,237
They get summoned to me.

579
00:23:55,390 --> 00:23:56,608
But you wanted discretion,

580
00:23:56,743 --> 00:23:58,471
and your office is within
an earshot of Jeff Malone.

581
00:23:58,495 --> 00:23:59,505
And you don't want him to hear

582
00:23:59,530 --> 00:24:01,049
what you're about to tell me.

583
00:24:01,201 --> 00:24:04,673
So first off, I went through
this backwards and forwards,

584
00:24:04,841 --> 00:24:09,916
and Jeff did a better job
than 99% of all attorneys.

585
00:24:10,033 --> 00:24:13,989
Fortunately for you,
I'm the one.

586
00:24:14,125 --> 00:24:15,426
You found a mistake.

587
00:24:15,594 --> 00:24:18,515
I found a blessing in disguise.

588
00:24:18,650 --> 00:24:20,185
What are you talking about?

589
00:24:20,302 --> 00:24:24,742
Jessica, we're not vulnerable
to allegations of parking

590
00:24:24,878 --> 00:24:26,413
because we never bought
those shares.

591
00:24:26,582 --> 00:24:28,050
We can't sell them back.

592
00:24:28,168 --> 00:24:29,429
I'm not talking
about selling them back.

593
00:24:29,453 --> 00:24:32,524
This mistake makes
the entire sale invalid.

594
00:24:32,643 --> 00:24:34,278
And we don't have exposure

595
00:24:34,395 --> 00:24:36,124
because the sale never happened?

596
00:24:36,149 --> 00:24:37,400
Just give me the word,

597
00:24:37,535 --> 00:24:38,963
and I'll David Blaine
this whole thing away.

598
00:24:38,987 --> 00:24:40,766
Louis, this is great work,

599
00:24:40,791 --> 00:24:42,710
but I don't want you to
do anything

600
00:24:42,879 --> 00:24:46,099
until you talk to Harvey.
Are you sure?

601
00:24:46,251 --> 00:24:47,385
Because I can just...

602
00:24:47,554 --> 00:24:49,555
Louis, I bought these shares
without telling him.

603
00:24:49,575 --> 00:24:51,693
I'm not getting rid of them
without telling him.

604
00:24:51,828 --> 00:24:54,698
Are we clear? As a bell.

605
00:25:01,547 --> 00:25:05,853
Well, someone saved the day.
Do tell.

606
00:25:06,022 --> 00:25:07,300
Jeff Malone just dropped
a giant deuce

607
00:25:07,324 --> 00:25:08,374
on Jessica's desk.

608
00:25:08,493 --> 00:25:10,004
Please tell me
you're being metaphorical.

609
00:25:10,028 --> 00:25:12,716
Nope. Made a huge mess
of the wexler purchase.

610
00:25:12,834 --> 00:25:14,903
- And you cleaned it up?
- Even better.

611
00:25:15,005 --> 00:25:17,141
Because of his blunder,
I'm gonna make it

612
00:25:17,310 --> 00:25:19,005
as though his shit-y deal
never even happened.

613
00:25:19,029 --> 00:25:20,507
- What did Jessica say?
- Oh, she loved it.

614
00:25:20,531 --> 00:25:22,617
- And what about Malone?
- That's the best part.

615
00:25:22,786 --> 00:25:24,348
That asshole doesn't
even know about it.

616
00:25:24,456 --> 00:25:26,960
What do you need me to do
to make this unwind happen?

617
00:25:27,094 --> 00:25:29,156
Nothing.

618
00:25:29,181 --> 00:25:30,827
Jessica just wanted me to run it
by Harvey first,

619
00:25:30,851 --> 00:25:32,363
but I haven't been
able to reach him.

620
00:25:32,388 --> 00:25:33,973
Able to reach him?

621
00:25:34,107 --> 00:25:36,343
Louis, what do you think is
gonna happen

622
00:25:36,478 --> 00:25:39,282
if Malone gets wind of this
before you talk to Harvey?

623
00:25:39,417 --> 00:25:41,971
Ah, shit, he's gonna
try to fix it himself.

624
00:25:42,122 --> 00:25:43,423
And once again, he'll be taking

625
00:25:43,558 --> 00:25:44,591
what's rightfully yours.

626
00:25:44,760 --> 00:25:45,770
And I'll be left holding
a big bag

627
00:25:45,795 --> 00:25:47,180
of Jeff Malone's giant deuce.

628
00:25:47,316 --> 00:25:49,067
Where are you going?

629
00:25:49,185 --> 00:25:52,824
To do what needs to be done.

630
00:25:52,976 --> 00:25:56,114
Rachel,
what the hell did you do?

631
00:25:56,248 --> 00:25:57,449
What are you talking about?

632
00:25:57,585 --> 00:25:59,955
Mike demanded that Harvey
dump Logan as a client,

633
00:26:00,123 --> 00:26:01,674
and it blew up the whole deal,

634
00:26:01,825 --> 00:26:03,521
and based on
what I know and Harvey doesn't,

635
00:26:03,546 --> 00:26:05,348
it wasn't Mike
behind that demand.

636
00:26:05,498 --> 00:26:08,019
It was you.

637
00:26:08,138 --> 00:26:10,140
- I'm so sorry.
- Sorry?

638
00:26:10,275 --> 00:26:12,311
What good does sorry do?

639
00:26:12,479 --> 00:26:13,841
Donna, I thought it was
the best thing

640
00:26:13,865 --> 00:26:15,154
for everyone involved.

641
00:26:15,178 --> 00:26:16,178
You thought it was the best
way to get

642
00:26:16,203 --> 00:26:17,203
Logan out of the picture

643
00:26:17,205 --> 00:26:18,383
and not deal with what happened.

644
00:26:18,407 --> 00:26:19,888
No, I tried to deal
with what happened

645
00:26:19,993 --> 00:26:22,830
without telling anyone,
which is what you told me to do.

646
00:26:22,965 --> 00:26:25,302
I did not tell you
to let your personal life

647
00:26:25,420 --> 00:26:26,503
affect Harvey's business.

648
00:26:26,639 --> 00:26:28,474
I was just trying
to get Mike and Harvey

649
00:26:28,592 --> 00:26:29,760
back on the same team.

650
00:26:29,895 --> 00:26:31,741
I want you to understand
that the way

651
00:26:31,765 --> 00:26:34,935
to do that isn't to pull strings
behind their backs.

652
00:26:37,025 --> 00:26:40,246
I do.

653
00:26:40,365 --> 00:26:42,762
Okay, well, there's got
to be some way to fix it.

654
00:26:42,786 --> 00:26:44,954
That's not the point.
It's being fixed.

655
00:26:45,090 --> 00:26:46,435
What are you talking about?

656
00:26:46,459 --> 00:26:48,879
Harvey's going over Mike's head.

657
00:26:49,013 --> 00:26:51,600
He went to see Charles Forstman
20 minutes ago.

658
00:27:00,651 --> 00:27:03,805
Whoever said size doesn't
matter never saw this table.

659
00:27:03,941 --> 00:27:07,747
Is that an insult
or a compliment?

660
00:27:07,849 --> 00:27:11,488
Knowing you, Charles,
you'll take it as both.

661
00:27:11,622 --> 00:27:14,993
How'd you get in here, Harvey?

662
00:27:15,129 --> 00:27:16,663
You crawled in
through the vents?

663
00:27:16,798 --> 00:27:18,879
I told your secretary I
was George Clooney's brother.

664
00:27:19,002 --> 00:27:21,204
She said it was obvious who
got the looks in the family.

665
00:27:21,206 --> 00:27:23,777
Great. Do me a favor.

666
00:27:23,912 --> 00:27:25,814
Tell her she's fired
on the way out.

667
00:27:25,948 --> 00:27:27,583
Can do.

668
00:27:27,719 --> 00:27:30,248
But first, I wanted
to show you these.

669
00:27:33,264 --> 00:27:35,727
You want to give me
the Aston Martin?

670
00:27:36,124 --> 00:27:37,574
"Give" is a strong word.

671
00:27:41,883 --> 00:27:43,468
You want me to buy you out.

672
00:27:43,587 --> 00:27:45,389
You're going to buy me out.

673
00:27:45,540 --> 00:27:47,893
So why come to me instead
of Mike Ross?

674
00:27:48,028 --> 00:27:50,681
Because I put him and Logan
Sanders in a room together,

675
00:27:50,817 --> 00:27:52,952
and those two assholes let
their personal shit

676
00:27:53,088 --> 00:27:54,456
get in the way of business.

677
00:27:54,590 --> 00:27:55,758
So what makes you think

678
00:27:55,893 --> 00:27:57,928
these two assholes
are gonna do any better?

679
00:27:58,064 --> 00:27:59,932
Because as much
as you hate my guts,

680
00:28:00,068 --> 00:28:03,957
you want this deal
and that car as much as I do.

681
00:28:04,074 --> 00:28:07,462
Harvey, taking
your car is tempting,

682
00:28:07,598 --> 00:28:12,823
but I don't think buying you
out makes sense anymore.

683
00:28:12,958 --> 00:28:14,209
Why not?

684
00:28:14,360 --> 00:28:17,214
Because you're standing
there asking me to do it.

685
00:28:17,333 --> 00:28:22,725
Now, walk your sorry ass
out of my office.

686
00:28:22,844 --> 00:28:24,712
Okay, Charles.

687
00:28:24,813 --> 00:28:28,819
But I'm afraid you're forcing me
to use my leverage on you.

688
00:28:28,921 --> 00:28:30,556
You don't have shit on me, pal.

689
00:28:30,691 --> 00:28:32,086
Who do you think bought
that Wexler block

690
00:28:32,111 --> 00:28:33,395
three days ago?

691
00:28:33,530 --> 00:28:35,375
I don't give a shit who
bought it three days ago.

692
00:28:35,400 --> 00:28:38,254
'Cause it just went back
on the market 30 minutes ago,

693
00:28:38,389 --> 00:28:40,424
and you're looking at
the man who owns it now.

694
00:28:50,879 --> 00:28:52,764
Jonathan, what
are you doing here?

695
00:28:52,883 --> 00:28:57,634
Forstman bought
the Wexler shares.

696
00:28:57,658 --> 00:28:59,710
What?

697
00:28:59,812 --> 00:29:03,184
They went back on the market,
and he snatched them right up.

698
00:29:03,319 --> 00:29:05,621
Holy shit.

699
00:29:05,757 --> 00:29:07,592
We win.

700
00:29:07,694 --> 00:29:09,829
- We do.
- Mm-hmm.

701
00:29:09,998 --> 00:29:13,837
You did.

702
00:29:14,005 --> 00:29:15,223
It's not over yet.

703
00:29:15,358 --> 00:29:17,510
I want you to draw up
a tender offer right away.

704
00:29:19,048 --> 00:29:21,651
- Jonathan.
- What?

705
00:29:21,787 --> 00:29:23,755
I've been thinking
about Forstman.

706
00:29:23,891 --> 00:29:25,593
And?

707
00:29:25,760 --> 00:29:27,089
You know we wouldn't have
been able

708
00:29:27,113 --> 00:29:28,481
to do this without him, right?

709
00:29:28,616 --> 00:29:29,817
No shit.

710
00:29:29,952 --> 00:29:31,046
Just think about what else
we could do with him.

711
00:29:31,071 --> 00:29:32,956
You want to team up with him?

712
00:29:33,091 --> 00:29:36,012
Well, you don't need
to convince me,

713
00:29:36,146 --> 00:29:37,658
but how the hell are
you gonna convince him?

714
00:29:37,683 --> 00:29:40,754
By giving him
a discount on this deal.

715
00:29:40,888 --> 00:29:42,056
How much of a discount?

716
00:29:42,158 --> 00:29:47,968
Thinking somewhere in
the neighborhood of... 100%.

717
00:29:52,277 --> 00:29:53,711
God damn it, Louis!

718
00:29:53,847 --> 00:29:55,298
What the hell did you do?

719
00:29:55,449 --> 00:29:56,634
What are you talking about?

720
00:29:56,785 --> 00:29:58,080
I just came from a meeting
with Charles Forstman,

721
00:29:58,104 --> 00:29:59,785
and when I reached for
my bargaining chips,

722
00:29:59,808 --> 00:30:01,242
he told me I didn't own them
anymore

723
00:30:01,393 --> 00:30:03,162
because you unwound
the Wexler sale.

724
00:30:03,281 --> 00:30:04,909
Well, I was trying to save
the firm from exposure.

725
00:30:04,933 --> 00:30:06,172
And who the hell told
you to do that?

726
00:30:06,196 --> 00:30:07,196
Jessica did.

727
00:30:07,221 --> 00:30:08,472
She told you to God damn wait,

728
00:30:08,573 --> 00:30:09,895
and you know it.
Check your phone.

729
00:30:10,010 --> 00:30:12,146
I tried calling you.
I left three messages.

730
00:30:12,315 --> 00:30:13,893
I don't care if you left me
a million messages.

731
00:30:13,917 --> 00:30:15,702
You were told to
wait for my approval,

732
00:30:15,838 --> 00:30:18,375
and you didn't listen
because you never God damn do.

733
00:30:18,492 --> 00:30:19,854
You know what, Harvey?
I always listen.

734
00:30:19,878 --> 00:30:22,097
I always play the good soldier,

735
00:30:22,232 --> 00:30:24,435
and what do I get for it?
Nothing.

736
00:30:24,570 --> 00:30:28,159
I may not be a name partner,
but I am a senior partner.

737
00:30:28,294 --> 00:30:29,713
You get it?

738
00:30:29,880 --> 00:30:31,382
I couldn't reach you,

739
00:30:31,550 --> 00:30:33,936
and I made
a goddamn judgment call.

740
00:30:34,088 --> 00:30:36,224
You want to know why you're
not a name partner, Louis?

741
00:30:36,360 --> 00:30:39,430
Because every judgment
call you make turns to shit.

742
00:30:42,337 --> 00:30:44,539
Well, then what do you want,
Harvey?

743
00:30:44,675 --> 00:30:47,846
I'll do anything
to make up for it.

744
00:30:48,014 --> 00:30:49,349
You want to do something, Louis?

745
00:30:49,517 --> 00:30:51,769
Instead of using Donna
to give me

746
00:30:51,888 --> 00:30:56,712
some stupid goddamn mug,

747
00:30:56,863 --> 00:30:59,717
stay the hell
out of my business.

748
00:31:17,185 --> 00:31:19,304
You mind grabbing me
a couple packs of sugar there?

749
00:31:19,473 --> 00:31:21,325
I don't work here.
I'm with Pearson-Specter.

750
00:31:22,812 --> 00:31:24,614
I don't give
a shit who you're with.

751
00:31:24,750 --> 00:31:26,262
If you're not here to give me
something...

752
00:31:26,286 --> 00:31:28,398
I'm here to give you Harvey
Specter on a silver platter.

753
00:31:28,423 --> 00:31:31,677
I already have Harvey Specter
on a silver platter.

754
00:31:31,813 --> 00:31:35,602
Not like you will
if you let me buy you out.

755
00:31:35,736 --> 00:31:39,492
Listen, asshole,
Harvey came by last night,

756
00:31:39,627 --> 00:31:40,627
tried to make a deal.

757
00:31:40,745 --> 00:31:43,082
I told him to shove it
up his ass,

758
00:31:43,218 --> 00:31:44,919
and don't think
I don't know good cop,

759
00:31:45,054 --> 00:31:46,472
bad cop when I see it.

760
00:31:46,591 --> 00:31:47,651
The good cop, bad cop
doesn't work

761
00:31:47,675 --> 00:31:49,427
when one of them hates
the other one.

762
00:31:49,596 --> 00:31:51,564
And what the hell is this?

763
00:31:51,683 --> 00:31:52,934
Your niece's diary?

764
00:31:53,102 --> 00:31:56,490
It's a time capsule of my rage.

765
00:32:00,783 --> 00:32:02,835
"April 22nd, 2009.

766
00:32:02,954 --> 00:32:05,040
"Harvey told me to file
a motion to dismiss

767
00:32:05,175 --> 00:32:07,211
the odor emitting
from my armpits."

768
00:32:07,329 --> 00:32:09,515
This is a joke.

769
00:32:09,634 --> 00:32:11,185
Once again, he
took my biggest fear,

770
00:32:11,336 --> 00:32:14,307
put it on display for
the entire world to see.

771
00:32:14,476 --> 00:32:16,528
Oh, yeah, I can go on.

772
00:32:16,680 --> 00:32:18,865
- He hates you that bad, huh?
- No.

773
00:32:18,984 --> 00:32:20,011
He doesn't give
a shit about me at all.

774
00:32:20,036 --> 00:32:21,371
I hate him that bad.

775
00:32:21,522 --> 00:32:24,994
You know, you don't have
the authority to buy me out.

776
00:32:25,129 --> 00:32:26,474
I went to Harvey's client
behind his back,

777
00:32:26,498 --> 00:32:28,166
and I got him. Oh, I see.

778
00:32:28,302 --> 00:32:30,170
I agree to this,
you steal his client.

779
00:32:30,305 --> 00:32:33,509
And he'll have lost to me,
which is far more humiliating

780
00:32:33,678 --> 00:32:35,062
than losing to you.

781
00:32:35,214 --> 00:32:39,020
You'd go to all this trouble
to stick it to Harvey?

782
00:32:39,188 --> 00:32:41,357
Read May 9th, 2012.

783
00:32:41,492 --> 00:32:44,496
I'd go to the ends
of the goddamn earth.

784
00:32:55,140 --> 00:32:57,673
What was so important
you couldn't me over the phone?

785
00:32:59,196 --> 00:33:01,359
I want to offer you something.

786
00:33:01,383 --> 00:33:02,884
My lucky day.

787
00:33:03,036 --> 00:33:06,692
Everyone's bearing gifts.

788
00:33:06,843 --> 00:33:09,146
You want me to
buy controlling interest

789
00:33:09,248 --> 00:33:11,250
in the Sidwell Investment Group.

790
00:33:11,369 --> 00:33:14,756
I want you to buy it
at a $80 million discount.

791
00:33:14,925 --> 00:33:16,927
The exact amount
I was gonna cut him out of.

792
00:33:17,063 --> 00:33:19,700
Was? Wait.

793
00:33:19,817 --> 00:33:21,819
Did you change your mind?

794
00:33:21,938 --> 00:33:23,350
You're not gonna cut him
out of Gillis?

795
00:33:23,375 --> 00:33:25,220
Guess you haven't heard.
I'm done with Gillis.

796
00:33:25,244 --> 00:33:29,601
I sold my interest
to Logan Sanders.

797
00:33:31,957 --> 00:33:33,325
What the hell you talking about?

798
00:33:33,460 --> 00:33:35,830
That wasn't our deal.
What can I tell you?

799
00:33:35,964 --> 00:33:38,193
When you're the biggest bully
in the yard,

800
00:33:38,218 --> 00:33:39,446
people give you
their lunch money

801
00:33:39,471 --> 00:33:41,574
without you even asking for it.

802
00:33:41,691 --> 00:33:43,977
Oh, my God. You son of a bitch.

803
00:33:44,080 --> 00:33:48,103
You promised me
that I would control

804
00:33:48,254 --> 00:33:49,555
what happened to that company.

805
00:33:49,690 --> 00:33:51,525
I promised you if we won.

806
00:33:51,644 --> 00:33:53,095
We didn't.

807
00:33:53,229 --> 00:33:56,752
- You did.
- Yes, I did.

808
00:33:56,887 --> 00:33:58,877
Then our other deal
is off the table,

809
00:33:58,901 --> 00:33:59,901
and you're gonna give
Jonathan Sidwell

810
00:33:59,926 --> 00:34:01,377
his goddamn cut.

811
00:34:01,512 --> 00:34:05,952
How about I give
you something even better.

812
00:34:06,088 --> 00:34:10,294
- What the hell is this?
- A job offer.

813
00:34:12,833 --> 00:34:16,237
You got to be kidding me.

814
00:34:17,910 --> 00:34:20,907
What, did you think
I was gonna hang you out to dry?

815
00:34:20,931 --> 00:34:23,752
I could use a smart son of bitch
like you working for me.

816
00:34:23,887 --> 00:34:26,166
You're the last person in
the world I'd want to work for.

817
00:34:26,191 --> 00:34:29,246
I am the only person in
the world you want to work for.

818
00:34:29,381 --> 00:34:31,801
- Why is that?
- Because you're a nobody.

819
00:34:31,936 --> 00:34:34,306
You're a former lawyer who's
been an investment banker

820
00:34:34,407 --> 00:34:37,304
all of ten minutes, and is about
to blow the biggest deal

821
00:34:37,329 --> 00:34:41,886
that ever came his way,
unless you come over to me.

822
00:34:56,014 --> 00:34:58,868
Go to hell.

823
00:35:06,433 --> 00:35:08,002
Harvey, we need
to have a little talk.

824
00:35:08,136 --> 00:35:10,171
I said everything
I needed to say last night.

825
00:35:10,307 --> 00:35:13,572
Now get the hell out.
I made a deal with Forstman.

826
00:35:13,597 --> 00:35:15,599
What?

827
00:35:15,750 --> 00:35:18,154
You stuck your nose
in my goddamn business

828
00:35:18,289 --> 00:35:20,591
after I told you to never do
that again?

829
00:35:20,726 --> 00:35:21,837
No, I saved
your goddamn business

830
00:35:21,862 --> 00:35:25,684
after you told me
to never do it again.

831
00:35:29,243 --> 00:35:32,976
- You got him to sign this?
- Damn right.

832
00:35:33,000 --> 00:35:35,279
- And who authorized it?
- Nobody.

833
00:35:35,304 --> 00:35:37,256
I lied and told Forstman
I had Logan's approval.

834
00:35:37,391 --> 00:35:40,312
Can we get Logan's approval?

835
00:35:40,447 --> 00:35:44,537
You're goddamn right we can.

836
00:35:44,671 --> 00:35:49,846
Louis, this has got to be
the most genius thing

837
00:35:49,982 --> 00:35:52,150
you have ever done
in your entire, wonderful,

838
00:35:52,286 --> 00:35:54,455
miserable life.

839
00:35:56,838 --> 00:35:57,838
So you're not mad at me?

840
00:35:57,863 --> 00:36:00,467
Mad at you? I could kiss you.

841
00:36:00,634 --> 00:36:02,687
And I can let you.

842
00:36:02,838 --> 00:36:04,307
Then go grab
a couple of your mugs.

843
00:36:04,441 --> 00:36:05,642
I'll crack open the scotch,

844
00:36:05,778 --> 00:36:07,446
and let's see
where this thing goes.

845
00:36:07,614 --> 00:36:09,951
Can do.

846
00:36:10,119 --> 00:36:12,622
Hey, Louis,

847
00:36:12,791 --> 00:36:18,266
how the hell did you get him
to go for it?

848
00:36:18,401 --> 00:36:21,271
We found common ground.

849
00:36:24,413 --> 00:36:27,250
One more thing.

850
00:36:31,058 --> 00:36:35,431
Charles Forstman got
the Litt the hell up.

851
00:36:47,522 --> 00:36:51,388
Mike, Mike,
Sidwell wants to see you.

852
00:36:51,412 --> 00:36:53,498
Don't tell me.

853
00:36:53,617 --> 00:36:55,452
He knows.

854
00:36:55,587 --> 00:36:58,424
Sh...

855
00:37:07,692 --> 00:37:09,077
You little piece of shit.

856
00:37:09,213 --> 00:37:10,748
Jonathan, let me explain.

857
00:37:10,882 --> 00:37:12,167
There's nothing to explain.

858
00:37:12,301 --> 00:37:14,638
You sold me out the second
you connected with Forstman.

859
00:37:14,806 --> 00:37:18,562
No, I thought I could get
out of it, all right?

860
00:37:18,697 --> 00:37:20,378
But then you took
Forstman's money, and I...

861
00:37:20,400 --> 00:37:21,701
Oh, you're gonna put that on me?

862
00:37:21,820 --> 00:37:24,824
I took his money because
I thought we were partners.

863
00:37:24,958 --> 00:37:27,227
I didn't know you were gonna
stab me in the goddamn back.

864
00:37:27,329 --> 00:37:28,379
Stab you in the back?

865
00:37:28,498 --> 00:37:30,517
If I didn't make
this deal happen,

866
00:37:30,669 --> 00:37:31,831
you said you were gonna fire me.

867
00:37:31,855 --> 00:37:33,136
I don't give a shit what I said.

868
00:37:33,240 --> 00:37:36,111
I took a chance on you.
You spat in my face.

869
00:37:36,280 --> 00:37:37,290
Jonathan.

870
00:37:37,315 --> 00:37:38,783
You stood right there selling me

871
00:37:38,951 --> 00:37:41,153
on Forstman to stop me from
finding out you betrayed me.

872
00:37:41,255 --> 00:37:44,309
No, I did that to stop me
from having to betray you.

873
00:37:44,461 --> 00:37:46,073
Jonathan, he still owes us
money, all right?

874
00:37:46,098 --> 00:37:47,433
We can still go after...

875
00:37:47,568 --> 00:37:48,434
There isn't enough money
in the world for me

876
00:37:48,570 --> 00:37:50,238
to ever trust you again.
Listen to me.

877
00:37:50,406 --> 00:37:51,574
I'm... No, you listen to me!

878
00:37:51,741 --> 00:37:55,547
There is no goddamn "we."

879
00:37:55,666 --> 00:37:58,520
You're fired.

880
00:38:00,225 --> 00:38:03,312
Jonathan, we can still talk
to Forstman, all right?

881
00:38:03,447 --> 00:38:04,865
You think I didn't try that?

882
00:38:04,983 --> 00:38:07,069
Who the hell do you think
told me

883
00:38:07,204 --> 00:38:08,872
that you sold me out
in the first place?

884
00:38:09,007 --> 00:38:12,071
Here.

885
00:38:12,096 --> 00:38:14,382
Put this on your mantle.

886
00:38:14,517 --> 00:38:19,559
Remember me every time
you God damn look at it.

887
00:38:34,120 --> 00:38:36,306
There is the man of the hour.

888
00:38:36,458 --> 00:38:41,733
Why didn't you tell me
what you were gonna do?

889
00:38:41,852 --> 00:38:43,381
Because if it didn't work,
I didn't want you

890
00:38:43,405 --> 00:38:44,606
to take any of the blame.

891
00:38:44,740 --> 00:38:48,696
Well, why didn't
you tell me afterwards?

892
00:38:48,815 --> 00:38:52,537
It's all anyone can talk about.

893
00:38:52,672 --> 00:38:55,843
Yeah, I don't care.

894
00:38:55,961 --> 00:38:57,129
Louis.

895
00:38:57,297 --> 00:38:58,899
Forstman's insisting
that I run the money

896
00:38:59,018 --> 00:39:00,446
through Switzerland
and the Caymans

897
00:39:00,470 --> 00:39:02,555
before it comes out on the
other side.

898
00:39:02,674 --> 00:39:06,480
What?
He's trying to avoid taxes.

899
00:39:06,614 --> 00:39:10,203
You're obligated to report it.

900
00:39:10,355 --> 00:39:15,914
I didn't, and I'm not going to.

901
00:39:16,032 --> 00:39:17,551
Louis, that's illegal.

902
00:39:17,702 --> 00:39:19,337
You didn't see the
look on Harvey's face

903
00:39:19,473 --> 00:39:21,641
when he found out that I
was the one who saved the day,

904
00:39:21,760 --> 00:39:24,931
and I am...

905
00:39:25,066 --> 00:39:28,236
Not gonna be the one
to see the look

906
00:39:28,388 --> 00:39:31,526
on his face
when he finds out that I didn't.

907
00:39:31,661 --> 00:39:35,501
Louis.

908
00:39:35,619 --> 00:39:38,590
Leave me alone.

909
00:39:42,682 --> 00:39:44,050
Hey, did you hear the good news?

910
00:39:44,185 --> 00:39:47,222
There is no good news.

911
00:39:47,358 --> 00:39:51,564
Logan won, which means
he's not going anywhere.

912
00:39:53,786 --> 00:39:56,874
You want to tell Mike
what happened, don't you?

913
00:39:56,992 --> 00:39:58,577
I am going to tell Mike
what happened.

914
00:39:58,713 --> 00:40:00,058
No, you're not.

915
00:40:00,082 --> 00:40:01,416
Harvey said he would drop Logan

916
00:40:01,551 --> 00:40:03,052
when this is over, and he will.

917
00:40:03,171 --> 00:40:05,618
And there is no way that
he's dropping Logan

918
00:40:05,642 --> 00:40:08,146
if Mike can't even be a client.

919
00:40:08,264 --> 00:40:09,598
What are you talking about?

920
00:40:09,733 --> 00:40:11,101
I just got a text from Amy.

921
00:40:11,236 --> 00:40:15,659
Donna, Mike got fired.

922
00:40:16,829 --> 00:40:18,781
Now you really can't tell him.

923
00:40:18,950 --> 00:40:20,919
You said I shouldn't
go behind his back,

924
00:40:21,037 --> 00:40:23,039
but not telling him is
going behind his back.

925
00:40:23,175 --> 00:40:24,152
Even if you were gonna tell him,

926
00:40:24,177 --> 00:40:25,845
this is the absolute worst time.

927
00:40:25,963 --> 00:40:27,013
If not now, then when?

928
00:40:27,132 --> 00:40:29,017
I mean, just wait
till he recovers,

929
00:40:29,136 --> 00:40:30,354
and then smack him down again?

930
00:40:30,471 --> 00:40:32,056
How about not
smacking him down at all?

931
00:40:32,192 --> 00:40:36,365
That would be great,
but I already did

932
00:40:36,482 --> 00:40:41,634
when I betrayed him, and I...
Rachel, if you do this,

933
00:40:41,659 --> 00:40:44,023
I am telling you it will
bore a hole in his brain,

934
00:40:44,047 --> 00:40:46,968
and you will be risking
your whole life with Mike.

935
00:40:47,086 --> 00:40:49,172
- I am risking it if I don't.
- Rachel.

936
00:40:49,341 --> 00:40:53,657
Donna, Mike kept a secret
from me that almost ripped us

937
00:40:53,681 --> 00:40:58,916
apart before we
even got started,

938
00:40:58,941 --> 00:41:02,864
and he found the courage
to trust me with it.

939
00:41:03,000 --> 00:41:08,541
So I need to find the courage
to trust him with this.

940
00:41:20,972 --> 00:41:26,977
 

