- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- What?
God. I'm so sorry.
Are you okay?
You know, there are
easier ways to kill me
if you're worried I'll rat you out
for cheating on the LSATs.
- What? Come on. Rachel.
- Unbelievable.
Rachel. Oh, God.
Rachel. Come on.
Let me buy you a fresh cup.
You actually going to buy it this time,
or are you going to steal it?
Okay, first of all,
I don't steal. I cheat.
There's a big difference.
And I don't
do it anymore.
Oh, great defense.
"I'm sorry, Your Honor.
I know that I murdered her,
"but I promise
I won't do it anymore."
Look, I understand
why you're mad
but I still don't think
you're being entirely fair.
Not fair?
What's not fair is that you repeatedly
help people skirt a system
that stands in the way
of me becoming a lawyer.
You know what? Why don't you give up
the whole saint act
since the only reason
you figured out I was cheating
is because you were thinking about
cheating yourself.
Thinking about cheating
and actually doing it
are two very different
things, Dr. Analogy.
Oh.
Whoa. Did I miss
an apocalypse?
Where is everyone?
You know, for someone
with a freak brain,
you manage to forget
everything important.
Follow me.
But don't talk to me.
Oh.
Not bad, Harvey.
The Prague hotel
in the black in less than three years
and a successful IPO.
Who said passion
wasn't productive?
I don't know anyone
that's ever said that.
- Jones, tell me something.
- Hmm?
You have 30 hotels in
12 different countries
but you spent last week
in Daniel Vega's Lisbon resort.
Well, just, you know,
checking out the competition.
That was more than a fact-finding
mission. You're thinking merger.
Do you honestly believe that I'd do that
without talking to you first?
I know you would.
Then, perhaps I did.
Jones, if you try
to pursue a merger,
you may not control what happens to your
business that you built so passionately.
Okay, Sherlock,
hear me out.
Combined, we're 100 hotels
in 23 countries.
I like having
multiple homes.
But you don't need
another name on the mortgage.
It's a good deal.
Yeah. And it's my job
to get you a better one. Okay?
Promise me you didn't do
a handshake deal.
Donna?
Who's ready for
Mock Trial 2011?
What, like,
make-believe trials?
Are we going to play
Monopoly after?
This is your
debutante ball.
The impression you make
on the partners will last.
- And let me guess. Harvey was...
- Oh, legendary.
Shocking.
Sydney Thompson was a consultant
with Lunders Global Initiative.
She had a few too many
and decided to entertain her friends
with an impersonation
of her boss, Lena Lunders.
This impersonation was recorded and
uploaded onto a social networking site.
The next day,
she was fired.
Sydney is now suing
for wrongful termination.
Can't cheat your way
out of this one.
The partners
have been instructed
to only use the associates
in emergency situations.
Let the games begin.
All right. When your name is called,
please step up and meet your match.
I think you mean
my bitch, Louis.
Ooh!
Jean Kaplan?
I'm glad Jessica finally chose a case
with a strong female character.
Last year, I was forced
to play a traffic cop.
It was a total
waste of my talent.
Wait a minute.
You play witnesses?
Oh, I don't play anything.
I embody.
And if I'm on your team,
you're a winner.
- Well, in that case...
- No.
Okay.
Kyle Durant.
Mike Ross.
Kyle for the plaintiff.
Ross for the defendant.
May the best man win.
Oh, by the way, Kyle, weren't you
a national Mock Trial champion?
That's right, Louis.
In high school, college,
and law school.
See the money, wanna stay
for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
I need an assessment of
all of Vega's hotels. Okay?
I want you to check annual earnings,
property value...
You should be writing.
Yeah, this all doesn't
sound like an emergency.
The Mock Trial...
Okay. I'm on it.
Uh, listen,
Harvey, about...
I don't give advice.
Okay. Please, sensei?
I'm out of my league
with this thing.
Listen to me.
Don't go to trial.
It's a mock trial. I think the trial
part is kind of a prerequisite.
All right.
Law is about
control, okay?
You can only control so much
with a jury, judge, witnesses,
and another lawyer
with an ego complex.
What if the lawyer doesn't
have an ego complex?
Every lawyer has
an ego complex.
The firm has
presented an exercise
where there's potential
for failure. Okay?
All I'm saying is try and create
a situation where
that's not even
a possibility.
Kobayashi Maru.
- Koba what, now?
- Star Trek.
Captain Kirk.
He wins a no-win situation
by rewriting the rules.
You're a Trekkie.
Hey. Captain Kirk
is the man, okay?
I don't want to hear
another word about it.
Now, enough with your fake law problem.
Let's deal with my real one.
Aye aye, Captain.
You want to know
how to do a cross?
Some people like
to use big words.
Some people like to
go for sympathy.
But personally, I'm a little more
go for the groin.
Oh, hey, Mike.
You mind dismissing the peanut gallery
so we can talk, Kyle?
I'm sorry, guys.
Looks like Ross here,
came to plead for mercy.
If you're here for the witness-exhibit
exchange, don't bother.
I already know who you're going to call
and what evidence you're going to use.
Actually, I'm not going to call any
witnesses or present any evidence.
- Let's settle.
- Or I could beat you.
The plaintiff has shown a pattern
of making derogatory statements
about my client.
- Hearsay.
- Not the emails.
Which have no tone of voice
and are subject to interpretation.
Which is exactly why
your argument is shaky at best.
- Then beat me in court.
- Kyle.
There is a reason
that Harvey chose me to be his guy.
Do you really want to find out
what that reason is?
And how do I know
this isn't some sort of trick?
It's not a trick.
It's just our chance
to stand out.
Look, settling gets us in and out
of there in five minutes.
You drop the suit, and you and I spend
the rest of the week
making ourselves
indispensable to the partners
while everyone else buries their heads
in Candy Land court.
I'm going against
my better judgment and trusting you.
So, we have a deal?
Daniel.
The paperwork looks good,
despite the fact that
you two decided to go lawyer commando.
But the devil's
always in the details.
Harvey, I know that impulse
purchases don't exist in your world,
but the timing
was right.
And as for the details,
I like to leave that to my man, Scott.
- Does he always like to be late?
- She.
Just got off a plane
from London.
Meet Ms. Dana Scott.
- Welcome.
- Hi. Thank you.
- Scottie.
- Harvey.
- Oh, you two know each other?
- We went to Harvard Law together.
Harvey was fifth
in the class and I was...
Oh, I forget.
What was it?
- Married to the library?
- That's right. Number one.
Number one at studying.
Okay. This way.
Tell me, Scottie,
what's my success rate
against you in the real world
where we practice real law?
Oh, Harvey, there should be no winners
or losers in a merger.
Just a happy new couple.
That's right.
3 and 0.
Well, I say
we let these two talk deal points
while I try your chef's
famous sea bass.
Absolutely.
Play nice. We like each other,
even if you two don't.
"Married to the library"?
It's not my fault the library
was the best you could do.
Do you have
the preliminary proposal?
No, I just flew in from London
completely unprepared.
Try not to be intimidated.
I used some big words.
Overcompensation
isn't that big of a word.
It isn't?
I can hardly wait to see the work
of a senior partner.
I see my promotion popped up on
your Harvey Specter Google alert.
That's not all
that's going to pop up.
Can't remember
the last time we had a bed.
Pretty convenient
that we're working on a hotel merger.
Remember the mining deal?
Shaft 27?
How could I forget?
Listen, about
the due diligence...
Uh-uh-uh, Harvey.
You know the rules.
No case negotiations
until we're done.
I think that
might be a while.
Oh. Couldn't resist seeing
brilliance in action, huh?
Actually, I have to be here.
I'm playing the part of the plaintiff.
Wow. I knew
you were pissed,
but I didn't realize
you were petty.
- What does that mean?
- It's an adjective.
- It means "small-minded, spiteful."
- Okay.
You chose to work with the one guy
who's going against me.
Kyle asked me
and I said yes.
You know what?
It doesn't really matter.
Because you're never
going to take the stand.
Really? How's that?
It's a surprise.
Prepare to watch
a mock trial legend be born.
Is Counsel ready to proceed
with opening statements?
We'd like to submit
a settlement agreement...
Plaintiff is ready,
Your Honor.
Which is it, Counselor?
Um, the counsel for the plaintiff and I
agreed to a settlement yesterday.
He must have
misunderstood.
We had discussed,
but I never agreed to anything.
Do you have
a signed agreement?
Uh, I...
No.
Then we are
ready to proceed.
You have the floor.
Thank you.
On March 31st, 2010,
Sydney Thompson was
unwittingly recorded on a cell phone.
She made a joke.
The type of joke that
I'm sure every person in this courtroom
has made at
one point or another.
And yet,
she was fired.
She was denied severance.
Mr. Ross. Mr. Ross.
Are you ready?
Um... The, uh...
The Defense...
Uh...
According to
Bowmaster v. Whitely,
if the party to a settlement
is surprised by the repudiation
of the settlement,
then the court must provide a reasonable
amount of time to prepare for the trial.
- Reasonable time.
- Yes, Your Honor.
You get five minutes.
Vega has more property.
Debeque has more potential.
Which is harder
to monetarily define.
This isn't
the library, Scottie.
My guy is
an up and comer.
That's why your
guy is pouncing.
Your client
is an impulse shopper.
Which is what may have made
him a quick success,
but could make him
an even faster failure.
So, he's a passionate guy.
He falls in love with
a city and he builds himself a hotel.
Who are you to argue
with his track record?
I'm a realist. And I have never seen
a deal pushed through so quickly.
So, what?
So, your guy might
wake up tomorrow
and decide that he
doesn't want to do this.
Which is why I'm not showing you our
private books without a signed deal.
- Is that a joke?
- Am I laughing?
Look, I may not have been awake during
our M&A clinic...
Except for when you
were copying my notes.
Which was no walk in the park.
You write like a monkey.
But in any case,
due diligence is a requirement.
I have an obligation
to my client.
Then, we don't
have a deal.
And everyone's going
to know it's because you killed it.
You know...
I don't see you rushing to
show us your private books.
I have nothing to hide.
You can have full access
to our books right now.
Great. You show me yours
and I'll show you mine.
Don't say it, Harvey.
Mike.
- Hey, are you okay?
- Now, you care?
Mr. Ross, I'm going to have to ask
you not to speak to my client.
She's not your client.
She is Rachel, the paralegal.
And I only have five minutes,
so you should really get out of my face.
What's your problem, Mike?
My problem is that
you don't have the balls
to make this
a fair fight, Kyle.
Lawyering isn't
about fighting fair.
And you better watch
your false accusations
or I might just sue you
for defamation.
Come on.
The defendant
wishes to countersue.
On what grounds?
I believe that's
my line, Counselor.
Defamation of character.
The plaintiff's video negatively
impacted the perception of Lena Lunders
and impaired her
financial well-being.
That's ridiculous,
Your Honor.
In order for there
to be defamation,
the statements made
would have had to have been false.
That's not
the case here.
Then, you should have no problem
proving that in court.
The countersuit is allowed.
Are you serious?
Would you like to approach
the bench and find out how serious I am?
Your Honor, the defense
should have filed counterclaims
before the trial began.
Yes.
He should have.
But no one in this crop of associates
had the foresight to do so.
And we drafted a whole
addendum just because we assumed
one of you would.
So, I'm going
to allow it.
Do you have a problem
with that?
No, Your Honor.
This is now
a defamation trial.
You have until Friday
to prepare.
Nice recovery.
Thinking on your feet.
But you wouldn't have had to if you
hadn't been so naive.
Thank you, Your Honor.
How did
the negotiation go?
You come out on top?
Why didn't you
tell me Scottie was opposing counsel?
Because I didn't want you to have
performance anxiety.
- About the case. She's tough.
- You're obvious.
- And your fly is unzipped.
- No, it isn't.
But it was earlier today.
- You can do better.
- Ooh. Is that what Scottie said?
Type up the deal points.
I got her to cave.
Debeque's going
to run the show.
All I had to do
was show her our books.
I can't believe it.
You gave me, like, the worst advice
anyone's ever given another person.
Take the drama
down a notch, Juliet.
I tried to settle and I got
completely blind-sided.
I told you to settle.
I didn't tell you to be stupid.
What do you think is going to happen
in the real world?
You have to be
prepared for anything.
Well, in the real world,
I won't have to be looking
for someone to play
my fake witness in my fake trial.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What do you think?
You think witnesses are just going to
jump up and present themselves?
Because they're not.
And sometimes, when you have one,
they disappear or recant.
And you know what you do?
You deal with it.
Mock Trial is about figuring out what
type of lawyer you want to be.
And there's only two types.
Winners and losers.
Okay. That sounds great, Harvey,
but I haven't prepared.
I don't have anyone
to play my client or my witness.
And apparently, I'm going up against
someone that I can't trust.
Figure out a way
to beat him, anyway.
Winners don't make excuses
when the other side plays the game.
Hey, Donna.
I proofed that final agreement
on the hotel merger.
Quick question.
Has Harvey ever heard of spell check?
- Oh, my God.
- Sorry.
Are you... No, no, no. It's okay.
No, no. You don't have to cry.
It's okay.
He says things sometimes, and they...
And they cut to the bone.
He does it to me, too.
I know. He says the...
It's not bad, right?
I can also do the Demi Moore single
tear, left eye or right eye,
if that's better
for the character.
Okay, I'm scared.
What's going on?
If I'm going to play
Lena Lunders for you...
I need to be able to use my full
range of emotions.
Oh, my God. I love you.
Yeah, I know.
Focus.
You need
another witness.
And at this point,
everybody else in the firm is booked up.
Aw! Is Mommy helping you
clean up your mess, Ross?
Am I Mommy
in this scenario?
What? Uh...
Ross is just... A baby.
Oh, my God.
I cannot believe
I'm going to lose to that tool.
Okay. Come on.
No pity parties.
Go to an outside source
for the other witness.
For the best friend, you need somebody
pretty, sympathetic,
and most importantly, willing to go
above and beyond for you.
What are
you doing here?
Jenny, come on.
I need your help.
I've got nowhere else to go.
You yelled at me.
Kissed me.
Pushed me away.
Disappeared.
I haven't talked to you in forever.
I don't even know
what's going on in your life.
Well, if you let me in,
I'll explain.
And I promise
it's a really good story.
So, you've been living a lie
this whole time.
Yeah.
That's awesome.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I mean, as far as
double lives go,
you're maybe not
as cool as Clark Kent.
- Still...
- Clark Kent.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Okay. You're cut off.
Mmm.
- What?
- Nothing.
It just feels really
good to tell you.
I don't really have anybody
I can talk to about it.
You trust me.
Yeah. I guess I do.
I like that.
Ooh, I really like this.
Hmm.
I've got to hand it
to you, Harvey.
You may not be able
to commit to a woman,
but you have been
in this place a very long time.
She gets me.
And has no needs.
I don't think you understand
how high maintenance this place is.
He agreed to
all your terms
despite my protests that
he could do better.
So, we're done.
Minus a few signatures.
That's not done.
Want me to leave?
Ladies and gentlemen
of the jury, please note...
Can I ask a question?
No, you can't ask questions
as a witness.
Don't ask questions.
Ladies and gentlemen...
Yeah, I know that.
But, um...
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
You're walking around like
you have a giant stick up your ass.
It's a trial, Jenny.
I... I have to be powerful.
But that's not you.
- Thanks.
- No.
You are charming and funny
and trustworthy.
That's your power.
And that's great when I'm trying to con
my way into the LSATs,
but this is a courtroom.
It's useless there.
But it's still you.
So?
Take a deep breath.
Just talk to me.
Ask me where do I work.
Where do you work?
Lunders Global Initiative.
Ask me how I know Sydney.
How do you know Sydney?
She was my friend.
And I've missed her every day
that she's been gone.
And why aren't you
friends anymore?
I don't know.
If you do it
like that
they'll fall in
love with you.
Scottie,
that was amazing.
Careful, Harvey.
You need to hydrate.
You just ran a marathon.
And I think
you just beat me.
Uh-oh.
That's a lawyer look.
Law school.
Post-Mock Trial
in the library.
Second Circuit
Court of Appeals. Class action
on the prep room table.
Dempsey settlement.
In my office,
on the desk and under.
So, what, are we doing
a highlight reel?
As a matter of fact,
we are.
Those were
top moments, right?
- They weren't bad.
- No, they were great.
And I just realized
this was better.
You were the best you've ever been
and I know why.
Why?
You hid something from me
in the negotiation.
And I want to know what.
You know what?
You are ridiculous.
Uh, you know what?
Don't do that. Okay?
- Do what?
- You think I don't know victory sex
when I see it? Huh?
- See it?
- What is it?
One of Vega's properties
is bankrupt?
The Buenos Aires one?
What, uh...
What do you want me to say, Harvey?
You... Yes.
- You got me. I screwed you.
- How?
Oh, my God. You want an
anatomy lesson now?
That's my shirt.
Consider it
a winner's reward.
Hey, Harvey.
You were right.
There's been a steady stream
of stock-buying by Vega's company
in the last 24 hours.
It's a hostile takeover.
Yeah. But why are they
disguising it as a merger?
They wanted access
to our private books.
- She tricked me.
- What?
She pretended she
didn't want to hand over their books
so I wouldn't notice when she asked
for ours. It's a classic maneuver.
She made me think
it was my idea.
How do you know that?
Because I taught her
how to do it.
So, now, they see
how strong Debeque's company is
and they want to buy it.
And they'll be running it by the time
Scottie's back in London.
Wow. I leave you
alone for two days.
This is my mistake.
This is Halley's Comet.
Take a good look.
Because it won't
happen again.
So, what are you
going to do?
I want to know which of Debeque's hotels
are the most valuable.
And how fast we can
get them on the market.
Wait. You want Debeque
to sell his best hotels?
It's called the
"Crown Jewel defense."
We unload the highest
grossing assets
and we make ourselves
look undesirable.
Debeque will never
agree to that.
Trust me, Debeque has enough
passion for his company
that he'll be willing
to chop off an arm to save the body.
Okay.
You know you had that memorized
the first time you read it, right?
Yeah, but I didn't
finish reading it
because a certain witness
chose to be distracting.
That must have
been rough for you.
Yeah. You have no idea.
Where can I
get some water?
I need to make sure
my voice holds up.
Right there.
I'll make you a deal.
Winner gets the girl.
You know, I'm never going to make
another deal with you again.
Hey.
They remind me of a younger,
less attractive you and me.
Please don't say
things like that.
And I know that you rigged the lottery
so that Mike would get Kyle.
Please. Rigged, expedited...
They're all just words.
Besides, don't you want to see
what your boy is made of?
You talking bet?
- Yeah.
- Usual amount.
I believe
we have a wager.
Some of us shower
before we go to work.
Mr. Specter.
You know what? Save it.
Right.
How are you feeling?
- Good.
- Good?
- Yeah.
- Good.
Is it inappropriate to take a Xanax if
you're a witness in a trial?
I've seen clients
do much worse.
Actually,
I'm not a client.
I'm a witness
in a friend's mock trial.
One thing. If you get into trouble,
don't play the case.
Play the man.
What are you
talking about?
Good lawyers
worry about facts.
Great lawyers worry
about their opponents.
Kyle is
cocky and devious.
Figure out a way to
use that against him.
Okay. Anything else?
Kick his ass.
Who's your friend?
Uh, Mike Ross.
Do you know him?
Uh, yeah. Uh, it's a big firm.
But I know who he is.
Yeah.
God, I don't know
why I'm so nervous.
I just know this is
a big deal to him
and I don't want to
let him down.
Hmm.
Sydney Thompson was at a party
and made a joke.
It wasn't meant to be mean
or to be taken as fact.
And it most certainly
was never meant to be public.
The defense will show...
That Sydney Thompson
chose to publicly defame her boss
with an impression that
she knew would be damaging
both to Lena Lunders'
reputation and her company.
I call Lena Lunders
to the stand.
Uh...
- Do you need a minute?
- No.
I can continue.
Thank you.
Please.
I'm a self-made woman.
I created the Global Initiative
to target problems in Third World
countries.
I take my work
very seriously.
And if a joke
can be made of that,
fine.
But as a woman in power, people look
at your success and label you.
They don't know
the complexity it takes
for a woman to succeed
in this business.
And when someone
undermines that...
Well...
We have to fight
for ourselves.
Don't we, Your Honor?
Objection.
So, it's hard to be
a woman in business?
That has nothing to do with
the facts of this case.
We can only understand the damage
your client has done
by fully understanding the care
with which Ms. Lunders has built her
reputation.
Um...
I'm sorry. Can you ask me
the question one more time?
Take a deep breath.
It's just you and me.
We're just going to have a conversation
about your job, okay?
Yeah. Okay.
How do you know the defendant,
Sydney Thompson?
We were coworkers. We started
at the same level.
And then, I was promoted
to be her immediate superior.
And do you know about
the video in question?
Yes, I was at the party
that night.
And what were you
celebrating that night?
My promotion.
Same night?
That's interesting.
Ms. Ginnesse, what did you think
of the impersonation?
It was too far.
It was mean.
So, why do you think
Ms. Thompson did it?
Ms. Lunders promoted me.
Sydney hated it.
And that's why
she made the video.
Well, thank you,
Ms. Ginnesse.
Nothing further,
Your Honor.
Did Sydney ever tell you
that she hated your promotion?
- Not exactly.
- Yes or no, please.
- No.
- Well, then, how do you know
that she hated
your promotion?
I could just tell.
Can you tell what
I'm thinking right now?
That you're wishing I would agree
with everything you say?
No.
I was thinking that if you could
actually read my mind,
I wouldn't bother
asking you questions.
But you can't read
my mind, can you?
No, I'm a managing director.
Not a magician.
No. And I'm pretty sure you can't read
Sydney's, either.
And you actually have no idea why
she made that video.
Correct?
I guess I don't. No.
Good afternoon, Ms. Scott.
Thank you.
Are you here to give me
a proper send-off?
I don't think we can
do that out here on the street.
You sure?
You tricked me.
I'm impressed.
To be fair,
Vega did want a merger.
I just convinced him that given your
client's propensity for rash purchases,
that allowing him
to stay in charge was a bad idea.
Vega needed Debeque's hotels
minus Debeque.
And
I found a way.
One that he never
asked for or wanted.
And one that he's
never going to get.
Is...
Is this for real?
Three of Debeque's properties that will
be on the market by the end of day.
He's never going to let you sell off
his crown jewels.
See, that's the thing
about passionate clients.
When they're crossed,
they get angry.
And they'll do anything
to get back.
Don't do this, Harvey.
Look.
There's another way we can do this.
We can get our clients
into a room together,
you can tell them
you were wrong,
and we can convince them
back into a merger.
Ms. Thompson, what was the intent
behind your impersonation?
I was just trying
to be funny.
Everyone in our office
makes jokes.
As a matter of fact, Ms. Lunders
encourages us to be informal.
I can't win this
just on the facts.
But I expected it.
I think everyone has
the impulse to move up
and at a certain point,
you just have to let it go.
So, that's what I did.
What are you
going to do?
I'm going to play the woman,
not the case.
You say you expected to be passed over
for a promotion, correct?
- Yes.
- And yet, you applied three times.
- And you were never promoted.
As I said. Yes.
When Nora Ginnesse was promoted,
you wrote scathing emails
to the rest of your coworkers
in response.
Not scathing.
The intent was to be funny.
Oh, right.
You like to be funny.
Who doesn't like
to laugh?
Someone whose reputation
has been ruined.
- Objection.
- Just a thought.
He's testifying.
Sustained.
Mr. Ross, questions.
I'm sorry, Your Honor. Forgive me.
I was just trying to be funny.
On your performance review,
Lena Lunders wrote,
"Good work ethic,
lacks skills."
Do you think that's
a fair assessment?
Fair? I...
I don't know.
Your coworkers were promoted and your
boss was calling you mediocre.
Are you mediocre?
No.
So, why haven't
you been promoted?
I don't know.
Do you think
you deserve better?
Doesn't everyone?
- So, why haven't you tried?
- I have tried.
Why haven't you improved?
I didn't say
I haven't improved.
Well, your review did.
Your five years
without a promotion did.
Look. You were so angry
that you weren't moving forward
that you lashed out
at your boss...
- Objection. Testifying.
- No.
- And everyone was moving past you.
- So, what?
- People making good on their potential.
- Badgering, Your Honor.
- People who can cut it.
- I can cut it!
Excuse me, Your Honor.
Settlement's still
on the table.
- What?
- Let's settle.
Same deal. Win-win.
No, I'm good.
Excuse me?
I've seen the dreamy
looks, Ross.
You like her.
So, you're offering me a settlement
because you don't want
to hurt her feelings.
But I'd rather see
if you'll break her.
Giddy-up, cowboy.
Counselor.
Would you like to proceed?
No, Your Honor.
Are you sure?
Yes, Your Honor.
Nothing further.
Well,
normally, we'd move on
to closing statements.
But it's been a long week. And honestly,
we all know where this is going.
So, the court rules in favor of
the defendant.
Court is adjourned.
Mr. Ross.
Naive and soft.
Not qualities we're looking for
at Pearson Hardman.
Gentlemen, I appreciate you
leaving the swords at home.
What started off
as a true merger
never needed to become
anything different.
Daniel, I want you
to listen to me.
I know Harvey, and he just wants to
merge your businesses
so he can double
his billable hours.
Quiet, Scott.
I want to hear
what he has to say.
I'm just here to get my client
the deal that he wants.
And what he wants is a merger.
Is that right, Jones?
That's right.
Daniel.
Your law firm overreached in a situation
where it wasn't necessary.
It's not entirely
Scottie's fault.
We lawyers all have
an instinct to win.
But sometimes, we may
not fully understand what that means.
We understand
what it means.
Well, maybe you do
and maybe you don't.
For me, it would be to see both men
return to the initial deal,
so that you can grow
both your businesses.
Instead of having one company with
a hostile reputation
and the other a shell
of what it once was.
I mean, that doesn't
sound like a win to me.
I'm sorry.
Let's just go back
to the original deal.
We can run it together.
You need anything? Because otherwise,
I'm going to head out.
Celebratory drinks
with the associates?
Yep.
And what exactly
are you celebrating?
You know what? You can save the
disappointment, Harvey.
- I know what I did.
- Do you?
Because what I saw is
that you backed off
because you were worried about hurting
your girlfriend's feelings.
It was a fake trial.
All right? I weighed
the pros and the cons and I decided
it wasn't worth hurting
someone for the result.
The result is you just told
every partner in this firm,
including myself, that you have
a weak stomach.
You don't have
what it takes.
You know, you keep telling me that I
have to decide
what kind of lawyer I want to be.
And if I were smart, I'd probably be
just like you.
Because everybody
knows you're the best.
But I'm also trying to decide what kind
of person I want to be.
And sometimes, I like my kind of person
a lot more than yours.
You want to know
what kind of person I am?
Tough, but fair.
I call it like I see it.
And what I see is a kid who asked
for an opportunity
and still hasn't decided
if he wants it or not.
Single malt, please.
Harvard Club? I thought you
hate this place.
Vega kicked me
out of his hotel.
So, you know, beggars.
Save the pout. You were head
of law review.
You clerked for a Supreme Court judge.
And you almost beat me.
I think that deserves
a drink. On you.
I'd laugh,
but I just got fired.
- From the firm?
- No.
But the firm is
not going to be happy.
That's why I'm not
already on a plane.
Hey, the Scottie I know
is tougher than that.
Is she?
Whoa.
You want to go back
to our alma mater
and see a lecture on why women are
better at science?
Might cheer you up.
Maybe. But I'm not
going with you.
Come on.
We're still friends.
I'm getting
married, Harvey.
His name is Steve.
And, uh, he asked
me a month ago.
And, um, when I get
back to London, I'm...
I'm going to say yes.
What would you
like me to say?
Nothing.
Come here.
I'm sorry I won.
No, Harvey.
I would hate it
if you were sorry about that.
You didn't have to
do that, you know.
- I know.
- I could have handled it.
I know.
That was a thank you,
if you couldn't tell.
I could tell.
So, um, Jenny was
a great witness.
Really likable
and pretty.
Yeah. Yeah, she is.
I know I was hard
on you this week.
- It's okay, Rachel.
- No, it...
Did you ever take a minute to wonder why
I was so mad at you?
I just expect more from you
than most people.
Why?
You're a smart guy.
You can figure it out.