No. Mike, stop!
Whoa.
- Sorry.
- Smooth.
You would have made
a nice ballerina.
I'm not going to apologize
for my lithe physique, okay?
And by the way, I was on the wrestling
team in high school, so...
Is something funny?
I'm just trying to imagine
you fighting someone.
Oh.
I would kill you.
- You wouldn't touch me.
- Why not?
Because you'd be too busy
staring at me in tights.
- No, I wouldn't.
- You're doing it right now.
You're not wearing
any tights.
I'm not
wearing any underwear.
I'm... You...
Okay. So, Mrs. Williams, we're going
to take you to the deposition
as soon as Kenny Verdasco
is finished. All right? Oh.
Did you two draw
the short straw?
I'm sorry?
You're in charge of corralling
the cancer patients.
It's not the most glamorous
duty in the world.
Oh.
I suppose you two
don't mind working together.
How long have
you been dating?
Oh, no, I'm sort of seeing someone else.
Oh, it's going to
happen sooner or later.
- Uh, excuse me.
- Uh, excuse me a moment.
Yes. Hi.
Uh, I'm sorry. I think
I'm in the wrong place.
Are you here for the
Emerson Petroleum depositions?
Oh, no, no.
I'm an old friend of Harvey Specter's.
This place is huge.
I always get turned around.
- Yeah.
- Maybe you can point me
- in the right direction?
- Uh, no problem.
You just see those doors right there?
Go through to the elevators
and up two floors.
And then, you're going to take a right
and down the hall, and you'll see Donna.
- Donna. Great. Thanks.
- Mmm-hmm.
Travis Tanner.
Mike Ross.
Good to meet you.
A pleasure to
meet you, too, Mike.
Take care.
My wife, Emily,
and I, we...
We saved every dollar
I made in the Army
and we moved here from
Apple Creek, New York, six years ago.
We bought a brownstone,
and we planted
a tomato garden.
We had barbecues
with the neighbors.
It was... It was
a dream come true.
After being diagnosed
with lung cancer,
I couldn't work anymore.
I mean, there's times
I have difficulty
even going up the stairs
to my daughter's room.
You attended Apple Creek
High School. Is that right?
All four years.
Your high school
was built in 1985.
What was there before?
An oil well.
Owned and operated
by Emerson Petroleum.
Now, Kenny, why was
the high school shut down?
Because 200 people who
taught at or attended Apple Creek High
were diagnosed with
some form of cancer.
I'm so sorry to interrupt.
That's for you, Larry.
Trust me. It's good. Use it.
- How do you know my name?
- It's all in there, Larry.
- Hey, are you Donna?
- Yeah. Can I help you?
Yeah. Mike Ross told me
to find you.
We were in the library and one of the
plaintiffs fainted, hit their head.
Oh, my gosh. Okay.
I'm on it. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Wrong office.
Harvey, I have to admit,
great job making Kenny Verdasco the face
of your class action suit.
I don't know who
Kenny Verdasco is.
Oh, well, you'd
better find out.
How about for starters you introduce
yourself, or I'm calling security?
- Donna?
- Relax. Relax.
Name's Travis Tanner.
You're Travis Tanner?
You've heard of me.
No.
I'm a senior partner
with Clyde-MacPhee.
We're based in Boston.
So are the Red Sox. I don't give a shit
about them, either.
That's funny.
You know, what's not funny is what's
happening to Kenny Verdasco.
At this moment, they're asking
him about his parents,
both heavy smokers.
Nasty habit.
Yes. A pack a day each.
I lived with them
until I was 18.
Then, they'll ask how,
in the army,
he was exposed to nickel, chromium,
and hydrocarbons.
I... I... I was
an infantry soldier.
I didn't have much choice
in the matter.
Not to mention
the frivolous lawsuit
he filed ten years ago against
the Shriver Grocery Chain.
It wasn't frivolous.
I slipped and shattered
my elbow.
If they're doing such
a great job down there,
what are you doing up
here in my office?
Because I gave them
all that.
And when they walk
out that door,
I'm going to be the one
who fires their asses.
So are you coming to
me for a pep talk?
You're going to
do great, kiddo.
No, you see, Emerson Petroleum was
going to lose this case.
So they called me in
to fix the situation.
And when I beat
Pearson Hardman,
I don't want anyone saying it was
because they didn't send in their best.
Well, I'm sorry to
disappoint you,
but Jessica Pearson's
handling this case herself.
And if you think that
she's not the best,
why don't you take a run
at her and find out?
All right, look.
I hear what you're saying.
But here's the thing.
I know that you
know who I am.
And I also know that
during your senior year,
you missed out on playing
in the state championship
because of your shoulder.
You can't pitch with
a bad shoulder.
And what do you know?
They won without you, Harvey.
Now, ask yourself something.
Are you going to let Jessica Pearson
play the big game for you? Hmm?
What's so funny?
I'm just thinking about
how I'm going to enjoy kicking your ass.
I'll see you in court.
See the money,
wanna stay for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
That was an attack
on my history,
my family, everything
I care about.
I told you this was coming.
They're just trying
to rattle you.
Yeah, well, they're doing
a hell of a good job.
Kenny, you're
our lead plaintiff.
You've got to keep
your composure.
I don't care
about composure.
I want to make a settlement.
That's exactly what they want.
Kenny, I'd like you
to meet Harvey Specter.
He's my right hand.
Can your right hand please tell me why
we shouldn't ask for a settlement?
I'm not against
settling one bit.
But if we go to them,
we're weak.
If they come to us,
we're strong.
Harvey's right. They came after you
because they're running scared.
Trust me. They'll come
to us soon enough.
Okay.
One more thing.
I'm going to postpone
the rest of the depositions.
Don't tell the rest of
the plaintiffs what happened.
What the hell was that?
I need you to let me
take over this case.
The guy that came
into my deposition.
- He called you out?
- Yeah.
- He's good.
You think I can't take him?
He brought up
the state championships.
Oh. Shoulder.
- Yeah.
- Ooh.
Take him.
- Be careful.
- I will.
I mean, bringing up
the state championships...
That's just... That's wrong.
Nothing I wouldn't have done.
Here you go.
I need you to dig
into Travis Tanner.
Find out where he's worked.
Where he's gone to school.
What cases he's won.
Why? You thinking about
starting a Wikipedia page for him?
I don't know anything about
how this guy operates.
And before I make a move,
I need to know everything
about how this guy operates.
Right. For his
Wikipedia page.
You think the Mavericks
didn't watch game film
on LeBron before
they played the Heat?
You're Harvey Specter.
You don't need to watch game film.
Do you know who's watched
more game film than anybody?
- No. Who?
- Michael Jordan.
What? How do
you know that?
You don't believe me?
Let's call him.
You have Michael Jordan's
phone number.
Yep.
If I hit this button right here,
I call Michael Jordan?
That's kind of how
a phone works.
Speed dial 23.
I'm doing it.
- Go for it.
- I'm going to ask him about baseball.
Do not ask him
about baseball.
Ah! Wrong...
Wrong number.
You're kidding me.
Oh, my God.
Who are you?
Everybody, stop
what you're doing.
Stand up and follow me
in the library.
Mike, that goes for you, too.
Up and at them.
Uh, yeah, Louis,
I'd love to,
but I have some work
to do for Harvey.
His Majesty can wait.
All associates in the library now.
Let's go.
Oh.
Rumor is we're getting
our annual raises early.
People are freaking out.
That's great, Harold.
I'm thinking about
getting a tattoo.
You need a raise
for that?
I'm really over-paying
for my apartment.
Good morning, everyone.
Many of you seem to think
this is about getting your raises early.
- It isn't.
- Suck.
We've discovered
a breach at the firm.
A confidential witness
list was leaked
to a rival firm.
Wakefield-Cady.
Now, it's entirely possible
that this was an honest mistake.
If so, we urge the
responsible party to come forward.
If not, we'll find out
soon enough.
Either way, we will
get to the bottom of this.
Louis.
Jessica seems to think
a mistake has been made.
I don't believe so.
I also don't believe
this is a matter of ethics.
It's a matter of loyalty.
Someone in this room
has betrayed us all,
and it makes me sick.
And the fact that it went to those
holier-than-thou pricks
at Wakefield-Cady...
You know what?
That makes me sicker.
Now, you all work together,
in the trenches,
shoulder to shoulder.
Which means one of you
must know who did this.
Now, if y'all harbor knowledge
of the perpetrator and do not turn him
in,
you are as bad as
the perpetrator himself.
You along with the
perpetrator will be fired.
He's doing George W. Bush.
You're either with us
or against us, folks.
He sounds like Bush,
but he looks just like Cheney.
You got something
to tell me, Harold?
Mmm-mmm.
No? Not that
dermatological problem
that you were talking
to me about earlier in my office?
- No? Not that one?
- No.
To show you how serious I am,
I have an incentive.
Whoever turns
this traitor in
receives $10,000.
You're welcome.
Feel free to
go back to work.
$10,000.
That's a big tattoo.
Yeah, it would be huge.
Why?
Louis. There was
a witness list...
I don't care. Tell me what
you learned about Travis Tanner.
It's all in there.
Travis Tanner went to Yale,
undergrad and law.
Honors in both.
He was a junior
tennis champion.
Tennis. Just like Louis.
Yeah. He played in
college, too.
Oh, my God.
More importantly, he was the youngest
senior partner at Clyde-MacPhee.
This guy's record
is off the charts.
Really?
He specializes in breaking
class action lawsuits.
Harris Tobacco,
Bell Pesticide,
GravTech Securities,
he broke them all.
How come
I've never heard of him?
Evidently, he doesn't like
to take public credit.
Stays off the radar.
He avoids the press.
I mean,
I only found this stuff
by looking through court records.
Now, it makes sense.
- What?
- Why he thinks I know him.
I know those other attorneys.
He thinks they've told
me about him.
- They never did?
- No.
- Why not?
- Because he beat them.
This guy's kind of a badass.
You want me to get
you an autograph?
No. I'm just respecting
our foe.
Foe?
It's from The Art of War.
No?
No. Look, I need to know how those other
cases are different from ours.
Well, those other cases
were spread out
geographically,
economically, socially.
Ours is in a single town.
A single school.
A single cluster
of plaintiffs.
Okay. That's good.
That tennis playing douche-bag, Travis
Tanner, is on the phone.
You know I listen.
Travis, what can I
do for you?
Yeah, I'm happy to discuss the case.
On one condition.
You're going to meet me
at Apple Creek High School.
See you in an hour.
Why do you want
to meet there?
Because that's ground zero.
And I want the emotion of that school
under my feet when I negotiate.
I thought you were
against emotions.
I'm against having emotions.
I'm not against using them.
Come on.
I thought we were homies.
Jimmy, I didn't
leak anything.
You know, I remember
you said you hated Louis Litt
and you were second-guessing
your decision to become a lawyer.
I told you that in confidence over
six Cosmopolitans.
That doesn't mean
you're not the guy.
Harold, really?
You drink Cosmopolitans?
Stop doing that. Unless you're with
girls, which you never are.
And Jimmy, are you kidding me?
Going after Harold?
What? How do you know
he didn't do it?
How do we know
you didn't do it?
Maybe you're the guy.
Oh, my God.
Guys, this is ridiculous.
All right, has it occurred to any of you
that maybe this is all just a big test?
Wow. Wow. Spoken like a person
with something to hide.
Louis was talking
about loyalty.
Maybe this is just some test
to see how loyal we are by not turning
on each other.
Are you kidding? Jessica would never
play along with something like that.
Even if it's not a test,
this is a law office,
not Lord of the Flies.
Everybody, get back to work.
Are these
the Galusska briefs?
You guys, Louis has been
hounding us for these.
Why hasn't anyone
taken them to him?
Are you serious? Wow.
You're scared of him.
It's Louis Litt.
It's not Darth Vader.
This is what courage looks
like, Jimmy. Pay attention.
Please.
Louis. The Galusska briefs.
Sorry they're late.
Thank you, Mr. Mike Ross.
You sure
you're ready for this?
I'm here, aren't I?
I've been looking into you.
You're an elusive man.
Yeah, well,
when you're number one,
you don't need to broadcast your
victories, Harvey.
That's funny.
Where I come from,
number one doesn't usually challenge
number two to a fight.
This school was
Apple Creek's pride.
Parents felt safe
sending their children here
and teachers felt safe
teaching here.
You know what Apple Creek
High School is now?
A bunch of trailers
on the outskirts of town.
All because 30 years ago, your clients
failed to cap an oil well
and gave them all cancer.
You see all these power lines around
here? They criss-cross the entire town.
Two miles down
that road, paint factory.
You've got a microwave tower.
And all this grass
that you see?
It's been treated with pesticide
every week for twenty years.
You say it's our fault.
I say you're wrong.
That office.
Mitch Rosewall.
Soccer coach.
Brain cancer.
Library. Monica Dodd volunteered.
She ran it for years.
Stomach cancer.
They both died last month,
and they sure as hell
didn't die from pesticide.
Can you prove it?
If we go to trial, it won't be about
proving anything.
It will be about Monica,
Mitch, and Kenny.
And you won't
stand a chance.
Oh, this is fun, Harvey.
I'm just sorry to say that we won't get
to do this in court.
Against my advice,
Emerson wants to settle.
You're kidding me.
After all this,
you want to settle.
No, I don't.
But those are
my instructions.
Call it a draw.
Mike, get over to
Kenny's house.
Tanner's going to try
and make him cave.
Hey, I came as soon
as I got the message.
Kenny?
It's Harvey Specter.
Was Travis Tanner here?
I was just with him.
He couldn't have
beaten me by much.
Sweetie, why don't you
go inside? Okay, baby.
Okay.
No, it wasn't him. It was someone else.
He wouldn't tell me his name.
He said he was with Pearson Hardman,
so I let him in.
Did he mention
Tanner's name?
No, but it was obvious
that's who he worked for.
He said me and the other plaintiffs
would be getting a settlement offer
soon.
- What else?
- He said if we don't take it,
that they're going
to go after us.
That they have dirt
on everyone.
He mentioned Eva Williams'
arrest for public intoxication.
Bernie Rutherford's shoplifting arrest
when he was in college.
That's criminal intimidation.
If they want to go after me, that's
fine. I can handle it.
But the others?
I don't know if they can.
You have to
stay strong, Kenny.
You cave,
everything falls apart.
One more thing.
What did this guy look like?
I don't know. He was average height.
Brown hair. Brown eyes.
Thanks.
You want me to start
figuring out who this guy is?
No. We'll never find him.
How did you know
Tanner was going after Kenny?
Because if I was the
type to go out of bounds,
that's exactly what I'd do.
- You're not?
- No.
Huh.
So what's our next move?
I'm calling in
reinforcements.
What do you mean?
If Tanner sent a guy
to intimidate Kenny,
he's got something else up his sleeve
and I want to know what it is.
Oh, man.
What?
Nothing. It's... You guys are like two
sides of the same coin.
What are you saying?
He's another me?
No one is another me.
You told Donna
I was another you.
I never said that.
You said you were
looking for another you,
and then you hired me.
So...
See how that works?
Logic?
Mike. Let's go.
In my office. Now.
Oh. Damn, Mike,
tell me you didn't leak
the documents, man.
Are you our
Benedict Arnold?
Benedict Arnold.
Nice reference.
You helping your high school
girlfriend with her homework again?
Okay, not cool, Mike.
You know Darla's in
community college.
I don't even know why you're laughing,
Harold. You don't have a chick.
She's of age.
So, you...
I am so very proud
of you, Mike.
Wow, I really wish
you weren't touching me right now.
You are what
loyalty looks like.
You rooted out
the person responsible for
leaking the witness list
to Wakefield-Cady.
Louis, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
It was almost cute how you hid the
evidence in the Galusska Briefs.
Like you didn't want
to take the credit.
What? Louis, I didn't
hide anything in...
Don't worry. No one's
going to label you a snitch.
Snitch.
We didn't even think
to check the fax machines.
That was brilliant.
The list was sent from
right here in this firm.
This is a copy of a fax submission
form sent from three days ago.
This doesn't
implicate anybody.
That's the confidential
employee code.
She must not have known that the
machine recorded it.
She?
Wait. Why am
I being suspended?
I didn't leak any documents.
Who told Louis I did this?
- Let's go, please. This way, miss.
- Get your arms...
No, no, no. Louis,
you have to stop this.
I didn't turn Rachel in.
Oh, that's so sweet, how you didn't
really mean to hand someone in.
Wait. Mike, stop.
You did a great thing.
And because of
that great thing,
$10,000.
And don't spend it in one place.
You say, "Thank you, Louis," and then,
"You're welcome, Mike."
Rachel.
- I don't want to talk to you.
- Hey, come on.
You want come on?
Why would you do that to me?
- I didn't do anything to you.
- I didn't fax that goddamn list.
And I didn't turn you in.
Then why was I
just suspended, Mike?
All I know is that I gave
Louis a stack of briefs
and there was some fax
with your confidential code on it.
Do you think that if I was
going to leak firm documents,
I'd be dumb enough to
fax them with my own code?
No, I don't. But
whoever did this must have framed you.
Yeah, well, it worked.
Rachel, look, you just... They're going
to investigate this.
They're going to
clear your name. You know that.
I have worked there
for five years,
and this is how
they treat me?
I'm suspended, Mike.
I'm probably
going to be fired.
I should sue them.
Okay, let's not do
anything rash, okay?
It's not rash.
It's standing up for myself.
Rachel, you're over...
Excuse me.
You wouldn't happen
to know what sort of wine
pairs well with a
duck l'orange, would you?
Mmm, try something with
a full-fruit flavor,
like a Cabernet Sauvignon.
Uh, Sauvignons are
a little bit oaky for my palate.
This article right here is
all about the resurgence of Pinot Noir.
You know, you could just pay me right
out in public.
But then I wouldn't feel
like James Bond.
Oh. Who does that make me?
Pussy Galore.
- Octopussy.
- Ah, that's enough, Harvey.
- What do you have for me?
- Nothing.
On paper, Tanner's clean.
He may break the rules,
but he covers his tracks.
You've never come up
empty for me before.
I didn't this time, either.
Tanner booked a conference room
at the Waldorf tomorrow at noon.
Divide and conquer.
He's going to gather
my plaintiffs, scare them,
and then give them
a low-ball offer.
And that's illegal.
What?
You've used me
for a lot of things.
You've never asked me to
investigate another attorney before.
This guy's good.
If he called your plaintiffs, I can get
his phone records and prove it.
He didn't make
those calls himself.
He's not going to be at the Waldorf
either tomorrow.
But I will.
Donna. Can you tell me about these
confidential employee codes
that Louis says Rachel used to fax the
witness list over to Wakefield-Cady?
I have a thousand things
to do before lunch.
Hold Mike's hand while he crosses
the street, not one of them.
Donna, this one's
for Rachel.
What do you need?
I know we use the billing codes to
charge the clients.
But what do we use
the employee codes for?
They're special codes for when you need
to use the firm's resources
- for personal reasons.
- We can do that?
- You can't. But Rachel can.
- Why?
Because a fifth-year paralegal
is more valuable to the firm
than a first-year associate.
Okay. So, do you
have a personal code?
I have two.
So where
do you get them?
They're generated by
the IT department.
We have an
IT department?
Well, the computers
don't run themselves.
At least until
Skynet goes active.
Sarah Connor.
- No.
- That's... I'll work on that.
- Really bad.
What?
Uh, hi. Excuse me.
I'm looking for Benjamin?
- You found him.
- Oh, great. I'm Mike Ross.
We just spoke on the phone.
Man, this place is like
Battlestar Galactica.
Where do you guys
keep the Cylons?
Pearson Hardman takes care of us because
we're on call twenty-four seven.
If a server goes down or
a partner's computer crashes,
people die.
That's a little dramatic,
don't you think, Ben?
It's Benjamin. I'm sure you don't like
it when people call you Mike.
Actually, I prefer Mike.
Well, Mike,
six months ago,
I was at Connolly White.
The network went haywire.
We were in a breach-of-contract
litigation worth $400 million.
They needed it fixed
in an hour.
No one thought
it could be done.
I had the network up and running again
in 23 minutes.
Is that dramatic
enough for you?
Wow. You're, like,
a regular Zuckerberg.
Zuckerberg?
Zuckerberg couldn't code
his way out of a paper bag.
You called about
the employee codes.
You're a first year.
You can't have one. Sorry.
Okay. Well,
I don't need one.
I just want to know
if it's possible
for someone to gain
access to somebody else's code.
Sure. For one person. Me.
I have access to
all of the codes.
Okay. So, in your
short tenure here,
has anyone ever asked you for access to
someone else's code?
Once. Last week.
- Who?
- I can't tell you that.
- Why not?
- IT officer client privilege.
Does that even exist, Ben?
It does in here.
All right, Ben.
Why don't we... make a bet?
I think you mean
a wager. Michael.
Yeah. Sure.
I'm going to tell you every single
number on this piece of paper,
and you're going to
give me that name.
And if you can't?
Then, I'm going to
give you this check.
For ten grand.
You get one number, one comma,
one decimal point wrong,
and that money is mine.
Oh, and when I win, I'll also take one
of those computers.
And for the record, there's not a single
comma on there.
You ready?
Rachel, it's Mike.
I figured out who leaked
the list to Wakefield-Cady.
It was Louis.
Call me back.
Hi. I'm Rachel Zane. I'm here for
my job interview.
- Welcome to Wakefield-Cady.
- Thank you.
Okay. As soon as
we get inside,
I need you to find every plaintiff
you interviewed
and tell them they're here
under false pretenses.
- Done.
- Kenny's meeting us here.
We need him to identify
the man who came to see him,
and we're going to wait for that guy to
approach any of our plaintiffs.
And if we connect
that guy to Tanner,
then we have him
on criminal intimidation.
And Emerson Petroleum
will have no choice but to settle.
Hey, Kenny. Good to see you.
This is going to be fun.
You were right.
He called
every one of them.
You see the guy?
No.
Start looking.
Hey, wait a minute.
Mrs. Williams.
Do you remember me? I'm Mike Ross.
From the office?
I remember you.
Do you mind if I ask you
what you're doing here today?
We were invited to come
and hear a settlement offer.
Really?
Uh, excuse me.
He came here himself.
Well, big mistake.
Sorry to ruin
your little brunch.
But I think
you know damn well
that you can't legally
address my clients.
Hey, I just came
for the juice.
Mmm. Pulp free.
I know I can't talk to
your clients directly.
But thank God
you're here, Harv.
Because what I can do
is I can talk to you.
Harvey,
Emerson Petroleum is
offering $25,000
to each and every
one of your clients!
If they don't take that,
this trial stretches out for years.
Cross-examinations
will be brutal.
They take our settlement,
and this whole thing
will be gone tomorrow.
Now, if any of your clients want to get
in touch with me,
here's my number.
Mr. Ross.
Harvey.
Erase that number.
You're not going to get away with what
you're doing. You know that, right?
What?
I just addressed you
with a raised voice.
Sometimes,
my ears aren't so good.
If other people heard me,
I apologize, Harvey.
I'm just glad you were smart enough to
figure out I booked the Waldorf,
Mmm. I think I
need to take this.
I'm guessing it's
one of your clients
wanting to take
my settlement offer.
Hello.
Tanner.
I'm coming after you.
Oh, I got your number.
The plaintiffs are scared.
They're talking about
accepting Tanner's low-ball offer.
Those floodgates open,
and we're done.
That's why I went to
go see Clarkson.
The legal finance guys.
If we can get our plaintiffs a loan
against a future jury award,
it will close the floodgates
and buy us more time.
Well, those loans
aren't cheap, Harvey.
Well, it's better than
settling for pennies on the dollar.
Then do it.
I tried, but they won't give us anything
without collateral.
They don't think you can win.
They're wrong.
Well, that's what
I like to hear.
I need a million dollars
to get that loan.
You're talking about
firm money?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, no way that happens.
- You don't think I'm a good bet?
- That has nothing to do with it.
This was your case.
And I gave it to you to win.
Which I will do, if you just show
some faith in me.
You can have my faith,
but you're not getting my money.
What are you doing here?
I left you three messages.
Louis framed you.
We can take him down.
I don't want to
take him down, Mike.
Why not?
Because I want a fresh start.
So, you don't want to work
at Pearson Hardman anymore?
I applied for a job
at Wakefield-Cady.
They offered it to me
in the room.
I start Monday.
You took a job at the company
that ended up with the leaked list?
Do you know what
that looks like?
I don't care
what it looks like.
I'm not guilty
and I need a job.
So the going gets rough
and you just quit.
No. I'm not quitting.
I was fired, remember?
No, you were suspended.
And you can still
save your job.
Well, if Louis wants
me gone, I'm gone.
Rachel, Louis tried to frame me once
and I fought back.
Why aren't you doing
the same thing?
Because except for you,
no one from Pearson Hardman
has contacted me at all.
Why would I fight
to stay there?
They're accusing me
of spilling secrets?
I'll show them
spilling secrets.
I'll tell Wakefield-Cady
everything.
I may not have
a photographic memory, Mike,
but I sure as hell
know a lot.
Rachel.
Moneypenny.
- Don't call me that.
- Why not?
Because she had a thing for him.
This is the other way around.
What, you don't like me?
I like you enough
to give you this.
What's that?
I tapped the phones
at Emerson Petroleum.
This is a conference call
between Travis Tanner
and several high-ranking
Emerson executives.
I hope they're talking about
more than just the weather.
They're talking about
Tanner intimidating your client.
Both you and I know that
without a warrant,
this recording is
not admissible in court.
It is if you testify that
you don't know where it came from.
Why did you do this?
Because you need it.
I'm not going to commit
perjury to win a case.
Oh, weird. Look what I found.
Oh. You are a prince
among men.
I don't understand
why you use skim milk
and then put whip cream
and sugar in it.
Because I use skim milk,
I can put whip cream
and sugar in it.
Ah.
What's wrong?
- Can we talk for a second?
- Yeah.
Last week, Louis got Rachel's
confidential code
from
the IT department.
And?
And it's a smoking gun.
He's the one that set her up.
Why would Louis
betray the firm?
Uh, I don't know. Maybe he's still upset
that he got passed over
for senior partner
and leaked the list
before he jumps ship.
Mike, Louis is
a lot of things.
But he's not a traitor.
That man bleeds
Pearson Hardman.
He's probably wearing Pearson Hardman
underwear right now.
Mmm, I went to the
tennis club with him.
Trust me.
He doesn't wear underwear.
I care about Rachel, too.
Louis didn't do this.
Okay.
And if you ever mention Louis' underwear
situation to me again...
You're the one
that brought it up.
- Go.
- Okay.
Seventy-four plaintiffs.
I can't believe they're willing to
cave for $25,000.
Slow down. We need to
figure out how to beat Tanner.
Guy's been a step ahead
of me this entire time.
Yeah, it's pretty
obvious why.
Why?
You told me that you knew he'd go to
Kenny because that's what you'd do.
If you were willing
to go out of bounds.
You anticipated him by
thinking about what you'd do.
And?
And that's exactly what
he's doing to you.
Maybe the only way to
get ahead of this guy is to...
I don't know, think about
what you wouldn't do.
Surprise myself. I like that.
You're welcome.
You going to tell me
what you're doing?
Nope.
That doesn't seem fair to
the person whose idea it was.
Ah. You're gone.
You wanted to talk, talk.
I did.
I want to put this
competition aside.
Call it a draw.
You tapping out, Harv?
This isn't about that.
This is about
real people.
You make them
a reasonable offer,
I'll get them to take it.
Real people?
You're standing there
in a $12,000 suit
asking me
not to do my job.
You care so much about
those real people,
I suggest you give them
your lunch money.
But don't ask me for mine.
Vanessa. I'm going to
need that wiretap after all.
Is there any more of that?
Last cup.
- Did you make any...
- No.
Dude, that's
common courtesy.
You finish a pot,
you make another one.
Are you going to turn me
in to Louis if I don't?
Hmm? Get me fired, too?
Michael.
Benjamin. You got
something for me?
A wager's a wager.
Fair is fair.
Here's your GX 9000.
You're a good man.
Use it for porn,
and I'll know.
Weird.
Hey, Louis. How you doing?
Why did Benjamin
just call you Louis?
I don't know.
He made a mistake.
Oh.
No, he didn't.
He called you Louis
because he thinks you are Louis.
What?
Because you
posed as Louis
to get Rachel's
employee code, didn't you?
Look, Mike,
it's not what you think.
It's exactly what I think.
Come on.
Start talking, Jimmy.
Or I'll go get Benjamin
and we can all go see Jessica together.
Listen.
Wakefield-Cady offered me
a junior partnership
if I leaked the witness list.
No. No, listen, Mike.
I have huge
law school debts.
Okay? I mean, don't you?
I can't wait for Pearson Hardman to
make me a partner.
So what are you still
doing here, then?
After I gave them the list,
they reneged on the offer.
Big surprise. Yeah,
I didn't see that one coming.
Just don't turn me in,
Mike. Please?
I came from nothing.
I worked my ass off to get into Harvard
Law and become an associate here.
You know who else
worked their ass off?
Rachel Zane.
The paralegal who got fired
because of what you did.
I didn't know
it was her code.
I just needed some numbers, man. I
didn't think I was going to get caught.
Look, Mike,
I made one mistake.
Okay?
I mean, haven't you ever
cut some corners?
Done some things
you regretted?
Jimmy, I like you,
man, okay?
But to clear
Rachel's name,
they have to know
she wasn't the one.
If you come forward,
maybe they fire you.
If I turn you in,
it's going to follow you
for the rest of your career.
It's up to you.
Harvey, I'm going
to do you a favor.
Why don't you tell
Mike Ross to take a hike?
He can stay.
Okay.
You see, 95 of
your plaintiffs
have already called me
about the settlement.
It's a matter of time before the rest of
them see the light. I win.
I don't know
the last time you checked,
but as of this morning,
all two hundred of my plaintiffs are
staying with me.
Bullshit.
I got them an advance
against their settlement.
No finance company in
their right mind will back your suit.
I don't know if they
taught you math at Yale,
but that's $5 million,
$25,000 a plaintiff.
Exactly what you tried
to buy them off for.
You know what this means.
I'm going to hammer them
all one by one.
Break them down.
And it's going to get ugly.
No, you're not.
What the hell is that?
It's a conversation between
you and Emerson Petroleum,
discussing how you sent a man to
intimidate Kenny Verdasco.
Take a listen. Don't worry.
It's not going to give you cancer.
No matter what
that is, it's not admissible.
Unless, of course, you had a warrant.
Which you didn't.
It showed up on my doorstep.
And I declared that
on this affidavit
which I'm about to
send to court.
Hmm.
So you're going to perjure yourself just
to win this case.
No. I'm not going
to perjure myself.
Even if I were,
it wouldn't be just to win this case,
it would be to get
your ass thrown in jail.
See, you have
power of attorney,
and you're going to
accept this settlement.
$2 million a plaintiff.
You're going to take it.
And you and that shit-eating grin are
going to fly back to Boston
and never come back
to my town again.
You can use mine.
I told you
I'd get his autograph.
I can't believe you.
You were going to
perjure yourself just to win.
I thought you
didn't cross lines.
That's the difference
between guys like you and him.
I had no intention of
submitting this affidavit.
I'm not going to
perjure myself.
But Tanner doesn't know that
and he never will.
How do you know?
Because a man who's willing
to break the rules
can't imagine
someone else wouldn't.
You said that you took my advice and
that you surprised yourself.
I did. That loan I got
for the plaintiffs?
I put up a million dollars
of my own money to get it.
If that's not having emotion,
I don't know what is.
Get out.
That seemed a little angry.
Feeling good?
Satisfied? Happy?
All right. Emotional.
Okay, maybe a little happy.
Two million dollars?
Didn't I tell you
he was my right hand?
I don't know what to say.
You don't say anything.
You tell me what it's like
when you deliver this news to everyone.
Thank you.
I told you I'd win.
And it's a good thing, too.
Because if you hadn't, oh...
What, oh?
There's no way we were going to cover
that million dollars.
None of it?
Nope. Hey,
how's your shoulder?
Amazing.
You called me?
Sure did.
Have a seat.
I'd prefer to stand.
Fair enough.
Uh, I made a mistake.
You were unfairly punished.
And I would like to officially just
welcome you back.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Are you kidding me?
You think I'm going to
make it that easy on you?
I want a raise.
- Three percent.
- Ten percent.
- Seven.
- Fine.
- And Pearson Hardman
pays for law school
when I decide to go.
Agreed.
And one more thing.
This should have been the first words
out of your mouth
when I walked in here.
You need to apologize
to me right now.
Or I'm going to file a lawsuit
against you first thing in the morning.
You're right.
I should have apologized.
But don't you threaten me.
I followed procedure
to the letter
and you have no basis
for a lawsuit.
No, I don't.
Not about this.
But if you don't think
I have a basis
for all the shit you've pulled
over the years I've been here,
think again.
I'm sorry.
Okay?
How'd it go?
I don't know if you had
plans tonight,
but you're going to cancel them and help
me put my office back together.
Sure thing. Just as long as you don't
quit halfway through.
Thank you, Mike.
Yeah. Sure thing.
So, where does this go?
Over there.