1
00:00:01,705 --> 00:00:02,910
Previously on Suits...

2
00:00:02,934 --> 00:00:04,429
Sheila Amanda Sazs,

3
00:00:04,430 --> 00:00:05,607
will you marry me?

4
00:00:05,631 --> 00:00:07,976
Yes, I'll marry you.

5
00:00:08,000 --> 00:00:10,478
When we have kids,
world, watch out.

6
00:00:10,502 --> 00:00:11,613
Louis, I don't want kids.

7
00:00:11,637 --> 00:00:14,416
Sheila, I'm gonna be a father.

8
00:00:14,440 --> 00:00:15,650
Mike Ross is not coming back
to this firm.

9
00:00:15,674 --> 00:00:17,369
You heard Louis.
He already gave him the job.

10
00:00:17,393 --> 00:00:19,487
I want to know
why the hell you came back.

11
00:00:19,511 --> 00:00:21,206
What matters is
that I'm staying,

12
00:00:21,230 --> 00:00:23,014
because this is where I belong.

13
00:00:23,032 --> 00:00:24,672
This makes it look
like Forstman's payment

14
00:00:24,683 --> 00:00:26,378
never went
to any offshore accounts,

15
00:00:26,402 --> 00:00:27,545
and that you never took
a piece of it.

16
00:00:27,569 --> 00:00:29,047
That's forgery.

17
00:00:29,071 --> 00:00:31,766
Which is a less of a crime
than what you did.

18
00:00:31,790 --> 00:00:33,935
- I had no choice!
- Bullshit, you had no choice!

19
00:00:33,959 --> 00:00:35,804
You could have said "no" at any
goddamn point along the way.

20
00:00:35,828 --> 00:00:37,722
One thing is for sure.

21
00:00:37,746 --> 00:00:40,942
When all this is over, I'm
gonna fire the shit out of you.

22
00:00:40,966 --> 00:00:45,730
I wouldn't be back here
if it wasn't for Louis.

23
00:00:45,754 --> 00:00:47,983
I'll take care of it.

24
00:00:48,007 --> 00:00:50,184
"Dear Harvey and Jessica,

25
00:00:50,208 --> 00:00:51,903
"I put all of you in jeopardy
for my own personal gain.

26
00:00:51,927 --> 00:00:55,523
"Effective immediately,
I, Louis Litt,

27
00:00:55,547 --> 00:00:58,549
"am resigning
from Pearson Specter.

28
00:00:58,567 --> 00:01:00,568
Please take care of my home."

29
00:01:23,008 --> 00:01:27,221
- One, two.
- Give me a second, gimme a sec.

30
00:01:27,245 --> 00:01:28,523
You're not dressed for it.

31
00:01:28,547 --> 00:01:30,525
Maybe we can get you
some trunks, go a few rounds.

32
00:01:30,549 --> 00:01:32,994
I think I've already
gone a few rounds.

33
00:01:33,018 --> 00:01:36,230
I need your help.

34
00:01:36,254 --> 00:01:38,199
Anything. What can I do for you?

35
00:01:38,223 --> 00:01:40,902
Clients. I need clients.

36
00:01:40,926 --> 00:01:42,504
Louis, the by-laws say that...

37
00:01:42,528 --> 00:01:43,905
Come on, Harvey. You think
I don't know what they say?

38
00:01:43,929 --> 00:01:45,206
I wrote the by-laws.

39
00:01:45,230 --> 00:01:47,598
Yeah, and who'd you
write 'em for, huh?

40
00:01:47,616 --> 00:01:51,046
Jessica, and she's not gonna
make an exception for you.

41
00:01:51,070 --> 00:01:52,246
Well, maybe she'll make one
for you?

42
00:01:52,270 --> 00:01:53,381
She's not going to.

43
00:01:53,405 --> 00:01:54,632
Harvey, do you think
I want to be here?

44
00:01:54,656 --> 00:01:56,685
I tried to get interviews
at six different firms

45
00:01:56,709 --> 00:01:58,887
and every one of them
said the same thing:

46
00:01:58,911 --> 00:02:00,355
It's a bloodbath out there.

47
00:02:00,379 --> 00:02:02,190
Which means if I can't
bring business with me,

48
00:02:02,214 --> 00:02:03,424
I might as well move to Siberia

49
00:02:03,448 --> 00:02:05,143
because I'm never gonna
find a job in this city.

50
00:02:05,167 --> 00:02:06,227
- Louis...
- Harvey.

51
00:02:06,251 --> 00:02:08,452
I'm not askin' for the moon.

52
00:02:08,470 --> 00:02:10,482
Just three companies that
I brought to the firm myself

53
00:02:10,506 --> 00:02:14,225
when they were nothing.

54
00:02:16,845 --> 00:02:18,406
Let me talk to Jessica.

55
00:02:18,430 --> 00:02:21,432
Thank you.

56
00:02:34,113 --> 00:02:36,174
Harvey, you don't look busy.

57
00:02:36,198 --> 00:02:38,459
Would you like to attend
the international securities

58
00:02:38,483 --> 00:02:40,562
law symposium? That depends.

59
00:02:40,586 --> 00:02:42,296
Is it in Vegas, Miami, or Rio?

60
00:02:42,320 --> 00:02:44,966
- Poughkeepsie.
- Send Paul Porter.

61
00:02:44,990 --> 00:02:48,186
What can I do for you?

62
00:02:48,210 --> 00:02:49,571
I just saw Louis.

63
00:02:49,595 --> 00:02:52,663
No. He's not getting
any clients.

64
00:02:52,681 --> 00:02:54,109
He just wants three.

65
00:02:54,133 --> 00:02:55,833
Letting them go won't break us.

66
00:02:55,851 --> 00:02:58,196
No, it won't,
but it will open the floodgates

67
00:02:58,220 --> 00:02:59,581
for every partner

68
00:02:59,605 --> 00:03:01,533
that ever thought of leaving
and taking their clients.

69
00:03:01,557 --> 00:03:03,034
He's not every partner

70
00:03:03,058 --> 00:03:05,153
and he's worked his fingers
to the bone for both of us,

71
00:03:05,177 --> 00:03:06,871
and he's asking for a crumb.

72
00:03:06,895 --> 00:03:08,656
And I give him that crumb,
and next thing you know,

73
00:03:08,680 --> 00:03:10,542
all the cookies
in the cabinet are gone.

74
00:03:10,566 --> 00:03:11,682
You don't know that.

75
00:03:11,700 --> 00:03:14,429
I do know that instead
of talking about giving.

76
00:03:14,453 --> 00:03:16,187
Louis' clients away,

77
00:03:16,205 --> 00:03:18,499
you should be working
on keeping your own.

78
00:03:18,523 --> 00:03:21,692
Jessica, I'll find a way
to keep Versalife,

79
00:03:21,710 --> 00:03:23,671
but that has nothing
to do with Louis.

80
00:03:23,695 --> 00:03:25,006
We owe the man something.

81
00:03:25,030 --> 00:03:27,442
And I'm giving him something.

82
00:03:27,466 --> 00:03:30,678
My phone rings and he gets
a glowing recommendation

83
00:03:30,702 --> 00:03:34,149
instead of me saying that he
left after committing a felony.

84
00:03:34,173 --> 00:03:35,984
No one's gonna call
if he can't get in the door.

85
00:03:36,008 --> 00:03:40,595
That's on him, not on me.

86
00:03:51,773 --> 00:03:54,225
Are you sure we
should be doing this?

87
00:03:54,243 --> 00:03:55,369
You really want those vultures

88
00:03:55,393 --> 00:03:57,255
in bankruptcy
picking through his stuff?

89
00:03:57,279 --> 00:04:00,308
It just doesn't feel okay
going through his things.

90
00:04:00,332 --> 00:04:01,976
Rachel, you haven't heard from
him. I haven't heard from him.

91
00:04:02,000 --> 00:04:03,928
If we don't pack up his stuff,
who will?

92
00:04:03,952 --> 00:04:05,263
I guess you guys
had the same idea I did.

93
00:04:05,287 --> 00:04:06,931
Yeah.

94
00:04:06,955 --> 00:04:09,317
- He didn't take that either?
- No.

95
00:04:09,341 --> 00:04:10,602
I just cleaned it.

96
00:04:10,626 --> 00:04:11,936
It was smudged

97
00:04:11,960 --> 00:04:14,105
and I didn't want to give it
back to him dirty.

98
00:04:14,129 --> 00:04:16,491
He must have been
in such a hurry.

99
00:04:16,515 --> 00:04:20,328
He was in a hurry 'cause
he was ashamed.

100
00:04:20,352 --> 00:04:24,355
I want to just
get this over with.

101
00:04:30,445 --> 00:04:33,374
- Jessica, what...
- Am I doing here?

102
00:04:33,398 --> 00:04:36,961
I'm here to tell you
that I know you know the truth

103
00:04:36,985 --> 00:04:38,296
about Louis' resignation.

104
00:04:38,320 --> 00:04:39,714
I don't know...

105
00:04:39,738 --> 00:04:43,607
Yes, you do, and I'm guessing
you didn't like it.

106
00:04:43,625 --> 00:04:44,636
You're right.

107
00:04:44,660 --> 00:04:46,054
I didn't.

108
00:04:46,078 --> 00:04:48,857
Because I don't think
that he deserves to be fired.

109
00:04:48,881 --> 00:04:52,060
That's funny, because I think
you both deserve to be fired.

110
00:04:52,084 --> 00:04:54,896
- What do you...
- You knew what he did,

111
00:04:54,920 --> 00:04:56,531
and you said nothing.

112
00:04:56,555 --> 00:04:59,200
So that's why you're here.

113
00:04:59,224 --> 00:05:00,401
To fire me.

114
00:05:00,425 --> 00:05:04,512
No. I'm here to give you
a second chance.

115
00:05:20,529 --> 00:05:21,839
Those don't look
like my case files.

116
00:05:21,863 --> 00:05:24,315
They're not,
but I didn't come empty-handed.

117
00:05:24,333 --> 00:05:26,261
I got you somethin'. A job?

118
00:05:26,285 --> 00:05:29,097
General counsel
at Procter & Gamble.

119
00:05:29,121 --> 00:05:31,989
Procter & Gamble?
What is that, a joke?

120
00:05:32,007 --> 00:05:34,825
They're in Cincinnati, which is
like, American for "Siberia."

121
00:05:34,843 --> 00:05:35,904
It's American for

122
00:05:35,928 --> 00:05:37,828
"number 31 on the Fortune 500,"

123
00:05:37,846 --> 00:05:39,908
and it's a chance
to make a fresh start.

124
00:05:39,932 --> 00:05:41,242
Whose idea was this chance?

125
00:05:41,266 --> 00:05:42,911
Her majesty?

126
00:05:42,935 --> 00:05:44,478
Oh, yeah, I bet she loved that.

127
00:05:44,502 --> 00:05:45,697
Ship me off
and never see me again.

128
00:05:45,721 --> 00:05:48,533
Louis, it was my idea,
and you should take it.

129
00:05:48,557 --> 00:05:50,451
Well, would you take it?

130
00:05:50,475 --> 00:05:51,508
No way on earth.

131
00:05:51,526 --> 00:05:52,587
You know why?

132
00:05:52,611 --> 00:05:54,655
Because this is Rome,

133
00:05:54,679 --> 00:05:56,791
you're a gladiator, and so am I.

134
00:05:56,815 --> 00:05:58,760
Then be a gladiator.

135
00:05:58,784 --> 00:06:01,095
Take this job and fight
your way back here.

136
00:06:01,119 --> 00:06:03,331
I don't have to go to Cincinnati

137
00:06:03,355 --> 00:06:05,300
to fight my way back here.

138
00:06:05,324 --> 00:06:08,326
I can goddamn fight Jessica.

139
00:06:09,962 --> 00:06:13,641
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪

140
00:06:13,665 --> 00:06:16,978
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪

141
00:06:17,002 --> 00:06:20,148
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪

142
00:06:20,172 --> 00:06:23,851
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪

143
00:06:23,875 --> 00:06:26,821
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪

144
00:06:26,845 --> 00:06:30,825
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪

145
00:06:30,849 --> 00:06:32,293
♪ All right ♪

146
00:06:32,317 --> 00:06:37,799
♪ Suits 4x10 ♪ This Is Rome
Original Air Date on August 20, 2014

147
00:06:37,823 --> 00:06:38,640
♪ the greenback boogie ♪

148
00:06:38,641 --> 00:06:42,741
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man.

149
00:06:42,742 --> 00:06:44,118
You here to pick up your things.

150
00:06:44,119 --> 00:06:46,270
I'm here to pick
the three clients that are mine.

151
00:06:46,271 --> 00:06:49,423
Those clients, like everyone
this firm represents,

152
00:06:49,424 --> 00:06:51,719
belong to me, and there's
nothing you can do about it.

153
00:06:51,743 --> 00:06:53,988
Oh yes there is,
'cause pursuant to the by-laws,

154
00:06:54,012 --> 00:06:55,245
you're required
to inform clients

155
00:06:55,263 --> 00:06:56,858
of any attorney's departure.

156
00:06:56,882 --> 00:07:00,084
If you fail to do so prior
to me giving you formal notice,

157
00:07:00,102 --> 00:07:01,863
they're up for grabs.

158
00:07:01,887 --> 00:07:03,164
Well, you wrote the by-laws.

159
00:07:03,188 --> 00:07:04,789
I'll take your word
that's what they say.

160
00:07:04,806 --> 00:07:07,201
Oh, I see. You don't think
I can take 'em from you, huh?

161
00:07:07,225 --> 00:07:10,038
Well, I'm the one who brought
them in and answered their call

162
00:07:10,062 --> 00:07:11,062
at 4:00 in the morning,

163
00:07:11,063 --> 00:07:13,041
when all you did
was take your cut.

164
00:07:13,065 --> 00:07:14,509
Is that all I did?

165
00:07:14,533 --> 00:07:16,243
Yes, and that's
why I'm gonna win them,

166
00:07:16,267 --> 00:07:17,845
because I deserve them.

167
00:07:17,869 --> 00:07:20,465
And that's what it always
is with you, Louis, isn't it?

168
00:07:20,489 --> 00:07:21,516
What you deserve.

169
00:07:21,540 --> 00:07:22,850
You're goddamn right it is,

170
00:07:22,874 --> 00:07:24,635
and you have some nerve
tellin' me no

171
00:07:24,659 --> 00:07:25,853
after all I've done for you.

172
00:07:25,877 --> 00:07:29,474
What you've done
is break the law,

173
00:07:29,498 --> 00:07:32,360
and I'm still willing to give
you a good recommendation.

174
00:07:32,384 --> 00:07:35,786
I don't need your
bullshit recommendation.

175
00:07:35,804 --> 00:07:37,699
I need clients, and if
you're not gonna give 'em to me,

176
00:07:37,723 --> 00:07:39,724
you better strap in,
because I'm gonna take 'em.

177
00:07:45,514 --> 00:07:46,741
Louis.

178
00:07:46,765 --> 00:07:48,242
You haven't returned
any of my phone calls.

179
00:07:48,266 --> 00:07:50,611
I don't like contact
during transitional periods.

180
00:07:50,635 --> 00:07:52,330
But you didn't even say goodbye.

181
00:07:52,354 --> 00:07:53,554
What is there to say, Katrina?

182
00:07:53,572 --> 00:07:55,550
Well...

183
00:07:55,574 --> 00:07:57,335
When you're ready,

184
00:07:57,359 --> 00:07:58,809
I would love to take you out
for dinner.

185
00:07:58,827 --> 00:08:00,788
We can't do that.
You're on the other side now.

186
00:08:00,812 --> 00:08:02,557
- What are you talking about?
- I gave Jessica notice.

187
00:08:02,581 --> 00:08:03,591
I'm going after three clients.

188
00:08:03,615 --> 00:08:04,615
- Louis...
- No-no-no.

189
00:08:04,616 --> 00:08:05,727
We're gonna go do battle,

190
00:08:05,751 --> 00:08:06,844
and I do not want to put you
in the position

191
00:08:06,868 --> 00:08:07,845
to fraternize with the enemy.

192
00:08:07,869 --> 00:08:10,988
You're not the enemy, Louis.

193
00:08:11,006 --> 00:08:14,969
Jessica had me contact all
of your old clients in person.

194
00:08:14,993 --> 00:08:17,188
She what?

195
00:08:17,212 --> 00:08:19,190
You can't approach them.
It's over.

196
00:08:19,214 --> 00:08:21,976
I have to get going.

197
00:08:22,000 --> 00:08:23,778
Louis!

198
00:08:23,802 --> 00:08:25,196
I am so sorry.

199
00:08:25,220 --> 00:08:27,532
I didn't want to do it.
Don't be.

200
00:08:27,556 --> 00:08:30,952
If it had to be somebody,
I'm glad it was you.

201
00:08:30,976 --> 00:08:32,843
I'm in the middle of a merger.

202
00:08:32,861 --> 00:08:33,988
What's so important
that I had to come down

203
00:08:34,012 --> 00:08:35,179
to your shitty office?

204
00:08:35,197 --> 00:08:36,558
This used to be
your shitty office.

205
00:08:36,565 --> 00:08:38,515
And after that,
it belonged to six other people,

206
00:08:38,533 --> 00:08:39,994
five of whom are now gone.

207
00:08:40,018 --> 00:08:41,129
What's your point?

208
00:08:41,153 --> 00:08:43,714
That things can change
in the blink of an eye.

209
00:08:43,738 --> 00:08:45,716
- Louis.
- Yes, Louis.

210
00:08:45,740 --> 00:08:47,835
Took all of ten seconds
to scrape his name off the wall.

211
00:08:47,859 --> 00:08:50,638
How long do you think it's gonna
take Jessica to scrape off mine?

212
00:08:50,662 --> 00:08:51,862
What are you lookin' for, Mike?

213
00:08:51,863 --> 00:08:54,642
Harvey, Jessica
sees me as a huge problem.

214
00:08:54,666 --> 00:08:56,227
The solution is just
to get rid of me.

215
00:08:56,251 --> 00:08:57,445
I don't want that to happen, so

216
00:08:57,469 --> 00:08:59,564
I need to solve
an even bigger problem.

217
00:08:59,588 --> 00:09:01,849
And you want me
to give you a bigger problem.

218
00:09:01,873 --> 00:09:03,067
I just got back.
I need you to give me

219
00:09:03,091 --> 00:09:04,952
the biggest problem you've got.
Fine.

220
00:09:04,976 --> 00:09:09,740
Sterling Pharmaceuticals
is merging with Pfizer.

221
00:09:09,764 --> 00:09:11,793
Come on, smart guy.
You want to solve the problem?

222
00:09:11,817 --> 00:09:13,027
You better be able
to identify it.

223
00:09:13,051 --> 00:09:14,996
There is no problem. They merge.

224
00:09:15,020 --> 00:09:17,331
They only make up 26%
of the market.

225
00:09:17,355 --> 00:09:20,001
That's... that's not
over the limit for 10b-6.

226
00:09:20,025 --> 00:09:22,420
But?

227
00:09:22,444 --> 00:09:24,005
Shit.

228
00:09:24,029 --> 00:09:25,539
Versalife puts us
over the limit.

229
00:09:25,563 --> 00:09:26,707
We have to drop them.

230
00:09:26,731 --> 00:09:29,233
Unless we figure out a way
around 10b-6.

231
00:09:29,251 --> 00:09:31,545
Like I told Jessica I would.

232
00:09:31,569 --> 00:09:32,736
You told her that?

233
00:09:32,754 --> 00:09:34,381
Harvey, no one has ever
been able to do that.

234
00:09:34,405 --> 00:09:35,516
Listen to me.
You want to make a splash?

235
00:09:35,540 --> 00:09:39,510
Part the Red Sea.

236
00:09:43,682 --> 00:09:46,694
Oh, no. "Oh, no," what?

237
00:09:46,718 --> 00:09:47,945
You have that look on your face

238
00:09:47,969 --> 00:09:49,253
like you want me to have
some emotional conversation

239
00:09:49,271 --> 00:09:50,781
I don't feel like having.
You know what, Harvey?

240
00:09:50,805 --> 00:09:53,000
I just came in here to see
if you needed anything.

241
00:09:53,024 --> 00:09:56,504
- I don't.
- Okay, fine.

242
00:09:56,528 --> 00:09:59,073
Listen, I know that
this whole thing with Louis

243
00:09:59,097 --> 00:10:00,458
is upsetting you.

244
00:10:00,482 --> 00:10:01,598
No. What's upsetting me,
is you saying

245
00:10:01,616 --> 00:10:02,743
you're here to see
if I need anything

246
00:10:02,767 --> 00:10:04,128
when you really want
to talk about Louis.

247
00:10:04,152 --> 00:10:06,714
I'm worried about him.
He's in a really bad place.

248
00:10:06,738 --> 00:10:08,249
You think I don't know that?
That's why I tried to help him.

249
00:10:08,273 --> 00:10:09,717
I got him a job
on a silver platter

250
00:10:09,741 --> 00:10:11,385
and he threw it in my face.

251
00:10:11,409 --> 00:10:12,419
And he shouldn't have done that.

252
00:10:12,443 --> 00:10:13,804
Yeah. Then why are you here?

253
00:10:13,828 --> 00:10:19,310
Because I still think
we can help.

254
00:10:19,334 --> 00:10:20,450
- Donna...
- Harvey.

255
00:10:20,468 --> 00:10:22,930
You did a good thing
by getting him that job.

256
00:10:22,954 --> 00:10:25,289
It was the right instinct,
but it was the wrong city.

257
00:10:25,307 --> 00:10:27,201
Yeah, I can't get him anything
in New York.

258
00:10:27,225 --> 00:10:28,569
I'm not talking about New York.

259
00:10:28,593 --> 00:10:31,562
Then what the hell
are you talking about?

260
00:10:38,270 --> 00:10:40,748
Nice grouping.

261
00:10:40,772 --> 00:10:42,833
How'd you know I'd be here?

262
00:10:42,857 --> 00:10:44,458
Because you go mudding
when you're happy,

263
00:10:44,475 --> 00:10:46,120
and you come here when you're
looking to blow off steam.

264
00:10:46,144 --> 00:10:48,312
Well, I am blowing off steam,
Donna,

265
00:10:48,330 --> 00:10:51,259
and I'm not finished, so
unless you can handle a pistol,

266
00:10:51,283 --> 00:10:54,785
do me a favor please
and just leave me alone.

267
00:11:03,878 --> 00:11:05,162
Uh, how do you...

268
00:11:05,180 --> 00:11:07,358
Connecticut junior
pistol championship finalist.

269
00:11:07,382 --> 00:11:08,475
Three years in a row.

270
00:11:08,499 --> 00:11:09,777
What years?

271
00:11:09,801 --> 00:11:12,169
Ask me that again
and I will use this on you.

272
00:11:12,187 --> 00:11:13,480
Is there anything
that you can't do?

273
00:11:13,504 --> 00:11:15,172
No, there isn't.

274
00:11:15,190 --> 00:11:19,176
Including talking Harvey
into getting you another job.

275
00:11:19,194 --> 00:11:20,510
So where is it this time?

276
00:11:20,528 --> 00:11:22,423
Cincinnati? Minneapolis?

277
00:11:22,447 --> 00:11:24,041
Anchorage, Alaska?

278
00:11:24,065 --> 00:11:25,326
Boston.

279
00:11:25,350 --> 00:11:27,378
Sheila.

280
00:11:27,402 --> 00:11:28,763
Yes, Sheila.

281
00:11:28,787 --> 00:11:29,931
You got Harvey
to do this for me?

282
00:11:29,955 --> 00:11:32,356
I got him to give you his word
he will do it,

283
00:11:32,374 --> 00:11:33,935
but after you turned down
Cincinnati,

284
00:11:33,959 --> 00:11:36,053
he's not gonna make the call
unless you say you're on board.

285
00:11:36,077 --> 00:11:37,221
- I can't.
- What do you mean, you can't?

286
00:11:37,245 --> 00:11:39,696
Donna, Sheila values strength.

287
00:11:39,714 --> 00:11:41,392
She's gonna
see this as me coming to her

288
00:11:41,416 --> 00:11:43,177
at a time of weakness.

289
00:11:43,201 --> 00:11:45,313
Louis, you go to Boston
with the sole purpose

290
00:11:45,337 --> 00:11:50,735
of being with her, she's gonna
see that as a sign of love.

291
00:11:50,759 --> 00:11:54,071
Tell him to make the call.

292
00:11:54,095 --> 00:11:55,712
Okay, Kyle, I think
the question you have to ask is,

293
00:11:55,730 --> 00:11:58,859
"where do I see myself
in ten years,"

294
00:11:58,883 --> 00:12:04,799
and unfortunately, the answer
is, "not as a Harvard graduate."

295
00:12:04,823 --> 00:12:07,418
Idiot.

296
00:12:07,442 --> 00:12:10,471
Louis, what are you doing here?

297
00:12:10,495 --> 00:12:13,975
I'm here to take you back.

298
00:12:13,999 --> 00:12:16,477
I-I don't understand,
the way we lef...

299
00:12:16,501 --> 00:12:19,513
I don't care how we left it.

300
00:12:19,537 --> 00:12:22,933
Not a day has gone by that
I haven't thought of you,

301
00:12:22,957 --> 00:12:26,553
and I can't hold
it back anymore.

302
00:12:26,577 --> 00:12:28,689
Sheila, I love you,

303
00:12:28,713 --> 00:12:32,893
and I want us to be together.

304
00:12:32,917 --> 00:12:36,781
Louis, this is wonderful,
but it's... it's...

305
00:12:36,805 --> 00:12:39,000
It's just a lot to take in.

306
00:12:39,024 --> 00:12:41,758
To believe that
you're really ready to commit.

307
00:12:41,776 --> 00:12:43,371
Well, how's this for ready?

308
00:12:43,395 --> 00:12:45,289
I'm taking a job in Boston.
What?

309
00:12:45,313 --> 00:12:46,540
I quit Pearson Specter.

310
00:12:46,564 --> 00:12:49,460
Oh, my g...

311
00:12:49,484 --> 00:12:52,046
I can't believe it.

312
00:12:52,070 --> 00:12:53,130
You did all that for me?

313
00:12:53,154 --> 00:12:54,348
Yes.

314
00:12:54,372 --> 00:12:56,550
Well, I...

315
00:12:56,574 --> 00:13:00,855
- Well, what?
- I got a job in Boston for you.

316
00:13:00,879 --> 00:13:02,189
Louis, did you
make that decision

317
00:13:02,213 --> 00:13:04,392
before or after you
quit your old job?

318
00:13:04,416 --> 00:13:05,926
What difference does it make?

319
00:13:05,950 --> 00:13:07,784
It makes a huge difference.

320
00:13:07,802 --> 00:13:10,398
You don't call for six months,
and then...

321
00:13:10,422 --> 00:13:11,866
One day you wake up,
quit your job,

322
00:13:11,890 --> 00:13:14,368
and suddenly I'm supposed
to fill the hole in your life?

323
00:13:14,392 --> 00:13:15,792
No-no-no-no-no,
it's not like that.

324
00:13:15,810 --> 00:13:17,705
- Okay, then what is it?
- I mean, do you know

325
00:13:17,729 --> 00:13:20,324
how hard it was
for me to not call you?

326
00:13:20,348 --> 00:13:22,827
I was tryin' to move on.
Then why didn't you move on?

327
00:13:22,851 --> 00:13:25,246
Because I realized
that I don't need New York.

328
00:13:25,270 --> 00:13:28,549
I need you.

329
00:13:28,573 --> 00:13:30,918
Louis, geography was
the least of our problems.

330
00:13:30,942 --> 00:13:32,453
No, I know.

331
00:13:32,477 --> 00:13:34,788
And... and I want you to know
that I've come around on that.

332
00:13:34,812 --> 00:13:37,058
You don't "come around"
on children.

333
00:13:37,082 --> 00:13:39,483
I don't want them, and I'm not
going to change my mind.

334
00:13:39,501 --> 00:13:41,651
You don't have to,
because I've changed mine.

335
00:13:41,669 --> 00:13:43,514
Okay, and I believe
that you believe that, it's...

336
00:13:43,538 --> 00:13:44,899
Well, then if you b...

337
00:13:44,923 --> 00:13:46,567
I'm just sensing
that you don't know where I'm...

338
00:13:46,591 --> 00:13:47,657
Louis, when I asked
if you'd quit first,

339
00:13:47,675 --> 00:13:49,659
I was asking because if...

340
00:13:49,677 --> 00:13:51,305
If I believed that you
were really ready

341
00:13:51,329 --> 00:13:53,807
to give up children, I would run

342
00:13:53,831 --> 00:13:56,944
into your arms and never let go,

343
00:13:56,968 --> 00:13:59,146
but if you're doing this
because you're down and out...

344
00:13:59,170 --> 00:14:00,337
But that's just it.

345
00:14:00,355 --> 00:14:02,116
Do you understand that
I was going to change

346
00:14:02,140 --> 00:14:05,536
my entire work schedule
weeks ago for you?

347
00:14:05,560 --> 00:14:09,590
Before all this.
You were going to.

348
00:14:09,614 --> 00:14:11,926
But you didn't. Sheila, please.

349
00:14:11,950 --> 00:14:12,927
You have to understand
where I'm...

350
00:14:12,951 --> 00:14:15,296
It was good to see you, Louis.

351
00:14:15,320 --> 00:14:19,373
Please go.

352
00:14:32,525 --> 00:14:33,776
I see frustration.

353
00:14:33,800 --> 00:14:37,480
You see me getting
my ass kicked by FTC rule 10b-6.

354
00:14:37,481 --> 00:14:38,109
And?

355
00:14:38,110 --> 00:14:40,320
Harvey needs and update
and I don't have shit.

356
00:14:40,344 --> 00:14:41,344
And if you were Harvey
and he was Jessica,

357
00:14:41,362 --> 00:14:43,040
you'd say you're all over it.

358
00:14:43,064 --> 00:14:44,491
I can make that happen.

359
00:14:44,515 --> 00:14:45,709
I'm all over it. Good.

360
00:14:45,733 --> 00:14:47,184
Donna, send a bottle
of Johnnie Walker Blue

361
00:14:47,202 --> 00:14:48,722
to Jonathan Palmer,
and get him tickets

362
00:14:48,736 --> 00:14:50,047
to the next Sox game,

363
00:14:50,071 --> 00:14:51,999
and then find out
when his wife's birthday is,

364
00:14:52,023 --> 00:14:54,101
his kid's birthday,
his dog's birthday.

365
00:14:54,125 --> 00:14:56,053
- How am I supposed to...
- I don't care how you do it.

366
00:14:56,077 --> 00:14:57,271
Figure it the hell out.

367
00:14:57,295 --> 00:14:58,272
Harvey, this is
a thank you to him.

368
00:14:58,296 --> 00:14:59,540
Why are you so mad at me?

369
00:14:59,564 --> 00:15:01,559
It's not a thank you,
it's an apology for you

370
00:15:01,583 --> 00:15:03,536
talking me into getting him
to give Louis a job.

371
00:15:03,537 --> 00:15:04,205
What did he...

372
00:15:04,206 --> 00:15:05,567
He didn't show up
to the interview,

373
00:15:05,573 --> 00:15:07,206
and what's happening
with our Versalife problem?

374
00:15:07,207 --> 00:15:08,601
I'm all over it.

375
00:15:08,625 --> 00:15:10,192
Yeah, "all over it" means
you don't have dick.

376
00:15:10,210 --> 00:15:13,546
Next time I see you,
have something.

377
00:15:15,198 --> 00:15:17,610
Jonathan Palmer's in Boston.

378
00:15:17,634 --> 00:15:20,480
Harvey got Louis a job there
because of Sheila, didn't he?

379
00:15:20,504 --> 00:15:22,231
- Yes.
- Donna, if he didn't show up

380
00:15:22,255 --> 00:15:24,066
for the interview, it means
it didn't work with Sheila.

381
00:15:24,090 --> 00:15:26,519
Shit.

382
00:15:26,543 --> 00:15:29,956
He's gonna be devastated.

383
00:15:29,980 --> 00:15:31,690
You bring him his box
of stuff yet?

384
00:15:31,714 --> 00:15:34,160
No, but I'm going to right now.

385
00:15:34,184 --> 00:15:35,995
- Let me do it.
- Listen to me.

386
00:15:36,019 --> 00:15:37,497
Harvey's pissed at you
because you don't have anything

387
00:15:37,521 --> 00:15:38,581
and Louis needs me.

388
00:15:38,605 --> 00:15:39,916
Donna, I am here
because that man

389
00:15:39,940 --> 00:15:40,967
put my well-being
before his own.

390
00:15:40,991 --> 00:15:43,803
He gave up going
after Sheila for me.

391
00:15:43,827 --> 00:15:45,894
For all I know, that's why it
didn't work out for him up there

392
00:15:45,912 --> 00:15:47,840
and it's...

393
00:15:47,864 --> 00:15:51,500
The least I can do,
is comfort him when he's down.

394
00:15:53,503 --> 00:15:56,505
Go.

395
00:16:01,044 --> 00:16:02,355
Come in, come in.

396
00:16:02,379 --> 00:16:03,745
What are you doin' here?

397
00:16:03,763 --> 00:16:06,826
Stuff has been sitting
on your desk for days.

398
00:16:06,850 --> 00:16:08,917
I wanted you to have it.

399
00:16:08,935 --> 00:16:12,498
Okay. I'll need it
for my new office.

400
00:16:12,522 --> 00:16:13,666
You got a job?

401
00:16:13,690 --> 00:16:17,977
- Not yet, but I will.
- Oh.

402
00:16:19,312 --> 00:16:21,123
Order of the Coif.

403
00:16:21,147 --> 00:16:24,126
Yeah, look who
graduated magna cum laude.

404
00:16:24,150 --> 00:16:26,912
Summa, actually,
for all the good it'll do me.

405
00:16:26,936 --> 00:16:29,849
I know there's got to be
a story behind this key. Yeah?

406
00:16:29,873 --> 00:16:31,517
From one of your
first cases or...

407
00:16:31,541 --> 00:16:32,718
Mike, do me a favor, please.

408
00:16:32,742 --> 00:16:35,110
Just stop it, will you?
Stop what?

409
00:16:35,128 --> 00:16:36,138
Stop asking questions that
you already know the answers to

410
00:16:36,162 --> 00:16:37,390
just to stay here longer.

411
00:16:37,414 --> 00:16:38,424
- Louis, I'm not...
- You're not what?

412
00:16:38,448 --> 00:16:39,948
Examining me? Yes, you are.

413
00:16:39,966 --> 00:16:42,061
You're just making small talk
while you look around the room

414
00:16:42,085 --> 00:16:44,363
to see if there are any
sharp objects in the vicinity.

415
00:16:44,387 --> 00:16:45,898
That is not why I came here.

416
00:16:45,922 --> 00:16:49,235
Well, it wasn't to deliver
a box of my shit.

417
00:16:49,259 --> 00:16:51,937
Look, when I was drowning,
you threw me a lifeline, okay?

418
00:16:51,961 --> 00:16:53,539
Okay, well,
that's nice of you to say,

419
00:16:53,563 --> 00:16:55,825
and I appreciate you
bringing over my things,

420
00:16:55,849 --> 00:16:57,877
but they're not exactly
a lifeline.

421
00:16:57,901 --> 00:16:59,612
I heard about Boston.

422
00:16:59,636 --> 00:17:01,581
What'd you hear?

423
00:17:01,605 --> 00:17:04,306
That Harvey got you a job
and you didn't even show up.

424
00:17:04,324 --> 00:17:06,168
Well, why would I
when the love of my life

425
00:17:06,192 --> 00:17:07,887
rips out my heart
and then stomps on it?

426
00:17:07,911 --> 00:17:09,171
Louis, I'm just trying to help.

427
00:17:09,195 --> 00:17:12,124
Well, you can't!

428
00:17:12,148 --> 00:17:14,483
I don't have Sheila.

429
00:17:14,501 --> 00:17:18,097
I don't have a job.

430
00:17:18,121 --> 00:17:22,424
And right now I'd just
prefer to be alone.

431
00:17:34,304 --> 00:17:37,450
No.

432
00:17:37,474 --> 00:17:40,036
Well, I don't care what he says.

433
00:17:40,060 --> 00:17:43,656
15% of bullshit
Is still bullshit.

434
00:17:43,680 --> 00:17:44,707
Dick.

435
00:17:44,731 --> 00:17:46,258
What can I do for you, Mike?

436
00:17:46,282 --> 00:17:48,494
I can see you're busy, sir, so
I'll just jump right to it and...

437
00:17:48,518 --> 00:17:49,995
Hold it right there.

438
00:17:50,019 --> 00:17:52,598
If this is your asking me
for Rachel's hand in marriage,

439
00:17:52,622 --> 00:17:56,435
you know, you're goin'
about it the wrong way.

440
00:17:56,459 --> 00:17:58,721
Sir, I think if I were gonna
do that, I'd have the foresight

441
00:17:58,745 --> 00:18:01,057
to ask your wife
how to approach you first.

442
00:18:01,081 --> 00:18:02,498
Good answer.

443
00:18:04,134 --> 00:18:06,062
I'm actually here
about Louis Litt.

444
00:18:06,086 --> 00:18:07,246
Yeah, I heard he resigned.

445
00:18:07,270 --> 00:18:09,248
He did, and he's looking
for a job.

446
00:18:09,272 --> 00:18:11,484
A fellow like that
should have his pick.

447
00:18:11,508 --> 00:18:13,619
Well, the partnership
agreement prohibits him

448
00:18:13,643 --> 00:18:15,121
from taking clients.

449
00:18:15,145 --> 00:18:16,956
- Ooh, shit.
- Yeah.

450
00:18:16,980 --> 00:18:19,381
Ah, Jessica doesn't
play around, does she?

451
00:18:19,399 --> 00:18:20,480
She took his firstborn too?

452
00:18:20,483 --> 00:18:23,462
Look, I know it's bad
out there, but...

453
00:18:23,486 --> 00:18:24,580
Bad? It's the apocalypse.

454
00:18:24,604 --> 00:18:25,887
And I'm not runnin'
a soup kitchen.

455
00:18:25,905 --> 00:18:28,668
If a partner
can't bring me clients...

456
00:18:28,692 --> 00:18:30,035
What's that?

457
00:18:30,059 --> 00:18:33,205
These are Louis' billables
for the last 15 years.

458
00:18:33,229 --> 00:18:36,475
Mm.

459
00:18:36,499 --> 00:18:38,844
This guy ever sleep?
And he doesn't just bill.

460
00:18:38,868 --> 00:18:40,763
He trains the associates,
he publishes.

461
00:18:40,787 --> 00:18:42,848
He will give his life to you.

462
00:18:42,872 --> 00:18:45,685
And you want me to do this
because you're with my daughter?

463
00:18:45,709 --> 00:18:47,436
I want you to do this
because I've never asked you

464
00:18:47,460 --> 00:18:49,271
for a thing, and
the first time I am,

465
00:18:49,295 --> 00:18:51,390
it's a favor for someone else.

466
00:18:51,414 --> 00:18:53,325
That's the kind of man
that your daughter is with.

467
00:18:53,349 --> 00:18:55,394
So it's because you're
with my daughter?

468
00:18:55,418 --> 00:18:57,279
You're gonna see it
how you're gonna see it,

469
00:18:57,303 --> 00:18:59,064
but the real question is:

470
00:18:59,088 --> 00:19:04,120
What are you gonna
do about Louis Litt?

471
00:19:04,144 --> 00:19:08,207
I'll meet with him.

472
00:19:08,231 --> 00:19:09,458
But there's no guarantee.

473
00:19:09,482 --> 00:19:13,245
Well, that's all I can ask.

474
00:19:13,269 --> 00:19:16,182
You tell my daughter to give
her old man a call sometime.

475
00:19:16,206 --> 00:19:18,907
Yes, sir.

476
00:19:22,545 --> 00:19:24,690
Hey. You look happy.

477
00:19:24,714 --> 00:19:28,194
I am happy, because today
I did a good thing.

478
00:19:28,218 --> 00:19:30,146
You're going to let me paint
the bedroom robin's egg blue?

479
00:19:30,170 --> 00:19:31,764
I said I did a good thing.

480
00:19:31,788 --> 00:19:33,839
I didn't say
I did a ridiculous thing.

481
00:19:35,308 --> 00:19:38,037
I got Louis a job interview
in New York.

482
00:19:38,061 --> 00:19:39,795
- What?
- Mm-hmm.

483
00:19:39,813 --> 00:19:41,940
- That's amazing!
- Yeah.

484
00:19:41,964 --> 00:19:44,109
Oh, I love you.

485
00:19:44,133 --> 00:19:45,300
I'm gonna fix you a drink
to celebrate.

486
00:19:45,318 --> 00:19:47,213
Well, you should fix
one for yourself too,

487
00:19:47,237 --> 00:19:49,582
because I couldn't have
done it without you.

488
00:19:49,606 --> 00:19:51,333
What do you mean?

489
00:19:51,357 --> 00:19:53,586
I mean the interview's
with your dad.

490
00:19:53,610 --> 00:19:54,837
What?

491
00:19:54,861 --> 00:20:00,059
I went to your dad for Louis.

492
00:20:00,083 --> 00:20:03,395
What?

493
00:20:03,419 --> 00:20:05,397
It's really sweet.

494
00:20:05,421 --> 00:20:07,989
But...

495
00:20:08,007 --> 00:20:09,435
Let's just say there's a reason

496
00:20:09,459 --> 00:20:12,238
that I didn't go to my dad
to pay for law school.

497
00:20:12,262 --> 00:20:13,239
I thought you said it was
because you wanted

498
00:20:13,263 --> 00:20:14,523
to do it yourself.

499
00:20:14,547 --> 00:20:17,476
It is, but other people
don't have a problem

500
00:20:17,500 --> 00:20:18,944
going to their parents

501
00:20:18,968 --> 00:20:23,004
because they don't have to wait
for the other shoe to drop.

502
00:20:23,022 --> 00:20:24,817
What are you talking about?

503
00:20:24,841 --> 00:20:26,385
He's not gonna
give something for nothing.

504
00:20:26,409 --> 00:20:28,487
So you mean after this, he's
gonna want something from me?

505
00:20:28,511 --> 00:20:33,682
I don't know, but he's gonna
want something from someone.

506
00:20:33,700 --> 00:20:38,403
If it gets Louis a fresh
start, I really don't care.

507
00:20:46,392 --> 00:20:47,649
Oh man...

508
00:20:47,673 --> 00:20:49,317
Really? Yeah.

509
00:20:49,341 --> 00:20:50,435
- You got to be kiddin' me.
- No.

510
00:20:50,459 --> 00:20:51,719
You went there too?

511
00:20:51,743 --> 00:20:52,770
Every Tuesday
for the last five years.

512
00:20:52,794 --> 00:20:55,106
Oh. Wednesday.

513
00:20:55,130 --> 00:20:57,825
Chicken parm day.

514
00:20:57,849 --> 00:20:58,860
More like Christmas to me.

515
00:20:58,884 --> 00:21:00,227
- Oh, I believe it.
- Oh, Louis.

516
00:21:00,251 --> 00:21:01,663
This has been a pleasure,

517
00:21:01,687 --> 00:21:04,732
but it's time that we got
down to the crux of the matter.

518
00:21:04,756 --> 00:21:06,034
You want to know why I resigned.

519
00:21:06,058 --> 00:21:07,591
Well, I did call Jessica,

520
00:21:07,609 --> 00:21:09,621
and she gave you
a glowing recommendation,

521
00:21:09,645 --> 00:21:11,122
and we both know
that's bullshit.

522
00:21:11,146 --> 00:21:12,624
You want to know the truth.

523
00:21:12,648 --> 00:21:14,264
Did I say anything
about the truth?

524
00:21:14,283 --> 00:21:16,678
I'm just makin' sure you know
I know that it's bullshit.

525
00:21:16,702 --> 00:21:19,080
But my truth is,
I don't care why you left.

526
00:21:19,104 --> 00:21:21,082
All I care about
is what you're gonna take.

527
00:21:21,106 --> 00:21:22,317
What?

528
00:21:22,341 --> 00:21:24,819
You take one client,
I could give a shit.

529
00:21:24,843 --> 00:21:27,444
How big it is, and I'll make you
a senior partner on the spot.

530
00:21:27,462 --> 00:21:28,723
Wait a second.

531
00:21:28,747 --> 00:21:30,692
Mike Ross said

532
00:21:30,716 --> 00:21:32,977
that I was not required
to bring business.

533
00:21:33,001 --> 00:21:34,595
This isn't about business.

534
00:21:34,619 --> 00:21:36,364
This is about balls.

535
00:21:36,388 --> 00:21:37,598
I don't need another grinder,

536
00:21:37,622 --> 00:21:39,400
I need a lawyer
who can kick a door in,

537
00:21:39,424 --> 00:21:41,369
and the door in question
is Pearson Specter's.

538
00:21:41,393 --> 00:21:43,404
You want to see if I can break
my partnership agreement?

539
00:21:43,428 --> 00:21:44,906
You're damn right I do,

540
00:21:44,930 --> 00:21:48,733
because if you can't do that,
then what the hell good are you?

541
00:21:50,602 --> 00:21:51,882
You're no different
than Jessica.

542
00:21:52,771 --> 00:21:55,249
I'll take that as a compliment.

543
00:21:55,273 --> 00:21:56,283
Well, if you'll excuse me,

544
00:21:56,307 --> 00:21:58,386
Sylvia will validate you
on the way out.

545
00:21:58,410 --> 00:21:59,554
Yeah, well,

546
00:21:59,578 --> 00:22:02,123
Robert, this is New York.
I take a cab.

547
00:22:02,147 --> 00:22:05,116
See, that's my way
of saying "get the hell out."

548
00:22:13,258 --> 00:22:14,602
Well, how long
is a little while?

549
00:22:14,626 --> 00:22:15,970
Do you have any...

550
00:22:15,994 --> 00:22:17,138
Louis!

551
00:22:17,162 --> 00:22:18,973
Excuse me.

552
00:22:18,997 --> 00:22:20,692
Katrina, what are
you doing here?

553
00:22:20,716 --> 00:22:22,309
You know what I'm doing here.
This isn't your client anymore.

554
00:22:22,333 --> 00:22:24,529
You're prohibited
from contacting them.

555
00:22:24,553 --> 00:22:27,031
- I-I'm not here to see...
- Neubacher Capital?

556
00:22:27,055 --> 00:22:28,616
Yes, you are.

557
00:22:28,640 --> 00:22:30,251
Just like you're going
to go see Carver Tech

558
00:22:30,275 --> 00:22:32,486
and Blackthorne Simons.

559
00:22:32,510 --> 00:22:34,255
How do you know that?

560
00:22:34,279 --> 00:22:35,923
- Because they called me.
- What are they saying?

561
00:22:35,947 --> 00:22:37,308
Doesn't matter
what they're saying.

562
00:22:37,315 --> 00:22:38,876
It's plain as day
you're trying to poach them.

563
00:22:38,900 --> 00:22:40,494
- Does Jessica know?
- Not yet.

564
00:22:40,518 --> 00:22:41,829
But if you keep doing this,
she's gonna find out.

565
00:22:41,853 --> 00:22:43,047
Yeah, well, let her sue me,

566
00:22:43,071 --> 00:22:44,354
'cause I don't have
any other choice.

567
00:22:44,373 --> 00:22:45,383
What are you talking about?

568
00:22:45,407 --> 00:22:46,884
Robert Zane offered me
senior partner

569
00:22:46,908 --> 00:22:48,436
if I can break
the partnership agreement.

570
00:22:48,460 --> 00:22:51,139
That is a major law firm
in New York.

571
00:22:51,163 --> 00:22:52,473
I'm not gonna get
a better chance than that.

572
00:22:52,497 --> 00:22:53,497
Louis...

573
00:22:53,498 --> 00:22:55,059
Look, tell Jessica
if you have to.

574
00:22:55,083 --> 00:22:57,445
I don't want to get you
in trouble, okay?

575
00:22:57,469 --> 00:23:01,205
But I just lost my job.

576
00:23:01,223 --> 00:23:03,350
And I just lost the woman
I love for the second time,

577
00:23:03,374 --> 00:23:05,119
all in one week.

578
00:23:05,143 --> 00:23:08,545
Now I have this chance
to turn my life around...

579
00:23:08,563 --> 00:23:12,716
with this one client.

580
00:23:12,734 --> 00:23:16,164
I'm gonna take it.

581
00:23:16,188 --> 00:23:19,273
Louis.

582
00:23:22,444 --> 00:23:25,339
You want one client,
I'll give you one client.

583
00:23:25,363 --> 00:23:27,564
What? Wait, no...

584
00:23:27,582 --> 00:23:29,376
When you agreed to take me on,

585
00:23:29,400 --> 00:23:31,763
I swore that
I would be loyal to you,

586
00:23:31,787 --> 00:23:34,548
and if I'm not loyal now,
then I never was.

587
00:23:34,572 --> 00:23:37,151
Katrina, if you do this
and Jessica figures it out,

588
00:23:37,175 --> 00:23:38,886
she will fire you,

589
00:23:38,910 --> 00:23:40,655
and I cannot live with that.

590
00:23:40,679 --> 00:23:42,556
That won't matter
if you get the job

591
00:23:42,580 --> 00:23:46,250
and you take me with you.

592
00:23:46,268 --> 00:23:50,387
Give me the goddamn name.

593
00:23:51,857 --> 00:23:53,451
What?

594
00:23:53,475 --> 00:23:54,735
I'm gonna tell you something,

595
00:23:54,759 --> 00:23:57,038
and I don't want
you to overreact.

596
00:23:57,062 --> 00:23:59,406
From the look on your face,
I'm not makin' any promises.

597
00:23:59,430 --> 00:24:00,430
I just got an email from Louis.

598
00:24:00,449 --> 00:24:02,243
He's going after Versalife.

599
00:24:02,267 --> 00:24:03,961
- Get me Ray.
- What are you gonna do?

600
00:24:03,985 --> 00:24:05,579
Get me Ray!

601
00:24:05,603 --> 00:24:07,048
Harvey, it was just
a notification email.

602
00:24:07,072 --> 00:24:09,300
You don't even know where he is!
Yes, I do.

603
00:24:09,324 --> 00:24:10,468
What are you talking about?

604
00:24:10,492 --> 00:24:13,187
That notification is required
by the bylaws.

605
00:24:13,211 --> 00:24:14,806
He's doing it
at the last second.

606
00:24:14,830 --> 00:24:17,414
I guarantee you he's walking
in Versalife's door right now.

607
00:24:22,137 --> 00:24:25,289
Hell do you think you're doing?

608
00:24:25,307 --> 00:24:27,568
Not doing, did.
I just signed Versalife.

609
00:24:27,592 --> 00:24:29,603
- You have no right.
- Please, I have every right.

610
00:24:29,627 --> 00:24:31,962
Because when I quit, Jessica
only notified my clients,

611
00:24:31,980 --> 00:24:33,241
not yours,
because she didn't think

612
00:24:33,265 --> 00:24:34,798
I had enough balls
to go after you head-on.

613
00:24:34,816 --> 00:24:36,160
That wasn't her, that was me,

614
00:24:36,184 --> 00:24:38,445
because I didn't think
you would stoop this low.

615
00:24:38,469 --> 00:24:40,971
Oh, too bad. You exposed
your flank, now you're too late.

616
00:24:40,989 --> 00:24:42,973
Yeah, and you can see
the fear in my eyes.

617
00:24:42,991 --> 00:24:44,618
Excuse me.

618
00:24:44,642 --> 00:24:46,977
I told you, you're too late.

619
00:24:46,995 --> 00:24:48,556
To tell them an unemployed clown

620
00:24:48,580 --> 00:24:50,457
just sold them
a pile of bullshit?

621
00:24:50,481 --> 00:24:54,011
You mean the bullshit that you
have to drop them as a client?

622
00:24:54,035 --> 00:24:55,179
The Pfizer merger.

623
00:24:55,203 --> 00:24:57,348
FTC rule 10b-6.

624
00:24:57,372 --> 00:24:59,633
They were not pleased
that you kept them in the dark.

625
00:24:59,657 --> 00:25:01,686
- You are a son of a bitch.
- Who's the clown now?

626
00:25:01,710 --> 00:25:03,137
You're a son of a bitch.

627
00:25:03,161 --> 00:25:04,438
I'm only taking one client

628
00:25:04,462 --> 00:25:05,829
that you're gonna
have to drop anyway.

629
00:25:05,847 --> 00:25:06,997
The least you could do
is be a gentleman about it.

630
00:25:07,015 --> 00:25:09,110
A gentleman? I got you two jobs!

631
00:25:09,134 --> 00:25:11,913
Two jobs in Siberia!

632
00:25:11,937 --> 00:25:14,171
Out of pity.

633
00:25:14,189 --> 00:25:16,117
I got you those jobs
out of compassion,

634
00:25:16,141 --> 00:25:17,651
just like when
I fought for Jessica

635
00:25:17,675 --> 00:25:19,486
to not fire you
in the first place.

636
00:25:19,510 --> 00:25:21,205
But when I take Versalife back,

637
00:25:21,229 --> 00:25:24,231
it's gonna be without
any feeling for you at all.

638
00:25:32,023 --> 00:25:33,301
What happened?

639
00:25:33,325 --> 00:25:35,603
I lost them,
but I'm gonna get 'em back.

640
00:25:35,627 --> 00:25:38,556
What I want to know is
how the hell did Louis find out

641
00:25:38,580 --> 00:25:39,696
that we had to drop them?

642
00:25:39,714 --> 00:25:40,725
I don't know.

643
00:25:40,749 --> 00:25:41,893
People know shit.

644
00:25:41,917 --> 00:25:42,977
People don't know shit.

645
00:25:43,001 --> 00:25:45,947
People get told shit.

646
00:25:45,971 --> 00:25:47,281
Jessica, I know I wanted
to throw him a bone,

647
00:25:47,305 --> 00:25:49,683
but I did not tell him.

648
00:25:49,707 --> 00:25:51,352
I wasn't talkin' about you.

649
00:25:51,376 --> 00:25:52,853
I was talking about Mike Ross.

650
00:25:52,877 --> 00:25:54,238
Bullshit, Mike didn't tell...

651
00:25:54,262 --> 00:25:55,740
Tell me you didn't have him
working on Versalife.

652
00:25:55,764 --> 00:25:57,575
- That doesn't mean...
- I knew it.

653
00:25:57,599 --> 00:25:59,383
He was working on Versalife.

654
00:25:59,401 --> 00:26:01,746
He owes Louis
for bringing him back here.

655
00:26:01,770 --> 00:26:03,553
That is motive and opportunity.

656
00:26:03,572 --> 00:26:06,200
You just want him gone
by any means necessary.

657
00:26:06,224 --> 00:26:09,536
Oh, I think I have been
more than clear about that.

658
00:26:09,560 --> 00:26:10,560
Yeah, well, try another theory,

659
00:26:10,579 --> 00:26:11,973
because Mike
would never do this.

660
00:26:11,997 --> 00:26:13,707
Oh, there are a lot of things

661
00:26:13,731 --> 00:26:17,044
you never thought
Mike Ross would do.

662
00:26:17,068 --> 00:26:19,713
Sell out an old man's company.

663
00:26:19,737 --> 00:26:21,715
Get in bed with a billionaire.

664
00:26:21,739 --> 00:26:25,409
Cut his boss out of a deal.

665
00:26:25,427 --> 00:26:28,990
- Jessica...
- People change, Harvey.

666
00:26:29,014 --> 00:26:30,080
And to top it all off,

667
00:26:30,098 --> 00:26:33,394
Louis is taking Versalife
to Robert Zane.

668
00:26:33,418 --> 00:26:36,397
Mike Ross' future father-in-law.

669
00:26:36,421 --> 00:26:39,390
Why don't you think about that?

670
00:26:49,951 --> 00:26:53,603
Mike, I need to know
what you have on Versalife.

671
00:27:00,795 --> 00:27:03,140
- It was me.
- What was you?

672
00:27:03,164 --> 00:27:04,358
Louis going after them
is my fault.

673
00:27:04,382 --> 00:27:05,983
- What did you...
- I went to Robert Zane

674
00:27:06,001 --> 00:27:07,895
and I asked him
to give Louis a job.

675
00:27:07,919 --> 00:27:09,263
That's it?

676
00:27:09,287 --> 00:27:11,032
You didn't tell him
about Versalife?

677
00:27:11,056 --> 00:27:13,401
Of course not, wh...
You think I would do that?

678
00:27:13,425 --> 00:27:14,485
Never mind what I think.

679
00:27:14,509 --> 00:27:16,293
You went to one
of our biggest competitors

680
00:27:16,311 --> 00:27:17,989
and put 'em together
with a desperate Louis.

681
00:27:18,013 --> 00:27:20,241
I did it because Louis
was desperate, all right?

682
00:27:20,265 --> 00:27:21,608
I went to see him the other day
to bring him his stuff,

683
00:27:21,632 --> 00:27:23,077
it was just... The other day?

684
00:27:23,101 --> 00:27:25,713
You're telling me when you
were supposed to be helping us

685
00:27:25,737 --> 00:27:27,114
keep our client,

686
00:27:27,138 --> 00:27:29,450
you were busy giving them
to Louis on a silver platter?

687
00:27:29,474 --> 00:27:31,886
I was, but I also figured out
how to get them back.

688
00:27:31,910 --> 00:27:33,504
- Why didn't you tell me then?
- 'Cause I was trying to think

689
00:27:33,528 --> 00:27:34,672
of a better option.

690
00:27:34,696 --> 00:27:36,313
What the hell's
wrong with this option?

691
00:27:36,331 --> 00:27:38,475
It involves going
to Walter Gillis.

692
00:27:47,825 --> 00:27:50,304
Well, look
who decided to drop by.

693
00:27:50,328 --> 00:27:52,023
The man who lost me my company

694
00:27:52,047 --> 00:27:54,308
and his partner
who tore it to shreds.

695
00:27:54,332 --> 00:27:56,333
Walter, I understand
how you must feel.

696
00:27:56,351 --> 00:27:57,667
So, why are you here?

697
00:27:57,686 --> 00:27:59,447
Because we have a proposition
for you.

698
00:27:59,471 --> 00:28:01,532
Does it involve an apology?

699
00:28:01,556 --> 00:28:04,725
It is an apology.

700
00:28:10,532 --> 00:28:12,182
You want me to buy Versalife?

701
00:28:12,200 --> 00:28:15,046
We want you to buy
a division of Versalife.

702
00:28:15,070 --> 00:28:16,520
The division
that makes that drug.

703
00:28:16,538 --> 00:28:18,832
They've been working on
anti-addiction meds for years.

704
00:28:18,856 --> 00:28:21,102
Look at the results.
This one works.

705
00:28:21,126 --> 00:28:23,527
But it's a money-loser
and it's gonna take years.

706
00:28:23,545 --> 00:28:25,056
They don't have
the capital, the patience,

707
00:28:25,080 --> 00:28:26,807
or the will. But you do.

708
00:28:26,831 --> 00:28:29,276
And let me guess, you two are
here out of the goodness

709
00:28:29,300 --> 00:28:31,479
of your hearts.
You want the truth?

710
00:28:31,503 --> 00:28:34,371
He'd be here whether this was
for his own good or not.

711
00:28:34,389 --> 00:28:37,234
For me, I'm here
because it gets me out of a jam.

712
00:28:37,258 --> 00:28:38,859
So you can stick it to us
if you want to,

713
00:28:38,876 --> 00:28:41,711
but if you do that...

714
00:28:41,730 --> 00:28:43,624
You're gonna miss the chance
to save a lot of other people

715
00:28:43,648 --> 00:28:44,881
just like Phillip.

716
00:28:44,899 --> 00:28:47,411
Don't ever talk to me
about Phillip again.

717
00:28:47,435 --> 00:28:48,829
- Walter...
- No.

718
00:28:48,853 --> 00:28:52,299
This is how all this started,
with you using my son.

719
00:28:52,323 --> 00:28:55,202
No, I'm the one
who used your son.

720
00:28:55,226 --> 00:28:57,805
I used him to get control
of your company,

721
00:28:57,829 --> 00:28:59,974
but everything Mike did
from the second he met you

722
00:28:59,998 --> 00:29:01,398
was to save your company,

723
00:29:01,416 --> 00:29:04,011
because when it comes
to caring about people,

724
00:29:04,035 --> 00:29:05,146
he's twice the man that I am,

725
00:29:05,170 --> 00:29:07,148
and by the way,
he never gave up on you,

726
00:29:07,172 --> 00:29:08,766
and he never sold you out.

727
00:29:08,790 --> 00:29:10,017
Bullshit.

728
00:29:10,041 --> 00:29:11,051
You're right, it is.

729
00:29:11,075 --> 00:29:14,221
Mike, no.

730
00:29:14,245 --> 00:29:16,023
The truth is,
is that I gave you my word.

731
00:29:16,047 --> 00:29:18,609
I told you I would never sell
you out and then I got into bed

732
00:29:18,633 --> 00:29:20,194
with someone
that I never should have trusted

733
00:29:20,218 --> 00:29:22,396
and I lost you your company.
Yes, you did.

734
00:29:22,420 --> 00:29:23,864
And that company
was your family.

735
00:29:23,888 --> 00:29:27,001
It gave you purpose,
but you still have money,

736
00:29:27,025 --> 00:29:28,619
and this is a purpose.

737
00:29:28,643 --> 00:29:32,006
Walter, if you don't want
to do this, I get it.

738
00:29:32,030 --> 00:29:34,074
But I need you to understand
that the only reason

739
00:29:34,098 --> 00:29:37,744
I even thought to come to you
in the first place

740
00:29:37,768 --> 00:29:39,346
is that I'm gonna regret
what I did to you

741
00:29:39,370 --> 00:29:43,407
for the rest of my life.

742
00:29:49,309 --> 00:29:50,309
Can I come in.

743
00:29:50,323 --> 00:29:52,107
Of course.

744
00:29:53,657 --> 00:29:56,942
I hope you're not
furious with me.

745
00:29:56,961 --> 00:29:59,445
I'm not mad.

746
00:29:59,463 --> 00:30:00,890
You're not?

747
00:30:00,914 --> 00:30:02,615
No.

748
00:30:02,633 --> 00:30:04,384
Well, good.

749
00:30:05,469 --> 00:30:06,813
I wanted to... Thank you

750
00:30:06,837 --> 00:30:08,954
for setting up that meeting
with Robert Zane.

751
00:30:08,973 --> 00:30:10,623
I just hope you understand
that if I had a choice,

752
00:30:10,641 --> 00:30:11,985
I never would have gone
after Versalife,

753
00:30:12,009 --> 00:30:13,459
but I had no choice.

754
00:30:13,477 --> 00:30:15,739
Louis, we took them back.

755
00:30:15,763 --> 00:30:17,963
What?

756
00:30:17,982 --> 00:30:19,743
But you had to drop them.

757
00:30:19,767 --> 00:30:21,995
Not anymore.

758
00:30:22,019 --> 00:30:24,881
We convinced them to sell
their trial drug division.

759
00:30:24,905 --> 00:30:27,973
Of course. You drop a drain
on their earnings,

760
00:30:27,992 --> 00:30:29,386
stock price
goes right through the roof.

761
00:30:29,410 --> 00:30:31,338
And their market share
falls below the threshold.

762
00:30:31,362 --> 00:30:32,589
But who the hell would buy it?

763
00:30:32,613 --> 00:30:35,748
Walter Gillis.

764
00:30:42,756 --> 00:30:45,068
Of course, Walter Gillis.

765
00:30:45,092 --> 00:30:46,826
- Louis, listen...
- Mike.

766
00:30:46,844 --> 00:30:48,828
You won.

767
00:30:48,846 --> 00:30:50,857
You're a brilliant lawyer.

768
00:30:50,881 --> 00:30:52,642
You are a brilliant lawyer.

769
00:30:52,666 --> 00:30:54,778
Yeah, I'm a brilliant lawyer
who's never gonna work again.

770
00:30:54,802 --> 00:30:56,029
Hey, stop.

771
00:30:56,053 --> 00:30:58,981
That is not true.

772
00:30:59,005 --> 00:31:00,750
Look... look... look
at everything that you have.

773
00:31:00,774 --> 00:31:03,175
A Harvard law diploma,
summa cum laude,

774
00:31:03,193 --> 00:31:04,587
Order of the Coif.

775
00:31:04,611 --> 00:31:06,956
Those are the credentials
of a supreme court justice.

776
00:31:06,980 --> 00:31:09,659
Nah, that and 2 bucks will
get me a seat on the subway,

777
00:31:09,683 --> 00:31:12,595
but thank you
for having the decency

778
00:31:12,619 --> 00:31:14,214
to tell me in person.

779
00:31:14,238 --> 00:31:15,465
Louis, come on.

780
00:31:15,489 --> 00:31:16,522
Let me... let me...

781
00:31:16,540 --> 00:31:17,767
Let me stick around for a while.

782
00:31:17,791 --> 00:31:19,024
We'll have... we'll have a couple
of drinks.

783
00:31:19,043 --> 00:31:23,973
You... you can tell me the story
about that key.

784
00:31:23,997 --> 00:31:26,409
Mike, I know
what you're tryin' to do.

785
00:31:26,433 --> 00:31:28,812
Now's not the time.

786
00:31:28,836 --> 00:31:31,838
Please go.

787
00:31:51,358 --> 00:31:55,805
Come in.

788
00:31:55,829 --> 00:31:57,563
You're not Louis Litt.

789
00:31:57,581 --> 00:32:00,176
No, I'm not. But if you're
expecting him to show up,

790
00:32:00,200 --> 00:32:02,645
it's gonna be a long wait.
You here to take his spot?

791
00:32:02,669 --> 00:32:05,404
I'll give you senior partner
right now.

792
00:32:05,422 --> 00:32:08,551
I'm here to tell you
you're not getting Versalife.

793
00:32:08,575 --> 00:32:10,553
I'm sorry,
I don't know who that is.

794
00:32:10,577 --> 00:32:12,822
It's the company
you tried to poach from me.

795
00:32:12,846 --> 00:32:15,080
- You seem upset.
- I'm not upset.

796
00:32:15,099 --> 00:32:16,893
I just wanted to remind you
you once told me

797
00:32:16,917 --> 00:32:19,662
I was a piece of shit for using
your daughter against you,

798
00:32:19,686 --> 00:32:21,998
but now you turn around
and use Louis against me?

799
00:32:22,022 --> 00:32:24,233
- No, that's not the same.
- It is to me.

800
00:32:24,257 --> 00:32:27,337
I may fight with him,
but he's still my family.

801
00:32:27,361 --> 00:32:30,262
- Then why did he leave?
- That's between me and Louis.

802
00:32:30,280 --> 00:32:34,243
I wanted Versalife, but it's
not worth gloating over.

803
00:32:34,267 --> 00:32:35,845
So why are you really here,
Harvey?

804
00:32:35,869 --> 00:32:37,797
I'm here to ask you
to take Louis anyway.

805
00:32:37,821 --> 00:32:39,349
And why would I do that?

806
00:32:39,373 --> 00:32:40,884
'Cause you're a smart man.

807
00:32:40,908 --> 00:32:44,521
If you do it, I'll owe you one.

808
00:32:44,545 --> 00:32:46,612
I don't need you owin' me one.

809
00:32:46,630 --> 00:32:49,159
Why don't you take the night
to think about it?

810
00:32:49,183 --> 00:32:50,426
'Cause if there's one thing
I've learned,

811
00:32:50,450 --> 00:32:53,970
you can never have
too many favors in the bank.

812
00:33:01,645 --> 00:33:02,939
You wanted to see me?

813
00:33:02,963 --> 00:33:05,492
I heard about Versalife.

814
00:33:05,516 --> 00:33:08,328
Good work.

815
00:33:08,352 --> 00:33:09,746
It wasn't you.

816
00:33:09,770 --> 00:33:11,280
No, it wasn't.

817
00:33:11,304 --> 00:33:13,950
You know I thought it was you.

818
00:33:13,974 --> 00:33:15,218
Harvey didn't tell me,

819
00:33:15,242 --> 00:33:17,504
but I didn't just
fall off the turnip truck.

820
00:33:17,528 --> 00:33:20,557
No, you didn't.

821
00:33:20,581 --> 00:33:22,147
What?

822
00:33:22,166 --> 00:33:26,151
Every damn time I think
there's no upside to having you,

823
00:33:26,170 --> 00:33:27,486
you do some shit
to make me think

824
00:33:27,504 --> 00:33:30,266
it's actually nice
to have you around.

825
00:33:30,290 --> 00:33:31,684
So, we're good?

826
00:33:31,708 --> 00:33:36,406
We're good after you
bill a few more hours tonight.

827
00:33:36,430 --> 00:33:37,974
Well, that's gonna
have to wait until later,

828
00:33:37,998 --> 00:33:41,166
because I am definitely
going out to celebrate.

829
00:33:41,185 --> 00:33:42,862
You've earned it.

830
00:33:42,886 --> 00:33:47,006
Jessica.

831
00:33:47,024 --> 00:33:51,777
She did what Harvey
would have done for you.

832
00:34:03,407 --> 00:34:05,691
- Jessica.
- Katrina.

833
00:34:05,709 --> 00:34:07,003
Is this about the...

834
00:34:07,027 --> 00:34:09,389
I can either fire you...

835
00:34:09,413 --> 00:34:11,530
or you can resign.

836
00:34:11,548 --> 00:34:14,811
The choice is yours.

837
00:34:14,835 --> 00:34:15,945
You know?

838
00:34:15,969 --> 00:34:18,180
I know.

839
00:34:18,204 --> 00:34:21,150
Then why are you being
so nice about it?

840
00:34:21,174 --> 00:34:23,542
Because letting you go
is enough.

841
00:34:23,560 --> 00:34:26,378
And you also don't want
to antagonize me,

842
00:34:26,396 --> 00:34:28,791
since I'll be working
for Robert Zane.

843
00:34:28,815 --> 00:34:31,744
You haven't heard?

844
00:34:31,768 --> 00:34:35,331
We got Versalife back.

845
00:34:35,355 --> 00:34:37,467
Louis won't be going to Zane,

846
00:34:37,491 --> 00:34:42,705
and neither will you.

847
00:34:42,729 --> 00:34:45,842
I wish you luck.

848
00:34:45,866 --> 00:34:47,232
You'll have my letter
of resignation on your desk

849
00:34:47,251 --> 00:34:48,251
in the morning.

850
00:35:24,362 --> 00:35:25,405
What took you so long?

851
00:35:25,429 --> 00:35:26,957
What are you,
the bathroom monitor?

852
00:35:26,981 --> 00:35:29,599
Well, if I were, I'd say you'd
gone three times in an hour.

853
00:35:29,617 --> 00:35:32,269
Yes,
and this is our third drink.

854
00:35:32,287 --> 00:35:34,414
You know they have medicine
for that, right?

855
00:35:34,438 --> 00:35:35,438
You saying I'm old?

856
00:35:35,439 --> 00:35:36,717
Yes, but I'm also saying

857
00:35:36,741 --> 00:35:38,135
I know you haven't been goin'
to the bathroom.

858
00:35:38,159 --> 00:35:39,803
All right, you want the truth?

859
00:35:39,827 --> 00:35:40,921
I've been calling Donna.

860
00:35:40,945 --> 00:35:42,806
Oh my God, that is so great.

861
00:35:42,830 --> 00:35:45,025
You guys finally
decided to take the plunge.

862
00:35:45,049 --> 00:35:47,427
I wanted to know
if Robert Zane called me back.

863
00:35:47,451 --> 00:35:48,451
Called you back about what?

864
00:35:48,469 --> 00:35:50,364
I asked him to hire Louis
anyway.

865
00:35:50,388 --> 00:35:52,099
- You're kidding.
- I'm not.

866
00:35:52,123 --> 00:35:53,790
I even told him
if he did I'd owe him one.

867
00:35:53,808 --> 00:35:56,537
- Hmm.
- What?

868
00:35:56,561 --> 00:35:57,872
Oh, I'm just tryin'
to figure out at what point

869
00:35:57,896 --> 00:36:00,630
in the last week
you decided to become a pussy.

870
00:36:00,648 --> 00:36:04,111
Oh, so doing something nice
for someone makes you a pussy?

871
00:36:04,135 --> 00:36:05,746
- I didn't say that exactly.
- Yes, you did.

872
00:36:05,770 --> 00:36:07,137
Let's just go through
some of the nice things

873
00:36:07,155 --> 00:36:08,448
you've done for people.
Okay, you know what, Harvey?

874
00:36:08,472 --> 00:36:09,717
Guilty as charged.

875
00:36:09,741 --> 00:36:12,720
I am nice, and if that makes me
a pussy, then so be it.

876
00:36:12,744 --> 00:36:15,089
Then it's settled:
You're a nice pussy.

877
00:36:15,113 --> 00:36:17,892
Miss, can I get a cosmo
here for my friend?

878
00:36:17,916 --> 00:36:19,393
Go ahead, order another drink.

879
00:36:19,417 --> 00:36:20,561
Just be careful,
'cause you're gonna

880
00:36:20,585 --> 00:36:22,129
be in the bathroom
in another five minutes.

881
00:36:22,153 --> 00:36:23,731
You going back
to the prostate again?

882
00:36:23,755 --> 00:36:26,100
What, like you've never
repeated jokes before?

883
00:36:26,124 --> 00:36:28,491
- I have no idea what...
- What I'm talking about?

884
00:36:28,509 --> 00:36:29,826
Let's see uh, "you see",

885
00:36:29,844 --> 00:36:31,494
that's funny,
because blah-blah-blah,"

886
00:36:31,512 --> 00:36:33,807
or "by blah-blah-blah,
I mean blah-blah-blah."

887
00:36:33,831 --> 00:36:35,776
- Okay, I get it.
- Oh, I'm just getting started.

888
00:36:35,800 --> 00:36:37,695
I could do this all night.
Hey, you know what?

889
00:36:37,719 --> 00:36:38,999
Now I have to go
to the bathroom.

890
00:36:39,003 --> 00:36:41,504
Go for it.
Take your time, no rush.

891
00:36:41,522 --> 00:36:45,525
If it hurts, call someone.

892
00:36:56,738 --> 00:36:59,099
Louis, what are you doing here?

893
00:36:59,123 --> 00:37:01,602
I'm waiting for Harvey.

894
00:37:01,626 --> 00:37:05,105
Harvey's not here.

895
00:37:05,129 --> 00:37:06,557
Then you'll have to do.

896
00:37:06,581 --> 00:37:08,275
Look, Louis,

897
00:37:08,299 --> 00:37:10,611
I know you've been
through a lot,

898
00:37:10,635 --> 00:37:11,895
but Harvey's gonna...

899
00:37:11,919 --> 00:37:14,448
I don't give a shit
what Harvey's gonna do.

900
00:37:14,472 --> 00:37:18,475
Okay, you're scaring me.

901
00:37:25,683 --> 00:37:27,962
You know what an Oscar
looks like?

902
00:37:27,986 --> 00:37:30,831
- What?
- Academy Award. Bald guy.

903
00:37:30,855 --> 00:37:33,417
I mean, of course
we all know what it looks like,

904
00:37:33,441 --> 00:37:35,336
but especially you,
you're an actress.

905
00:37:35,360 --> 00:37:36,726
It's the highest honor
in your field.

906
00:37:36,744 --> 00:37:39,473
I mean, of course you don't need
to be told what it is.

907
00:37:39,497 --> 00:37:42,042
- What are you talking about?
- The highest academic honor

908
00:37:42,066 --> 00:37:46,263
in Harvard law is
the Order of the Coif.

909
00:37:46,287 --> 00:37:48,932
You don't get a trophy.

910
00:37:48,956 --> 00:37:51,185
You get three things.

911
00:37:51,209 --> 00:37:54,605
You get a parchment
to hang on your wall,

912
00:37:54,629 --> 00:37:57,691
a medal to wear at graduation,

913
00:37:57,715 --> 00:38:00,250
and this.

914
00:38:00,268 --> 00:38:04,921
Now, this key
doesn't say "Order of the Coif."

915
00:38:04,939 --> 00:38:06,423
It doesn't say anything.

916
00:38:06,441 --> 00:38:07,901
It's just a symbol.

917
00:38:07,925 --> 00:38:09,236
What does that have
to do with Harvey?

918
00:38:09,260 --> 00:38:10,927
It doesn't.
It has to do with Mike.

919
00:38:10,945 --> 00:38:13,374
You know what, Louis?
It's been a long day, can...

920
00:38:13,398 --> 00:38:17,711
It's about to get longer.

921
00:38:17,735 --> 00:38:21,248
See, Mike asked me about this.

922
00:38:21,272 --> 00:38:24,941
And I thought he was...

923
00:38:24,959 --> 00:38:29,189
I thought he was trying to get
my mind off of my problems,

924
00:38:29,213 --> 00:38:31,258
but then he did it again.

925
00:38:31,282 --> 00:38:33,927
And it got me to thinking:

926
00:38:33,951 --> 00:38:38,482
Mike graduated magna cum laude.

927
00:38:38,506 --> 00:38:42,769
He's in Order of the Coif.

928
00:38:42,793 --> 00:38:45,322
But he didn't recognize this.

929
00:38:45,346 --> 00:38:47,658
So he forgot a stupid key.

930
00:38:47,682 --> 00:38:50,544
Mike Ross doesn't forget
anything.

931
00:38:50,568 --> 00:38:52,779
See, the reason
he didn't recognize this

932
00:38:52,803 --> 00:38:58,168
was because he never got one,
because...

933
00:38:58,192 --> 00:39:01,478
He didn't go to Harvard.

934
00:39:01,496 --> 00:39:03,646
Louis, we've been
down this road before.

935
00:39:03,664 --> 00:39:05,059
Mike is the Harvard database.

936
00:39:05,083 --> 00:39:06,844
But he's not in the yearbook,

937
00:39:06,868 --> 00:39:08,262
and according
to his credit report,

938
00:39:08,286 --> 00:39:10,848
his address during his law
school years was in New York.

939
00:39:10,872 --> 00:39:14,657
He even paid rent the first
of the month in person.

940
00:39:14,675 --> 00:39:17,971
- Well, I'm sure there's an...
- Sit down!

941
00:39:17,995 --> 00:39:21,498
Last year, you told me not to
tell Sheila about Mike's file.

942
00:39:21,516 --> 00:39:24,695
You acted like you cared
about me.

943
00:39:24,719 --> 00:39:28,031
You didn't give a shit about me.

944
00:39:28,055 --> 00:39:29,983
You cared about you!

945
00:39:30,007 --> 00:39:31,007
And Harvey! No.

946
00:39:31,025 --> 00:39:32,202
- And Mike!
- No.

947
00:39:32,226 --> 00:39:33,921
- And Jessica!
- Louis, that's not true!

948
00:39:33,945 --> 00:39:36,323
Well, let's call Sheila
right now.

949
00:39:36,347 --> 00:39:38,375
I know all of the numbers
by heart.

950
00:39:38,399 --> 00:39:40,761
I mean, she may not
be interested in me anymore,

951
00:39:40,785 --> 00:39:43,330
but she will definitely be
interested in a fraud claiming

952
00:39:43,354 --> 00:39:46,323
that he went to Harvard.

953
00:39:52,747 --> 00:39:57,033
I'm sorry.

954
00:39:57,051 --> 00:40:02,372
You're sorry?

955
00:40:02,390 --> 00:40:06,393
You've been lying to me
since the day Mike Ross arrived.

956
00:40:08,729 --> 00:40:12,126
I knew Harvey and Jessica
never really accepted me,

957
00:40:12,150 --> 00:40:14,461
but I thought
you were different.

958
00:40:14,485 --> 00:40:16,463
I thought you were my friend.

959
00:40:16,487 --> 00:40:21,391
- I am your friend, Louis.
- No, you're not.

960
00:40:21,409 --> 00:40:26,807
And don't you ever
say that to me again.

961
00:40:26,831 --> 00:40:29,376
Where are you going?

962
00:40:29,400 --> 00:40:33,537
To see your friend Jessica.

963
00:40:39,427 --> 00:40:42,429
Louis knows.

964
00:40:48,803 --> 00:40:50,397
Louis.

965
00:40:50,421 --> 00:40:51,949
I know you're a stickler
for the rules,

966
00:40:51,973 --> 00:40:54,424
so I figured I'd just
come by to return my I.D.

967
00:40:54,442 --> 00:40:55,758
You want an explanation.

968
00:40:55,776 --> 00:40:57,404
I want to see you
perp walked through the bullpen

969
00:40:57,428 --> 00:41:01,175
with your pretty little jacket
draped over your handcuffs.

970
00:41:01,199 --> 00:41:04,878
But until then, yeah,
I'll take an explanation.

971
00:41:04,902 --> 00:41:08,882
When I found out the truth
about Mike Ross,

972
00:41:08,906 --> 00:41:11,218
it had already been done.

973
00:41:11,242 --> 00:41:13,854
By Harvey?

974
00:41:13,878 --> 00:41:17,307
Right after he
made senior partner over me?

975
00:41:17,331 --> 00:41:19,560
That's when he hired the fraud?

976
00:41:19,584 --> 00:41:21,061
That's the correct timeline,
right?

977
00:41:21,085 --> 00:41:22,646
Yes.

978
00:41:22,670 --> 00:41:24,064
So instead of turning him in,

979
00:41:24,088 --> 00:41:26,233
you cover it up. Louis-

980
00:41:26,257 --> 00:41:28,602
and the one time
that I do something...

981
00:41:28,626 --> 00:41:32,573
you don't cover it up at all.

982
00:41:32,597 --> 00:41:34,241
You throw me to the wolves.

983
00:41:34,265 --> 00:41:36,376
I saved you from the wolves.

984
00:41:36,400 --> 00:41:39,162
Then I ask you
for the smallest gesture,

985
00:41:39,186 --> 00:41:41,448
just to allow my career
to continue with dignity,

986
00:41:41,472 --> 00:41:46,276
and you couldn't muster
the tiniest shred of compassion.

987
00:41:48,412 --> 00:41:50,057
What do you want me to say?

988
00:41:50,081 --> 00:41:54,484
I want you to tell me
you're a liar!

989
00:41:54,502 --> 00:41:58,505
And a hypocrite!

990
00:42:02,209 --> 00:42:06,212
I want you to say you're sorry.

991
00:42:09,767 --> 00:42:15,582
I am a liar.

992
00:42:15,606 --> 00:42:19,609
And I am a hypocrite.

993
00:42:21,845 --> 00:42:25,092
But I will not say I'm sorry,

994
00:42:25,116 --> 00:42:29,352
because I did what I did
to protect this firm.

995
00:42:29,370 --> 00:42:31,882
Well, looks like the captain's
about to go down with her ship.

996
00:42:31,906 --> 00:42:34,101
Bullshit.

997
00:42:34,125 --> 00:42:35,636
You want something.

998
00:42:35,660 --> 00:42:37,271
Oh, I told you.
I want to see you in...

999
00:42:37,295 --> 00:42:39,172
In handcuffs?

1000
00:42:39,196 --> 00:42:43,226
If that were true, the police
would be here instead of you.

1001
00:42:43,250 --> 00:42:48,204
No, you wanted to see me squirm

1002
00:42:48,222 --> 00:42:52,225
before asking me
for what you really want.

1003
00:42:55,012 --> 00:42:58,075
I'm not gonna
give you the satisfaction,

1004
00:42:58,099 --> 00:43:02,162
so you might as well
spit it out.

1005
00:43:02,186 --> 00:43:04,498
You asked me what I wanted
once before, and I told you,

1006
00:43:04,522 --> 00:43:09,225
and then you told me
that I couldn't have it.

1007
00:43:09,243 --> 00:43:13,590
But now I can.

1008
00:43:13,614 --> 00:43:16,476
Pearson...

1009
00:43:16,500 --> 00:43:21,014
Specter...

1010
00:43:21,038 --> 00:43:22,956
Litt.

1011
00:43:22,980 --> 00:43:28,980
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man

