I hear you're interviewing
replacements this morning.
I am.
Are you good at what I do.
I'm great at what I do.
Then you start tomorrow.
I'd like to propose a change
to the current compensation
formula.
How many partners do you have
in your pocket
if we put your proposal
to a vote?
I can get 45%.
I'm gonna get you
the difference.
This is Harvey's
last three income statements,
and I found them sitting
in the copy machine.
You came to work for me, so now
it's time for you to decide.
Are you with me or not?
I just called for a vote,
and I hope you've been
saving your money,
because your gravy train's
about to leave the station.
- Okay, I'm dialing 911.
- It's not a heart attack.
It's a panic attack.
Remember when I said
if I wanted you to make up
for the compensation vote
I would come to you directly?
Well, now I am.
Well, let's take a look
at your resume.
Witness tampering,
extortion, bribery.
Forgery fits right in.
I actually looked
into your mommy,
and it turns out
that the whole time
you were home with Daddy,
Mommy was out banging...
[blues rock music]
♪ ♪
Hey, Harv.
How's it going?
♪ ♪
You're absolutely certain
the man
was this Travis Tanner person?
Yes.
And yet you're just as certain
the woman wasn't Donna?
That's what I said.
I know that, but you
haven't said who she was.
Why are you looking at me
like that?
You know why.
I don't know who she was.
Okay, then let's try this.
Why do you think Travis Tanner
all of a sudden
popped into your subconscious?
Because I'm in the middle
of a case against him.
Well, since you don't want to
talk about the dream anymore,
why don't we talk
about the case?
That's not creepy at all.
I was just wondering
why you changed your hair.
Hair's the same
as it's always been.
You trying to look older?
Younger?
Whatever it is,
it isn't working.
Are you finished?
'Cause I'm actually trying
to catch up
on some billables here.
Hey, I just stopped by
to give you a little gift
for winning the Zane case.
A gift? You've never
given me a gift after a case.
That's not true.
Come to think of it, you've
never even congratulated me,
which means you're
actually here because,
oh, my God, you miss me.
- I did... not miss you.
- Are you okay?
Do you want to come over
tonight?
We can watch
Sleepless in Seattle.
- Do you want your gift or not?
- That's it?
My gift looks a lot
like a folder.
It's a case.
You and me killing it
against Travis Tanner.
- Just like old times?
- Just like old times.
- Well, what are we waiting for?
- Nothing.
He's on his way over with
a settlement offer right now.
Settlement?
That doesn't sound like Tanner.
- Sounds exactly like Tanner.
- How's that?
He's starting off
waving a white flag.
Yeah, he's doing it
just to go behind our backs
so he can attack our flank.
So you're saying we need
to watch our flank.
No, I'm saying we need
to attack his.
- What?
- I'm just gonna say it.
Every time we go up against
Tanner, it gets brutal.
You just had a panic attack
the other day,
so are you sure this is really
what you need right now?
It's exactly what I need
right now.
Let's go get him.
Louis?
What's this?
That is a token
of my appreciation.
You told me to trust Harvey
with Esther and you were right.
Now Harvey and I are good.
Well, if you're gonna
give me a gift
every time I turn out
to be right,
then I'm gonna need
a bigger apartment.
Well, not every time,
but this time.
Your mud club.
I'm going mudding?
Even better.
We are going mudding.
Wow, Louis.
I don't know what to say.
This is, um....
- Wonderful?
- Inappropriate.
Oh, come on, Donna.
I don't think you understand.
Picture this.
You and me, side by side,
completely naked,
our bodies covered
in the juices of Mother Earth.
Oh, yeah, now I can see exactly
how it's totally appropriate.
Exactly.
And Donna, trust me.
When you dip your virgin toe
in the deep warmth of my mud,
you're never gonna be
the same again.
[knocks on door]
Jessica, we have a problem.
I went through the bylaws.
Turns out the new compensation
structure is in violation
of subsection C35.
So the vote in itself is moot.
So you're saying
we're going back
to the old compensation
structure?
No, I'm not saying that.
Subsection C35 is saying that.
There's only one problem.
Subsection C35 didn't exist
24 hours ago.
- Jessica...
- Cut the shit, Louis.
Tell me what this
is really about.
[sighs]
It's about me trying to make
things right with Harvey.
And I have no problem with that.
But I also need you
to make things right with me.
What are you talking about?
That vote was an assault
on my power.
I sneak this by,
I don't get my power back.
It just makes me
the same as you and Jack.
So you're not going to undo
this thing the same shady way
that the two of you passed it
in the first place.
Jessica, I told you,
leaving Harvey's compensation
in the copier was an accident.
And a man named Santa Claus
climbs down chimneys
and leaves presents under trees.
Okay, fine, I get it.
You don't believe me.
But how the hell am I supposed
to convince the senior partners
to take money
out of their own pockets?
That's your problem.
You want to reverse that policy,
bring it up for a vote.
Like a man.
♪ Suits 5x05 ♪
Toe to Toe
Original Air Date on July 22, 2015
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
[blues music]
[elevator bell dings]
♪ ♪
Excuse me, tiger.
Don't you want to check in
at reception?
- Oh, I know where I'm going.
- No, you don't.
Yeah, I'd say you know who I am,
but you're not Donna.
No, I'm not.
But I do know who you are.
Well, then you know
who I'm here to see.
I also know that the very
first time you ever came here,
you walked right past security
and by Donna.
But like you just said,
I'm not Donna.
I like you.
You filling in for the day?
None of your business.
Hey, I'm just saying,
when Red gets back,
maybe you want
to come work for me.
I already have a job.
And right now it's
getting your sorry ass
into the conference room.
♪ ♪
So what are you gonna do?
The only thing I can do.
Get Harvey to ask me
for something else.
No, not an option.
Donna, the only way
I can get this done
is with Jack Soloff's help,
and there is no way
that he's gonna reverse
the very same proposal
that put him on the map.
I'll tell you
what Harvey would do.
I don't care
what Harvey would do,
because I cannot do
what Harvey would do.
What would Harvey do?
He'd find a way to make it
worth Jack's while.
Get Rachel to get me a list
of every major corporate merger
pending in the next month.
There is the Louis
I came to work for.
You are right. Here I am.
And I'm gonna get it done.
And when I do, you and I are
going for a long, slow mud.
No, we're not.
If you're here to check the air,
it's like a sauna
on the 38th floor.
Good to see you, Harvey.
Nice to know some people
never change.
No witty rejoinder?
What's going on?
You slowing down
in your old age?
Could be low T.
And I could talk shit
with guys all day,
but I'm here because
I care about my client.
Well, then maybe your client
shouldn't have tried
to launch a company
with stolen IP.
That IP wasn't stolen.
Alyssa created it herself.
It doesn't matter whether
she created it or not.
She signed a contract
that says we own it,
and it was on our laptop that
she took home on her last day.
And we're not letting you walk
out the door with our property.
Okay, I told you
this isn't about me.
Okay, what do you want, Tanner?
I want to make an offer.
Alyssa is willing
to give you a 15% stake
to drop this whole thing.
She could make it 100%
for all I care.
- We're not settling.
- You don't have to settle,
but you do have to present
that offer to your client
and you know it.
I will, I just need
to get it translated
from bullshit to English.
Harvey, look at me.
That's a fair offer.
No, you look at me and tell me
you're not doing something
behind our backs right now.
- I'm not.
- Well, we are.
Your secretary said
you wouldn't file a TRO
until after this meeting.
Oh, we didn't.
Turns out that Miss Lang
has some outstanding debts,
so we just went ahead
and bought those up
and put a lien on her property.
The sheriff's padlocking
her offices as we speak.
Harvey, don't do this.
You'll be sorry.
Tell that to the judge.
We're filing that TRO
in the morning.
I'm telling you,
I'm not the guy I used to be,
but if you hit me,
I'm not turning the other cheek.
You're gonna get hit back.
What are you so happy about?
I told you,
it's exactly what I needed.
You've gone up against
this man how many times?
Enough to know that
he's a piece of shit
that'll cross whatever line
it takes to win.
All I've heard so far
is the line that you crossed.
Listen, you may understand
some things about people,
but you don't understand
what I do.
Well, it sounds to me like
what you did was attack a man
that was waving a white flag.
Were you listening?
He wasn't waving a white flag,
he was setting us up.
How can you be so sure?
Because I know Tanner.
Okay, well, if you know so well
what he was capable of,
why was it such a good idea
to pick a fight with him?
Because it's what I do.
Well, maybe it's time to
consider changing what you do.
(Rachel)
Okay, here we go.
What about Gentech
and Orion Pharmaceuticals?
Monster merger, contingent fee,
and huge upside.
And Cravath is listed
as the attorney of record,
which means if they swap out,
it blows the whole thing up.
Okay, well, that's the last one.
Shit.
Wait, this has been here
the whole time.
What about John Dellmore?
They're merging
with Arkin Financial.
Haven't been announced yet,
it's just sitting there
- ripe for the taking.
- No, not gonna happen.
Dellmore's been with
Harmon and Shupe for decades.
So what? Harmon and Shupe
is a third-tier law firm
and Shupe is a joke.
She's also John Dellmore's wife.
Well, so then maybe
we can convince Dellmore
that his wife is a trollop.
- Louis!
- God damn it!
What is going on?
I need Jack Soloff to overturn
the compensation vote,
and the only way for me
to do that is to bring in
a big contingent client.
And share the money with him.
Exactly!
And none of these people are it.
Okay.
Wait, where are you going?
Like you said,
none of these people are it.
It's late, we're both exhausted,
and I've got a test
in the morning.
Rachel, please.
Louis, I'm sorry.
We'll work on it
tomorrow morning, I promise.
Rach...
[sighs]
Gentlemen, I don't like granting
TROs without a good reason.
We have a good reason,
Your Honor.
It's called a contract.
A contract that explicitly
states that any product
Alyssa Lang developed
during her employment
is the property of our client.
Unfortunately that contract
is unenforceable.
It is unless I woke up
in Russia this morning.
Your Honor, I have here a copy
of Alyssa Lang's
birth certificate.
She may have signed
that contract,
but it isn't binding because
she was only 16 at the time.
What?
Your Honor, I know this man,
and that document
could have come from anywhere.
Get it verified
by the labs at Quantico.
All it's gonna prove
is that Alyssa Lang
had no legal capacity to sign.
It doesn't matter how old
she was when she signed it.
It was ten years ago.
She's cashed every paycheck
she got since.
And you can argue that at trial,
but we have laws
protecting minors for a reason,
and I'm not granting a TRO.
And one more thing, Your Honor.
We have payment in full,
discharging her debt,
and are requesting her doors
be reopened.
That has nothing to do
with why we're here.
Save it for trial, Mr. Specter.
It's lunch.
I'm hungry, and those padlocks
are coming off today.
[bangs gavel]
What the hell was that?
That was the sound
of your face hitting the canvas.
I suggest you stay down.
I'm not staying anywhere,
you son of a bitch.
- Excuse me?
- You heard me.
Your client was 16 years old and
you conveniently left that out
of your changed man speech.
I didn't tell you about her
because I knew you wouldn't
listen to a thing I said after
I offered you a fair deal
and you told me to go to hell.
Bullshit.
You didn't tell us because
you wanted to blindside us
in court.
Hey, you're the one who
turned out the lights out
on Alyssa's business while
I was extending an olive branch.
Bullshit again.
We both know
that settlement offer
was nothing but a distraction.
You want a distraction?
That is a draft of Alyssa Lang's
sexual harassment complaint
against your client.
As far as our offer goes,
it wasn't a distraction
because we haven't
filed that yet
and our offer's
still on the table.
I advise you to take it.
You didn't believe the sexual
harassment allegation?
- Not a chance.
- Why not?
Well, for starters,
it came out of Tanner's mouth.
And I know Tim Petroff,
and he didn't cheat on his wife.
And you're angry at him
for that?
You're damn right I am!
There are some things
you just don't do.
Like lie?
Like threaten to rip
a man's family apart.
Hmm.
What?
I just find it interesting
that you talk about family
as if it were sacred,
yet you've never married.
You've never had
a family of your own.
I don't see any
macaroni paintings
or school pictures
in here either.
And my personal life
is not the topic here.
So why don't we get back
to what is?
If it was such a good idea
to pick a fight with Tanner,
why were you so angry at him
for doing exactly
what you knew he would do?
You're the doctor.
You tell me.
Okay, maybe because
getting angry at someone
is a way to avoid facing
what's going on with yourself.
[elevator bell rings]
Oh, good, you're back.
Can't be good
if you're out here.
Oh, I didn't want you
to get ambushed. There's a...
Tim Petroff of BetaSoft
in my office.
He's been wearing out
your carpet for half an hour.
Tanner must have sent him a copy
of the complaint.
If you mean that paper balled up
in his fist, I'd say he did.
Thanks for the heads-up,
Gretchen.
Tim, before you say anything...
Sexual harassment?
What the hell is this?
It's only a draft.
It hasn't been filed yet.
And that's supposed
to make me feel better?
It's a goddamn lie.
I have never done anything
remotely resembling
harassing anyone.
- Tim, calm down.
- I'm not going to calm down.
This is a complete twisting
of who I am.
I want this woman destroyed.
It's not her.
It's her lawyer.
I don't care who it is.
I have a wife and children,
and I want this thing gone.
Then you should know there's
a settlement on the table.
Mike!
Not now.
What settlement?
A 15% stake in her venture.
Are you out of your mind?
You think I'm gonna settle
with these people
based on blackmail?
No one's settling.
Yeah, you're damn right
no one's settling.
Now earn your money and blow
this woman out of the water.
You heard him.
Figure out a way to put the
screws to her once and for all.
Harvey.
And I don't want to hear
any shit about my state of mind.
I'm not gonna say anything
about that,
but what I will say is that
if Tanner's willing to make her
do this, what's to say
he's not willing to make her
do something worse?
What do you want to do, Mike?
You want to back down?
No, I want to get Tanner fired.
It's not legal for us
to talk to her.
There's no law against me
running into her by accident.
Rachel, what are you doing here?
I've been looking
all over for you.
Don't you mean, "Hey, Rachel,
how did your test go?"
I don't care how your test went.
I just need you to get me
everything you can
on John Dellmore.
Louis, we've already
been over this.
His lawyer's his wife.
You're never gonna sign him.
Well, that's just it.
I don't need to sign him.
I only need to pretend
to sign him.
Okay.
That's a bad idea.
No, it's not.
If Jack thinks I signed
Dellmore,
and I tell him
I'll give him a piece,
he'll know it's worth
a fortune to him
and he'll overturn the vote.
And what are you gonna do
when he finds out
the whole thing was a lie?
He won't.
I'll make up some sob story
about how Dellmore
made up with his wife
and we'll live
to fight another day.
He's never gonna believe that.
Rachel, Katrina would have been
on board with this from day one.
Okay, Louis, I'm sorry.
I am not trying to
rain on your parade,
but when Jack finds out,
he's going to hate you forever.
Well, I made a promise
to Harvey.
And if it's a choice
between Jack hating me
and breaking that promise,
I'm picking Harvey
every single time.
What exactly do you need?
I need a way to dazzle
the shit out of John Dellmore.
Thank you.
I don't understand.
My bill's been paid?
- Yes, sir, it has.
- By who?
Uh, by me.
And who exactly are you?
I'm Louis Litt.
And not only did I
pay for your check,
I also brought you another one.
You're donating $50,000
to my charity.
Yes.
Why would you want to...
Because it may not look like it,
but I was homeless.
I spent two years
on the streets,
and had it not been for your
family's organization,
I would not be the man
I am today.
Is there anything I can do
to thank you?
Just keep doing
what you're doing.
You, sir,
are a true American hero.
[chuckles]
- Thank you.
[bluesy rock music]
♪ ♪
Oh, good, you're here.
What the hell was that?
That was John Dellmore.
Yeah, I know who it is.
Why was he giving you a hug?
Because I just convinced him
to let us handle his merger.
Does that have something
to do with why we're here?
It's got everything to do
with why we're here,
because I knew that you
would never believe
that I could close Dellmore.
You're right.
If I hadn't seen it myself,
I never would have believed it.
And why is that?
Because I'm a grinder?
Here's the thing, Jack.
When you took on Harvey,
you pitted the grinders
against the rainmakers,
and that was a good move,
but you want to move
to the next level?
We need to be both grinders
and rainmakers.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
What are you saying?
I'm saying
that we need to revisit
the compensation agreement.
No way.
Why would I do that?
Because when
we get this business,
it will be worth a fortune
to us.
- "Us"?
- Yes, us, Jack.
If you are with me on this,
I will give you 50 cents
to every dollar that I make.
Yeah.
Let's get this done.
Careful, it's really hot.
A woman once sued McDonald's
for getting burned.
[both giggle]
Although I guess you could
just say you got burned
and sue them anyway.
Who are you?
Doesn't matter who I am.
It matters who I work for.
Tim Petroff.
You can't talk to me.
I'm just fixing my coffee.
You want to walk away,
walk away, but before you do,
I'm gonna say
to nobody in particular
that you should fire
your lawyer.
I'm not firing anybody.
Well, then you should also know
that falsely accusing someone
of sexual harassment
is a criminal offense,
and no matter what
Travis Tanner has told you
to convince you that you'll
get away with it, you won't.
There's nothing
in that complaint
that isn't factually correct.
You are twisting those facts
and you could ruin a man's life,
and you know it.
Oh, and how is that different
from what he's doing to me?
- It's completely different.
- Is it?
I worked for that man
60 hours a week for 10 years,
and now that I want
to start my own company,
he not only wants to crush me,
but he told people
I stole the idea.
If that's not ruining a person's
life, then I don't know what is.
Oh, and as far
as Travis Tanner goes,
sexual harassment
wasn't his idea.
It was mine.
And when he tried
to talk me out of it,
I told him he could either
get on board
or watch me get another lawyer.
Rachel Zane,
you glorious creature.
- Glorious?
- Yes, glorious.
I mean, you were masterful.
The charity, his lone lunches
at his favorite restaurant,
having Jack show up
at the perfect time.
I mean, you are not only
a brilliant attorney,
you're the backbone
of this entire...
Louis, I'm not going
mudding with you.
God damn it!
What did Donna tell you?
She told me
that if it went well,
you would come in here trying
to get a celebratory mud,
and that if it didn't go well,
you would try to get
a sympathy mud.
Wait a second, I could have
got a sympathy mud?
No, you couldn't.
But the good news is, you got
what you wanted with Jack,
and on top of that, Louis,
you really made a difference
in the lives
of homeless children.
Which reminds me.
After the vote,
I want you to put a stop payment
on that check.
Okay, no... that is
a despicable thing to do.
Please, any charity
claiming to do a good thing
is clearly a scam.
I won't have it.
So you mean you're cheap?
You know what, for someone who
won't throw me a sympathy mud,
you're very judgmental.
Louis.
What can I do for you?
You can give me your proxy.
Why would I do that?
Because you asked me to bring
the compensation issue up
for a vote like a man and I did.
And is Jack Soloff
aware of this?
Not only aware of it,
he's voting for it.
And however did you get him
to do that?
Let's just say that
you wanted me to do this
like Harvey would have
and not like I would have,
but I did the best of both.
Then you have my proxy.
Harvey, I talked to Alyssa Lang
and there's something
you should know.
Let me guess, she batted
her eyes, told you a sob story,
and now you think she's
some kind of innocent.
No, I don't.
In fact, she told me that the
sexual harassment idea was hers.
And why do I need to know that?
I think we should consider
taking the deal.
Well, we're not gonna do that.
Why not?
Because first of all,
there's now way on Earth
that Tim's gonna settle.
You could convince him
and you know it.
And second of all,
there's no way on Earth
that that suit was her idea.
Harvey, you weren't there,
all right?
Yeah, I didn't have
to be there to know
that if Tanner could
convince her to do that bullshit
in the first place,
he could sure as hell get her
to say it was her idea.
He couldn't have known
that I was gonna contact her.
He could, and he did.
And I don't want to hear
another word about it.
And while you were away trying
to get her to cut him loose,
I was here trying to figure out
how to do
what Tim asked us to do
and blow her away.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Harvey, this isn't a joke.
I'm not joking.
The only way to get Tanner
to back down
is to point a cannon
in his face.
You're not pointing it
You're pointing it in hers,
and once you put this in motion,
there's no guarantee that you're
gonna be able to pull it back.
She should have thought of that
before she hired Travis Tanner.
♪ ♪
Listen, I'm gonna start
by introducing the proposal,
then you chime in.
Jack, I gave you 50%
of Dellmore,
but I need to be seen
as leading the charge on this.
Louis, I got the partners
in line by telling them
it was my proposal.
Okay, so I'll introduce you
with my full support
and then you can just
take it from there.
Okay.
Oh, and by the way,
when we win this thing,
maybe you and I
can go mudding together.
Why don't we just focus
on our meeting?
Right.
First of all, I would like
to thank everyone for coming.
The issue at hand
is a very important proposal
that Jack and I
have been working on.
I have both Harvey
and Jessica's proxies.
And I am pleased to say this
measure has their full support.
- Jack.
- Thank you, Louis.
In light of the impact
of recent changes in the firm
resulting from
the new compensation structure,
Louis and I strongly feel
that there should be
no new policy changes
for the next 12 months.
What?
And as Louis just said, the name
partners gave their blessing.
So why don't we make it
unanimous?
All in favor?
Motion seems to have passed.
Next order of business.
What the hell did you just do?
What the hell did I do?
I protected my own interests.
- We had a deal!
- We didn't have a thing.
You think I bought
that John Dellmore stunt
at the restaurant?
I was on to you the second
you walked over to my table.
I let you give me
that bullshit speech
about grinders and rainmakers
just so I could do
what I just did.
Okay, I get it.
You made your point,
you made a name for yourself,
but, Jack,
you need to undo this.
What makes you think
I could have undone it
in the first place?
They voted for that proposal
because it put more money
in their pockets,
and now it's there to stay.
By the way, if you want
to go mudding with someone,
why don't you ask
Harvey Specter?
Because it doesn't take a genius
to figure out
that he's the one that got you
to carry his water
in the first place.
[slaps]
Thanks.
I got you the special.
Did you say no pickles?
You didn't say no pickles.
I didn't say,
"Order my lunch."
So sue me.
You send the notification
over to Tanner?
Two hours ago.
Then it won't be long.
What?
I didn't say anything about your
state of mind after Tim Petroff
because I wasn't worried
about it then,
- but I am now.
- Mike...
- What if it doesn't work?
- It'll work.
- And what if it doesn't?
- Then it's on Tanner.
No, it's on you, because
I'm telling you right now,
Tanner is not driving
this thing.
Well, speak of the devil.
You son of a bitch.
You filed criminal charges
against my client?
You're damn right we did.
She forged
a fake driver's license
and attached it to her W2.
- That's ten years of tax fraud.
- Oh, you piece of shit.
This is crossing the line
even for you.
For me?
Ever since the day I met you,
all you've done is cross lines,
and it started with you
ripping off cancer victims,
not to mention every other thing
you've ever done.
Hey, I told you
I am not that guy anymore.
Yeah, right before you tried
to ruin my client's life
with some bullshit
sexual harassment charge.
Right after he padlocked
my client's livelihood.
Yeah, you're damn right he did!
- Harvey...
- Because if you're on a case
against me,
it's just a matter of time
until you eviscerate
someone I care about.
Eviscerate?
If I was gonna eviscerate
someone you cared about,
all I'd have to do is point out
how Donna's no longer
working for you.
- Hey, get out of here, Tanner.
- She's working for Louis Litt.
- What did you just say to me?
- You heard me.
And then I'd go up to her
and say, "What happened, Red?
"Did Harvey get tired
of banging you?
"Or was he such a lousy lay
that you left him
"for the guy down the road
just like Harvey's mom
"did to dear, old Dad?"
Harvey! Harvey! Stop!
Tanner, get out of here now!
Go!
You're absolutely convinced
Tanner couldn't be
telling the truth?
What does it matter?
Well, you could be ruining
this woman's life.
That's not my problem.
So you don't believe
in second chances?
I didn't say that.
No, you just said a man you
didn't trust swore he changed.
And instead of giving him
a chance to prove that,
you launched an all-out war.
Were you listening
to my goddamn story?
Did you hear what he said?
That is not a man
that's changed.
No, I'm talking about
what you did.
You launched an all-out war.
I did that for my client.
And for your information,
I've given plenty of people
second chances.
- Like who?
- Louis, for one.
Mike.
Donna, Scottie,
my brother, my...
Your what?
I thought we were talking
about the case.
We started by talking
about your dream.
Yeah, the one I had
because of my case.
Mm-hmm. And you said the woman
in that dream wasn't Donna.
But it doesn't add up,
because the man was Tanner
and you just told me what he
said about her the same day
that you had that dream.
Yeah, well, I don't care
if it doesn't add up
because I'm telling the truth.
And yet you have tells
all over you that say otherwise.
Then you don't know what a tell
is, because I don't have any.
All right.
We'll see who knows
what a tell is.
You want to play poker with me?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I'm gonna play poker with you.
And when I win,
and you're out of money,
you're gonna tell me the truth.
And what do I get
when you're out of money?
It doesn't matter 'cause
it's never gonna happen.
- Hey.
I need to talk to you
about something.
What's going on?
I just got a call
from Travis Tanner.
He wants me to meet him
in half an hour.
Well, you have to tell Harvey.
I left him two messages.
He hasn't gotten back to me,
but even if he does,
he's gonna tell me not to go.
Well, then don't go.
You can't go behind
Harvey's back.
That's the thing.
What if going to see Tanner is
more like having Harvey's back?
What are you talking about?
The client on the other side
of our case
made a fake ID ten years ago
and now Harvey's ready
to send her to prison for it,
and he's only doing it
because of Tanner.
Okay, but it's still
Harvey's call.
And if he makes that call
in his current state of mind,
he might regret it
for the rest of his life.
What do you mean,
his current state of mind?
A couple of weeks ago,
I walked into Harvey's office
and he was having
a panic attack.
Oh, my God.
And on top of that, yesterday,
the two of them
got into a yelling match
that ended
with Harvey punching Tanner.
Okay, look.
Do whatever you have to do.
Have Harvey's back.
Where is he?
- I don't know.
- Bullshit, you don't know.
Jessica, I swear I haven't
seen him since last night.
Then I need to know,
did he lie to me?
Donna...
I've always trusted you.
Now I need you to trust me.
Did he do some underhanded shit
to fool Jack and it backfired?
Yes.
That's exactly what he did.
Then find him.
And tell him to come see me.
What can I say?
Kings full of 6s.
[scoffs]
All right, Harvey, you won.
What do you want?
Can't I take a minute
to enjoy my win?
You can.
But once our time's up,
I'm done granting wishes.
Well, in that case,
I want you to tell me
the worst mistake you ever made
as a therapist.
That wasn't part of the deal.
No, no, no, no.
You didn't make a deal with me
because you were so sure
you were gonna beat me.
Well, you didn't,
and it's time to pay the piper.
Well, I'm not going to do it.
Look who's deflecting now.
Look, I get it, okay?
You're here because your fears
are affecting your work,
and now you're trying to find
a time where I failed at my job
so that you can lash out at me.
And I'm not gonna let you do it.
No, I just want you to know
what it feels like to be me
in here with you, and if
you're not willing to do that,
then what the hell good are you?
I killed someone.
What?
I do a lot of work
as an expert witness
in corporate
competency situations.
- You mean substance abuse?
- Yes.
And usually
it's high-powered people
looking to keep their jobs.
But this time it was different.
A client needed someone
to get his son out of rehab
so that he could attend
his mother's funeral.
I knew it was a mistake
to even get involved
because he wanted it so badly,
but he was a long-time client
and I cared about him,
so I did it.
I evaluated his son.
And I knew... I knew deep down
inside he wasn't ready,
but I gave the go-ahead anyway,
and the night of the funeral,
he overdosed and died.
- I'm so sorry.
- Hmm.
Well, I don't want you
to be sorry.
I want you to sit your ass down
and tell me the truth
about the dream.
I told you before.
I'm telling you the truth.
I don't know who this woman was.
You know what,
I just opened myself up to you
to show you that I know
what it's like to be you,
but I don't.
Because I know that
the only way to come to terms
with what's inside
is to let it out.
And until you figure that out,
you might as well
get the hell out
because you're wasting
both our time.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I remember when you
used to ride a bike.
used to be a scumbag
but you didn't pretend
you weren't.
Why am I here, Tanner?
I want you to reconsider
our settlement offer.
And what makes you think we're
going to accept the same deal
that you brought us before?
Because I've sat across
from you,
and I know that you care about
more than just the fight.
Well, I'm sorry,
but that fight's gonna end
with Alyssa Lang
going to prison.
Yeah, but it doesn't have to.
And the only reason
it's gonna end that way
is because that deal
is coming from me.
How the hell am I supposed
to believe a word you say?
What do you want me to say, huh?
That I got tired
of playing the goon?
Because I did.
Yeah, I woke up one morning
and I said,
"Enough is enough."
And I haven't taken one case
that I don't believe in
or done anything
that I couldn't stomach since.
Look, Mike.
I don't have a leg to stand on.
I don't have another move,
but you can convince Harvey
to convince Petroff
not to destroy this girl's life.
You just need to decide if
you're willing to do that, man.
Travis, you keep saying
that Harvey won't take the deal
because your name's on it.
But if you really are
a changed man,
maybe it's time you prove it.
♪ ♪
[glass clinks]
Oh.
Hey, you're not toner.
Donna, please, leave me alone.
Louis, you can't hide
in here forever.
I have to because
I made a promise to Harvey,
and not only did I drop
the ball, I shit the bed.
And on top of that,
I lied to Jessica telling her
that I wouldn't be doing any
more underhanded shit with Jack.
Well, she knows what you did.
And it's time to face the music.
Oh, did you not just hear me?
I defied a direct order.
I admit that,
I might as well tell her
that I put Harvey's salary
in the copy machine
in the first place.
You know what, maybe you should.
That's really hilarious.
What, are you crazy?
No, Louis, I'm not.
You keep making bad decision
after bad decision.
And this is a chance
to wipe them all clean.
It's not gonna wipe
anything clean.
All it's gonna do
is get me fired.
[sighs]
Yeah, maybe it will.
The one thing I do know
is you've lost Jessica's trust.
This at least gives you
a chance to get it back.
It's a hell of a lot better
than cowering in here.
♪ ♪
What is it, Louis?
I'm here to tell you the truth.
That you lied when you said
you weren't going
to do anything underhanded
with Jack?
That I was the one
that left Harvey's salary
in the copy machine...
on purpose.
♪ ♪
Why aren't you saying anything?
Because I haven't decided
what I'm going to do.
♪ ♪
But what you're going to do...
is get Jack goddamn Soloff
up here.
♪ ♪
- You wanted to see me?
- Yes, I did.
Louis has brought something
to my attention.
And what is that?
Well, according to
subsection C35 of the bylaws,
we broke protocol
when we changed
the compensation formula.
Bullshit.
There is no subsection C35.
You're wrong.
- Here, take a look.
- I don't need to look.
And if you're asking me
to sell this to the partners,
you're shit out of luck.
No, you're shit out of luck.
Because Louis didn't just
come to me with the bylaws.
He admitted that it was you
who deliberately put
Harvey's salary out there
for all the world to see.
Isn't that right, Louis?
I...am sorry, Jack.
I had to come clean.
- It was the right thing to do.
- You lying piece of shit.
Watch it, Jack.
You're talking
to a name partner.
And you're saying
that he's lying,
but as head
of the compensation committee,
you had access
to Harvey's salary.
I didn't leave that document out
and I can prove it.
- How is that?
- I know for a fact that...
Oh, let me help you out.
The reason you stopped yourself
is that you were going to say
Louis left it out.
But if you knew that,
and still didn't come forward,
then I can fire your ass
for that, too.
But you're not going to do that
because you'd also
have to fire him.
And you can't afford
another shake-up.
You're right.
I can't.
But I don't care,
because I'd rather fire you both
than to let you push me around.
So it's up to you, Jack.
Stand by provision C35...
or pack up your shit.
♪ ♪
[scoffs]
Forgive me, Jessica,
you're right.
♪ ♪
Next time I'll read the bylaws
more carefully.
♪ ♪
You knew this whole thing
would play out this way
the second it started, right?
I had a pretty good idea.
Jessica...
when am I gonna learn
not to defy you?
You're never going to learn.
But as long as I know that,
we'll be okay.
[chuckles]
I...
Feel like going mudding tonight?
- No.
- I figured.
You better be here to tell me
Tanner's walking away.
I'm here to tell you
that I met with him today.
You went to see him
without telling me?
- I left you two messages.
- So the hell what?
You don't cut me out
of a meeting on my case.
Your case?
Well, Tanner's made a settlement
offer on your case,
and I think that we
should take it.
Are you kidding?
We have a boot to his throat.
We don't have to settle.
All we have to do is decide
how hard to press.
You're not pressing
on his throat,
you're pressing
on Alyssa Lang's.
So all he has to do is claim
that he's a changed man
and you take his side over mine?
I'm not on his side.
Our client stands to make
a fortune from this deal
- without lifting a finger.
- I don't give a shit.
You saw what he did,
and you heard what he said.
And you said when
we started this,
it would be just like old times,
but right now,
you're acting like the bad guy,
not him.
That piece of shit
hasn't changed
and I'm not settling with him.
And I'm not asking you to.
What the hell is that?
It's the original offer.
Only now the attorney of record
is Katrina Bennet.
I had Tanner remove himself
from the case,
so now you're not settling
with him.
You're just doing
what's best for everyone.
♪ ♪
Take the deal.
You sure you don't want
to read it first?
I don't have to.
♪ ♪
[whispers]
Ahh!
[upbeat music]
Rachel, I cannot talk right now.
I'm going mudding with Donna.
No, Louis, you're going mudding
with both of us.
Ahh.
Oh!
Louis?
♪ ♪
I have to say, I'm surprised you
called for another appointment.
What can I say?
You telling me that story
got to me.
So you're ready
to tell the truth?
I am.
The woman in my dream was Donna.
Well, I'm glad you came back
to talk about it.
And since you've opened up
to me,
I'm going to open up to you.
I believe you're telling
the truth.
- That's opening up?
- No, this is.
I believe you're telling
the truth,
but I don't think the woman
in your dream
was actually Donna.
I think it was your mother.
I don't believe it.
I tell you the thing that's
been eating at me for days,
and you're calling me a liar?
No, I'm not calling you a liar.
Your dream was a representation
of unresolved issues.
The only unresolved issue
is I opened up
and you're turning on me.
Harvey, bringing up your mother
isn't turning on you.
You have no idea what
bringing up my mother is to me!
No, I don't. That's the whole
point of what we're doing here.
It doesn't matter what we're
doing here 'cause we're done.
Harvey, Harvey, look.
I don't care how much money
you make
or how many women
you sleep with.
You have issues in your life
that will keep you
from having real relationships.
And you can tell yourself
all you want
that it has nothing to do
with your mother,
but it's a lie and you know it.
Hmm.
Well, like I said, we're done.
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man