1
00:00:00,909 --> 00:00:02,781
Previously on Suits...

2
00:00:02,782 --> 00:00:04,977
You're good with me working
on the takeover with Logan.

3
00:00:05,001 --> 00:00:08,314
As long as we don't let that
affect this.

4
00:00:08,338 --> 00:00:09,982
We won't.

5
00:00:10,006 --> 00:00:11,550
I do always get what I want,

6
00:00:11,574 --> 00:00:14,236
and what I want to do with
this company is strip it down,

7
00:00:14,260 --> 00:00:15,487
flip it over, and then...

8
00:00:15,511 --> 00:00:16,939
That's enough. We're done.

9
00:00:16,963 --> 00:00:18,240
You're right.

10
00:00:18,264 --> 00:00:19,491
We are.

11
00:00:19,515 --> 00:00:21,243
When I told you that
our relationship was now

12
00:00:21,267 --> 00:00:22,945
purely professional,
I was serious.

13
00:00:22,969 --> 00:00:25,030
What's not purely professional
about lunch?

14
00:00:25,054 --> 00:00:27,283
Unless you mean the sex
that'll be following lunch.

15
00:00:27,307 --> 00:00:30,068
Phillip, your son, you lost him,

16
00:00:30,092 --> 00:00:33,038
and that's what this company
is to you now, your family.

17
00:00:33,062 --> 00:00:35,574
I lost both my parents
when I was 11 years old,

18
00:00:35,598 --> 00:00:38,210
so I know a little something
about needing family.

19
00:00:38,234 --> 00:00:40,078
Since when does the S.E.C.
go around

20
00:00:40,102 --> 00:00:42,882
intimidating law firms
by going after their clients?

21
00:00:42,906 --> 00:00:44,800
They don't,
but they will when Eric Woodall

22
00:00:44,824 --> 00:00:47,843
starts there next week.

23
00:00:56,502 --> 00:00:57,930
Another all-nighter?

24
00:00:57,954 --> 00:00:59,732
Yeah.

25
00:00:59,756 --> 00:01:00,933
Work or school?

26
00:01:00,957 --> 00:01:01,957
Work.

27
00:01:01,958 --> 00:01:04,370
What were you working on?

28
00:01:04,394 --> 00:01:06,288
You know what I was working on.

29
00:01:06,312 --> 00:01:08,157
I am so sorry, but I'm so tired.

30
00:01:08,181 --> 00:01:10,326
I have to go get some sleep
before I go back to the office.

31
00:01:10,350 --> 00:01:11,350
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.

32
00:01:11,351 --> 00:01:12,778
I haven't seen you in two days.

33
00:01:12,802 --> 00:01:14,330
Give me five minutes.

34
00:01:14,354 --> 00:01:17,466
Okay, but I can't be responsible

35
00:01:17,490 --> 00:01:19,251
for anything that I say.

36
00:01:19,275 --> 00:01:21,170
Well, okay, in that case,

37
00:01:21,194 --> 00:01:23,172
is Logan going
after another board member?

38
00:01:23,196 --> 00:01:24,256
Nice try.

39
00:01:24,280 --> 00:01:25,557
Mm, is he running out of cash?

40
00:01:25,581 --> 00:01:27,176
I can't tell you that.

41
00:01:27,200 --> 00:01:30,596
Did you love him?

42
00:01:30,620 --> 00:01:33,632
How long have you been waiting
to ask me that?

43
00:01:33,656 --> 00:01:35,768
You know, just when you were
at your weakest

44
00:01:35,792 --> 00:01:39,688
and most vulnerable.

45
00:01:39,712 --> 00:01:43,575
I did love him,
but I don't love him now.

46
00:01:43,599 --> 00:01:46,051
I love you.

47
00:01:47,303 --> 00:01:48,998
Who ended it?

48
00:01:49,022 --> 00:01:51,773
- Does that matter?
- It does to me.

49
00:01:54,527 --> 00:01:56,338
I ended it.

50
00:01:56,362 --> 00:01:58,156
Now, do you have
any other burning questions,

51
00:01:58,180 --> 00:02:00,926
or can I go to sleep, please?

52
00:02:00,950 --> 00:02:02,661
Um, let me see.

53
00:02:02,685 --> 00:02:05,130
What's the most expensive thing
you ever shoplifted?

54
00:02:05,154 --> 00:02:06,832
Were you a mean girl?

55
00:02:06,856 --> 00:02:08,968
Are you interested in taking
a pole dancing class?

56
00:02:08,992 --> 00:02:11,387
You know what?
We'll get into that later.

57
00:02:11,411 --> 00:02:14,189
Sweet dreams.

58
00:02:14,213 --> 00:02:15,213
God, enough about you.

59
00:02:15,214 --> 00:02:16,859
I want to talk about me.

60
00:02:16,883 --> 00:02:18,343
We were just talking about you.

61
00:02:18,367 --> 00:02:20,863
Not enough.

62
00:02:20,887 --> 00:02:22,781
All right, fine.
Let's talk about Harvey.

63
00:02:22,805 --> 00:02:24,733
- Mm.
- So guess what he's been up to.

64
00:02:24,757 --> 00:02:26,235
What?

65
00:02:26,259 --> 00:02:30,072
He found the master tapes
for his father's solo album.

66
00:02:30,096 --> 00:02:32,491
He's working on buying them.

67
00:02:32,515 --> 00:02:35,544
He's been trying to find them
ever since he lost his father.

68
00:02:35,568 --> 00:02:39,164
Oh, I see why
you're telling me this.

69
00:02:39,188 --> 00:02:40,699
You're trying
to humanize Harvey,

70
00:02:40,723 --> 00:02:44,036
because you're afraid of what
this fight is gonna do to us.

71
00:02:44,060 --> 00:02:46,388
I'm afraid because of what
it's already doing to you.

72
00:02:46,412 --> 00:02:48,040
I'm talking Ali-Frazier.

73
00:02:48,064 --> 00:02:49,091
Come on, Donna.

74
00:02:49,115 --> 00:02:51,043
Listen to me.

75
00:02:51,067 --> 00:02:52,428
They started out like brothers.

76
00:02:52,452 --> 00:02:54,229
Then they went toe-to-toe
three times,

77
00:02:54,253 --> 00:02:57,516
and Joe Frazier went to
his grave hating Muhammad Ali.

78
00:02:57,540 --> 00:02:59,902
I didn't know
you were a boxing fan.

79
00:02:59,926 --> 00:03:01,904
I'm a Harvey fan.

80
00:03:01,928 --> 00:03:05,847
So am I, and that's why
I'm giving him my best.

81
00:03:08,217 --> 00:03:11,269
Thanks for the coffee.
You're welcome.

82
00:03:16,776 --> 00:03:17,953
You're in late.

83
00:03:17,977 --> 00:03:19,338
I was up late.

84
00:03:19,362 --> 00:03:21,256
Working on my stuff?

85
00:03:21,280 --> 00:03:23,959
Working on a lot of stuff.

86
00:03:23,983 --> 00:03:24,983
What can I help you with?

87
00:03:24,984 --> 00:03:27,046
I wanted to talk to you.

88
00:03:27,070 --> 00:03:29,048
About?

89
00:03:29,072 --> 00:03:32,184
Well, when I told you before
that I'm not the same guy

90
00:03:32,208 --> 00:03:34,520
that I used to be,
what I meant was,

91
00:03:34,544 --> 00:03:37,606
I got caught up in emotion
back then.

92
00:03:37,630 --> 00:03:39,758
I'm not caught up
in emotion anymore.

93
00:03:39,782 --> 00:03:40,976
And?

94
00:03:41,000 --> 00:03:43,695
And that means
that I'm gonna have to do

95
00:03:43,719 --> 00:03:45,481
some calculated things,

96
00:03:45,505 --> 00:03:47,316
and I needed to know
that you're okay with that.

97
00:03:47,340 --> 00:03:50,152
Why wouldn't I be?

98
00:03:50,176 --> 00:03:51,653
You know why.

99
00:03:51,677 --> 00:03:53,205
Logan,
you don't have to come and have

100
00:03:53,229 --> 00:03:54,656
these little check-in talks
with me.

101
00:03:54,680 --> 00:03:57,242
I am a big girl, and I know how
these things work.

102
00:03:57,266 --> 00:04:01,880
So just do what you have to do,
and stop worrying about me.

103
00:04:01,904 --> 00:04:05,273
Great.

104
00:04:09,695 --> 00:04:11,623
Harvey,
what the hell's going on?

105
00:04:11,647 --> 00:04:13,759
At the moment,
I'm 18 minutes away

106
00:04:13,783 --> 00:04:16,678
from owning Steve McQueen's
Shelby Cobra.

107
00:04:16,702 --> 00:04:18,013
You know what I'm talking about.

108
00:04:18,037 --> 00:04:19,798
Last time I saw you,
you told me you were gonna

109
00:04:19,822 --> 00:04:21,150
get me this company.

110
00:04:21,174 --> 00:04:23,519
I just found out Walter Gillis
funded his pension.

111
00:04:23,543 --> 00:04:25,303
Did you think
they wouldn't fight back?

112
00:04:25,327 --> 00:04:26,822
I expected them to fight.

113
00:04:26,846 --> 00:04:28,640
Right now,
we're getting our ass kicked.

114
00:04:28,664 --> 00:04:30,475
Well, what scorecard
are you looking at,

115
00:04:30,499 --> 00:04:33,162
because we just got them
to give up half their war chest

116
00:04:33,186 --> 00:04:34,413
just to stay in the fight.

117
00:04:34,437 --> 00:04:36,165
I don't give a shit
what the scorecard says.

118
00:04:36,189 --> 00:04:37,315
I want a knockout.

119
00:04:37,339 --> 00:04:38,617
Well, it doesn't work that way.

120
00:04:38,641 --> 00:04:39,651
It can if you hit them
below the belt.

121
00:04:39,675 --> 00:04:40,869
- Logan...
- Save it.

122
00:04:40,893 --> 00:04:43,088
When my father went up
against Carl Icahn,

123
00:04:43,112 --> 00:04:44,923
he said that you waited
till he wasn't looking,

124
00:04:44,947 --> 00:04:47,543
you walked up behind him,
and you shot him in the back.

125
00:04:47,567 --> 00:04:49,995
Walter Gillis isn't Carl Icahn.

126
00:04:50,019 --> 00:04:52,181
I'm not talking
about Walter Gillis.

127
00:04:52,205 --> 00:04:54,049
I'm talking about Mike Ross.

128
00:04:54,073 --> 00:04:55,667
I don't care
who you're talking about.

129
00:04:55,691 --> 00:04:58,020
That Icahn deal
was completely different.

130
00:04:58,044 --> 00:05:01,673
The only difference I see
is that this deal

131
00:05:01,697 --> 00:05:03,642
is against your surrogate son.

132
00:05:03,666 --> 00:05:08,803
So are you willing to do this
or not?

133
00:05:09,972 --> 00:05:11,683
You want below the belt?

134
00:05:11,707 --> 00:05:14,286
I'll give you below the belt.

135
00:05:14,310 --> 00:05:18,157
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪

136
00:05:18,181 --> 00:05:21,543
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪

137
00:05:21,567 --> 00:05:24,863
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪

138
00:05:24,887 --> 00:05:28,167
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪

139
00:05:28,191 --> 00:05:31,443
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪

140
00:05:31,444 --> 00:05:35,444
♪ Suits 4x03 ♪ Two in the Knees
Original Air Date on June 25, 2014

141
00:05:35,445 --> 00:05:36,758
♪ all right

142
00:05:36,782 --> 00:05:42,214
♪ all that time imagine this ♪

143
00:05:42,238 --> 00:05:43,255
♪ The greenback boogie

144
00:05:43,279 --> 00:05:49,279
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man

145
00:05:54,594 --> 00:05:56,906
Louis, we talked about this.

146
00:05:56,930 --> 00:06:00,626
It's just so weird to see him
in my old office, you know?

147
00:06:00,650 --> 00:06:03,329
It's like when you drive
by the house you grew up in,

148
00:06:03,353 --> 00:06:04,880
and there's another family
in there,

149
00:06:04,904 --> 00:06:06,549
and all you want to do is
break in and make yourself soup.

150
00:06:06,573 --> 00:06:07,883
You know that feeling?

151
00:06:07,907 --> 00:06:09,084
Well, it depends on the soup.

152
00:06:09,108 --> 00:06:11,220
- Mushroom barley.
- Then no.

153
00:06:11,244 --> 00:06:12,871
Hey, did you get him
that apology gift

154
00:06:12,895 --> 00:06:14,373
I told you to get him?

155
00:06:14,397 --> 00:06:15,808
Except instead of scotch,
I got us two front-row tickets

156
00:06:15,832 --> 00:06:17,393
to the ballet.

157
00:06:17,417 --> 00:06:18,877
Oh.

158
00:06:18,901 --> 00:06:21,730
Well,
it's the thought that counts.

159
00:06:21,754 --> 00:06:23,983
Louis, can I help you
with something?

160
00:06:24,007 --> 00:06:25,217
Yes.

161
00:06:25,241 --> 00:06:29,054
You and me,
we got off on the wrong foot.

162
00:06:29,078 --> 00:06:33,159
Words were said,
hurtful caricatures were drawn,

163
00:06:33,183 --> 00:06:34,660
and I did some bad things too.

164
00:06:34,684 --> 00:06:36,412
Water under the bridge, Louis.

165
00:06:36,436 --> 00:06:37,863
Well, no, not to me.

166
00:06:37,887 --> 00:06:42,234
See, um, I once was told
that actions have consequences,

167
00:06:42,258 --> 00:06:45,777
and I want to turn things around
by inviting you...

168
00:06:47,730 --> 00:06:50,576
to the American Ballet Company's
production of Giselle.

169
00:06:50,600 --> 00:06:52,428
The ballet?

170
00:06:52,452 --> 00:06:55,047
Yeah, you and me tonight.

171
00:06:55,071 --> 00:06:56,348
Wow.

172
00:06:56,372 --> 00:06:58,100
Louis, I would love to go
to the ballet with you.

173
00:06:58,124 --> 00:07:01,353
I really would, but I have
Knicks tickets tonight, man,

174
00:07:01,377 --> 00:07:02,938
and I never miss a game.

175
00:07:02,962 --> 00:07:04,857
All right, I'm gonna let it go
that you're choosing basketball

176
00:07:04,881 --> 00:07:07,759
over Giselle, but I really need
to make this up to you, Jeff.

177
00:07:07,783 --> 00:07:08,861
I can't be in the red.

178
00:07:08,885 --> 00:07:11,597
I am always,
always in the black,

179
00:07:11,621 --> 00:07:13,148
and I don't mean that
in a racial sense.

180
00:07:13,172 --> 00:07:16,592
Well, now that you mention it,
I could really use some advice.

181
00:07:18,628 --> 00:07:19,771
About a case?

182
00:07:19,795 --> 00:07:21,457
About Jessica.

183
00:07:21,481 --> 00:07:23,775
I just pulled Adam Grieves
as opposing counsel.

184
00:07:23,799 --> 00:07:25,461
And long story short,
he hates me,

185
00:07:25,485 --> 00:07:27,965
and I could really use Jessica's
help to run some interference,

186
00:07:27,987 --> 00:07:31,217
but I'm the new guy,
it's only my second case,

187
00:07:31,241 --> 00:07:33,836
and I don't know what to do.

188
00:07:33,860 --> 00:07:35,387
Well, I'll tell you
what I'm gonna do.

189
00:07:35,411 --> 00:07:37,506
I'm gonna get you
front-row tickets

190
00:07:37,530 --> 00:07:39,948
to Jessica Pearson's help.

191
00:07:43,870 --> 00:07:45,464
Okay, Harvey, you didn't
bring me here to make me

192
00:07:45,488 --> 00:07:47,099
choke down
these brussels sprouts.

193
00:07:47,123 --> 00:07:49,235
No, I didn't,
but you are going to have

194
00:07:49,259 --> 00:07:51,320
to choke down something else.

195
00:07:51,344 --> 00:07:53,072
Let me guess.
This is about Walter Gillis.

196
00:07:53,096 --> 00:07:54,473
No, it's not about Walter.

197
00:07:54,497 --> 00:07:56,108
It's about the line of credit

198
00:07:56,132 --> 00:07:57,409
that you're about to stop
giving him.

199
00:07:57,433 --> 00:07:59,278
And why on earth
would I do that?

200
00:07:59,302 --> 00:08:01,580
Because if you don't,
I have a feeling

201
00:08:01,604 --> 00:08:03,365
that every
Pearson Specter client

202
00:08:03,389 --> 00:08:05,484
that you currently
do business with,

203
00:08:05,508 --> 00:08:07,920
suddenly gonna move
their accounts to Chase.

204
00:08:07,944 --> 00:08:10,205
You really want to cripple
his company that badly?

205
00:08:10,229 --> 00:08:11,757
His company's already dead.

206
00:08:11,781 --> 00:08:13,042
He just doesn't know it yet.

207
00:08:13,066 --> 00:08:14,993
That doesn't give you
the right to threaten me.

208
00:08:15,017 --> 00:08:17,630
If I were threatening you,
I'd come right out and say it.

209
00:08:17,654 --> 00:08:19,848
If you don't do this,
tomorrow morning,

210
00:08:19,872 --> 00:08:23,018
you lose $2 billion
worth of deposits.

211
00:08:23,042 --> 00:08:24,520
You son of a bitch.

212
00:08:24,544 --> 00:08:26,004
That he is.

213
00:08:26,028 --> 00:08:28,274
- What are you doing here, Mike?
- What do you mean?

214
00:08:28,298 --> 00:08:30,392
I just came
for the brussels sprouts.

215
00:08:30,416 --> 00:08:32,227
You know how I know
how good they are?

216
00:08:32,251 --> 00:08:33,512
How?

217
00:08:33,536 --> 00:08:34,846
Because this is where Harvey
brings bankers

218
00:08:34,870 --> 00:08:36,649
to strong-arm them
into doing some bullshit.

219
00:08:36,673 --> 00:08:38,567
- Don't listen to him.
- No, he should listen to me.

220
00:08:38,591 --> 00:08:41,620
I'm Walter Gillis' partner,
and if he cuts off our funding

221
00:08:41,644 --> 00:08:44,022
at any point in the next two
months following this lunch,

222
00:08:44,046 --> 00:08:46,024
then the next time
you're talking about

223
00:08:46,048 --> 00:08:48,900
these brussels sprouts will be
in front of a grand jury.

224
00:08:50,720 --> 00:08:53,749
Oh, Vernon,
don't take it personally.

225
00:08:53,773 --> 00:08:55,467
He did the same thing
to the guy from Leeds

226
00:08:55,491 --> 00:09:00,195
at the exact same table
seven months ago.

227
00:09:08,454 --> 00:09:11,266
Louis, I got your memo,

228
00:09:11,290 --> 00:09:13,352
and if you want to get
an antique diving bell

229
00:09:13,376 --> 00:09:16,739
for your new office,
it's on your dime.

230
00:09:16,763 --> 00:09:18,991
Okay, that's bullshit,
but whatever.

231
00:09:19,015 --> 00:09:20,442
I'm here about Jeff Malone.

232
00:09:20,466 --> 00:09:21,944
I am not the principal.

233
00:09:21,968 --> 00:09:24,279
You two are gonna have to work
your shit out on the playground.

234
00:09:24,303 --> 00:09:25,914
But you see, that's just it.

235
00:09:25,938 --> 00:09:27,599
We already did.

236
00:09:27,623 --> 00:09:29,952
Something's not right.

237
00:09:29,976 --> 00:09:31,286
Why are you here?

238
00:09:31,310 --> 00:09:33,589
I'm here because you need
to run interference.

239
00:09:33,613 --> 00:09:35,541
I thought you just said
you worked it out.

240
00:09:35,565 --> 00:09:37,909
No, not with me,
with Adam Grieves at the S.E.C.

241
00:09:37,933 --> 00:09:39,545
He has it in for Malone.

242
00:09:39,569 --> 00:09:41,797
Louis, I'm glad you two
are going to be

243
00:09:41,821 --> 00:09:44,266
walking to school together
from now on,

244
00:09:44,290 --> 00:09:47,970
but I hired Jeff Malone
to handle the S.E.C.,

245
00:09:47,994 --> 00:09:52,858
not to get me to handle them
for him.

246
00:09:52,882 --> 00:09:55,978
You know, you're always
telling me not to make enemies,

247
00:09:56,002 --> 00:09:59,398
and for the first time
since Harvey,

248
00:09:59,422 --> 00:10:01,233
I have just made a new friend,

249
00:10:01,257 --> 00:10:05,093
so I'm asking you...

250
00:10:07,263 --> 00:10:08,490
Please do it for my friend.

251
00:10:08,514 --> 00:10:09,875
Louis...

252
00:10:09,899 --> 00:10:13,185
If you won't do it for him,
please do it for me.

253
00:10:15,655 --> 00:10:18,217
I just had a very interesting
chat with Louis Litt.

254
00:10:18,241 --> 00:10:20,502
Louis is a very interesting guy.

255
00:10:20,526 --> 00:10:22,388
Did you know he's never eaten
an olive?

256
00:10:22,412 --> 00:10:25,090
I did not, but I do know
you fed him some bullshit.

257
00:10:25,114 --> 00:10:26,634
- That doesn't sound like me.
- Really?

258
00:10:26,649 --> 00:10:28,310
'Cause he thinks we need
to work together

259
00:10:28,334 --> 00:10:30,512
because there's bad blood
between you and Adam Grieves.

260
00:10:30,536 --> 00:10:31,814
I don't like to talk about it.

261
00:10:31,838 --> 00:10:33,399
Of course not,
because you and Adam Grieves

262
00:10:33,423 --> 00:10:35,651
play basketball every Wednesday.

263
00:10:35,675 --> 00:10:38,070
What happens on the court,
Jessica, stays on the court.

264
00:10:38,094 --> 00:10:41,940
And I thought I was clear
about boundaries.

265
00:10:41,964 --> 00:10:43,409
Well, listen,
if that's really how you feel,

266
00:10:43,433 --> 00:10:45,411
why don't you just tell Louis
that you want to bow out

267
00:10:45,435 --> 00:10:49,281
because you don't trust yourself
around me?

268
00:10:49,305 --> 00:10:52,201
Yeah, I didn't think so.

269
00:10:52,225 --> 00:10:56,978
See you tomorrow.

270
00:10:59,849 --> 00:11:01,376
What happened to going
below the belt?

271
00:11:01,400 --> 00:11:02,711
I went below the belt.

272
00:11:02,735 --> 00:11:05,297
The referee stepped in and threw
a grand jury at my face.

273
00:11:05,321 --> 00:11:06,632
Well, I wasn't asking you
to go below the belt

274
00:11:06,656 --> 00:11:07,966
with the company.

275
00:11:07,990 --> 00:11:09,968
I was asking you to go
below the belt with Ross.

276
00:11:09,992 --> 00:11:11,220
What are you talking about?

277
00:11:11,244 --> 00:11:13,021
I'm saying you hire
a private investigator

278
00:11:13,045 --> 00:11:14,690
to find every skeleton
in his closet.

279
00:11:14,714 --> 00:11:17,008
He wakes up in the morning, and
it's all over the front page.

280
00:11:17,032 --> 00:11:18,610
Logan, that's not going
below the belt.

281
00:11:18,634 --> 00:11:19,728
That's just nuts.

282
00:11:19,752 --> 00:11:21,313
You're full of shit.

283
00:11:21,337 --> 00:11:23,198
You don't want to do this,
because you don't have

284
00:11:23,222 --> 00:11:24,616
the stomach to do it
to your boy.

285
00:11:24,640 --> 00:11:26,518
No, I don't want to do it,
because we're on a path

286
00:11:26,542 --> 00:11:28,987
to win this thing,
and I let you bait me into doing

287
00:11:29,011 --> 00:11:30,823
what I already did
because I thought you were

288
00:11:30,847 --> 00:11:32,524
just a little impatient.

289
00:11:32,548 --> 00:11:35,360
But now I'm starting to realize
what it really is.

290
00:11:35,384 --> 00:11:36,384
What is that?

291
00:11:36,385 --> 00:11:39,131
Who's full of shit now?

292
00:11:39,155 --> 00:11:41,083
This has nothing to do
with Rachel.

293
00:11:41,107 --> 00:11:43,886
You got there pretty damn fast.

294
00:11:43,910 --> 00:11:47,089
Hey, I asked you to put
Mike Ross down with one punch.

295
00:11:47,113 --> 00:11:49,708
You said you would,
and you didn't.

296
00:11:49,732 --> 00:11:53,401
So either do what I'm asking,
or I'll do it myself.

297
00:12:05,014 --> 00:12:06,725
You can't do it, Harvey.

298
00:12:06,749 --> 00:12:07,993
Yes, I can.

299
00:12:08,017 --> 00:12:09,411
Logan's gonna do it anyway.

300
00:12:09,435 --> 00:12:10,779
At least this way it'll be me.

301
00:12:10,803 --> 00:12:12,564
What's the difference
if you hire somebody

302
00:12:12,588 --> 00:12:14,533
to look into Mike or Logan does?

303
00:12:14,557 --> 00:12:16,597
You know damn well they're gonna
uncover his secret.

304
00:12:16,609 --> 00:12:18,537
I don't know that,
and you don't either.

305
00:12:18,561 --> 00:12:21,123
- Yeah, I do.
- No one's ever found it before.

306
00:12:21,147 --> 00:12:22,875
Because you were hiding it
from people

307
00:12:22,899 --> 00:12:25,243
who weren't looking for it,
not from people who are.

308
00:12:25,267 --> 00:12:29,848
What do you want from me, Donna?

309
00:12:29,872 --> 00:12:31,967
I want you to get Mike
to give up.

310
00:12:31,991 --> 00:12:33,302
Well, I'm not gonna do that,

311
00:12:33,326 --> 00:12:34,970
because I know
he's not gonna give up.

312
00:12:34,994 --> 00:12:37,422
- How do you know that?
- Because I know.

313
00:12:37,446 --> 00:12:38,807
This is Mike
we're talking about.

314
00:12:38,831 --> 00:12:40,475
If it were anyone
other than Mike,

315
00:12:40,499 --> 00:12:42,644
I'd have an article
in the Journal tomorrow.

316
00:12:42,668 --> 00:12:44,279
That's not what you told Logan.

317
00:12:44,303 --> 00:12:46,949
Because I goddamn lied
to Logan, and it didn't work.

318
00:12:46,973 --> 00:12:50,101
Now I'm gonna do
what I have to do.

319
00:12:50,125 --> 00:12:53,271
Well, the least you can do
is warn him.

320
00:12:53,295 --> 00:12:54,456
He's on the other side.

321
00:12:54,480 --> 00:12:55,657
I'm not gonna warn him.

322
00:12:55,681 --> 00:12:58,299
That's not how it works.

323
00:13:00,770 --> 00:13:02,447
Well, maybe you should think
of something

324
00:13:02,471 --> 00:13:04,406
that won't ruin
his goddamn life.

325
00:13:12,743 --> 00:13:13,830
Hey.

326
00:13:14,451 --> 00:13:16,195
You ready to get down
to business?

327
00:13:16,219 --> 00:13:17,697
- Yes, I am.
- Good.

328
00:13:17,721 --> 00:13:20,233
I was thinking that maybe we
could do all this over lunch.

329
00:13:20,257 --> 00:13:21,567
It's 10:30.

330
00:13:21,591 --> 00:13:23,236
There's a lot to discuss,
Jessica.

331
00:13:23,260 --> 00:13:25,104
No, there isn't.

332
00:13:25,128 --> 00:13:26,656
We need to bury them
in paperwork.

333
00:13:26,680 --> 00:13:27,940
No, we don't.

334
00:13:27,964 --> 00:13:29,442
We just need to come up
with a legitimate reason

335
00:13:29,466 --> 00:13:30,576
why Brooks made that trade.

336
00:13:30,600 --> 00:13:31,911
There is no legitimate reason.

337
00:13:31,935 --> 00:13:33,413
I didn't say there needs
to be one, Jessica.

338
00:13:33,437 --> 00:13:34,780
I said we need to find one.

339
00:13:34,804 --> 00:13:37,634
You are taking to defense
like a fish to water.

340
00:13:37,658 --> 00:13:38,968
Well, you didn't bring me
in here

341
00:13:38,992 --> 00:13:41,087
just for my genetically superior
bone structure, did you?

342
00:13:41,111 --> 00:13:43,789
Mm, no, that's what
I brought him in for.

343
00:13:43,813 --> 00:13:47,593
Hey, sorry I'm late.
I was just getting up to speed.

344
00:13:47,617 --> 00:13:48,794
You brought Louis in.

345
00:13:48,818 --> 00:13:50,296
Of course.

346
00:13:50,320 --> 00:13:54,017
Three heads are better than two,
unless you have an objection?

347
00:13:54,041 --> 00:13:55,151
No.

348
00:13:55,175 --> 00:13:56,569
Are you kidding me?

349
00:13:56,593 --> 00:13:59,322
I would never turn down
a threesome, right, buddy?

350
00:13:59,346 --> 00:14:00,907
I hear you.

351
00:14:00,931 --> 00:14:04,193
Good, because Jessica and I
were just having

352
00:14:04,217 --> 00:14:06,446
a little difference of opinion
about what to do next.

353
00:14:06,470 --> 00:14:09,082
Yes, and I'm sure Louis,
the man that I hired,

354
00:14:09,106 --> 00:14:12,335
the man who owes
his very career to me,

355
00:14:12,359 --> 00:14:13,703
will see things my way.

356
00:14:13,727 --> 00:14:15,538
Well, I don't want to step
on anyone's toes.

357
00:14:15,562 --> 00:14:18,341
No, Louis, you're not stepping
on anyone's toes here,

358
00:14:18,365 --> 00:14:21,044
and to be fair, I think
you're an amazing attorney

359
00:14:21,068 --> 00:14:22,512
who doesn't owe anyone anything.

360
00:14:22,536 --> 00:14:24,681
Ooh, do you work out?

361
00:14:24,705 --> 00:14:27,467
Oh, I-I try to stay fit.

362
00:14:27,491 --> 00:14:28,968
Try?

363
00:14:28,992 --> 00:14:30,353
Mission accomplished.

364
00:14:30,377 --> 00:14:32,338
Can we get to the point?

365
00:14:32,362 --> 00:14:34,057
Lou? Louis?

366
00:14:34,081 --> 00:14:36,809
Jeff and I have two different
approaches to this case.

367
00:14:36,833 --> 00:14:39,178
Exactly, go for the knockout
punch or bore them to death.

368
00:14:39,202 --> 00:14:40,730
Oh, well,
when you frame it that way...

369
00:14:40,754 --> 00:14:43,015
I can't believe you're using
that old debate team trick.

370
00:14:43,039 --> 00:14:44,484
Farm boy strong.

371
00:14:44,508 --> 00:14:45,568
That's what you are.

372
00:14:45,592 --> 00:14:47,520
Jessica, what debate team trick?

373
00:14:47,544 --> 00:14:49,822
Calling my approach
"Bore them to death"

374
00:14:49,846 --> 00:14:51,207
and yours "A knockout punch."

375
00:14:51,231 --> 00:14:52,358
Man, you're really good at this.

376
00:14:52,382 --> 00:14:54,210
Are you...
Have you done this before?

377
00:14:54,234 --> 00:14:55,578
Sure have.

378
00:14:55,602 --> 00:14:57,863
Look, Jessica, you can make
assumptions about how

379
00:14:57,887 --> 00:15:00,249
this farm boy's gonna come down
on this all you want to,

380
00:15:00,273 --> 00:15:04,443
but I think we all pretty much
know he's playing on my team.

381
00:15:05,895 --> 00:15:07,706
Jeff, you're right.

382
00:15:07,730 --> 00:15:09,175
You are right, and in fact,

383
00:15:09,199 --> 00:15:11,227
I think that,
because you and Louis

384
00:15:11,251 --> 00:15:15,565
see eye to eye on this case,
that you should work together,

385
00:15:15,589 --> 00:15:16,682
and I should bow out.

386
00:15:16,706 --> 00:15:18,684
You actually think
that bothers me?

387
00:15:18,708 --> 00:15:23,740
Because now I've this farm boy
all to myself, Jess.

388
00:15:23,764 --> 00:15:25,324
Just you and me, cowboy.

389
00:15:25,348 --> 00:15:28,050
It's like Ernie and Bert.

390
00:15:29,853 --> 00:15:31,063
Jeff Malone is in love with me.

391
00:15:31,087 --> 00:15:32,198
What?

392
00:15:32,222 --> 00:15:33,449
I was just in a meeting
with him,

393
00:15:33,473 --> 00:15:35,118
and he started off
by patting my shoulder.

394
00:15:35,142 --> 00:15:36,569
He's a jock, Louis.

395
00:15:36,593 --> 00:15:37,754
That's just how they are.

396
00:15:37,778 --> 00:15:39,705
No, he was then rubbing
my shoulders.

397
00:15:39,729 --> 00:15:41,007
Then he touched my arm.

398
00:15:41,031 --> 00:15:42,091
He's all over me.

399
00:15:42,115 --> 00:15:43,209
Wow.
What was that meeting about?

400
00:15:43,233 --> 00:15:44,544
It doesn't matter.

401
00:15:44,568 --> 00:15:47,580
Donna, his arguments are loaded
with double meaning.

402
00:15:47,604 --> 00:15:50,272
Who invokes the penal code
in an S.E.C. case?

403
00:15:52,042 --> 00:15:54,470
He said "penal"?

404
00:15:54,494 --> 00:15:55,638
Three times.

405
00:15:55,662 --> 00:15:57,256
The third time,
we were just talking about

406
00:15:57,280 --> 00:15:59,091
the Glass-Steagall act,
which is purely civil, and it...

407
00:15:59,115 --> 00:16:00,593
God damn it, woman,
do I have to draw you a map?

408
00:16:00,617 --> 00:16:01,778
I mean, come to think of it,

409
00:16:01,802 --> 00:16:03,696
athletes coming out
is all the rage now.

410
00:16:03,720 --> 00:16:06,816
And guess what his favorite
sport is: Basket... Ball.

411
00:16:06,840 --> 00:16:09,118
Oh, my God.

412
00:16:09,142 --> 00:16:10,269
Shut the front door.

413
00:16:10,293 --> 00:16:11,604
No,
I want to shut the back door.

414
00:16:11,628 --> 00:16:13,072
Okay, Louis,

415
00:16:13,096 --> 00:16:16,626
now that we've firmly
established his gayness,

416
00:16:16,650 --> 00:16:17,850
why would he think you're gay?

417
00:16:17,851 --> 00:16:19,328
I mean, you're...

418
00:16:19,352 --> 00:16:22,071
Straight as an arrow.

419
00:16:23,824 --> 00:16:25,625
I may have said
that I eat cock for breakfast,

420
00:16:25,642 --> 00:16:26,952
lunch, and dinner.

421
00:16:26,976 --> 00:16:28,120
What?

422
00:16:28,144 --> 00:16:29,639
It was a different kind
of cock, Donna.

423
00:16:29,663 --> 00:16:33,125
Okay, Louis, what exactly
do you want from me?

424
00:16:33,149 --> 00:16:34,927
I want you to tell me
what I should do about it.

425
00:16:34,951 --> 00:16:36,979
I'm gonna tell you exactly
what you're gonna do about it:

426
00:16:37,003 --> 00:16:38,097
Nothing.

427
00:16:38,121 --> 00:16:39,265
What do you mean, "nothing"?

428
00:16:39,289 --> 00:16:40,766
I mean don't give him
anything back.

429
00:16:40,790 --> 00:16:42,491
He'll get the message.
It'll pass.

430
00:16:45,045 --> 00:16:46,823
Donna, I don't think
you understand the power

431
00:16:46,847 --> 00:16:50,660
of my sexuality.

432
00:16:50,684 --> 00:16:52,144
What are you doing?

433
00:16:52,168 --> 00:16:54,413
Oh, you know, it's just a
little something for your file.

434
00:16:54,437 --> 00:16:56,249
I have a file?

435
00:16:56,273 --> 00:16:57,834
That information is classified.

436
00:16:57,858 --> 00:16:59,836
- Wait, why?
- It's in your file.

437
00:16:59,860 --> 00:17:01,618
Oh, shit.

438
00:17:15,158 --> 00:17:17,053
Harvey Specter.

439
00:17:17,077 --> 00:17:19,672
If you'd be more comfortable,
I have a couple rocks

440
00:17:19,696 --> 00:17:21,140
you could crawl out from under.

441
00:17:21,164 --> 00:17:23,943
Most people would go with some
tall weeds I could hide behind.

442
00:17:23,967 --> 00:17:25,528
Most people don't take
these fights personally.

443
00:17:25,552 --> 00:17:27,846
I do.
That's exactly why I'm here.

444
00:17:27,870 --> 00:17:29,482
Meaning?

445
00:17:29,506 --> 00:17:31,517
I came here to tell you
something man-to-man,

446
00:17:31,541 --> 00:17:33,342
because I know what this company
means to you.

447
00:17:33,343 --> 00:17:35,020
If you knew what this company
meant to me,

448
00:17:35,044 --> 00:17:37,990
you wouldn't be trying
to steal it.

449
00:17:38,014 --> 00:17:41,694
Walter,
I know how your son died.

450
00:17:41,718 --> 00:17:43,696
Get the hell out of my office.

451
00:17:43,720 --> 00:17:48,701
Not before I tell you that
Mike Ross was a drug dealer.

452
00:17:48,725 --> 00:17:52,088
Bullshit he was,
and I'm calling security,

453
00:17:52,112 --> 00:17:53,923
and if you're not gone
by the time they get here,

454
00:17:53,947 --> 00:17:56,092
their job's going to be
getting me off you.

455
00:17:56,116 --> 00:17:58,928
Fine, I'll go, but ask him.

456
00:17:58,952 --> 00:18:01,147
Ask him if he ever dealt drugs.

457
00:18:01,171 --> 00:18:04,850
Ask him if he ever refused
to take a drug test.

458
00:18:04,874 --> 00:18:06,936
Ask him if he was ever high
at work.

459
00:18:06,960 --> 00:18:08,187
I said, "get out."

460
00:18:08,211 --> 00:18:10,055
And ask him
if on the very day he came to me

461
00:18:10,079 --> 00:18:13,933
looking for a job he had a
briefcase filled with marijuana.

462
00:18:15,585 --> 00:18:20,533
This is how you do this,
come here "man-to-man"

463
00:18:20,557 --> 00:18:25,705
and use my son's death
to take my company from me?

464
00:18:25,729 --> 00:18:29,782
Well, you are nothing
but a piece of shit.

465
00:18:31,534 --> 00:18:33,912
You're right.
I am a piece of shit.

466
00:18:33,936 --> 00:18:38,123
But that doesn't make what
I'm telling you any less true.

467
00:18:48,918 --> 00:18:50,446
Walter, what are you doing here?

468
00:18:50,470 --> 00:18:52,281
I'm having second thoughts.

469
00:18:52,305 --> 00:18:54,099
About the takeover.

470
00:18:54,123 --> 00:18:56,268
About you.

471
00:18:56,292 --> 00:18:57,570
I'm sorry. I don't understan...

472
00:18:57,594 --> 00:18:59,961
Have you ever been involved
in a drug deal?

473
00:19:04,017 --> 00:19:05,911
Walter, look, I'm trying to save
your company here.

474
00:19:05,935 --> 00:19:07,463
And I'm here to find out
what kind of man

475
00:19:07,487 --> 00:19:10,466
I'm in business with,
so I'm going to ask you again.

476
00:19:10,490 --> 00:19:12,775
Have you ever been involved
in a drug deal?

477
00:19:21,785 --> 00:19:24,063
What did Harvey tell you?

478
00:19:24,087 --> 00:19:25,631
Looks like he told me the truth.

479
00:19:25,655 --> 00:19:27,817
The truth is that Harvey
can't beat us,

480
00:19:27,841 --> 00:19:30,135
so he's trying to divide us, and
he's using your son to do it.

481
00:19:30,159 --> 00:19:32,355
Just like you used his memory
to make you my partner.

482
00:19:32,379 --> 00:19:34,156
To save your life's work.

483
00:19:34,180 --> 00:19:37,142
Another lie from another liar.

484
00:19:37,166 --> 00:19:38,494
You two deserve each other.

485
00:19:38,518 --> 00:19:41,470
We're done.

486
00:19:49,446 --> 00:19:51,540
- Mike, are you okay?
- I don't care who you find.

487
00:19:51,564 --> 00:19:53,959
I want you to hire someone to
get every piece of dirt there is

488
00:19:53,983 --> 00:19:55,160
on Logan Sanders.

489
00:19:55,184 --> 00:19:56,629
- Uh...
- Just do it.

490
00:19:56,653 --> 00:19:57,680
Where are you going?

491
00:19:57,704 --> 00:19:59,822
To take care of something else.

492
00:20:05,139 --> 00:20:07,014
Couple things.
It's Porter birthday.

493
00:20:07,015 --> 00:20:09,261
I got him that weird zucchini
cake he likes from the Bronx.

494
00:20:09,285 --> 00:20:10,328
What cake?

495
00:20:10,352 --> 00:20:11,963
Somebody returned
Stutman's chair.

496
00:20:11,987 --> 00:20:13,465
It was missing?

497
00:20:13,489 --> 00:20:16,134
And the "no questions asked"
memo in the kitchen worked.

498
00:20:16,158 --> 00:20:18,303
- What did it stop?
- Mm, it's not important.

499
00:20:18,327 --> 00:20:19,804
None of these things
are important.

500
00:20:19,828 --> 00:20:21,839
Oh, and one more thing.

501
00:20:21,863 --> 00:20:24,342
Louis thinks Malone
is in love with him.

502
00:20:24,366 --> 00:20:26,177
Your secret's safe.

503
00:20:26,201 --> 00:20:30,538
And you're welcome.

504
00:20:32,975 --> 00:20:34,986
Hey, Louis,
do you have a minute?

505
00:20:35,010 --> 00:20:37,522
Well, it's about all I have,
'cause I'm super, super busy.

506
00:20:37,546 --> 00:20:39,324
Yeah, well, listen,
I just wanted to check in

507
00:20:39,348 --> 00:20:41,326
and see if you're ready
to pull an all-nighter.

508
00:20:41,350 --> 00:20:42,794
I just got
all the brokerage tapes in,

509
00:20:42,818 --> 00:20:44,496
and I figure we could just
grind it out.

510
00:20:44,520 --> 00:20:45,664
Tonight?

511
00:20:45,688 --> 00:20:47,716
Tonight,
unless you want to go right now

512
00:20:47,740 --> 00:20:49,033
and just pound it out
all at once.

513
00:20:49,057 --> 00:20:50,302
Okay, that's it.

514
00:20:50,326 --> 00:20:51,726
I mean,
you have got this all wrong.

515
00:20:51,727 --> 00:20:56,424
Jeff, I like you... as a friend.

516
00:20:56,448 --> 00:20:58,710
Right, Louis.

517
00:20:58,734 --> 00:21:00,762
I like you too.

518
00:21:00,786 --> 00:21:02,514
I think I've made that
perfectly clear.

519
00:21:02,538 --> 00:21:05,383
Too clear, man, too clear.

520
00:21:05,407 --> 00:21:07,068
I mean, enough
with the come-ons, already.

521
00:21:07,092 --> 00:21:08,603
- What?
- Yeah, I mean, I get it.

522
00:21:08,627 --> 00:21:10,822
You know, we're a perfect match,
you know,

523
00:21:10,846 --> 00:21:12,357
if you go that way,
ebony and ivory.

524
00:21:12,381 --> 00:21:15,193
But I play
a different instrument, so...

525
00:21:15,217 --> 00:21:16,911
Oh, Louis, no...

526
00:21:16,935 --> 00:21:18,747
Look, I... look, it's just that...

527
00:21:18,771 --> 00:21:20,665
I just don't...
I don't want there to be,

528
00:21:20,689 --> 00:21:23,418
you know, just awkwardness,
especially since Jessica

529
00:21:23,442 --> 00:21:25,503
just bowed out,
and it's just me and you now.

530
00:21:25,527 --> 00:21:27,094
Right.

531
00:21:29,765 --> 00:21:33,261
Well, now that you've seen
right through me, Louis,

532
00:21:33,285 --> 00:21:37,749
I... I am disappointed.

533
00:21:37,773 --> 00:21:39,851
Are you gonna be okay?

534
00:21:39,875 --> 00:21:42,520
To be honest, I'm feeling
a little raw right now.

535
00:21:42,544 --> 00:21:44,712
Oh, shit.

536
00:21:46,498 --> 00:21:48,092
I'm sorry.

537
00:21:48,116 --> 00:21:49,761
Maybe it's best
if you just told Jessica

538
00:21:49,785 --> 00:21:51,262
that she needs to step back in.

539
00:21:51,286 --> 00:21:53,698
- Yes.
- Yeah.

540
00:21:53,722 --> 00:21:55,640
Can do, yeah.

541
00:21:58,143 --> 00:21:59,738
Get up.

542
00:21:59,762 --> 00:22:01,156
You here to fight me?

543
00:22:01,180 --> 00:22:02,574
Oh, should I wait for you
to turn your back?

544
00:22:02,598 --> 00:22:03,941
That seems to be
more your speed.

545
00:22:03,965 --> 00:22:06,277
I'm sorry, were you
expecting me to give you a call?

546
00:22:06,301 --> 00:22:08,296
No, I was expecting you to be
a human being.

547
00:22:08,320 --> 00:22:10,665
From where I'm sitting,
I was a goddamn saint.

548
00:22:10,689 --> 00:22:12,167
Oh, yeah? How's that?

549
00:22:12,191 --> 00:22:13,835
If I didn't do what I did,
Logan was gonna hire

550
00:22:13,859 --> 00:22:16,805
a private investigator to
smear you up and down the block.

551
00:22:16,829 --> 00:22:18,723
- So what?
- You know what.

552
00:22:18,747 --> 00:22:22,560
I shot you in the knees, so he
wouldn't shoot you in the face.

553
00:22:22,584 --> 00:22:23,895
You're welcome.
You know what, Harvey?

554
00:22:23,919 --> 00:22:25,347
I'm gonna take pass
on the thank-you

555
00:22:25,371 --> 00:22:26,631
and instead skip right
to the part where I call you

556
00:22:26,655 --> 00:22:27,732
a piece of shit.

557
00:22:27,756 --> 00:22:28,900
You know what?

558
00:22:28,924 --> 00:22:30,604
I'm getting a little tired
of hearing that.

559
00:22:30,626 --> 00:22:32,637
And what does that make you
for threatening to bring

560
00:22:32,661 --> 00:22:34,155
criminal charges
in that restaurant?

561
00:22:34,179 --> 00:22:35,573
You deserved criminal charges

562
00:22:35,597 --> 00:22:37,308
for what you were doing
in that restaurant.

563
00:22:37,332 --> 00:22:38,777
You didn't have a problem
when we did it

564
00:22:38,801 --> 00:22:40,245
seven months ago
to the guy from Leeds.

565
00:22:40,269 --> 00:22:43,031
Seven months ago, you weren't
lying to somebody about me.

566
00:22:43,055 --> 00:22:44,949
I didn't lie,
and seven months ago,

567
00:22:44,973 --> 00:22:48,152
you were goddamn here.

568
00:22:48,176 --> 00:22:50,672
So that's what this is about.

569
00:22:50,696 --> 00:22:52,457
You can't stand
that I got out of here

570
00:22:52,481 --> 00:22:54,209
and that I'm succeeding
without you.

571
00:22:54,233 --> 00:22:56,678
Without me?

572
00:22:56,702 --> 00:22:58,496
I made you.

573
00:22:58,520 --> 00:23:00,215
Without me, you're nothing.

574
00:23:00,239 --> 00:23:02,267
Right there.

575
00:23:02,291 --> 00:23:04,669
That's who you are,
and that's why I left.

576
00:23:04,693 --> 00:23:06,838
Bullshit. Don't lay that on me.

577
00:23:06,862 --> 00:23:09,607
You left because you needed
to feed that huge ego.

578
00:23:09,631 --> 00:23:12,110
Ego? Ego?

579
00:23:12,134 --> 00:23:14,229
If I stayed here, you know what
would have been hanging

580
00:23:14,253 --> 00:23:16,197
over my head for the rest
of my life.

581
00:23:16,221 --> 00:23:18,316
Which is why I told you
to move somewhere

582
00:23:18,340 --> 00:23:19,567
nobody ever knew you.

583
00:23:19,591 --> 00:23:22,570
But you stayed here,
so that thing is still

584
00:23:22,594 --> 00:23:24,906
over your goddamn head,
and I stopped it.

585
00:23:24,930 --> 00:23:27,325
I don't care what you think
you stopped.

586
00:23:27,349 --> 00:23:28,743
You're gonna go
to Walter Gillis,

587
00:23:28,767 --> 00:23:30,495
and you're gonna make
this thing right.

588
00:23:30,519 --> 00:23:31,529
It is right.

589
00:23:31,553 --> 00:23:32,914
It's over. You lost.

590
00:23:32,938 --> 00:23:34,866
Nothing's over.

591
00:23:34,890 --> 00:23:36,701
And you're the one who lost
something today.

592
00:23:36,725 --> 00:23:38,136
What are you talking about?

593
00:23:38,160 --> 00:23:40,672
You went personal.
I went personal.

594
00:23:40,696 --> 00:23:44,248
Your father's master tapes...
I've got 'em.

595
00:23:47,085 --> 00:23:50,087
Those tapes have nothing to do
with this deal.

596
00:23:51,924 --> 00:23:54,425
They do now.

597
00:23:59,882 --> 00:24:03,394
Harvey...

598
00:24:03,418 --> 00:24:04,418
I did this.

599
00:24:04,419 --> 00:24:06,397
- What?
- The tapes.

600
00:24:06,421 --> 00:24:09,083
Mike found out about them
from me.

601
00:24:09,107 --> 00:24:11,235
I've been meeting him for coffee
just because I wanted

602
00:24:11,259 --> 00:24:13,288
to make sure that everything
was okay between the two of you,

603
00:24:13,312 --> 00:24:16,741
and I never, ever thought that
he would do something like this.

604
00:24:16,765 --> 00:24:19,127
I'm so, so sorry.

605
00:24:19,151 --> 00:24:23,047
It's not your fault, Donna.

606
00:24:23,071 --> 00:24:24,933
- What are you gonna do?
- Nothing.

607
00:24:24,957 --> 00:24:26,634
The tapes have nothing to do
with this deal.

608
00:24:26,658 --> 00:24:30,555
The second I believe they do,
I'm done.

609
00:24:30,579 --> 00:24:32,924
Ugh, perfect timing.

610
00:24:32,948 --> 00:24:34,108
Do you want me
to get rid of him?

611
00:24:34,132 --> 00:24:36,617
I'll handle it.

612
00:24:38,504 --> 00:24:40,815
What part of
"drag Mike Ross through the mud"

613
00:24:40,839 --> 00:24:42,433
did you not understand?

614
00:24:42,457 --> 00:24:44,369
The part where you come off
looking like a rich,

615
00:24:44,393 --> 00:24:45,570
vindictive douche bag.

616
00:24:45,594 --> 00:24:46,938
That's not your call to make.

617
00:24:46,962 --> 00:24:49,941
Based on your years
of experience in takeovers?

618
00:24:49,965 --> 00:24:52,109
Here's something they didn't
teach you in snowboarding school

619
00:24:52,133 --> 00:24:53,211
or wherever the hell you went

620
00:24:53,235 --> 00:24:55,163
before you decided to be
a grown-up.

621
00:24:55,187 --> 00:24:57,465
Never destroy anyone in public

622
00:24:57,489 --> 00:24:59,968
when you can accomplish
the same result in private.

623
00:24:59,992 --> 00:25:01,285
Meaning?

624
00:25:01,309 --> 00:25:03,254
I severed Mike's ties
with Walter Gillis.

625
00:25:03,278 --> 00:25:04,839
It's over.

626
00:25:04,863 --> 00:25:06,943
You know, you told me
that Mike Ross wasn't a threat,

627
00:25:06,949 --> 00:25:08,560
and then he handcuffed us
with a T.R.O.

628
00:25:08,584 --> 00:25:10,645
You said that you'd
take him down with one blow,

629
00:25:10,669 --> 00:25:12,180
and then he got back up.

630
00:25:12,204 --> 00:25:15,400
So here's something that I did
learn in snowboarding school.

631
00:25:15,424 --> 00:25:18,269
When someone talks shit,
I demand proof.

632
00:25:18,293 --> 00:25:19,521
Proof of what?

633
00:25:19,545 --> 00:25:21,940
Logan, we won. You don't need...

634
00:25:21,964 --> 00:25:23,191
Need to what?

635
00:25:23,215 --> 00:25:25,860
Come off like a rich,
vindictive douche bag?

636
00:25:25,884 --> 00:25:28,413
I want proof
that he's giving up his bid,

637
00:25:28,437 --> 00:25:29,814
and if I don't get it
by the morning,

638
00:25:29,838 --> 00:25:31,482
I'm gonna call
my private investigators,

639
00:25:31,506 --> 00:25:34,859
and I'm gonna finish
what I started.

640
00:25:46,165 --> 00:25:47,509
Where are you going?

641
00:25:47,533 --> 00:25:48,844
Where do you think I'm going?

642
00:25:48,868 --> 00:25:50,712
To get Mike to sign an agreement
to give up his bid.

643
00:25:50,736 --> 00:25:52,064
You can't.

644
00:25:52,088 --> 00:25:53,088
Why not?

645
00:25:53,089 --> 00:25:54,089
Because you were right.

646
00:25:54,090 --> 00:25:55,984
He's never gonna listen to you.

647
00:25:56,008 --> 00:25:58,386
Donna, I know you're feeling
bad about the tapes, but...

648
00:25:58,410 --> 00:25:59,688
That has nothing to do with it.

649
00:25:59,712 --> 00:26:01,156
Then what are you saying?

650
00:26:01,180 --> 00:26:03,909
I feel guilty that I told him,
but what he did,

651
00:26:03,933 --> 00:26:05,894
that's on you.

652
00:26:05,918 --> 00:26:07,598
And the reason he's not gonna
listen to you

653
00:26:07,603 --> 00:26:09,114
is because you acted like
an asshole.

654
00:26:09,138 --> 00:26:10,532
Excuse me?

655
00:26:10,556 --> 00:26:12,084
He came in here
wanting an explanation

656
00:26:12,108 --> 00:26:15,787
for why you did what you did,
and you threw gas on the fire.

657
00:26:15,811 --> 00:26:17,956
I gave him an explanation.

658
00:26:17,980 --> 00:26:21,760
Yeah,
you told him he was nothing.

659
00:26:21,784 --> 00:26:23,262
You know what?

660
00:26:23,286 --> 00:26:25,413
About a half an hour ago, you
told me this was all your fault.

661
00:26:25,437 --> 00:26:28,083
A half an hour ago,
I was thinking about what I did.

662
00:26:28,107 --> 00:26:30,052
I wasn't thinking
about what you said to him.

663
00:26:30,076 --> 00:26:31,637
It doesn't matter
what I said to him.

664
00:26:31,661 --> 00:26:34,723
I saved him.

665
00:26:34,747 --> 00:26:37,693
Harvey, you said before
if it had been anybody

666
00:26:37,717 --> 00:26:39,945
other than Mike, you would have
done what Logan wanted

667
00:26:39,969 --> 00:26:41,263
without blinking an eye.

668
00:26:41,287 --> 00:26:43,932
Well, if anybody other than Mike
had walked in here

669
00:26:43,956 --> 00:26:46,985
the way he did,

670
00:26:47,009 --> 00:26:49,271
you would have shown him
the tiniest bit of compassion.

671
00:26:49,295 --> 00:26:51,606
He bought those tapes
before he ever walked in here.

672
00:26:51,630 --> 00:26:55,210
Those tapes were not the first
thing that he told you about,

673
00:26:55,234 --> 00:26:56,778
but he made damn sure
they were the last.

674
00:26:56,802 --> 00:26:59,631
So you just flagged me down
to call me an asshole?

675
00:26:59,655 --> 00:27:00,666
No, I flagged you down
to tell you

676
00:27:00,690 --> 00:27:02,751
that he's not gonna listen
to you,

677
00:27:02,775 --> 00:27:05,243
but he might listen
to somebody else.

678
00:27:09,315 --> 00:27:10,893
Just heard from Louis.

679
00:27:10,917 --> 00:27:12,311
He has the stomach flu,

680
00:27:12,335 --> 00:27:14,012
so I'm gonna have to step in
tonight.

681
00:27:14,036 --> 00:27:16,181
Oh, that's too bad.

682
00:27:16,205 --> 00:27:18,267
This wouldn't have anything
to do with him thinking

683
00:27:18,291 --> 00:27:19,968
you're in love with him,
would it?

684
00:27:19,992 --> 00:27:21,153
No idea.

685
00:27:21,177 --> 00:27:22,688
Feel like Sushi?

686
00:27:22,712 --> 00:27:24,856
Jeff, you can play
all the games that you want,

687
00:27:24,880 --> 00:27:27,159
but an all-night review
of the evidence

688
00:27:27,183 --> 00:27:28,994
is a waste of my time.

689
00:27:29,018 --> 00:27:30,913
So why don't you get
a couple of associates?

690
00:27:30,937 --> 00:27:33,332
And I will see you
in the morning.

691
00:27:33,356 --> 00:27:37,536
Listen, if you don't want
to be here, that's fine.

692
00:27:37,560 --> 00:27:39,037
But I am gonna do this
by myself,

693
00:27:39,061 --> 00:27:41,006
because I don't have associates
do my work.

694
00:27:41,030 --> 00:27:42,424
And why is that?

695
00:27:42,448 --> 00:27:44,566
Do you really want to know why?

696
00:27:48,020 --> 00:27:52,217
Dalton Foster was a con man
who somehow convinced

697
00:27:52,241 --> 00:27:55,187
terminally ill people to sign
over their insurance policies.

698
00:27:55,211 --> 00:27:57,723
Anyway,
he was my first big case,

699
00:27:57,747 --> 00:28:00,175
so I decided
that I would get some help

700
00:28:00,199 --> 00:28:04,863
going through the evidence,
just like this.

701
00:28:04,887 --> 00:28:07,015
The help screwed up.

702
00:28:07,039 --> 00:28:08,650
Dalton Foster walked.

703
00:28:08,674 --> 00:28:12,287
Six months later,
he pulled the exact same scam.

704
00:28:12,311 --> 00:28:14,156
Only this time, the problem was,

705
00:28:14,180 --> 00:28:17,859
one of his dying clients
had a miraculous recovery.

706
00:28:17,883 --> 00:28:22,553
So one day, Dalton came up
from behind her...

707
00:28:23,856 --> 00:28:26,491
And he beat her to death
with an aluminum bat.

708
00:28:28,527 --> 00:28:30,973
So am I glad you're here,
Jessica?

709
00:28:30,997 --> 00:28:32,374
Yes.

710
00:28:32,398 --> 00:28:33,976
Did I take advantage of Louis?

711
00:28:34,000 --> 00:28:35,377
Absolutely.

712
00:28:35,401 --> 00:28:38,680
I may play games
to get us together,

713
00:28:38,704 --> 00:28:42,401
but I never play games
with a case.

714
00:28:42,425 --> 00:28:44,676
Never.

715
00:28:51,417 --> 00:28:53,662
You have a minute?

716
00:28:53,686 --> 00:28:54,830
This must be serious.

717
00:28:54,854 --> 00:28:56,064
Why is that?

718
00:28:56,088 --> 00:28:57,749
Because you usually
just tell me what to do.

719
00:28:57,773 --> 00:29:00,168
Remember when you said
if I want you to deliver

720
00:29:00,192 --> 00:29:02,260
a message to Mike,
I should come to you directly?

721
00:29:05,064 --> 00:29:06,758
You want me to get him
to give up.

722
00:29:06,782 --> 00:29:08,877
If Mike doesn't give up tonight,

723
00:29:08,901 --> 00:29:10,712
Logan is gonna hire someone
to dig up

724
00:29:10,736 --> 00:29:13,715
everything they can on him.

725
00:29:13,739 --> 00:29:16,184
That's why you went to Gillis.

726
00:29:16,208 --> 00:29:17,769
You had no choice.

727
00:29:17,793 --> 00:29:20,588
That's not the way Mike saw it.

728
00:29:20,612 --> 00:29:23,392
You know, you could have come
to me before you did that.

729
00:29:23,416 --> 00:29:25,500
I'm coming to you now.

730
00:29:27,720 --> 00:29:28,780
How do I bill it?

731
00:29:28,804 --> 00:29:30,399
The same way we bill everything.

732
00:29:30,423 --> 00:29:33,224
Say it took twice as long
as it did.

733
00:29:43,769 --> 00:29:45,714
Okay, I take it back.

734
00:29:45,738 --> 00:29:46,998
My strategy?

735
00:29:47,022 --> 00:29:49,217
My strategy isn't
"knockout punch."

736
00:29:49,241 --> 00:29:51,336
We should've called it
"needle in a haystack."

737
00:29:51,360 --> 00:29:52,804
Getting frustrated?

738
00:29:52,828 --> 00:29:55,974
This guy?
This guy does not shut up.

739
00:29:55,998 --> 00:29:57,476
I now know about his bronchitis,

740
00:29:57,500 --> 00:29:59,311
his problems
with his dry cleaner,

741
00:29:59,335 --> 00:30:01,430
but absolutely no explanation
whatsoever

742
00:30:01,454 --> 00:30:02,814
about why he cashed out.

743
00:30:02,838 --> 00:30:04,850
Oh, you mean besides
being tipped that he invested

744
00:30:04,874 --> 00:30:06,234
in a giant Ponzi scheme.

745
00:30:06,258 --> 00:30:08,103
Wait.

746
00:30:08,127 --> 00:30:09,488
What?

747
00:30:09,512 --> 00:30:11,490
It's a call with an analyst
predicting a downturn

748
00:30:11,514 --> 00:30:14,443
in small-cap stocks
in the next quarter.

749
00:30:14,467 --> 00:30:18,887
Listen.

750
00:30:25,227 --> 00:30:27,839
The Ponzi fund was made up
of small-cap stocks.

751
00:30:27,863 --> 00:30:32,160
That's a legit reason for him
to have cashed out.

752
00:30:32,184 --> 00:30:35,964
Exactly what we need to get
the charges dropped.

753
00:30:35,988 --> 00:30:38,967
And exactly the kind of call
a junior attorney

754
00:30:38,991 --> 00:30:43,188
might have missed.

755
00:30:43,212 --> 00:30:45,340
So do you see why we needed
to do this together?

756
00:30:45,364 --> 00:30:46,915
Yes, I see.

757
00:30:56,809 --> 00:30:59,394
What is it?

758
00:31:04,316 --> 00:31:07,829
I have responsibilities that you

759
00:31:07,853 --> 00:31:10,132
just don't want to understand.

760
00:31:10,156 --> 00:31:12,667
No, I don't.

761
00:31:12,691 --> 00:31:16,555
I am the only woman partner

762
00:31:16,579 --> 00:31:19,007
at this level in the city.

763
00:31:19,031 --> 00:31:21,760
If word got out
that I hired a partner

764
00:31:21,784 --> 00:31:23,311
that I was
in a relationship with...

765
00:31:23,335 --> 00:31:25,096
What, you'd be disbarred?

766
00:31:25,120 --> 00:31:29,684
You think this is a joke.

767
00:31:29,708 --> 00:31:33,721
I think you're making excuses
for keeping me out of your life,

768
00:31:33,745 --> 00:31:35,490
Jessica,
and I'm calling you on it.

769
00:31:35,514 --> 00:31:37,025
Oh, what the hell is that
supposed to mean?

770
00:31:37,049 --> 00:31:40,495
It means that I'm making you
a promise, all right,

771
00:31:40,519 --> 00:31:42,664
that no one... no one will ever
find out about us,

772
00:31:42,688 --> 00:31:45,750
so if that's what
you're really afraid of,

773
00:31:45,774 --> 00:31:48,086
if that's what's truly
holding you back,

774
00:31:48,110 --> 00:31:50,195
then it is off the table.

775
00:31:56,318 --> 00:32:00,488
I'm sorry.

776
00:32:15,421 --> 00:32:17,983
Hey, so I know we said

777
00:32:18,007 --> 00:32:19,651
we're not supposed to talk
about the deal...

778
00:32:19,675 --> 00:32:22,844
Why did you lie to me?

779
00:32:25,898 --> 00:32:28,182
What are you talking about?

780
00:32:31,520 --> 00:32:33,131
When I asked you
about you and Logan,

781
00:32:33,155 --> 00:32:37,285
you said that you ended it.

782
00:32:37,309 --> 00:32:40,695
According to this,
you swore it was him.

783
00:32:44,833 --> 00:32:47,752
This is my deposition
from his divorce.

784
00:32:52,991 --> 00:32:54,603
You read this? Why... why would...

785
00:32:54,627 --> 00:32:58,573
He looked into me.
I looked into him.

786
00:32:58,597 --> 00:32:59,841
This is looking into me.

787
00:32:59,865 --> 00:33:02,143
You still haven't answered
the question.

788
00:33:02,167 --> 00:33:04,112
Mike, I told you the truth.

789
00:33:04,136 --> 00:33:08,149
Logan was trying to patch
things up with his wife,

790
00:33:08,173 --> 00:33:10,818
and he asked me to back
his story, so I did.

791
00:33:10,842 --> 00:33:15,674
You lied for him.

792
00:33:15,698 --> 00:33:17,699
You loved him that much.

793
00:33:18,901 --> 00:33:20,161
I told you that I loved him.

794
00:33:20,185 --> 00:33:23,798
Yeah,
but you didn't tell me that.

795
00:33:23,822 --> 00:33:25,517
And I've been sitting here
all night

796
00:33:25,541 --> 00:33:28,042
wondering why you wouldn't...

797
00:33:30,162 --> 00:33:32,797
Why wouldn't you tell me that?

798
00:33:40,255 --> 00:33:42,890
I'm gonna tell you now.

799
00:33:44,677 --> 00:33:48,456
We had an affair.

800
00:33:48,480 --> 00:33:53,461
We fell in love,
and he wanted to marry me,

801
00:33:53,485 --> 00:33:57,365
and I said no,

802
00:33:57,389 --> 00:34:01,469
and then three months later,
he had a change of heart,

803
00:34:01,493 --> 00:34:03,204
and he wanted to get back
with his wife

804
00:34:03,228 --> 00:34:05,507
during his divorce proceedings,
so he asked me to help him,

805
00:34:05,531 --> 00:34:10,044
and I did.

806
00:34:10,068 --> 00:34:13,315
But when he wanted to marry me,
I said no,

807
00:34:13,339 --> 00:34:17,819
because he wasn't the man
I want to spend my life with.

808
00:34:17,843 --> 00:34:20,762
You are.

809
00:34:34,476 --> 00:34:36,004
I love you.

810
00:34:36,028 --> 00:34:38,946
I love you too.

811
00:34:54,857 --> 00:34:56,301
Surprise.

812
00:34:56,325 --> 00:34:57,553
What? What? You have to go.

813
00:34:57,577 --> 00:34:58,671
- What are you talking about?
- She's here.

814
00:34:58,695 --> 00:35:01,873
Logan,
is there somebody at the door?

815
00:35:01,897 --> 00:35:03,726
Just...

816
00:35:03,750 --> 00:35:06,595
I am, um...
I'm from Pearson Hardman,

817
00:35:06,619 --> 00:35:09,738
and I... I had a few files
to bring your husband.

818
00:35:11,507 --> 00:35:13,902
Where are they?

819
00:35:13,926 --> 00:35:16,655
They're... they're right here.

820
00:35:16,679 --> 00:35:18,630
Um...

821
00:35:21,684 --> 00:35:23,278
Get out.

822
00:35:23,302 --> 00:35:24,697
Allison, what the hell?

823
00:35:24,721 --> 00:35:26,081
It is 7:30 in the morning.

824
00:35:26,105 --> 00:35:27,566
You think I'm an idiot?

825
00:35:27,590 --> 00:35:28,671
What are you talking about?

826
00:35:28,691 --> 00:35:29,952
I know that that's her.

827
00:35:29,976 --> 00:35:31,453
God, I told you I'm not...

828
00:35:31,477 --> 00:35:33,405
Stop lying to me.

829
00:35:33,429 --> 00:35:35,541
At least be a man
and admit that that's her.

830
00:35:35,565 --> 00:35:37,042
I don't even know that girl,
okay?

831
00:35:37,066 --> 00:35:38,711
And you think that if I was
having an affair

832
00:35:38,735 --> 00:35:42,604
that I would have it with a
paralegal from my father's firm?

833
00:35:58,054 --> 00:35:59,765
Rachel.

834
00:35:59,789 --> 00:36:02,100
I want you to stop
the personal attacks on Mike.

835
00:36:02,124 --> 00:36:03,485
I know.
It sounds terrible, but...

836
00:36:03,509 --> 00:36:04,787
And it's how the game is played.

837
00:36:04,811 --> 00:36:06,038
I don't care.

838
00:36:06,062 --> 00:36:09,208
I want you to stop.

839
00:36:09,232 --> 00:36:12,517
Look, can we talk
about this inside, please?

840
00:36:18,474 --> 00:36:19,802
I understand that you...

841
00:36:19,826 --> 00:36:22,921
No, look,
you say you're a changed man,

842
00:36:22,945 --> 00:36:26,475
but what you're doing now, it's
not a change for the better.

843
00:36:26,499 --> 00:36:27,843
It's for the worse.

844
00:36:27,867 --> 00:36:29,628
You told me
this wasn't gonna be a problem.

845
00:36:29,652 --> 00:36:34,633
And you stood right here
and told me

846
00:36:34,657 --> 00:36:36,819
that you didn't love your wife.

847
00:36:36,843 --> 00:36:38,904
And then three months later,

848
00:36:38,928 --> 00:36:42,858
you asked me to lie for you,
so you could get her back.

849
00:36:42,882 --> 00:36:44,443
Rachel...

850
00:36:44,467 --> 00:36:48,313
You don't have to stop this
because you're some changed man.

851
00:36:48,337 --> 00:36:51,807
You have to stop this, Logan,
because you owe me.

852
00:36:57,196 --> 00:36:59,447
Okay.

853
00:37:00,650 --> 00:37:03,451
Okay.

854
00:37:09,125 --> 00:37:10,469
Louis.

855
00:37:10,493 --> 00:37:12,938
Listen, I was up late,
I haven't had my coffee,

856
00:37:12,962 --> 00:37:16,642
so can we talk about whatever
this is in, like, an hour?

857
00:37:16,666 --> 00:37:18,727
I'll be quick.

858
00:37:18,751 --> 00:37:20,362
I ran into your enemy
this morning.

859
00:37:20,386 --> 00:37:22,865
You remember Adam Grieves?

860
00:37:22,889 --> 00:37:25,851
He asked me to tell you
that you guys

861
00:37:25,875 --> 00:37:27,152
are still on for ball
on Wednesday.

862
00:37:27,176 --> 00:37:28,353
Listen, Louis...

863
00:37:28,377 --> 00:37:30,455
Everything you told me,
it was bullshit.

864
00:37:30,479 --> 00:37:33,525
You're not trying to get
into my pants.

865
00:37:33,549 --> 00:37:36,328
You're trying to get
into Jessica's.

866
00:37:36,352 --> 00:37:38,247
You thought you could move
your way up the ladder,

867
00:37:38,271 --> 00:37:41,216
and you used my friendship
to cozy up to her.

868
00:37:41,240 --> 00:37:42,801
Louis, that's just not true.

869
00:37:42,825 --> 00:37:45,704
Well, then, what is it?

870
00:37:45,728 --> 00:37:49,197
Why did you lie to me
to get me off this case?

871
00:37:55,571 --> 00:37:59,875
Tell me what I'm missing here,
Jeff.

872
00:38:04,046 --> 00:38:06,057
That's what I thought.

873
00:38:06,081 --> 00:38:07,743
Louis, please...

874
00:38:07,767 --> 00:38:11,079
For once I let my guard down
and believed that someone

875
00:38:11,103 --> 00:38:14,356
genuinely liked me
without a hidden agenda.

876
00:38:17,310 --> 00:38:21,029
I will not make that mistake
again.

877
00:38:33,659 --> 00:38:37,222
I'm here to see Mike Ross.

878
00:38:37,246 --> 00:38:39,308
What the hell are you
doing here?

879
00:38:39,332 --> 00:38:41,894
I came to see you.

880
00:38:41,918 --> 00:38:43,946
I have a meeting.

881
00:38:43,970 --> 00:38:47,866
I came to apologize.

882
00:38:47,890 --> 00:38:49,651
For what?

883
00:38:49,675 --> 00:38:52,270
For trying to win dirty.

884
00:38:52,294 --> 00:38:56,291
I can't undo what I've already
done, but I can stop doing it.

885
00:38:56,315 --> 00:39:00,612
I don't want to win that way.

886
00:39:00,636 --> 00:39:02,414
That sounds like something
your publicist

887
00:39:02,438 --> 00:39:05,951
would tell Forbes.

888
00:39:05,975 --> 00:39:09,421
Why don't you tell me
why you're really here?

889
00:39:09,445 --> 00:39:13,141
You want the truth?

890
00:39:13,165 --> 00:39:16,701
I don't want to hurt Rachel.

891
00:39:38,340 --> 00:39:41,003
Walter.

892
00:39:41,027 --> 00:39:42,871
I have nothing to say to you.

893
00:39:42,895 --> 00:39:45,323
Walter, please.

894
00:39:45,347 --> 00:39:46,959
You have 30 seconds.

895
00:39:46,983 --> 00:39:50,178
Okay, look, I get it.

896
00:39:50,202 --> 00:39:51,847
I tried to tell you
there's more to the story.

897
00:39:51,871 --> 00:39:53,048
You didn't want to hear it then,

898
00:39:53,072 --> 00:39:54,499
and you don't want
to hear it now.

899
00:39:54,523 --> 00:39:56,551
But you need to hear this.

900
00:39:56,575 --> 00:39:58,503
Whether you like me or not,

901
00:39:58,527 --> 00:39:59,855
I am the only one
in your corner,

902
00:39:59,879 --> 00:40:02,641
and you know it.

903
00:40:02,665 --> 00:40:07,195
I started this company
with no one to trust but myself.

904
00:40:07,219 --> 00:40:09,281
That's how I go out,

905
00:40:09,305 --> 00:40:10,849
so be it. We're done.

906
00:40:10,873 --> 00:40:12,150
Well, I'm sorry to hear that,

907
00:40:12,174 --> 00:40:14,619
because I'm gonna be
in your corner anyway.

908
00:40:14,643 --> 00:40:17,188
I just bought another 2%
of your stock,

909
00:40:17,212 --> 00:40:19,524
which means
I'm saving your company

910
00:40:19,548 --> 00:40:22,817
with or without you.

911
00:40:24,904 --> 00:40:28,723
Time's up.
I don't want to see you again.

912
00:40:49,178 --> 00:40:50,939
Jeff, it's late.

913
00:40:50,963 --> 00:40:55,827
It's not about us.

914
00:40:55,851 --> 00:40:57,062
Woodall.

915
00:40:57,086 --> 00:40:59,064
It started.

916
00:40:59,088 --> 00:41:00,749
How many?

917
00:41:00,773 --> 00:41:03,201
Seven clients, seven subpoenas,

918
00:41:03,225 --> 00:41:05,810
all coming tomorrow.

919
00:41:08,531 --> 00:41:11,733
It's time for you
to start earning your money.

920
00:41:28,584 --> 00:41:30,812
You get me a present?

921
00:41:30,836 --> 00:41:33,338
It's from Mike.

922
00:41:36,308 --> 00:41:37,786
It's my dad's tapes.

923
00:41:37,810 --> 00:41:41,073
He said they're yours.

924
00:41:41,097 --> 00:41:42,791
You got him to back down.

925
00:41:42,815 --> 00:41:47,662
No, but I got Logan to back off.

926
00:41:47,686 --> 00:41:50,582
How'd you manage that?

927
00:41:50,606 --> 00:41:52,306
It's between me and my client.

928
00:41:56,112 --> 00:41:59,457
You know, you could have come
to me first.

929
00:41:59,481 --> 00:42:01,166
I'm coming to you now.

930
00:42:09,198 --> 00:42:15,198
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man

