[Car horn blares]
You're late.
Nope. 30 seconds early.
Good. Learning to tell time.
Ha ha ha.
I won't be in today.
What? Does Jessica know?
I don't tell Jessica
everything.
Oh, it's like a "Harvey
Specter's day off"
kind of a thing?
Should I call Ed Rooney,
see if we can
get Sloane out of school?
Not in the mood today.
Life moves pretty fast
if you don't
stop and look around
once in a while.
What do you think about
Hardman running for
managing partner?
- Think he's going to win.
- Why?
Because you don't
call for a vote
unless you have the votes.
Good.
We need to tip the scales
in her favor.
Okay. What do you
need me to do?
I need you to step up.
You're not going to like it.
And Jessica can't know
it came from me.
I gave Hardman the road map
to settling with Tanner.
You voted for it.
Haven't we done enough
to Jessica?
We're not doing this
to Jessica,
we're doing this for Jessica.
We gonna cross the line
with this?
We've been crossing lines
long before we even ever met.
How do I know the Patriots
aren't going 19-0?
Because no team from Boston
is going undefeated
when the road
goes through New York.
You got that right.
Goddamn Patriots.
- Your dad called.
- I'll call him later.
He always asks why
the idiots in charge
haven't made you partner yet.
He's so proud. It's sweet.
He's right.
You have that look
on your face.
Louis is getting a secretary.
Her name...
is Norma.
What is she, 100 years old?
She won't last a week.
You heard it here first.
Oh, and Jessica's
on her way down.
So, you buried the Jessica news
to lead with the Louis news.
I'm not apologizing
for who I am.
[Knocking, door squeaking open]
Hi, is this the location of
the douchebag convention?
It is now.
I thought you went to work.
- I had to get this.
- Whoa.
Look at that.
The world's smallest burrito.
Which is why I got more.
Whoa. Breakfast of champions.
Trevor, I can't.
I'm a bike messenger.
I deliver packages,
or people die.
Am I gonna have to give you
a code red?
Both: Mm...
- Okay.
- Ohh.
All you did was weaken
a country today, Kaffee.
Well, what can I say?
Really? Okay.
- I gotta go to work.
- Thank you.
Remember, we're going out
tonight, so...
you know, don't be you.
Oh, wait a minute. I still
owe you from last week.
No, no, no, you get
the dickhead discount.
Oh, is that 30%? Or is that
the shitface coupon?
Same thing, because you're
a shitface and a dickhead.
Right, got it.
Have a great day!
Later, asshole.
Later. [Door closes]
Shit.
I need your help on something.
Show me the skulls,
I'll crack 'em.
Not for this. For this,
I need your discretion.
I also need to know
you'll take it seriously.
I haven't worked in
the mail room
in a long time, Jessica.
Someone's stealing from our
clients' escrow accounts.
Why isn't Daniel here?
Daniel's managing partner.
Isn't that why Daniel
should be here?
And I'm in charge of the money.
Oh, you want to go to him with
a solution, not a problem.
You don't always have to
let your superiors know
what you're up to.
I'll try to remember that.
Really? I thought you were
under the impression
you had invented it.
What do you need me to do?
I need you to step up.
Do whatever you have to do
to find out who did it,
and do it quietly. I will.
And when I do,
I want you to step up for me.
What do you want, Harvey?
I'm an associate
who kicks more ass
than any partner
in this goddamn firm.
I want a seat at the table.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right
♪ all that time imagine this ♪
♪ The greenback boogie
There's so many partners,
it could be anyone of them.
Watson scares the kids,
but I don't make him
for the embezzler.
The embezzler?
He's not a Batman villain.
And it's just that kind of
thinking that has led you
to not catching him.
I was just assigned this
15 minutes ago.
Have you ever looked into
Dortch's eyes?
- Yeah, he's cross-eyed.
- Or is he?
What does that even mean?
Is there a reward for this?
Yes. I make Jessica happy,
I make partner.
Ooh, then we get
a bigger office.
Then I get a bigger office.
Hey, I'm helping you out here.
Are you?
What do you think
about Ginsberg?
We need to follow the money.
Which will lead
straight to Rutherford.
This would be so much more fun
with margaritas.
Okay, that's it. I need facts,
and I need them right now.
Well then,
why did you ask me to
guess who did it?
I didn't.
- Then why am I here?
- I need you to tell me
who handles these five
escrow accounts.
Oh. Well, that's easy.
Zoe.
God, why didn't you just say so
in the first place?
Get out.
If you want to talk to
Monica Eton,
call her yourself.
I called her, but she hung up
the minute I said
Pearson Hardman.
Of course she did.
She hates everybody here.
- She doesn't hate you.
- Well, no,
but that's because
I'm adorable.
See, I can't help you
with that.
So why don't you try using
your powers of adorability
for good? Not a word.
And that is not being adorable.
Mike, seriously, this is
not a small thing.
Look, the last time you
asked me to help you
it was about Donna, and look at
how that turned out.
Okay, that wasn't me,
and this isn't that...
Monica Eton is not Donna.
Maybe not, but she still
means something to me.
So tell me why I should
convince her to talk to someone
who works at a firm
that she hates.
Because...
You don't know
the real reason why she left.
Monica.
Hey, it's so funny
running into you.
Louis, we both work here.
Yeah. Listen, I just wanted
to tell you that
I joined
the Hudson Racquet Club.
You know, I just figured
I'd treat myself
for making junior partner.
Good for you.
Yeah, I'd love to get you
out on the court.
Maybe like, if you're
available Saturday?
- I can't.
- I can't Saturday, but...
Monica, Louis.
- Harvey.
- H-dog.
- No.
- What?
No, listen. I wanted to
talk to you about...
Cashing and burning
with Monica?
I didn't crash and burn
with her.
So why don't you stop quoting
whatever "B" movie
that came from, and call me
when you finally see Amadeus.
Salieri, Mozart.
Are you wearing braces?
- Proudly.
- Walk me through that.
I will walk you through it.
Uh, for starters,
it costs $15,000...
Okay, I don't have time
for this.
I heard you had a closed-door
meeting with Jessica.
I did. Or I didn't.
Either way, it's
none of your business.
I just think it's weird
when, you know,
you have a one-on-one with her,
when you're an associate
and I'm a junior partner.
Proudly wearing braces.
You mi... for your information,
it is a very small step
from junior to senior partner
when you have straight teeth.
Just know that people take you
very seriously.
[Snapping fingers]
That tie. I have the same one.
I don't want to see it again.
What would he have said if you
weren't wearing braces?
What a dick.
Mark my words, if I am ever
in charge of anyone,
I am going to be the most
beloved leader
that those lucky bastards
have ever seen.
You know what I'd do, I'd be...
H-dog? H-dog?
Zoe Lawford.
I'm sorry, you are?
The only man here who could
beat you at pool.
Uh, head-to-head is even.
I'm up by one.
Well, I thought you'd
given up altogether.
You don't call,
you don't write.
I was just trying to give it
a little time.
You know, letting mystery
build back up.
You mean you didn't know
I transferred
to beautiful escrow.
Hey, I have my finger
on the pulse.
[Laughing] Really?
Name three associates
in tax law.
Boring, more boring,
and boring in a skirt.
Oh! August 3rd.
Date of my transfer.
I did know.
We miss you up there.
We miss me, or you miss me?
We miss you.
I need you.
You're here to look at my
files, aren't you?
I need you to type in
your password
and leave for five minutes.
You're doing something wrong.
No, I'm fixing something wrong.
- Fixing what?
- That, I can't tell you.
Why? Don't trust me?
I do. But if I tell you,
then I'm breaking
someone's trust in me.
Okay, let me just
get this straight.
You're asking me
to risk my job to help you
solve a mysterious problem
for an unknown person,
based on nothing but your word?
That's exactly what I'm asking.
Ahh.
[Keyboard clacking]
Oh my God, there's an emergency
in wills and trusts.
Thank you. Cheers.
[Bottles clinking]
You ready?
I am. Hit me, hit me.
All right, um... All right.
This guy. Favorite movie.
Grease.
Both: 2.
- Yes, I agree with you.
Oh. What about this,
Rico Suave over here,
what are you thinking?
Shaves his chest.
No. No, no, man,
that's a thing that like,
real men do now.
Oh, I don't think so.
- Yeah...
- I'm sorry,
did you just say real men
shave their chests?
Oh, um, not... not real men.
Just me. That's all.
I like him. He's funny.
- And hairless.
- Oh, I'm Jenny.
Mike.
And just so you guys know, uh,
he shaves his chest
because he is, I'm very proud
of him, an Olympic swimmer.
- I am.
- Is that right?
So that's what you do when you
meet girls, you lie?
- Totally.
- If they're hot.
We also buy them drinks,
I'm not sure if...
- Oh, we drink.
- Uh, yeah.
- Bartender?
- Yeah? No, go for it.
Wait, no way a girl
thought you were
a point guard for the Knicks.
Well, you've never
seen me dribble.
Uh, I would like to know
something about you
that's not a lie.
Ooh.
Um...
I love my grandmother.
Well, now we know why
he's single.
Come on, it's kind of sweet.
Look, I...
I'm not usually in it for him,
but I really gotta
step in here.
Um...
Dude's a genius. Trevor, stop.
- No, no, no...
- What do you mean, genius?
- All right.
- It's not a thing, it's just...
No, no, no, here we go.
Ask him a math question.
Hard as you want.
- Trevor.
- Hard as you want!
Anything.
What's 75 times 863,
minus 10?
64,715.
- Bang.
- How do we know that's right?
Uh, it's right. It's right.
All right, think of a book
you read in high school,
he will recite the first page...
I don't want to do this,
- Verbatim.
- I don't want to do it.
Come on, come on, come on,
just do it... do it for me.
Moby Dick.
"Call me Ishmael.
Some years ago,"
"never mind how long ago
precisely,"
"having little or no money..."
Old Man and the Sea.
"The box with the baits was
under the stern of the skiff"
"along with the club that was
used to subdue the big fish..."
I know that one,
that's not right.
Oh, no, no, no.
I got bored, I did page seven.
Curious George.
I can't.
I can't do that.
What? Come on, you can do
the other ones, you don't know
Curious George?
I never read Curious George.
You never read Curious George?
Monkeys freak me out.
My girlfriend and I
have to go to the bathroom.
Mmhmm.
I have to go to the bathroom.
And when we come back,
these drinkies...
Will be filled.
Absolutely, 100%.
[Sighs heavily]
Dude, what are you doing?
Are you trying to blow this?
What are you talking about?
I know that you have
Curious George,
I've seen it on your bookshelf.
For once, we don't have to lie.
My mom gave me that book.
She read it to me every night.
I'm not going to use it
to just pick up some girl.
You don't have to do anything.
Let me tell them. Okay?
You'll probably go home
with both of them.
Trevor. Stop.
Fine.
I hate your guts.
I followed the money.
Let's hear it.
Louis Litt is the man
we're looking for.
Are you sure?
I told you
I followed the money.
Which, by the way, he's been
spending left and right.
You're talking about
the braces.
$15,000.
Not to mention
the Hudson Racquet Club.
Who knows what else?
That club costs $60,000 a year.
What are you going to do?
I'm gonna break him down,
and I'm gonna crack him open.
[Knocking on glass door ]
You wanted to see me?
I did.
Well, if this is about Norma?
Truth be told, we can
do a lot better.
This isn't about Norma.
Pray tell.
How can your your newest
junior partner
be of service to thee?
Pray tell?
You can pray tell me
how the hell you got the nerve
to stand in front of my face
after what you did.
I couldn't help it.
All those late nights.
Your fibers are so tantalizing.
What?
I fell asleep on your couch,
just once, because it's
so damn soft.
Not the topic of
this conversation.
Is this about
the MySpace profile?
Because I can take that down.
Okay, fine.
You got me.
I've copied the complete
works of Shakespeare
and I've charged it to
those bastards at C.M.,
I regularly raid Harvey's
liquor, and I've
taken every raspberry-bran bar
from the kitchen
that we've ever bought... Louis...
I need to know where
Stanley gets them, do you?
Enough!
Well, should I just...
what, pack my things?
Not necessary.
Thank you, Jessica.
Thank you for your mercy.
Louis.
Yeah.
You will replace every one of
those goddamn bran bars.
Yes.
And, I promise not to walk
barefoot in the library
ever again. Out.
Okay.
Next time you bring me a name,
make goddamn sure
it's the right one.
I followed the money.
You got lost on the way.
You saying Louis was framed?
I'm saying you shit the bed.
I gave you a job to do,
and you promptly
asked for a seat at the table.
You want to sit
with the grown-ups?
Do your job like a man.
Ouch.
What?
You need me to remove
Jessica's foot from your ass?
You heard all that?
Intercom was on.
Couldn't help myself.
Has it ever been on before?
Has it ever been off?
Wait, what?
I listen to your
private conversations?
Gotta go.
- Wait.
- What?
I don't like to be wrong.
It made sense, Harvey.
Louis is the firm's
financial wizard.
Look. Louis might not
have done it,
but he can help me
figure out who did.
You're going to ask Louis
for help on something this big?
When a dog smells a bone,
he digs.
Doesn't mean you
have to tell him
what kind of bone
he's digging for.
Just so we're clear,
I'm gonna keep listening to
your private conversations.
- Pickles.
- Peppers.
Here you go.
Here you go. That's fine.
Oh yeah, that girl Nikki
called me.
Oh, that's awesome.
I don't even know how she got
my number, it's weird.
I do.
I asked her out.
She wanted your number instead.
I didn't tell her about
the Curious George thing.
What?
I don't know, it's...
I just felt like I kind of
hit it off more
with that Jenny girl,
that's all.
The blonde?
She's not even as hot.
I liked her better.
Well, you can't
do anything now.
Girls have rules about
that kind of shit.
Wait a minute.
Are you... is this a snake?
Are you snaking my girl
right now?
No, I already did.
- You called her?
- Of course I did.
- What a dick.
- [Laughing] What?
- Son of a bitch.
- I... I don't have
rules against that shit. Okay.
Aw, whatever. That Nikki girl's
pretty hot too.
Yeah.
Look at this clown.
He walks like he's got
a rod up his ass.
Nice haircut, guy.
Man, if I ever look like that,
shoot me.
Monica, you work late
all the time.
I'm not 22. You are.
All I'm saying is, you work
80 hours a week
while studying for the LSATs
every night.
Well right, but that's because
this time next year
I want to be in law school,
and five years from now
I want to be a lawyer.
Five years from now,
you're gonna be
a kick-ass lawyer
at Pearson Hardman.
How often does Louis
ask you out?
Every single day.
There are laws
to protect you from
sexual harassment, you know.
Believe me, the day I need
a law to protect me from Louis
is the day I stop
being a lawyer.
Busy?
Very funny, Harvey, let's get
to it, okay?
Because you happen to be
interrupting
my lunchtime sanctuary.
You think I don't know
lunchtime sanctuary
means staring at Monica?
First of all,
I'll have you know that
I have been coming here
way before her.
And I will be coming here
every Thursday at 1:00 p.m.
till the day I die.
Now let me see your friend's
financials.
Why are the names
all blacked out?
Because of how sensitive it is.
How sensitive is it?
He works at a powerful firm.
I can't tell you which one.
They have an embezzler.
Ahh, so that's what your
closed-door meeting
with Jessica was about.
We're being hired
by another firm.
I'm sworn to secrecy.
If we can figure out
who this is,
a very big head will roll.
Where? Hufton and Wood?
Bagwell and Rose?
Oh, come on. Those assholes
at Jacobson and Kearney?
[Whispering] Look, I told you,
I was sworn to secrecy.
My God, this is just like
a maze of raw data.
Can you make any sense of it?
Yeah, I already have.
Look at this.
See?
He's setting up this patsy
to take the fall.
He's not even gonna see it
coming, what a "smuck."
I'm sorry, did...
did you just say,
what a "smuck?"
No, I said what a "smuck."
You mean schmuck.
Huh?
You know a schmuck, right?
"Smuck."
Monica?
Mike Ross.
Can I join you?
Chair's empty.
I appreciate it.
Rachel said this was about
one of my old cases?
This is a lawsuit that we just
drew up in your name,
seeking $10 million in damages
from Pearson Hardman.
Should have seen this coming.
Five years ago you got screwed.
One way to put it.
You had options
you didn't explore.
And you're
exploring them for me.
I can make what stopped you
before go away, yes.
Harvey will back your claim.
What about Jessica?
You don't need Jessica.
Why are you doing this?
Does it matter?
No. It doesn't.
I don't want anything
to do with this.
Last five years haven't been
easy for you, have they?
You don't know
anything about me.
I know you've been
working retail.
It's a boutique
on Park Avenue, right?
It's a good job, you're making
what, maybe 40 grand a year?
This is Manhattan.
What, are you covering rent
with that?
So you're the new attack dog.
Well, Spot,
I'm not revisiting a story
I spent the last five years
trying to forget.
Just take it with you.
You may change your mind.
And if you call me,
I'll come fetch.
- It's Daniel Hardman.
- What?
He's been playing a shell game.
He's moving money out of one
account and into another.
For an entire year.
Your partner sold you out.
Daniel has never done
anything unethical.
And the fact that
you don't like him...
I know, isn't reason
to falsely accuse him.
I'm not.
You falsely accused Louis.
I stake my career on this.
You are.
He did it.
Shit.
He did.
You have to go to the D.A.
I'm going to Daniel.
Who's not doing their job
like a man now?
I'm giving him the courtesy
of explaining himself.
You shouldn't.
What you do if it were me?
[Knocking door ]
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Come in.
- Oh. Thanks.
Oh...
Are those for me, probably?
Yeah. That's a thing, right?
Uh, bringing flowers
for the roommate of
the girl you're taking...
you're just gonna take
one of those, okay.
Who's gonna tell her?
You? Lieutenant Weinberg?
That's from.
- A Few Good Men.
- Yeah.
Yeah. I get HBO.
[Mouthing words] I love you!
Uh, Nikki is gonna be out
any minute, so...
Am I dressed okay, for her?
[mouthing words]
Yeah, uh, you look fine.
- Good?
- Yeah.
Would... can you me the truth?
You don't want the truth.
"'Cause deep down
in places you don't
[together] "talk about at
parties, you want me"
"on that wall,
you need me on that wall..."
Hey, Nikki.
Hi.
Uh, wow.
Those look beautiful.
Ohuh, yeah... um,
so... so, do you.
So they-I'm gonna go
put these in water. Okay.
[Whispering] You liar.
Look at her.
You did want to look perfect
on your first date.
Yeah, I do.
Ready?
Yeah, I'm ready. Are...
- are you ready?
- Yeah.
Then we, ready.
For dinner. Everyone's ready,
- isn't that great?
- Good Night.
That great?
Something I can help you with?
Yon help me understand why
you've been stealing
from our clients.
Jessica, I can...
Oh, God damn Daniel.
It was for Alicia.
She's dying.
What?
Breast cancer.
Stage four.
Why didn't you say anything?
She found a lump a year ago.
It was the worst day
of our lives.
I have no words.
I thought I could
handle it myself.
And the money?
Treatments.
Not covered by insurance.
Why not?
They're not in the books.
But I don't care.
She's not dying because
I didn't spend the money.
You stole $1/2 million.
I don't expect you
to forgive me.
What do you expect?
I honestly don't know.
Wild Maine salmon,
braised fennel
mushroom polenta,
arugula salad,
and do you really need
to keep doing this?
U really are a genius.
Sexy, right?
What'd you get on your SATs?
Ooh, 1590.
Yeah, it was an ambiguous
question, I don't know.
I really don't like
to talk about it.
Oh, no, no, no.
Here, let me get that,
c'mon. Parents' plastic.
They're cool.
Cool.
Listen, um...
Why don't we go back
to your place, cause
I'm live in Brooklyn,
and I kinda in
a strange roommate situation...
I want to pay you $1000
to take the LSATs for me.
Oh.
What?
That's why you snaked me
from Jenny.
I don't know what you're
talking about. Unbelievable.
We're not all born geniuses.
And I need your help.
Yeah, you might not
be a genius,
but you know exactly
what you're doing.
And you're not getting my help.
Come on.
What do you want?
Oh, I don't want anything.
Because I'm not
your trained monkey.
Tell your mommy thanks
for dinner.
Grammy!
Oh my God, what's the matter?
Bob, what happened?
Relax, Mike.
Edith's fine, I'm just gonna
go get her a glass of water.
Grammy, here, look at me.
What happened?
I don't know.
I think the floor was wet.
The floor was wet,
how did the floor get wet?
Well, it happened fast.
But I'm okay.
But, what are you doing here?
I thought you had a date.
Uh, it di...
no, it didn't work out.
So, you came to see
your grandmother.
That's not normal, Michael.
Rea... are we gonna do this,
right now?
- Hey.
- Thank you, Bob,
I really appreciate it.
That's what neighbors are for.
Here, you drink that,
and we'll be right back.
Okay?
- For what it's worth...
- Uh-huh.
[Whispering] The floor wasn't
wet.
You know, if I were you, I'd get
full-time care for Edith.
- Are you crazy?
- Did you hear me?
His wife's dying of cancer.
So you're going to
let him walk?
No, nobody's walking.
The firm's taking out a loan
against its assets.
Daniel will pay it back.
Great. My dad has gout,
can I have $1 million?
Coldhearted son of a bitch.
You know those Tuesday lunches
at the Harvard Club?
He's taking Alicia to chemo.
He stole from our clients,
which means he's stealing
from us.
When it was Louis,
you were ready to break him down
and crack him open.
Daniel is the reason
why I'm here.
He plucked me from the bullpen
when I didn't know my ass
from my elbow.
He saw a star
to hitch his wagon to.
This is Manhattan, Harvey.
How many black women do you see
with their name on the door?
You know what, he was smart
to put your name first.
That way you might not notice
that you'd always be number two.
- Careful, Harvey.
- Then again,
maybe you're okay staying
number two... Scottie Pippen...
Don't pull that shit on me.
We made a deal,
and I honored it.
It's time for you to honor it.
Wow, a man's wife's dying,
and the first words out
of your mouth are "you owe me."
Who's the bad guy now?
[Clears throat]
You asked me what
it's gonna take.
It's gonna take $5,000.
- Keep your voice down.
- Why, am I making you nervous?
Yes.
Good. Now you know
how I'm gonna feel.
You're asking me
to expose myself
so that you can go
make a fortune.
So either you figure out
how to pay me,
or you roll the dice
on your own.
But trust me when I tell you,
these tests aren't easy.
Well, they are for me.
Okay.
Good.
What made you change your mind?
None of your business.
- You're not Monica.
- Oh, no, I'm...
- Rachel Zane.
- How did you know that?
I'm Donna. I know everything.
- Everything?
- You started three months ago,
you have a peach yogurt
every morning,
you've got a cute pair
of suede pumps
I totally plan on stealing,
and your father's Robert Zane,
name partner at Rand,
Kaldor, and Zane.
And, apparently, you don't like
people knowing who your dad is.
Well, they just...
they treat you differently.
Your secret's safe with me.
No, it doesn't really matter.
I won't be here that long.
It is the cafeteria?
Because it is way better
than it used to be.
Nope.
I live for foie gras Fridays.
- They don't have that.
- Don't they?
You're weird. We'll be friends.
Anyway, I should go.
I'm just gonna leave
this stuff here for Monica.
She should be back pretty soon.
She just has Tuesday pilates
at Chelsea Pier.
Every Tuesday?
Now, I thought
you knew everything.
I do.
What are you so bouncy about?
You're gonna be so happy
that I listen to your intercom.
[Doorbell rings]
Who is it?
Room service.
What are you doing here?
Delivering champagne.
I see you can afford it
since the money you've been
stealing from our clients
hasn't been going to
your wife's cancer treatments.
Hey, Monica, how's it going?
- Harvey.
- Daniel and I need a minute.
Letter of resignation.
You're gonna sign it,
and then name Jessica
as your successor.
I don't think so.
Unflinching in the face
of defeat.
It's not defeat.
You come after me
for embezzlement,
every Pearson Hardman client
you've got is gone.
Which is why Jessica
won't let me do that.
Then why are you here?
Waiting for your wife.
What are you talking about?
She's invited to a fund raiser.
She'll be at the front desk
in three minutes.
You don't sign, they'll send her
up to this room.
You do sign, they'll send her
to another room.
You dragged a woman
racked with cancer here
to blackmail me?
You think it's me
she's gonna have issue with?
You goddamn bastard.
Says the man cheating
on his dying wife.
- You don't know anything.
- I do.
I've seen you with her,
and I know you love her.
And this has nothing to do
with that.
I also know that you don't want
the rest of Alicia's life
spent picturing this.
If she wasn't sick,
she could probably get over it.
She's not getting
any better, Daniel.
You have two minutes.
It's your call.
[Knock on door]
There's something
I think you should know.
Please.
Mike Ross had lunch
with Monica Eton today.
I saw him hand her a filing.
And why do you think
this concerns me?
I just think that their meeting
on the eve
of the firm's vote suggests
that Jessica's making a move.
You've been good to me
since you've been back.
She hasn't.
Do what you will.
About time.
I wasn't sure you'd make it.
Especially since
you didn't give me a reason.
I've got about 5,000 reasons.
We'll be fine.
Oh, my God, you're high.
- I'm fine.
- Are you crazy?
I'm about to do
something illegal, okay?
It helps calm me down.
Great, you'll be calm.
How the hell are you gonna
handle the test?
I don't know,
maybe the same way I handled
your little quiz
the other night.
- You were high.
- And drunk.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I've got a test to take.
And I've gotta miss a couple
of questions on purpose.
It's done. Hardman's gone.
Harvey...
What is it?
I don't know how to say this.
Just say it, Donna. What?
Your dad...
he had a heart attack.
Harvey, I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
[Quietly, voice quivering]
Oh, my God.
- Good morning, Monica.
- Jessica.
You look tired. Did you get
much rest last night?
- I want to explain.
- I'm not here for excuses.
Then why are you here?
- To see you off.
- My relationship with Daniel
has nothing to do
with my work here.
I need to know
I can trust my people.
You're not my people.
You can't fire me.
I'll sue for wrongful
termination.
Which will lead me
to implicate you
in Daniel's crimes.
- I had nothing to do with that.
- Didn't you?
Diamond earrings,
diamond bracelet,
and trips to, let's see now...
Mexico... France... Hong Kong.
Hope you liked that one.
- I didn't know.
- I don't care.
You are
a Harvard-educated lawyer.
Do you think that a jury
will believe
you had no idea
where that money came from?
Don't do this.
Louis will accept
your resignation,
and I will never
see you here again.
I expected a fight,
but not a dirty one.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Mike Ross met with Monica Eton.
And what does that have
to do with me?
I am disappointed that
you felt the need to go there.
I'm disappointed
you think I did.
You really expect me
to believe that you didn't...
Stop right there!
You know,
you might fight dirty,
and Harvey might fight dirty,
but I don't.
What the hell are you doing?
Trying to get Monica Eton to
file a sexual harassment suit
against Daniel Hardman?
Okay she left because
of their affair,
which he paid for
with embezzled money.
- That was five years ago.
- And her life fell apart!
I know you think
you're trying to help me,
but drop it, immediately.
Wow. That's what
all this was about?
Nice performance.
I'm trying to help Jessica.
Mike, you cannot
keep me in the dark.
Not when you're the one
asking me for help.
Couldn't take the chance
that you wouldn't help.
You told me it was about
one of Monica's old cases.
You lied like it's
second nature.
Our backs are against the wall.
I did what I had to do.
And you're proud of that?
Rachel, sometimes
you have to cross a line
to do the right thing. Wow...
Harvey has really
rubbed off on you.
I didn't learn that
from Harvey.
Heh.
Holy shit, dude.
Pays to be a nerd.
Yeah, but you still
don't get the girls.
I don't know,
I guess I'm gonna use this
to get my grandma some help.
Too bad it was
a one-time-only deal.
Actually, she has three friends
who want to use
my services, so...
- Oh, good.
- We're in business.
'Cause you're gonna need
to start paying
all the rent around here.
What?
Oh, did you think
you were the only one
stepping up his game?
Meaning?
[Chuckles]
What? Trevor, no, no, no.
Not a good idea.
No.
Which is why I'm moving out.
Unless you want in,
in which case,
you know, I'm still moving out.
But we could go together...
move into a much,
much nicer apartment.
[Knock on door] That's Jenny.
First date.
Could you not tell her
about this?
Go get the door.
Unbelievable.
[Sighs] Jenny.
Aren't you a sight
for sore eyes.
Daniel came in last night
to pick up his things.
Threw a phone at my head.
You duck,
or is his aim that bad?
- He throws like a girl.
- I'm not surprised.
You needed me?
I wanted you to be
the first to know.
We have a new partner.
Andrew McCutcheon.
Solid candidate.
A simple thank you
would suffice.
Me thank you? Never.
Well, I have a partners
meeting in five minutes.
I'm gonna break the news
that I'm taking Daniel's office.
- Who's taking yours?
- I'm looking at him.
Jessica...
Thank you.
One last tip.
Don't let Louis in here
after hours.
Finally an office big enough
for your balls.
Okay, I am not touching
that one.
You would if you had
bigger balls.
Hold on a sec, did you listen
on Jessica's intercom?
- No. She told me.
- Before me?
Well, I was the one
to figure it out about Daniel.
Oh, and how did she know that?
Let's just focus
on what's important.
You just made partner.
We just made partner.
I'll grab the can opener.
Whoa, whoa,
that's pre-trial ritual.
We're making an exception.
- I'll get the thumbtacks.
- Two dozen?
- Three dozen.
- Ooh, going for the record!
- Zoe.
- Harvey.
Is word out already?
Word about what?
Oh, don't be coy.
I just made partner.
You're here to congratulate me.
I knew it.
It was Hardman, wasn't it?
What do you want me to say?
Nothing.
I know how it is around here.
Secrets and lies...
standard procedure.
I didn't build
the sandbox, Zoe.
No, you just like
to play in it.
- And you don't?
- No.
And I don't like watching
what it's doing
to a man I care about.
- Zoe...
- I'm leaving.
Today's my last day.
Because of this?
Look, I did what I did
for the good of the firm.
You think that's
what I'm talking about?
Do you know what this is?
It's my condolences,
which I expected to leave
on your desk,
because I thought you'd be out
mourning your father.
- I had...
- What, bigger fish to fry?
Don't you see?
That's what this place does.
There's always bigger fish.
I am dealing how I deal.
Harvey, you've lost your way.
How'd it go yesterday?
Fine. Mike pull it off?
- Yep.
- He suspect you were in on it?
- Nope.
- Well, now they know.
Gonna swing us some votes.
We threw Daniel's ass out
once, we'll do it again.
- Damn right.
- One more thing.
I'm getting Donna back.