.
- Mike Ross is a fraud,
and I'm gonna make sure
he never sees the inside
of a courtroom again
unless he's wearing
an orange jumpsuit.
- That woman doesn't get
anything
by prosecuting a fraud like you,
but she would love to get
Harvey Specter.
- I'm not turning on Harvey.
- You gotta listen to me!
I'm throwing you
a goddamn lifeline!
- I want to tell Jeff
the truth about Mike Ross.
- He told you he loved you,
didn't he?
- I just don't want to lie
to him anymore.
- Your whole story about how
Louis got his name on the door
is bullshit!
- And I came here
to tell you the truth.
- It's over.
We're done.
- Never even thought
for a second
that you would even consider
an idea so disgusting
as turning on Harvey.
- The only reason
I thought about it
is because I am scared to death
of you going to prison.
- I explicitly told you
to stay away from Mike's case.
- I don't care.
- Donna, I don't think
you get it.
There is going to come a time
where you're gonna
have to choose
between yourself and them.
- If they're gonna come for me,
they're gonna come for me.
- Are you saying you
coming back to me?
- Yes, I am.
- Then I'll see you
back in the office tomorrow.
[playing scales]
♪ ♪
- Dad, you know
I have to practice.
- I know you do, sweetheart,
but there's something
I have to tell you.
- What is it?
- We're moving to Connecticut.
- What?
Why?
- Your mom and I think
it's best for you.
- And what if it's not
best for me?
- Honey, it is.
And I found us a great apartment
just outside Hartford.
Lot more kids.
You're gonna love it.
- An apartment.
- That's right.
It's gonna be so much better
than this big, creaky...
- There's something
you're not telling me.
- No, there isn't.
- Yes, there is.
- How do you know that?
- I don't know,
but I do.
- Oh, okay, Donna.
My... business hasn't
worked out,
and your uncle offered me a job.
I'm so sorry, honey.
- It's okay, Daddy.
- I'll let you practice.
- Dad?
Will there be a room
for my piano?
- Honey, I'm afraid
there won't be.
But your aunt teaches
musical theater
just a few towns away.
I've already signed you up.
- Thanks, Daddy.
- Ms. Paulsen.
Could I get you a drink?
- I'm not gonna be here
long enough to finish it.
- Oh, you're gonna be here
till I tell you you can go.
- Which you're gonna tell me
sooner than you think,
because I've don't have
anything to say.
- I get it.
Harvey Specter was your boss
for a long time...
Maybe even more
than your boss...
In which case,
there's no chance in hell
you didn't know that he was
conspiring with Mike Ross
to break the law.
- The only thing I know is...
that unless you're gonna
arrest me,
I'm walking out that door
right now.
- Good.
You're as tough
as I expected you to be,
so for now, you are free to go.
- I told you
I wouldn't be here long.
You're gonna get the door
for me?
- Oh, I'm not opening the door
to be polite.
I'm opening the door so I can
see the look on your face
when you see who's in that room
across the hall.
- Dad?
What the hell did you do?
- I didn't do anything.
Turns out your father
got himself involved
in a shady real estate deal
several years ago.
- My father has never done
anything wrong in his life.
- Just like Mike Ross
and Harvey Specter
have never done anything wrong?
Ms. Paulsen, maybe
you should reassess
the quality of the men
in your life.
- Let me in that room.
- Sorry, not possible.
But next time
you see your father,
maybe you explain to him
you put his life on the line
for the man you work for.
- You know, I never thought that
I'd say this to another woman,
but you are
a cold, heartless bitch.
- I am, and I've got a card.
Why don't I just leave that
in your purse?
In case you change your mind
about helping me out
with Harvey Specter.
- ♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
.
- What are you working on?
- I'm just trying to figure out
what Gibbs is gonna do next,
figure out how to fight it.
- Is there anything
I can do to help?
- Yeah, you can tell me
what your father said
you should do about me.
- How would that help?
- Because I can't
really focus on this
while I'm worrying about that.
- He told me to look
in the mirror.
- And?
- How do you expect him
to react, Mike?
He's angry and he's hurt, and...
- Rachel.
- He told me to get rid of you.
- Good.
- Why good?
- Because you told me
that you would stay with me
no matter what, and when you
keep things like that from me,
it makes me wonder.
But when you tell me and
I see that look in your eyes,
I don't.
- Mr. Litt,
I'm all settled in.
I just wanted to say
that I'm so thrilled to be
a part of your te...
- Yeah, you're happy as a clam.
Let's get one thing straight.
You may have filled
Donna's shoes with Harvey,
but it's not gonna be that easy
filling them with me.
- Well, if that's how
you want to play it.
I already know that.
I heard all about you.
- Yeah?
From Donna?
- From Norma.
- What?
You knew Norma?
- Damn skippy.
Played mah-jongg
with that woman
every Tuesday night
for the last 30 years.
- Mrs. Fillstein's game
on 81st Street?
- The very one.
- I've been trying to get
into that game forever.
- You know she kept you out,
right?
- Ah...
Norma did that to me?
- Well, I can't say
as I blame her.
Said it was her only
peaceful night of the week.
30 seconds in,
I can see what she means.
But you could turn this around.
Play your tiles right with me,
I could put in a word for you.
- Oh, anything you could do
would be so appreciated.
- Yeah.
That's more like it.
- I can do even better.
Please, make yourself at home.
Take the day.
- Well, in that case,
I'll see you tomorrow morning,
bright and early.
- You're here.
- I am.
- It's good to have you back,
Harvey.
- Good to be back, Donna.
All right,
enough sentimentality.
I need you to...
- Clear your schedule for
the next two months? Done.
I also gave half your business
to the partners that backed you
and the rest
to Jessica and Louis.
- I didn't ask you to do that.
- No, you asked me
to come back to your desk.
- I sure as hell did.
- What's next?
- What's next is,
get Mike into this office,
and I don't want him wearing
casual clothes;
I want him
with his Superman outfit on.
- He's gonna need
a hell of a lot more
than a cape and some tights,
because I just got
a special delivery
from the U.S. Attorney's office.
- Don't tell me;
she's issued subpoenas
for every case
Mike's ever touched.
- She issued subpoenas
for anything
anyone at this firm
has ever touched.
- What does that mean?
- It means they're not just
after Mike anymore.
They're officially
coming after all of us.
- Mike's already here.
I'll get him.
- I'm telling you, Harvey,
this move is no joke.
That woman gets in the door,
she will find something
to pressure someone into saying
whatever she wants,
and I'll be damned if I'll
let her rifle through my house.
- What exactly are you saying?
- I'm saying we need
outside counsel.
- Absolutely not.
There's nobody we can trust.
- There is one person
we can trust,
because you already told her
Mike's goddamn secret.
- Jessica, I am not bringing
Scottie into this thing.
I'm telling you
I can handle this.
- You don't even have a strategy
to stop these subpoenas.
- Well, then I guess
it's a good thing I do.
- Well, then why don't you stop
patting yourself on the back
and start telling me
what the hell it is?
- We go on offense.
- What exactly does that mean?
- It means that
we don't have to prove
that she can't subpoena
our records;
she has to prove that she can.
And she doesn't have
a shred of evidence
proving that you knew about me.
- If she got those subpoenas
in the first place,
she must have something.
- Wrong, I worked
in the D.A.'s office
for five years.
Judges give out subpoenas
like candy.
- Then I suggest the two of you
get the hell on down there
and take
that woman's candy away.
- The fact is, Your Honor,
she has no grounds
to even issue these things
in the first place.
- What is he even doing here?
- I'm here because I'm a lawyer
and I'm innocent
until proven guilty.
And those subpoenas aren't
about coming after me;
they're about coming after him.
- You're damn right they are,
because there's no way
he didn't know you're a fraud.
- Where exactly is your evidence
of either one of those things?
- I see. They're not trying
to fight these subpoenas.
They're trying to get me to turn
over whatever evidence I have,
which I don't have to do
for another three weeks.
- You'll do whatever I say
you have to do.
Now, I want to know
what started this whole thing.
- We received an anonymous email
from a reputable source.
- Yeah, and a stranger
called me the other day
saying you killed six people.
Can I subpoena her bank records?
- You think this is a joke?
- You're damn right
this isn't a joke.
I'm being accused of a crime
based on some bullshit email
no one's even seen.
- I'd ask if you have that email
on you, Ms. Gibbs,
but I wouldn't want to put you
in the position of lying to me,
so let's have it.
[quiet dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- This is from a general
Harvard faculty address.
- It is. We are working
on tracking down the sender.
- Well, you'd better find them,
because without
corroborating testimony,
I'll not only quash
these subpoenas;
I'll toss the entire case.
♪ ♪
- Son of a bitch.
It's Henry Gerard.
- Harvey, if Gerard was gonna
say something,
why would he wait until now?
- I don't know,
but it's the only goddamn person
it could be.
- All right, then I'm gonna
go see him.
- And do what?
- I'm gonna get to him
before Gibbs does,
get him to recant.
- This isn't testimony.
It's a tip to a crime
you actually committed.
- I don't care.
We have leverage on Gerard.
- Were you in there?
This woman has her sights
on both of us.
You go up to Boston,
she's gonna have people
crawling all over Harvard,
and you're gonna be the one
who led her to Gerard.
- I can't just sit here and wait
for the sword to drop.
- Wait a second.
You can't go there,
I can't go there,
but I know someone who can.
- Jessica.
I was wondering when you were
gonna show up at my door.
- So you've heard
about Mike Ross.
- Oh, everybody's heard
Now I finally know what you were
hiding from me the whole time.
But what I don't know
is how the hell
you let something like this
happen in the first place.
- We'll talk about that
in a minute.
But I'm not just here
to apologize
for what happened between us.
I'm here to ask for your help.
- You want me to represent
the firm.
- If it comes to it,
I want you to represent me.
- You got a lot of nerve
coming in here to ask me that.
- Jeff, please.
I made the mistake
of not trusting you once.
I don't want to make
that same mistake again.
- Then you're gonna have to tell
me the truth about everything
right now, and it's not
gonna be protected
by attorney-client privilege,
and you're gonna have to trust
that I'm not gonna turn you in.
- I was never worried that
you were gonna turn me in.
I was worried about
putting you in a position
where you had to lie.
But I was ready to tell you
that night anyway,
so I might as well tell you now.
- Rachel, what's going on?
- I just got a call.
They took Donna down to
the U.S. Attorney's office.
- We have to get down there
right now.
- No, we don't.
I'm gonna take care of her.
You go ahead and do what
we were gonna do together.
- Harvey, Donna getting
taken in changes everything.
- It changes nothing,
so stop talking to me
and do what you have to do.
.
- It was Henry Gerard.
- What?
- The person who handed me in
was Henry Gerard.
It was an anonymous email.
- No way. How would he even know
that you're not a lawyer?
- That case we took last year,
he figured it out.
- Well, then why would he wait
to turn you in now?
- I don't know,
but what I do know is,
you need to get up there and you
need to get him to take it back.
- How the hell am I
supposed to do that?
- That's what you and I are
gonna figure out right now.
- Wait a second.
Where's Harvey?
- He's got an important
meeting that...
- What could be
more important than this?
- Louis,
it's a personal matter...
- Where is he?
- They brought Donna in
for questioning.
- Goddamn it, this is
what I was afraid of.
I'm heading down there
right now.
- Louis... Louis,
listen to me.
They're gonna try and put
pressure on Donna
to turn on Harvey,
and the best way
to make that pressure go away
is to make Gerard go away,
which can make this whole case
go away.
- Give me the goddamn email.
- Now, before you go up there,
we're gonna...
- I'm sorry.
Wait a second.
Why would someone who knows
you're guilty
call you a "potential" fraud?
- I-I don't know.
He's trying
to cover his ass somehow.
- "A potential fraud besmirching
the sacrosanct name
of hallowed
Harvard University"...
- Louis, we really don't
have time for this. Please.
- Mike, I know who wrote
this email.
It's not Henry Gerard.
- Excuse me, miss.
Are you alone, or can
an old man pull up a seat?
[both chuckle]
- Hi, Dad.
Oh.
- So have you
looked over the deal?
- I have.
- And you see the potential
I'm talking about?
- It's a great project.
- But?
- [sighs]
I'm not sure how wise it is
for you to get
back into development.
- I understand you would
feel that way
after what it did to you, but...
- I feel that way
because of what it did to you.
- Donna, I told you.
The banks are crazy for
this kind of thing right now.
All I need is $250,000.
I can get a loan
five times the size.
- I don't know; that just
sounds really risky.
- Aren't you always telling me
that Harvey says
if you want to get ahead,
you need to take risks?
- That's why you came to me.
You're not looking for my money;
you're looking for Harvey's.
- It would just be
to secure the loan.
After the bank gives me
the money, he's free and clear.
- Harvey's never gonna
go for that.
I mean, even I know
that's not legal.
- Donna, people do
this kind of thing all the time.
It's a sleight of hand,
nothing more.
- Dad, you're doing fine.
Do you really need to risk
everything again?
- Donna, I manage
a real estate office.
Everybody there makes more.
Everybody there is doing better.
I used to be better.
I know I can do this.
Please, all you have to do
is ask Harvey.
If he says no, he says no.
- Dad, I'm so sorry.
- Don't worry, sweetie.
People have tried to rattle
my cage plenty of times.
It's never worked before,
and it's not gonna work now.
- That's what I told her.
You're gonna be okay.
Donna, can you give us a minute?
- Harvey...
- Yeah?
- They're saying
this has to do with that deal
I talked to you about
seven years ago.
- And?
- Is there something
you're not telling me?
- The only thing
I haven't told you
is that I'm gonna get him
out of this, no matter what.
What the hell did you do?
- What are you talking about?
- They didn't bring you in here
if you didn't do something
seven years ago, and if
I'm gonna get you out of this,
I need to know what you did.
- I did what everybody else did.
I inflated my collateral
because you shut me down,
so don't come in here telling me
this is my fault.
- I shut you down
to protect Donna
from getting involved
in exactly something like this.
This is on you, not on me.
- Well, aren't you
high and mighty,
coming in here accusing me
of putting my daughter at risk
when the whole reason
she's in the position she's in
is because of something you did?
That's right.
They told me this is
because they're trying
to get Donna to testify
against you,
and they want me to help them
get her to do it.
- Then why don't you?
- Because I know
it would kill her,
and no matter what
you may think,
I would never do anything
to hurt my daughter.
- Did you talk to Donna?
- I talked to Harvey, and
he said it's gonna be f...
- I don't care what he says.
What are they
coming after her for?
- Mike, Harvey asked me
not to...
- Rachel, what are they
coming after her for?
- They're not coming after her
for anything.
They're coming after her father.
- What?
- Turns out he was involved
in some sort of real estate deal
and they're saying it wasn't
on the up-and-up.
- Goddamn it!
- Mike, calm down.
It's nothing.
Harvey's gonna get them
out of it.
Look, it's really
just a minor violation,
and no one would even care
if it weren't for...
- Me. You were just about to say
if it weren't for me.
- Mike, I...
- That's it.
I'm pleading guilty.
I'm gonna take
the reduced sentence,
I'm gonna do the time,
and all of this
is gonna go away
once and for all.
- That's not an option,
and you know it.
The only reason
they went after Donna's dad
is to get to Harvey and Jessica.
If you plead guilty, all you're
gonna do is help them do that,
so you're either gonna
turn on the two of them
or you're gonna fight this thing
out till the end.
- We need to talk.
- About what?
- About what we're going to do
if that prosecutor
gets ahold of those subpoenas.
- You mean what we're gonna do
about the letter that Mike has
that proves you knew
he was a fraud.
- Yes, that's what I mean.
I'm assuming you were
smart enough
to destroy that thing
the second they let you out.
- And I'm assuming you
destroyed the affidavit
that you had Rachel sign saying
she knew the truth about me.
- I didn't,
but I had the same conversation
with Louis, we worked it out,
and I'm here to tell you
I will get rid of mine
if you get rid of yours.
I knew it;
you're actually considering
turning your back
on me and Harvey.
- I'm not turning my back
on anyone,
but we both know
you've done some things
that make me question
whether or not I can trust you.
- Well, then,
the least you can do
is find the time to speak
with my attorney
before that ruling comes down.
- Your attorney?
- I'm sure you've heard of him.
His name's Jeff Malone.
- You're even lower
than I thought you were,
and I didn't even think
that was possible.
- Coming from someone
with your moral compass,
I take that as a compliment.
- What gives you the right
to come after
my secretary's father?
- I'm not the one
prosecuting him.
It just so happens that
one of my colleagues
is going after him on
a completely unrelated matter.
- Bullshit, the only reason
you're doing this
is to put pressure on Donna
to come after me.
- Well, now that you mention it,
the judge did say
I needed something tying you
to Mike Ross's fraud
in order to get those subpoenas,
and maybe that something
is Donna Paulsen.
I should ask her.
- You already did ask her,
and now you're manufacturing
a bullshit case
against an innocent man,
and I'm gonna make sure
you pay for it.
- He's not in here
because of what I did.
He's in here
because of what you did.
So instead of blaming me,
take a look in the mirror,
'cause all you have to do
is admit what you did,
and all of this goes away.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
.
- Louis.
What are you doing here?
- You know why I'm here.
I'm here because of this.
- I don't know what that is.
- Please, your language
is all over it.
You might as well have
signed your name.
What I want to know is why.
- [sighs]
I got a call about an article
on Mike Ross's meteoric rise
to junior partner.
Problem is, I remember
every student
that's ever gone here,
and there is no Mike Ross,
so I double-checked
my file room,
and then I sent this.
- Sheila, you are
messing with my firm.
Why didn't you come to me first?
- Because it didn't occur to me
that I had to.
- That is bullshit!
You reported it anonymously
because you didn't want
to look bad.
You didn't trust me
to keep you out of it.
- No, I reported it anonymously
because I was ashamed that
it happened on my watch,
but I'm not gonna stand by
while somebody besmirches
the good name
of Harvard University.
- You have no proof that
Mike Ross besmirched anything.
- Why are you
defending this lowlife?
- Because if you'd
come to me first,
I could have stopped
this whole thing from happening.
- Oh, my God.
You knew.
- Sheila, please, you don't
know him like I know him.
- What exactly are you
doing here, Louis?
- I want you to retract
that email.
Tell 'em that you made
a mistake; you found the file.
- I can't do that.
- Sheila, please.
- When we broke up,
I forced myself to accept it,
because ultimately I knew
we wanted different things,
but it killed me, because I also
knew that we were soul mates.
But the fact that you're
asking me to do this...
We are not soul mates.
- I'm begging you.
At least don't come forward.
- I never was gonna
come forward, Louis.
Now leave me alone.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
I thought I'd find you here.
How are you doing?
- Well, they're coming
after my father
for something he didn't do.
How do you think I'm doing?
- I'm sorry.
Do you want to be alone?
- [sighs]
No. I'm sorry. It's just...
- Donna, please,
you're worried sick
for someone you love.
I get it.
- It's just, last year
my life was in Harvey's hands,
and he told me that my worrying
about what would happen
if he lost would only make it
more likely for him to lose.
- I know, and you can't help
but worry about it,
because it's your father.
- No, I can't.
- And you can't help wondering,
if it comes down to it,
what will you do?
- What?
No, Rachel, how can you
even ask me that?
I get it.
Because if it comes down to it,
you want Mike to consider
turning on Harvey.
- That's not what I said.
- You know, if you're
just here to get me
to think about doing that,
I don't need that right now.
- No, no, no, Donna,
I came in here
because I care about you
and I am...
[sighs]
I'm sorry that
I even brought it up.
- Are you sorry?
- Excuse me?
- Do you think that I don't know
that all your problems
are solved
if I tell them
that Harvey did this?
- No, Donna, all of my problems
are solved if Mike tells them.
But, yes, my life gets
a whole lot better
if Harvey takes responsibility
for what he did.
- What he did was
give Mike a chance
to make something of himself.
- Which is why Mike's never
gonna turn on him.
But you know what?
I would be lying if I said
it didn't cross my mind
that maybe Mike should think
about making a deal.
And you can't tell me that
since they picked up your father
that the thought hasn't
crossed yours too.
- Well, thinking about it
and talking about it
aren't the same thing,
and right now, I'm focusing
on having faith in Harvey.
- Louis, what the hell?
I've been looking for you
all morning.
What happened?
- It was her.
- [sighs]
And?
- She's not gonna
retract the email.
- Shit.
What did she say?
- Oh, what the hell
do you think she said?
Said she knows you're a fraud,
she's not gonna take it back,
and now that she's figured out
that I've been a part of it,
she can't stand the sight of me.
- All right, then we need
to think of something else...
- Oh, did you just hear
what I just said?
She can't stand the sight of me.
- Louis, I know
you're feeling bad,
but right now,
Donna is under the gun.
- What do you want me
to do about that?
- I don't know, but if she
doesn't retract that email
and they find her...
- No, they're not gonna
find her,
because she sent it
from a general faculty email
because she's ashamed of herself
like she's ashamed of me.
And this is all your fault,
so get the hell out of my office
instead of trying to figure out
a way to cover your goddamn ass!
- You can believe this or not,
Louis, but right this second,
I'm actually looking out
for Donna.
- I'm sorry, Mike.
Right this second,
I cannot help you.
- Good, you're here.
Listen, I need you
to take care of...
- Before we get
to the game plan,
I need to know what's going on
with Donna's father.
- I'm taking care of it.
Did you get Louis
to go see Gerard?
- It wasn't Gerard.
It was Sheila Sazs.
- You gotta be kidding me.
Louis told his girlfriend
about you?
- No, Harvey, you told
your girlfriend about me.
Louis risked his neck
to get Sheila
to take that email back
to save our asses.
- What are you
so bent out of shape for?
- I'm bent out of shape
because he couldn't do it,
and on top of that, Donna's dad
is only in this mess
because of what we did,
and you won't let me help.
- That's right, Mike;
I won't let you help,
because you're
under investigation
for being a fraud.
- You're under investigation
too, and if we're
supposed to act like there's
nothing to be ashamed of,
then let's act like there's
nothing to be ashamed of.
- Okay, that's all
well and good, Mike,
but I'm the one representing
Donna's father, not you,
which means I'm the only one
with a credible reason
to pay a visit to the banker
that gave him
that shitty loan
in the first place.
- Harvey, this is killing me!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I have to do something.
- Right now,
the best thing you can do
is think about what
we're gonna do
if they put it together
about Louis's girlfriend,
because if they find her,
we're in deep shit.
♪ ♪
.
[groovy music]
♪ ♪
- [clears throat]
- How did you find me here?
- I remember every game you have
from our work on your case.
And I knew I had to find you
at a place
where we couldn't be bothered
by anyone from Harvard.
- Because everyone from Harvard
now knows you didn't go there.
- Which is why I need
someone from Harvard
to tell them that I did.
- Are you crazy?
- No, I'm smart.
All they have is
an anonymous tip
and no corroborating evidence.
You sign this affidavit saying
that I was in your class,
their whole case gets dismissed.
- And what if it doesn't?
- Then I go to trial.
This is reasonable doubt.
I get acquitted,
they can never try me again.
- Or it's not reasonable doubt,
you don't get acquitted,
and I go to jail for perjury.
- I remember when you were
willing to commit perjury
and we didn't just stop you;
we saved your ass.
- I don't care. I'm not
risking everything for you.
- This isn't just for me,
all right?
They are coming after everyone
that I care about.
- I feel for you, Mike,
which is why I never turned
you in in the first place,
but I can't do
what you're asking.
- And what if I
anonymously told Harvard
that you took a bribe
from a student for a grade?
You willing to bet everything
that I won't do that?
- You do what you have to do,
but I'm not putting
my life in jeopardy
by signing that goddamn thing.
- Wait a minute, wait, wait.
What if I had a way
that you could help me
without having to
perjure yourself?
- And how exactly
would I do that?
- It's right in your wheelhouse.
We're playing poker too.
I just...
I just need you
to help me bluff.
- Harvey, I need to ask you
to do something.
- Of course, Donna.
I'd do anything for you.
- Well, it isn't for me.
It's for my father.
He wanted to know
if you would consider
investing
in his real estate project.
- I'm sorry.
I can't do that.
- You just said that you would
do anything for me.
- I meant I'd consider anything,
and I just did.
- You haven't even looked at it.
- I don't need to.
You're family to me,
he's family to you,
and you don't invest money
with family.
- That's not what you said
when Marcus needed money
for his restaurant.
- That's different.
- Why?
- Because Marcus actually knew
what the hell he was doing.
- You know what, Harvey?
If you don't want to invest,
don't invest,
but I don't need
a lecture from you
on what a bad businessman
my father is.
- Yes, you do.
- Oh, really?
Why's that?
- Because if I know you,
you're thinking of giving him
access to your 401(k).
- So? What if I am?
- Donna, this man lost
your family's money once.
You're gonna give him
the chance to do it again?
- Harvey, this man is my father,
and he has been there for me
my whole life.
And I know what happened
between you and your mother,
but don't you judge him
for what she did.
How dare you? This has
nothing to do with that.
You have a blind spot
when it comes to him.
I'm trying to protect you.
- Well, you're not.
You're being an asshole.
And for your information,
keeping me from being there
for my father
isn't protecting me.
It's pissing me the hell off.
- Good, Donna, you're here.
Look, I need you to...
- The only thing I need is
for you to tell me what you did,
because I just found out
that they're
formally charging my father
with bank fraud tomorrow.
- Goddamn it.
- What did you do?
- All I did was
strong-arm a banker.
- And why the hell would you
need to strong-arm a banker?
- Because he had evidence
that needed to get lost.
- I knew there was something
you weren't telling me.
What the hell happened
seven years ago?
- What happened is,
you came to me
asking a favor for your father,
so I went to him
asking a favor of my own.
- Bullshit.
You don't ask people for favors.
You force them to do things!
- You're goddamn right I do.
I told your father
if he took your money,
I'd pull every string I have
to shut his deal down.
- You had no right to do that.
- I don't care if I had
a right to do it or not.
I wasn't gonna let you
lose everything
just because you couldn't see
the truth about him.
- The truth is, you went
behind my back,
and then he did
something illegal,
and now I have to choose
between you and him
because of what you did!
- What I did was keep you
from being involved
in this mess.
- No, Harvey, what you did
was start this mess
the day you went ahead
and hired a fraud.
- What happened?
- They're formally charging
Donna's father,
and we need to figure out a way
to get his case thrown out.
- Well, then we have to get
my case thrown out,
because then they won't care
about Donna's dad.
- And how the hell are we
gonna do that?
- I went to see Gerard.
- God damn it, didn't I
tell you not to do that?
- That was before we knew
he wasn't the one
that tipped them off.
- If he wasn't the one
who tipped them off,
what the hell
did you go to him for?
- I went to him for this.
- This is a vaguely worded
statement.
It doesn't even specifically say
you went to Harvard.
- It doesn't have to.
It says that he's known me
to be an amazing lawyer,
that I've shown mastery
of the material that he teaches,
and that as far
as he's concerned,
I'm an outstanding student
of the law.
- It's total bullshit.
- It's not total bullshit,
all right?
If they don't find Sheila
and we do this,
we could get
the whole case thrown out.
- Gibbs'll see
right through this.
She'll put Gerard on the stand,
and she'll ask him point blank
if he knows for a fact
that you never went to Harvard,
and we'll have signed
our own death warrant.
- She's not gonna do that,
because it violates
the number one rule of being
a lawyer that you taught me:
don't ask a question that
you don't have the answer to.
- It's too big a risk.
- Harvey, Donna's dad
is at risk,
and he's at risk because of me.
The only way to get him out
is to have me to turn on you
or for us to get
this whole thing thrown out,
so are you on board
with this or not?
- We better pray
this bullshit works,
because, if it doesn't,
at least one of us
is gonna end up
in prison tomorrow.
- All right,
what are we doing here?
- Your Honor, we have a motion
to dismiss Mike Ross's case.
- On what grounds?
- On the grounds that
I have a letter here
from Professor Henry Gerard
of Harvard Law
saying that Mike Ross
was in his class.
- This is ridiculous.
Even if Mr. Ross
were in that class,
it doesn't mean
he was matriculated.
- You still haven't shown
any evidence that he wasn't,
which is why that document
should get this case dismissed.
- This document is
a cryptically worded
piece of shit,
and you're a man
who has a reputation
for crossing the line.
- Ms. Gibbs, language.
What are you implying?
- Your Honor,
there's a good chance
he coerced this Professor Gerard
into signing this thing.
- So our exhibits are
all from blackmail,
but yours are squeaky clean
because you're Mother Teresa?
- I may not be Mother Teresa,
but I don't resort to coercion
to get my evidence.
- Then what exactly
are you doing
with Donna Paulsen's father?
- Care to tell me
what he's talking about?
- I'll tell you.
She fabricated a charge
against an innocent businessman
to pressure my secretary
into giving false testimony
against me.
- Your Honor,
it's standard practice
to find leverage
against a vital witness.
- Oh, is it also standard
practice to have
a federal marshal rough me up
in a holding cell?
- Ms. Gibbs, if I find out
there's an abuse of power here,
I will be switching
my focus to you.
- Then before you rule
on their motion,
the state has the right
to question
this Professor Gerard.
- Your Honor, can Ms. Gibbs
and I have a minute alone?
- Please.
- You think I don't know this
letter is complete bullshit?
I pull this clown
up on the stand,
he's gonna tell me
the truth in a minute.
- Okay, this clown is one of
the most distinguished ethics
professors in the country.
You put him up there,
this case is over for you
before you even get started.
- Then why the hell
isn't he here right now
verifying this thing?
- Because that kid cares
more about Donna Paulsen
than he does about himself.
- What do you want?
- I want to make a deal...
That letter for Donna's father.
- [scoffs]
This is too good for you.
If you really had Gerard,
he'd be down here right now.
- If it were up to me,
he'd be down here right now,
but this is Mike's call.
This is a one-time offer,
and the clock's ticking.
You still get to go to trial,
we get Donna and her father
off limits,
and we both live
to fight another day.
- I want my subpoenas too.
- No way.
Judge said no.
- You try to pull this thing
out at trial,
I will rip your professor friend
to shreds.
- Your Honor, Ms. Gibbs and I
have come to an agreement.
She's dropping all charges
against James Paulsen,
and we withdraw
our motion to dismiss.
.
- See you next week.
- Nice club.
- Are you new?
- Just visiting.
Not much of a golfer.
- Unfortunately, neither am I.
- Harvey Specter.
- Jim Paulsen.
I assume this is
about the opportunity
Donna brought you.
- It'd be an opportunity
if the numbers added up, Jim,
but they don't.
- I don't understand.
I thought you were
the type of man
that was willing to take risks.
- I am... but not if it puts
people I care about in jeopardy,
which is why I'm here
to tell you
that when Donna
offers you her 401(k),
you're gonna tell her
you don't need it anymore.
- No offense, Mr. Specter,
but what my daughter does
with her money is
none of your business.
- Well, it became my business
when Donna put you
so far up on a pedestal
that she couldn't smell
the bullshit
you were dishing out.
- It's not bullshit.
- Yes, it is.
I looked at that deal.
There's no way you're getting
the kind of money you need
without doing something shady.
- Inflating my assets
to get a loan isn't shady.
Everybody does it.
- That's what everybody thinks
until the music stops,
which is why if you involve
Donna in this deal,
so help me God, I will pull
every string I have
to tie your project up in court
for the next 20 years.
- I'm just trying
to make my way.
- All I'm telling you is,
you can make it without Donna.
- You act as if you think
I don't love my own daughter.
- People who love other people
don't put them in positions
to break the law.
[footsteps approaching]
- I just got off the phone
with my dad.
He told me the good news.
- I told you
I'd take care of it.
- What did you do?
- It's not important.
- Harvey.
- We withdrew our motion
to dismiss Mike's case
in exchange for her
leaving you alone.
- So I hurt Mike's case.
- No, you didn't.
The whole thing was based
on a bluff
that never would have
held up anyway.
[sighs]
This way, we at least got
something for it.
- Thank you, Harvey.
And I'm sorry for what I said.
- No.
You were right to say it.
I never should have put you
in this position, Donna.
If you want to go back to work
for Louis, I'll understand.
- No, you shouldn't have put me
in that position,
but if I was gonna leave you
for hiring Mike,
the time to do that
would have been years ago.
- I hope I'm not interrupting
your premature celebration.
- You better not be
reneging on our deal.
- Oh, no, I'm gonna honor it.
I just dropped by
to serve you with these.
You and your partners are
hereby subpoenaed
to hand over every single
document in the entire firm.
- No.
No way the judge granted that
just because we withdrew
our motion to dismiss.
- She didn't.
She granted it when
a Sheila Sazs from Harvard
came forward and said she wrote
that anonymous email.
That's right, Mr. Specter.
Your chances of winning
this case just took
a mighty big turn for the worse.
- What are you doing here?
- You never came to see me,
so I thought I would come to you
and find out why
you're so willing
to let all those
dangerous letters
just keep floating around
out there.
- I think you mean letters that
are dangerous to your client.
- Well, I'm holding one
right here
that puts your woman
in a world of trouble, Mike,
so no, no, I don't.
- Oh, I get it.
I didn't crumble to Jessica,
so now you're here
to take a shot at
strong-arming me into a trade.
- No, see, I came to see why,
when the woman that's been
protecting you for so long
asks you for a simple
gesture of trust,
you seem to think that all she's
doing is protecting herself.
- Because she is
protecting herself.
- You're goddamn right
that's what she's doing,
but that's not all she's doing,
because from the second
that she found out about you,
she's had to lie for you,
and she still treated you
like family,
and it cost her everything.
- Give me a break. Until now,
it didn't cost her anything.
- You better watch yourself.
- What the hell are you doing?
- It cost her
her relationship with me!
You didn't know about that,
did you?
Well, now you do.
- So you'll destroy that
if I give you mine?
- I'm an attorney.
I can't destroy evidence.
But you?
You can do whatever you want.
- You trust me to do that?
- [chuckles] No, Mike.
Jessica does.
- Louis, I need you to sit down.
- What is it?
What happened?
Is your father okay?
I'll go down there right now.
- He's fine.
Harvey took care of it.
- Oh, well, then I don't need
to sit down.
'Cause whatever it is,
if you're okay, I'll be okay.
- Sheila came forward.
- What?
- She admitted she was
the one to write the email.
- That's not possible.
She promised me
she wouldn't do that.
- I'm sorry, Louis, but she did.
- I need to be alone.
- Louis, I don't think
this is the time for you to...
- I said get out.
- He did it?
- He did.
- What did you say to him?
- I told him
how much it cost you,
and then I did
what we talked about.
- Well, it's a good thing
you did,
because those subpoenas
just came down.
- [sighs]
Jessica, I don't know
that I've ever been
much of a spiritual person,
but I would be lying
if I didn't admit
that sometimes I think
God has a plan.
- What are you saying?
- I'm saying that maybe
he's trying to show you
that there's more to life
than Pearson Specter Litt.
I'm not gonna be
your attorney on this one.
I think you can find
someone better.
- No.
I trust you, and there's no way
I find someone
that I trust more.
- Then find me when
this is all over,
and we'll see if we can put
that trust to better use.
- Gretchen, whatever it is,
it can wait till tomorrow.
- This can't wait.
I want to apologize to you.
- For what?
- When Jack Soloff nominated
Mike Ross for partner,
I know it hurt Harvey a little,
because he wanted to be
the one to do it,
so I called the "ABA Journal"
to write an article about Mike.
I wanted to surprise Harvey
with it.
- You're saying the article
that tipped Sheila off was you?
- Yes.
- Why are you telling me this?
- Because I'm sorry.
And if anyone ever asks,
I'll deny ever saying this,
but... I know
you all knew.
And I'm with you.
- [sighs]
Hey.
- Hey.
- What's the matter?
- I know I said I don't want you
to keep things from me,
but I don't want to keep things
from you either.
- What are you keeping from me?
- It's actually
good and bad news.
We had a chance to get this
whole case thrown out today,
and it didn't work,
but we did get Donna off,
and for the first time,
I actually started to believe
we can get out of this thing.
- And why were you afraid
to admit that to me?
- Because I didn't want to
get your hopes up.
And I didn't really
believe it before.
Yeah, what's up?
- Sheila Sazs came forward,
which means they're gonna
try and pit us all
against each other even more.