1
00:00:00,806 --> 00:00:02,516
Previously on Suits...

2
00:00:02,517 --> 00:00:03,735
You really know him.

3
00:00:03,854 --> 00:00:05,155
I really do.

4
00:00:05,274 --> 00:00:07,110
- Never.
- No.

5
00:00:07,279 --> 00:00:08,975
Why not?

6
00:00:09,000 --> 00:00:10,786
Because you can never go back.

7
00:00:10,921 --> 00:00:12,590
Forstman's insisting
that I run the money

8
00:00:12,709 --> 00:00:14,071
through Switzerland
and the Caymans

9
00:00:14,179 --> 00:00:15,661
before it comes out
on the other side.

10
00:00:15,683 --> 00:00:16,884
You're obligated to report it.

11
00:00:17,019 --> 00:00:18,437
I didn't, and I'm not going to.

12
00:00:18,573 --> 00:00:19,584
What are you talking about?

13
00:00:19,608 --> 00:00:20,943
Rachel, hey. Logan and I kissed.

14
00:00:21,062 --> 00:00:23,733
Mike, no. Please.

15
00:00:23,868 --> 00:00:25,750
When I said that it
didn't matter what I do next

16
00:00:25,873 --> 00:00:29,548
because I have you,
I was wrong because we're done.

17
00:00:29,699 --> 00:00:31,336
That's your fee
for putting this deal

18
00:00:31,504 --> 00:00:32,755
together. You son of a bitch.

19
00:00:32,873 --> 00:00:34,353
You didn't bring me here
for you to sign on the arrows.

20
00:00:34,377 --> 00:00:35,706
You brought me here for me
to sign on the arrows.

21
00:00:35,731 --> 00:00:37,065
Yep.

22
00:00:37,184 --> 00:00:39,237
You cannot take a job
with that man.

23
00:00:39,389 --> 00:00:40,551
What are you gonna do about it?

24
00:00:40,576 --> 00:00:42,222
I hired Mike Ross
back at the firm.

25
00:00:42,246 --> 00:00:44,282
- What?
- You're really gonna drop me?

26
00:00:44,418 --> 00:00:45,419
You're damn right I am.

27
00:00:45,571 --> 00:00:48,927
I never want to see you again.

28
00:00:49,079 --> 00:00:50,743
- Are you back here?
- No, no.

29
00:00:50,767 --> 00:00:54,558
I'm... stay somewhere for a while.
Mike-

30
00:00:54,726 --> 00:00:56,071
Rachel,
whatever you're gonna say,

31
00:00:56,096 --> 00:00:58,093
now is not the time to say it.

32
00:00:58,117 --> 00:01:00,237
I'm coming back
to work tomorrow.

33
00:01:00,373 --> 00:01:01,575
If you can't accept that,

34
00:01:01,709 --> 00:01:05,417
then whatever you were gonna
say to me won't matter.

35
00:02:08,269 --> 00:02:10,156
Thought you might need this.

36
00:02:10,291 --> 00:02:11,636
Thank you.

37
00:02:11,660 --> 00:02:15,635
So, the way I see it,
you've got three options.

38
00:02:15,787 --> 00:02:19,093
You can wear what you
were wearing last night,

39
00:02:19,262 --> 00:02:20,742
you can go back to your place
and change,

40
00:02:20,766 --> 00:02:25,158
or you can grab anything
you want from my closet.

41
00:02:25,310 --> 00:02:27,832
Nothing? I thought for sure
you would leap at the chance...

42
00:02:27,982 --> 00:02:30,421
Mike's coming back to work
today.

43
00:02:30,556 --> 00:02:31,624
I know.

44
00:02:31,759 --> 00:02:33,339
- What am I gonna do?
- You're gonna do

45
00:02:33,363 --> 00:02:35,734
what you've been doing
since the day Mike left.

46
00:02:35,835 --> 00:02:38,250
You're gonna walk into Harvey's
office with your head held high,

47
00:02:38,275 --> 00:02:39,503
and you're gonna do your job.

48
00:02:39,528 --> 00:02:40,729
- Mike's job.
- Rachel...

49
00:02:40,847 --> 00:02:45,206
I don't know how to be
near him without being near him.

50
00:02:45,358 --> 00:02:48,665
I'll tell you how.
Give him space.

51
00:02:48,800 --> 00:02:50,218
I don't want to give him space.

52
00:02:50,370 --> 00:02:52,223
I want to run to him

53
00:02:52,375 --> 00:02:54,512
and hold him and tell him
that I love him.

54
00:02:54,647 --> 00:02:55,682
I know, but, Rachel,

55
00:02:55,850 --> 00:02:57,362
if you try to pull him
towards you right now,

56
00:02:57,387 --> 00:02:59,107
all you're gonna
do is push him away.

57
00:02:59,241 --> 00:03:01,361
Trust me. Let things be.

58
00:03:01,497 --> 00:03:02,875
They'll turn out the way
they're supposed to.

59
00:03:02,900 --> 00:03:06,256
You don't know that.

60
00:03:06,408 --> 00:03:10,683
I do know that.

61
00:03:10,802 --> 00:03:13,107
Okay.

62
00:03:13,258 --> 00:03:15,563
Rachel, I'm gonna tell you
something I've never told you.

63
00:03:19,991 --> 00:03:23,582
I slept with Harvey.

64
00:03:23,717 --> 00:03:27,509
Oh, my God.

65
00:03:27,643 --> 00:03:28,704
But you told me that...

66
00:03:28,729 --> 00:03:30,649
I know what I told you.

67
00:03:30,800 --> 00:03:32,486
It was once,
and I never would have done it

68
00:03:32,605 --> 00:03:34,943
if we were still
working together.

69
00:03:35,110 --> 00:03:36,913
But then,
he left the D.A.'s office,

70
00:03:37,032 --> 00:03:41,819
and... it happened.

71
00:03:41,844 --> 00:03:43,072
And then, the next time
I saw him,

72
00:03:43,097 --> 00:03:44,660
he wanted me to come with him
to the firm,

73
00:03:44,684 --> 00:03:46,220
and I did, and that was that.

74
00:03:46,337 --> 00:03:48,084
Would you have wanted
a relationship with him?

75
00:03:48,109 --> 00:03:50,647
I would have wanted to try,

76
00:03:50,781 --> 00:03:54,015
but he wasn't ready.

77
00:03:54,040 --> 00:03:56,828
And if I had pushed him
to be ready,

78
00:03:56,963 --> 00:03:58,860
I would be sitting here
talking to somebody else

79
00:03:58,885 --> 00:04:02,726
about somebody I used to work
with a long time ago.

80
00:04:02,877 --> 00:04:04,813
What are you saying?

81
00:04:04,932 --> 00:04:07,196
I'm saying everything turned
out the way it was supposed to.

82
00:04:07,221 --> 00:04:08,691
But you said the reason

83
00:04:08,825 --> 00:04:13,034
that you two never... is
because you can never go back.

84
00:04:16,009 --> 00:04:17,712
I lied.

85
00:04:23,695 --> 00:04:25,281
Oh, I'd let you go,

86
00:04:25,431 --> 00:04:27,201
but I was here first.

87
00:04:27,320 --> 00:04:29,156
Words to live by
by Harvey Specter,

88
00:04:29,291 --> 00:04:31,878
the most selfish man
in the world.

89
00:04:31,997 --> 00:04:33,142
Don't mind if I do.

90
00:04:33,167 --> 00:04:35,421
Wait a second.

91
00:04:35,556 --> 00:04:36,924
What are you
doing here so early?

92
00:04:37,093 --> 00:04:38,344
I always get in this early.

93
00:04:38,479 --> 00:04:40,767
You never get in this early,
and I know that for a fact

94
00:04:40,902 --> 00:04:43,858
because this is the time
I get in every single day.

95
00:04:43,993 --> 00:04:45,171
You should sleep in once
in a while.

96
00:04:45,196 --> 00:04:46,317
It's good for you. Trust me.

97
00:04:46,449 --> 00:04:48,119
I do it every single day.

98
00:04:48,253 --> 00:04:49,922
It just so
happens that this morning,

99
00:04:50,041 --> 00:04:51,259
I have work to do.

100
00:04:51,377 --> 00:04:53,463
What work?

101
00:04:53,600 --> 00:04:55,636
The Schmoolkinsberg brief.

102
00:04:55,805 --> 00:04:58,143
The Schmoolkinsberg brief?

103
00:04:58,310 --> 00:04:59,511
That's what you're going with?

104
00:04:59,614 --> 00:05:00,736
It's not gonna write itself.

105
00:05:00,850 --> 00:05:02,787
I'm taking your name
off the wall.

106
00:05:02,905 --> 00:05:05,210
Seriously, I'm here
for the Tokyo markets.

107
00:05:05,327 --> 00:05:06,880
Name one Tokyo market.

108
00:05:07,031 --> 00:05:09,168
- The Nikkei.
- Name another.

109
00:05:09,304 --> 00:05:12,571
Honda, Toyota, Kia.

110
00:05:12,595 --> 00:05:13,729
Kia's Korean.

111
00:05:13,881 --> 00:05:15,494
Yeah, but they're
in the same time zone.

112
00:05:15,518 --> 00:05:17,939
Where it is currently dinner.

113
00:05:18,075 --> 00:05:19,527
I'm a tired of this inquisition.

114
00:05:19,662 --> 00:05:21,866
This is exactly
why I don't come in this early.

115
00:05:22,034 --> 00:05:24,622
And the reason that you're
here this early this morning

116
00:05:24,740 --> 00:05:27,095
is because it's
Mike Ross' first day back.

117
00:05:27,214 --> 00:05:28,883
Is it?

118
00:05:37,437 --> 00:05:39,491
Louis,
why are you here so early?

119
00:05:39,626 --> 00:05:41,079
I am taking
this Forstman document,

120
00:05:41,247 --> 00:05:46,090
and I am burying it
in the bowels of these files.

121
00:05:46,259 --> 00:05:48,563
And then,
I am putting these files

122
00:05:48,682 --> 00:05:51,604
deep in the bowels
of our storage.

123
00:05:51,772 --> 00:05:53,157
Louis, please stop saying
bowels.

124
00:05:53,309 --> 00:05:55,156
Katrina, I don't have time
to give a shit about bowels,

125
00:05:55,181 --> 00:05:56,917
'cause after this,
we are starting fresh.

126
00:05:57,034 --> 00:05:58,931
And I don't want to hear about
Gillis Industries, Sean Cahill,

127
00:05:58,956 --> 00:06:01,794
Charles Forstman ever again.

128
00:06:08,863 --> 00:06:11,178
Well, look who it is,
Bonnie and Clyde.

129
00:06:11,202 --> 00:06:12,620
Just the people I wanted to see.

130
00:06:12,740 --> 00:06:13,991
What do you want, Sean?

131
00:06:14,125 --> 00:06:15,912
To serve you with this.

132
00:06:16,030 --> 00:06:19,755
What the hell is that?

133
00:06:19,873 --> 00:06:22,678
He wants all files relating to
the Gillis Industries takeover.

134
00:06:22,814 --> 00:06:23,909
Oh, I don't want the files.

135
00:06:23,933 --> 00:06:25,435
I'm taking them. Bullshit.

136
00:06:25,552 --> 00:06:28,024
We have 60 days
to fight that or comply.

137
00:06:28,193 --> 00:06:29,578
You want to tell him
or should I?

138
00:06:29,729 --> 00:06:32,251
It's not a subpoena, Harvey.
It's a search warrant.

139
00:06:32,403 --> 00:06:34,506
So you're gonna give me
all the files,

140
00:06:34,625 --> 00:06:37,547
or you're gonna head downtown
with these two fine gentlemen.

141
00:06:37,716 --> 00:06:39,101
Okay, Sean.

142
00:06:39,253 --> 00:06:40,772
Have it your way.

143
00:06:40,890 --> 00:06:42,393
You're going to take that hall.

144
00:06:42,527 --> 00:06:44,040
You're going to run
into what appears

145
00:06:44,064 --> 00:06:45,986
to be the mummified remains
of a legal secretary.

146
00:06:46,102 --> 00:06:47,571
- Her name is Norma.
- Mm-hmm.

147
00:06:47,707 --> 00:06:49,743
She's gonna limp you
up to the 60th floor

148
00:06:49,912 --> 00:06:52,417
where you will find
30 years worth of files

149
00:06:52,551 --> 00:06:54,597
that haven't been sorted
since the Reagan Administration.

150
00:06:54,622 --> 00:06:55,623
Or is it the 56th floor?

151
00:06:55,759 --> 00:06:57,595
It could be the 35th floor
for all I know.

152
00:06:57,731 --> 00:06:58,598
The point is,
while you're trying

153
00:06:58,733 --> 00:07:00,101
to find the Ark of the Covenant,

154
00:07:00,270 --> 00:07:03,025
we'll be downtown in front of
a judge blocking this bullshit.

155
00:07:03,160 --> 00:07:04,789
You think the threat
of you getting to a judge

156
00:07:04,814 --> 00:07:07,036
before I find what I want
is gonna get me to leave?

157
00:07:07,170 --> 00:07:08,421
Then stay,

158
00:07:08,540 --> 00:07:10,688
but who do you think's gonna
get the job done faster?

159
00:07:10,712 --> 00:07:13,601
You and those two windbreakers
or Bonnie and Clyde.

160
00:07:56,232 --> 00:07:59,172
Welcome home, sailor.

161
00:07:59,465 --> 00:08:01,084
You were out to sea a long time.

162
00:08:01,253 --> 00:08:03,056
I was, but now I'm back.

163
00:08:03,174 --> 00:08:05,929
And this place
hasn't changed a bit.

164
00:08:06,064 --> 00:08:07,349
Maybe it has.

165
00:08:07,484 --> 00:08:08,852
Is this a new Spinner's album?

166
00:08:08,971 --> 00:08:11,219
No, and you know it's not new.
You and Harvey joked about it.

167
00:08:11,244 --> 00:08:12,673
I could have sworn
that was a different one.

168
00:08:12,697 --> 00:08:14,339
Said the man
with the photographic memory.

169
00:08:14,351 --> 00:08:15,964
Okay, that doesn't mean
I've seen every album...

170
00:08:15,988 --> 00:08:17,434
You have no idea
where to go, do you?

171
00:08:17,458 --> 00:08:20,296
- Not a clue.
- Come with me.

172
00:08:23,339 --> 00:08:24,809
Donna, I went to the bullpen.

173
00:08:24,977 --> 00:08:27,147
Some guy with a soul patch
was sitting at my desk.

174
00:08:27,282 --> 00:08:29,068
That's because
it's not your desk anymore,

175
00:08:29,203 --> 00:08:31,100
and you're not cool enough
to pull off a soul patch.

176
00:08:31,125 --> 00:08:32,209
I dispute that.

177
00:08:32,360 --> 00:08:34,140
Are you even capable
of growing a soul patch?

178
00:08:34,165 --> 00:08:37,171
I had a goatee
my sophomore year of never.

179
00:08:37,339 --> 00:08:38,701
Look, it's not your desk anymore

180
00:08:38,726 --> 00:08:40,239
because you're on the other side
of the bullpen now.

181
00:08:40,263 --> 00:08:41,431
Which other side?

182
00:08:41,549 --> 00:08:43,591
The other side. Like,
not the side that you were on.

183
00:08:43,605 --> 00:08:44,966
Towards the door
or away from the door?

184
00:08:44,991 --> 00:08:46,136
Which door are you talking
about?

185
00:08:46,161 --> 00:08:47,256
Which door are you
talking about?

186
00:08:47,280 --> 00:08:49,043
You know what?
Just shut up and keep walking.

187
00:08:49,068 --> 00:08:50,229
You're not here five minutes,

188
00:08:50,236 --> 00:08:51,673
and you're already a pain
in my ass.

189
00:08:54,080 --> 00:08:56,936
This is the other side
of the bullpen.

190
00:08:59,275 --> 00:09:00,610
- Are you serious?
- I know.

191
00:09:00,762 --> 00:09:01,947
I fought it tooth and nail.

192
00:09:02,099 --> 00:09:03,578
I mean, if it were up to me,
you'd be setting up shop

193
00:09:03,602 --> 00:09:04,787
in the file room.

194
00:09:04,939 --> 00:09:06,408
You did this, didn't you?

195
00:09:06,576 --> 00:09:09,442
Well, I didn't not do it.

196
00:09:09,466 --> 00:09:10,551
Thanks, Donna.

197
00:09:10,670 --> 00:09:14,176
It's good to have you back,
Mike.

198
00:09:14,311 --> 00:09:15,897
Well, some of us have work
to do,

199
00:09:16,015 --> 00:09:17,077
and of course, by "some of us,"

200
00:09:17,102 --> 00:09:18,604
I mean you.

201
00:09:18,739 --> 00:09:20,134
As soon as word got out
that you were coming back,

202
00:09:20,159 --> 00:09:21,995
the partners started
taking numbers

203
00:09:22,147 --> 00:09:25,347
to give the boy wonder
their work.

204
00:09:25,372 --> 00:09:27,543
- Thanks, Donna.
- You already thanked me.

205
00:09:27,660 --> 00:09:29,881
Not for that.

206
00:09:30,016 --> 00:09:31,184
For not mentioning Rachel.

207
00:09:31,302 --> 00:09:32,664
- Mike...
- Come on.

208
00:09:32,689 --> 00:09:35,895
You expect me to believe
you don't know what's going on?

209
00:09:36,014 --> 00:09:38,903
I know enough to know
that it's between you and her.

210
00:09:50,097 --> 00:09:52,077
Shit.

211
00:09:52,102 --> 00:09:53,353
Look who's back.

212
00:09:53,522 --> 00:09:56,695
Shit, look who's still here.

213
00:09:56,864 --> 00:09:58,282
Somebody had to pick up
your slack

214
00:09:58,417 --> 00:10:00,454
while you were shiting the bed
on Wall Street.

215
00:10:00,589 --> 00:10:02,686
Which is why it's good to be
back here where there's a shity

216
00:10:02,711 --> 00:10:05,611
lawyer like you
to make me look good.

217
00:10:05,635 --> 00:10:07,221
It's good to see you.

218
00:10:07,355 --> 00:10:08,416
Thanks, Katrina.

219
00:10:08,441 --> 00:10:10,361
Don't thank me. Thank Louis.

220
00:10:10,480 --> 00:10:12,483
Oh, I did when he hired me back.

221
00:10:12,601 --> 00:10:15,624
I'm sure you did, and I'm sure
he would never tell you this,

222
00:10:15,742 --> 00:10:20,000
but I wanted you to know what he
gave up to bring you back here.

223
00:10:20,136 --> 00:10:22,590
- What are you talking about?
- Jessica gave Louis one wish

224
00:10:22,726 --> 00:10:23,977
when he closed Forstman,

225
00:10:24,096 --> 00:10:26,600
and he had a whole plan
to manage his work schedule

226
00:10:26,736 --> 00:10:29,501
so he could try
to reignite things with Sheila.

227
00:10:29,526 --> 00:10:32,197
And he gave all that up
because he cared more about you

228
00:10:32,333 --> 00:10:35,205
than he did about himself.

229
00:10:38,163 --> 00:10:39,776
- I didn't know that.
- Well, like I said,

230
00:10:39,800 --> 00:10:41,670
I thought you should.

231
00:10:50,659 --> 00:10:52,495
Welcome back.

232
00:11:06,030 --> 00:11:07,415
I have court in ten minutes.

233
00:11:07,566 --> 00:11:09,480
Now, what are you three doing
in front of my face?

234
00:11:09,505 --> 00:11:11,318
We're here because he showed
up at our offices this morning

235
00:11:11,342 --> 00:11:12,627
with a search warrant.

236
00:11:12,762 --> 00:11:14,024
A search warrant,
I'm sorry to say,

237
00:11:14,049 --> 00:11:15,350
you have no authority to stop.

238
00:11:15,469 --> 00:11:17,222
Yes, you do
because he deliberately

239
00:11:17,357 --> 00:11:19,060
went outside your authority
to get it.

240
00:11:19,194 --> 00:11:20,312
- What?
- Your Honor,

241
00:11:20,448 --> 00:11:21,910
I went to a different judge
because my office

242
00:11:21,934 --> 00:11:23,464
tried to reach you,
but you were unavailable.

243
00:11:23,488 --> 00:11:25,184
Check with your clerk.
There's a record of the call.

244
00:11:25,209 --> 00:11:26,931
Did you make it
from Judge Franklin's house?

245
00:11:26,946 --> 00:11:29,836
Because he's the one who signed
the warrant at 8:30 last night.

246
00:11:29,970 --> 00:11:32,285
The same judge you play golf
with every Thursday.

247
00:11:32,310 --> 00:11:34,825
And Barack Obama plays
basketball with Eric Holder.

248
00:11:34,849 --> 00:11:35,933
Let's arrest everybody.

249
00:11:36,102 --> 00:11:37,938
I'm not interested in everybody.

250
00:11:38,107 --> 00:11:39,619
I'm interested in
why you went around me.

251
00:11:39,643 --> 00:11:41,140
Because I needed a warrant
last night

252
00:11:41,164 --> 00:11:43,250
to stop them from destroying
evidence this morning.

253
00:11:43,369 --> 00:11:45,540
And the day someone's guilty
until proven innocent

254
00:11:45,657 --> 00:11:48,323
is the day that argument
holds an ounce of water.

255
00:11:48,348 --> 00:11:49,850
Better get your glass, Harvey.

256
00:11:50,001 --> 00:11:51,448
That day's coming
sooner than you think.

257
00:11:51,472 --> 00:11:53,368
Well, it's not today.

258
00:11:53,393 --> 00:11:54,674
I'm revoking your search warrant

259
00:11:54,696 --> 00:11:55,977
until we can have
a full hearing.

260
00:11:55,983 --> 00:11:57,463
- Your Honor...
- Now, that's enough.

261
00:11:57,487 --> 00:12:00,376
If you want to go rummaging
around in a law firm's files,

262
00:12:00,527 --> 00:12:02,881
you better come to me
with more than innuendo.

263
00:12:06,592 --> 00:12:07,593
I better get going.

264
00:12:07,727 --> 00:12:09,430
I have to look up
the word "innuendo,"

265
00:12:09,549 --> 00:12:14,086
if you know what I mean.

266
00:12:14,110 --> 00:12:17,032
Harvey, I'm telling you, that
man is not going to stop coming.

267
00:12:17,168 --> 00:12:19,672
I'm going to suggest
something radical here.

268
00:12:19,790 --> 00:12:21,125
And what is that?

269
00:12:21,243 --> 00:12:23,380
We could just give him
what he wants.

270
00:12:23,549 --> 00:12:25,101
The fact is
we've got nothing to hide.

271
00:12:25,253 --> 00:12:27,451
Harvey, I don't care
that we have nothing to hide.

272
00:12:27,475 --> 00:12:29,255
A police officer
follows a car long enough,

273
00:12:29,279 --> 00:12:30,647
he's gonna find
a busted taillight.

274
00:12:30,766 --> 00:12:33,321
And even if he doesn't,
he's gonna bust it himself.

275
00:12:33,456 --> 00:12:34,601
Well, what are you
suggesting we do?

276
00:12:34,626 --> 00:12:36,472
I don't know,
but this whole witch hunt

277
00:12:36,497 --> 00:12:39,169
is about Cahill thinking
you colluded with Mike Ross.

278
00:12:39,304 --> 00:12:40,305
So now that he's back,

279
00:12:40,456 --> 00:12:42,009
why don't you collude
with that fraud

280
00:12:42,144 --> 00:12:44,014
and get us the hell out of this?

281
00:12:50,041 --> 00:12:52,495
See you got yourself an office.

282
00:12:52,861 --> 00:12:54,881
Yeah, it's not as nice
as the one I had, but...

283
00:12:55,000 --> 00:12:56,385
It's still a step up.

284
00:12:56,504 --> 00:12:58,785
You mean because it's smaller
or because the view is worse?

285
00:12:58,809 --> 00:13:01,848
I mean
because it's my old office.

286
00:13:02,016 --> 00:13:03,151
You're shiting me.

287
00:13:03,270 --> 00:13:04,822
Look in the top left drawer.

288
00:13:11,205 --> 00:13:14,211
- You're serious.
- I am.

289
00:13:14,347 --> 00:13:15,464
Donna said she did this.

290
00:13:15,599 --> 00:13:17,585
She had the idea
to give you an office.

291
00:13:17,721 --> 00:13:19,273
It was my idea
to give you this office.

292
00:13:19,425 --> 00:13:20,706
And it just
happened to be empty.

293
00:13:20,812 --> 00:13:21,813
Something like that.

294
00:13:21,814 --> 00:13:23,734
Right.

295
00:13:23,869 --> 00:13:26,707
It's good to have you back
where you belong.

296
00:13:26,826 --> 00:13:28,495
Okay, enough fun.

297
00:13:28,631 --> 00:13:30,417
Sean Cahill's trying
to go through every file

298
00:13:30,551 --> 00:13:32,315
we have on the takeover. You in?

299
00:13:32,340 --> 00:13:34,069
I sure as hell
don't want to do an amicus brief

300
00:13:34,093 --> 00:13:35,596
for Paul Porter. Good.

301
00:13:35,765 --> 00:13:37,183
Then figure out a way
to keep Cahill

302
00:13:37,318 --> 00:13:38,798
from getting his hands
on our documents,

303
00:13:38,822 --> 00:13:40,775
and do it fast
because we don't have much time.

304
00:13:40,943 --> 00:13:42,496
Harvey, have you considered

305
00:13:42,614 --> 00:13:44,700
the fact that he's been
going after us for collusion,

306
00:13:44,836 --> 00:13:47,023
and we didn't collude?
What are you getting at?

307
00:13:47,125 --> 00:13:49,095
Why don't we just give
him all the files?

308
00:13:49,197 --> 00:13:50,198
We have nothing to hide,

309
00:13:50,332 --> 00:13:51,829
and fighting him makes it
look like we do.

310
00:13:51,853 --> 00:13:53,054
That's what I said to Jessica.

311
00:13:53,056 --> 00:13:54,251
You know what she said to me?

312
00:13:54,276 --> 00:13:56,005
"A cop follows a car
long enough,

313
00:13:56,029 --> 00:13:57,542
"he's gonna find
a busted taillight.

314
00:13:57,566 --> 00:13:59,619
And even if he doesn't,
he's gonna bust it himself."

315
00:14:03,029 --> 00:14:05,133
Speaking of Jessica,

316
00:14:05,252 --> 00:14:10,563
you never told me how she felt
about me coming back.

317
00:14:10,715 --> 00:14:13,571
Find a way to beat Cahill,
and then ask me that again.

318
00:14:20,254 --> 00:14:22,124
You just had to get
to him first, didn't you?

319
00:14:22,259 --> 00:14:23,387
What, did you give him a lock
of your hair?

320
00:14:23,412 --> 00:14:24,764
What are you talking about,
Louis?

321
00:14:24,916 --> 00:14:26,562
You think I didn't notice
you conveniently put Henderson

322
00:14:26,586 --> 00:14:28,366
in my old office so you
can give Mike your old office?

323
00:14:28,390 --> 00:14:29,452
For your information,

324
00:14:29,477 --> 00:14:32,483
Louis, Henderson
begged for your old office

325
00:14:32,617 --> 00:14:34,403
because he thinks
you're the best attorney

326
00:14:34,572 --> 00:14:36,101
that's ever walked the face
of this earth.

327
00:14:36,125 --> 00:14:37,878
Oh, bull... really?

328
00:14:37,997 --> 00:14:40,635
Absolutely.

329
00:14:40,787 --> 00:14:43,559
So you're not just saying
that to butter me up

330
00:14:43,677 --> 00:14:45,430
so I'll let this go?

331
00:14:45,566 --> 00:14:46,767
Hand to God,

332
00:14:46,901 --> 00:14:48,798
or as Henderson would say,

333
00:14:48,823 --> 00:14:50,943
"hand to Louis." Okay, then.

334
00:14:51,078 --> 00:14:55,119
Just as long as you're not
trying to pull one over on me.

335
00:14:55,255 --> 00:14:56,924
That Henderson is going places.

336
00:15:02,807 --> 00:15:07,116
Don't move.

337
00:15:07,234 --> 00:15:08,870
What are you doing?

338
00:15:09,021 --> 00:15:11,292
Taking a mental picture
of this moment.

339
00:15:11,411 --> 00:15:12,829
Louis, that's not a mental...

340
00:15:12,964 --> 00:15:15,502
Mike Ross, the prodigal son,
returns.

341
00:15:15,671 --> 00:15:16,922
- Thanks.
- You're very welcome.

342
00:15:17,058 --> 00:15:21,434
And Louis, I want to thank
you again for bringing me back.

343
00:15:21,568 --> 00:15:22,986
I'm never gonna forget it.

344
00:15:23,105 --> 00:15:26,589
And if there is every anything
that I can do to repay you...

345
00:15:26,614 --> 00:15:28,093
Mike, please.

346
00:15:28,117 --> 00:15:29,251
Don't insult me.

347
00:15:29,403 --> 00:15:32,593
You do not owe me,
and if you really care about me,

348
00:15:32,745 --> 00:15:36,603
you will never mention
repaying me with a favor again.

349
00:15:36,754 --> 00:15:38,784
- Really appreciate it, Louis.
- Good.

350
00:15:38,809 --> 00:15:41,007
Now, I need you to drop
whatever it is you're doing...

351
00:15:41,031 --> 00:15:42,628
Oh, Louis,
I can't drop what I'm doing.

352
00:15:42,653 --> 00:15:43,987
Harvey just asked me to...

353
00:15:44,123 --> 00:15:45,267
What do you mean you
can't drop what you're doing?

354
00:15:45,291 --> 00:15:46,520
I just brought you back here.
You owe me.

355
00:15:46,545 --> 00:15:47,856
You just told me
never to mention that again.

356
00:15:47,881 --> 00:15:49,216
What, do you think I meant that?

357
00:15:49,335 --> 00:15:50,086
I said that because that's
what people say.

358
00:15:50,220 --> 00:15:51,588
Now, what you say is,

359
00:15:51,724 --> 00:15:52,768
"screw what Harvey
asked me to do.

360
00:15:52,793 --> 00:15:53,821
"I don't give a shit about him.

361
00:15:53,845 --> 00:15:55,287
I only give a shit about you,
Louis."

362
00:15:55,399 --> 00:15:56,577
Louis, this isn't
just for Harvey.

363
00:15:56,602 --> 00:15:57,603
It's for the firm, okay?

364
00:15:57,739 --> 00:15:58,856
Sean Cahill... Bullshit.

365
00:15:58,992 --> 00:16:00,788
That's just the kind of thing
that Harvey...

366
00:16:00,812 --> 00:16:02,642
did you just... did you just...

367
00:16:02,667 --> 00:16:03,729
did you just say, "Sean Cahill"?

368
00:16:03,753 --> 00:16:04,964
Yeah. He's trying to get access

369
00:16:04,989 --> 00:16:06,351
to our files
on the Gillis takeover.

370
00:16:06,376 --> 00:16:08,691
Why didn't you
say that in the first place?

371
00:16:08,715 --> 00:16:10,184
We need to fight
this son of a bitch

372
00:16:10,334 --> 00:16:11,580
with the full force
of the law, Mike.

373
00:16:11,605 --> 00:16:13,251
- That's what I was doing.
- Then, do it.

374
00:16:13,276 --> 00:16:14,454
You don't have time
to work on this case.

375
00:16:14,478 --> 00:16:16,398
I need to bring it to Katrina.

376
00:16:16,533 --> 00:16:18,988
- Louis, are you okay?
- No, I am not okay.

377
00:16:19,123 --> 00:16:20,553
Mike, this is an attack
on our firm,

378
00:16:20,577 --> 00:16:22,690
and an attack against one of us
is an attack against all of us.

379
00:16:22,715 --> 00:16:24,384
Get the hell to work.

380
00:16:28,512 --> 00:16:29,764
We're in trouble.

381
00:16:29,899 --> 00:16:32,070
Sean Cahill is trying
to get the Gillis files.

382
00:16:32,188 --> 00:16:34,358
Louis, you buried that document.

383
00:16:34,493 --> 00:16:35,744
You don't understand.

384
00:16:35,896 --> 00:16:37,699
The SEC is gonna have
these files forever,

385
00:16:37,835 --> 00:16:39,564
and eventually,
they're gonna see the money

386
00:16:39,588 --> 00:16:41,218
went in one place
and came out the other,

387
00:16:41,243 --> 00:16:44,716
and I'm the person who did it.

388
00:16:44,852 --> 00:16:46,281
What do you need me to do?

389
00:16:46,305 --> 00:16:48,753
I want you to cover up
my tracks as best you can.

390
00:16:48,777 --> 00:16:50,112
And what are you going to do?

391
00:16:50,264 --> 00:16:51,148
I'm going to try to fix it
so the goddamn thing

392
00:16:51,284 --> 00:16:52,953
never happened
in the first place.

393
00:17:01,424 --> 00:17:02,809
What are you doing here?

394
00:17:02,961 --> 00:17:05,098
I didn't think we had
any further business to discuss.

395
00:17:05,233 --> 00:17:06,518
We don't. We just have a problem

396
00:17:06,653 --> 00:17:08,189
with the business we just did.

397
00:17:08,308 --> 00:17:10,070
Are you here to shake me down
for more money?

398
00:17:10,078 --> 00:17:11,280
I'm here to give it all back.

399
00:17:11,448 --> 00:17:13,395
- Louis, I told you...
- No, just listen to me, okay.

400
00:17:13,420 --> 00:17:16,459
The SEC... they're trying
to get access to our files.

401
00:17:16,627 --> 00:17:19,827
That happens, they see that
your payout was routed offshore

402
00:17:19,852 --> 00:17:21,093
and you didn't pay taxes on it.

403
00:17:21,105 --> 00:17:23,360
They'll see
I haven't paid taxes.

404
00:17:23,510 --> 00:17:25,815
I have until the third quarter
of two years from now

405
00:17:25,950 --> 00:17:27,368
to report that income,

406
00:17:27,520 --> 00:17:28,990
and if I need to, I will.

407
00:17:29,124 --> 00:17:30,794
Are you crazy?

408
00:17:30,912 --> 00:17:32,213
They're not idiots.

409
00:17:32,365 --> 00:17:35,304
Nobody has money wired through
a Swiss bank and the Caymans

410
00:17:35,423 --> 00:17:37,403
if they're planning
on reporting it to the IRS.

411
00:17:37,428 --> 00:17:40,210
That's not proof of anything,
and the only thing

412
00:17:40,234 --> 00:17:42,364
they'll definitely find if they
get a look at those files

413
00:17:42,390 --> 00:17:43,574
is that you embezzled money.

414
00:17:43,692 --> 00:17:45,161
So get out of my office.

415
00:17:45,280 --> 00:17:46,365
Listen to me, goddamn it.

416
00:17:46,499 --> 00:17:50,257
We need to undo this deal.

417
00:17:50,409 --> 00:17:52,178
I tell you what, Louis.

418
00:17:52,296 --> 00:17:57,106
Have a seat.

419
00:17:57,225 --> 00:17:59,896
You want peace of mind?

420
00:18:00,065 --> 00:18:03,288
Draw up the same paperwork
we already signed.

421
00:18:03,440 --> 00:18:06,773
Only this time, have Harvey
sign it instead of you.

422
00:18:06,798 --> 00:18:08,000
What?

423
00:18:08,118 --> 00:18:09,003
You're the one
who said you'd go to the ends

424
00:18:09,137 --> 00:18:10,148
of the earth to stick it to him.

425
00:18:10,172 --> 00:18:11,373
Taking his client is one thing.

426
00:18:11,392 --> 00:18:12,393
Framing him for a felony?

427
00:18:12,395 --> 00:18:13,430
That's another.

428
00:18:13,564 --> 00:18:15,017
It's your call.

429
00:18:15,151 --> 00:18:16,653
Use your name,
replace it with his,

430
00:18:16,805 --> 00:18:18,157
I don't give a shit.

431
00:18:18,309 --> 00:18:22,167
But the deal
is staying in place.

432
00:18:38,834 --> 00:18:41,505
I heard they hired
a new hotshot attorney,

433
00:18:41,674 --> 00:18:43,427
but they never said
how handsome he was.

434
00:18:43,544 --> 00:18:45,241
Look, Rachel,
I'm really swamped right now.

435
00:18:45,266 --> 00:18:48,439
Too swamped to even
stop by and say, "hello"?

436
00:18:48,573 --> 00:18:50,721
Saying hello is just
gonna lead to saying a lot more,

437
00:18:50,745 --> 00:18:54,285
and now is not the time
to have it out.

438
00:18:54,422 --> 00:18:56,208
Well, I'm not here
to have it out with you.

439
00:18:56,376 --> 00:18:59,265
I am here to work with you
on fighting off Sean Cahill.

440
00:18:59,383 --> 00:19:00,517
I don't need any help.

441
00:19:00,636 --> 00:19:02,021
But you just
said you were swamped.

442
00:19:02,139 --> 00:19:03,902
Because I'm trying to avoid
having a conversation with you,

443
00:19:03,927 --> 00:19:07,067
which, obviously, isn't working.

444
00:19:07,201 --> 00:19:09,321
Well, Mike,
I am Harvey's associate now.

445
00:19:09,441 --> 00:19:11,304
So you working a case with him,
you're working it with me.

446
00:19:11,328 --> 00:19:12,810
He didn't say anything
to me about it.

447
00:19:12,915 --> 00:19:14,584
Well, he said it to me.

448
00:19:14,720 --> 00:19:18,511
Why do you think I'm here?

449
00:19:18,645 --> 00:19:20,542
I don't care what he said.
It's not a good idea.

450
00:19:20,567 --> 00:19:22,832
What isn't? For us to even be
in the same room together?

451
00:19:22,856 --> 00:19:24,325
Not right now. No.

452
00:19:24,444 --> 00:19:26,447
You're the one
who chose to come back here.

453
00:19:26,582 --> 00:19:28,618
So?

454
00:19:28,754 --> 00:19:30,005
So you don't get

455
00:19:30,157 --> 00:19:32,378
to act disappointed
that I work here too.

456
00:19:32,496 --> 00:19:33,714
Rachel. Listen to me.

457
00:19:33,832 --> 00:19:35,535
I told you that I needed space.

458
00:19:35,670 --> 00:19:37,806
What do you call
staying in a hotel?

459
00:19:37,943 --> 00:19:40,314
Based on this conversation,
I call it a smart move.

460
00:19:40,448 --> 00:19:42,401
Okay, Mike, I'm sorry.

461
00:19:42,537 --> 00:19:43,538
Where are you going?

462
00:19:43,656 --> 00:19:45,326
Get some air.

463
00:19:51,424 --> 00:19:52,559
Wow.

464
00:19:52,677 --> 00:19:54,741
They hire you back after helping
them break the law,

465
00:19:54,766 --> 00:19:56,329
and this is
what they give you for lunch?

466
00:19:56,353 --> 00:19:58,751
You wouldn't ask that if you'd
ever had one of these bagels.

467
00:19:58,776 --> 00:20:00,947
Maybe not,
but let me ask you this.

468
00:20:01,081 --> 00:20:04,538
You remember that game show
called Let's Make a Deal?

469
00:20:04,673 --> 00:20:05,841
Not interested.

470
00:20:05,960 --> 00:20:07,406
You haven't heard
what's in it for you.

471
00:20:07,430 --> 00:20:09,193
I don't need to hear
what's in it for me because I

472
00:20:09,217 --> 00:20:11,303
know what's in it for you.

473
00:20:11,440 --> 00:20:12,641
You're a smart kid.

474
00:20:12,758 --> 00:20:13,999
I see why they wanted you back.

475
00:20:14,112 --> 00:20:15,507
I'm gonna get back
to my bagel, which is gonna

476
00:20:15,532 --> 00:20:18,320
taste so much better
when I'm not looking at you.

477
00:20:18,456 --> 00:20:22,474
All right, before you gobble
that up, think about this.

478
00:20:22,499 --> 00:20:25,314
Sooner or later,
I'm gonna get those files,

479
00:20:25,339 --> 00:20:27,369
but there's nothing to stop you
from giving them to me

480
00:20:27,394 --> 00:20:28,930
all on your own.

481
00:20:29,065 --> 00:20:30,433
If you do that,

482
00:20:30,602 --> 00:20:32,772
any of those files
that say "Mike Ross,"

483
00:20:32,941 --> 00:20:37,166
I'll replace with "anonymous
former employee."

484
00:20:37,285 --> 00:20:38,313
That would be tempting, Sean,

485
00:20:38,337 --> 00:20:41,008
if I actually had something
to hide.

486
00:20:46,691 --> 00:20:49,863
Oh, I do have
one more question, though.

487
00:20:50,015 --> 00:20:52,714
Is Harvey footing the bill?
What?

488
00:20:52,738 --> 00:20:55,493
For your room at the Soho Grand.

489
00:20:55,628 --> 00:20:57,631
That's where you're staying,
right?

490
00:20:57,750 --> 00:20:58,861
You should try the Cobb salad.

491
00:20:58,886 --> 00:21:01,809
It's out of this world.

492
00:21:06,355 --> 00:21:07,383
Guess who just got propositioned

493
00:21:07,407 --> 00:21:08,909
by a striking blonde?

494
00:21:09,027 --> 00:21:11,198
Please tell me
it was Kate Upton.

495
00:21:11,333 --> 00:21:12,561
Isn't she a little young
for you?

496
00:21:12,586 --> 00:21:14,432
Last night, she told me
I was the perfect age.

497
00:21:14,457 --> 00:21:15,709
To be her father.

498
00:21:15,844 --> 00:21:17,590
When are you gonna understand
they all want a daddy, Mike?

499
00:21:17,614 --> 00:21:19,026
You want to talk about Cahill
or just

500
00:21:19,051 --> 00:21:20,781
keep bragging about things
that never actually happened.

501
00:21:20,806 --> 00:21:23,027
- What did Cahill want?
- It's not what we wanted.

502
00:21:23,145 --> 00:21:24,363
It's what he gave me.

503
00:21:24,481 --> 00:21:25,593
Well, let's have it.

504
00:21:25,618 --> 00:21:27,181
Son of a bitch
knew I was staying at a hotel.

505
00:21:27,205 --> 00:21:28,466
- What are you getting at?
- Didn't you say

506
00:21:28,491 --> 00:21:30,533
he sidestepped Judge Hopkins
to get a search warrant

507
00:21:30,545 --> 00:21:31,580
for our files?

508
00:21:31,749 --> 00:21:33,301
You're thinking
he went around Hopkins

509
00:21:33,452 --> 00:21:34,731
to get authorization
to follow us?

510
00:21:34,756 --> 00:21:37,010
I'm thinking he never
got authorization at all.

511
00:21:37,145 --> 00:21:38,430
Then we need to get a list

512
00:21:38,565 --> 00:21:40,903
of the SEC's requests
for surveillance by tomorrow.

513
00:21:41,021 --> 00:21:42,573
I have a friend at justice.

514
00:21:42,691 --> 00:21:44,337
Since when?

515
00:21:44,362 --> 00:21:46,124
Okay, I don't,
but I thought it sounded cool.

516
00:21:46,250 --> 00:21:47,869
Mike, this is serious.

517
00:21:48,004 --> 00:21:49,807
We need that list,
and we need it by tomorrow.

518
00:21:49,926 --> 00:21:51,796
On it.

519
00:21:59,348 --> 00:22:00,700
Good new, Louis.

520
00:22:00,852 --> 00:22:05,161
I not only misfiled
and misdated that document,

521
00:22:05,296 --> 00:22:08,395
I added in 10,000 others
that look just like it.

522
00:22:08,420 --> 00:22:11,225
That thing is as buried
as it's ever going to be.

523
00:22:11,377 --> 00:22:12,228
What the hell difference
does it make?

524
00:22:12,379 --> 00:22:14,851
It's all for nothing.

525
00:22:14,986 --> 00:22:17,992
- What happened with Forstman?
- What do you think?

526
00:22:18,110 --> 00:22:19,361
He didn't go for it.

527
00:22:19,530 --> 00:22:22,870
No, something else happened
because you wouldn't

528
00:22:23,005 --> 00:22:25,125
be this upset
if he just turned you down.

529
00:22:25,260 --> 00:22:27,274
He wouldn't undo anything,

530
00:22:27,299 --> 00:22:30,355
but he is willing to let me pin
the whole thing on Harvey.

531
00:22:30,472 --> 00:22:31,891
How could you even do that?

532
00:22:32,027 --> 00:22:33,088
Oh, I don't know.

533
00:22:33,112 --> 00:22:35,650
Make up a new document,
forge his signature.

534
00:22:35,786 --> 00:22:37,465
Doesn't matter 'cause
I'm not gonna do it.

535
00:22:37,489 --> 00:22:40,077
- Louis...
- Katrina, enough.

536
00:22:40,213 --> 00:22:41,799
You did good work,

537
00:22:41,917 --> 00:22:44,671
but the truth is, if we
have to turn over those files,

538
00:22:44,808 --> 00:22:45,890
they find that transaction.

539
00:22:45,893 --> 00:22:48,766
I'm gonna end up in prison.

540
00:22:51,574 --> 00:22:55,531
Then you and I better

541
00:22:55,667 --> 00:22:59,090
figure out a way to make sure
Harvey wins that motion.

542
00:23:04,337 --> 00:23:06,224
Okay.

543
00:23:09,366 --> 00:23:10,534
Don't you have a funny way

544
00:23:10,653 --> 00:23:12,539
of giving someone space. What?

545
00:23:12,691 --> 00:23:15,413
Not only did you do exactly
what we talked about not doing

546
00:23:15,548 --> 00:23:18,336
but you lied, and you
used Harvey's name to do it.

547
00:23:18,472 --> 00:23:20,224
- I am sorry.
- No, sorry's not good enough.

548
00:23:20,375 --> 00:23:23,014
This is the second time we've
had this conversation recently,

549
00:23:23,149 --> 00:23:26,750
and I want to know why the hell
we're having it again.

550
00:23:26,774 --> 00:23:28,243
I didn't mean to lie.

551
00:23:28,362 --> 00:23:30,415
I just... I went to Mike to talk...

552
00:23:30,567 --> 00:23:31,835
That's my point.

553
00:23:31,954 --> 00:23:33,484
You couldn't even make it
through one day?

554
00:23:33,508 --> 00:23:34,592
I thought that I could.

555
00:23:34,711 --> 00:23:37,132
And then, I saw
him sitting there, and I just...

556
00:23:37,266 --> 00:23:38,896
Rachel, just because
something's hard to do

557
00:23:38,920 --> 00:23:40,305
doesn't mean
that you can't do it.

558
00:23:40,424 --> 00:23:42,277
Okay. I shouldn't have
brought Harvey into it,

559
00:23:42,395 --> 00:23:44,783
but I am not going to apologize
for talking to Mike

560
00:23:44,902 --> 00:23:47,073
because he and I aren't the same
as you and Harvey.

561
00:23:47,240 --> 00:23:48,910
Excuse me?

562
00:23:49,045 --> 00:23:51,059
- That didn't come out that I...
- I did not tell you

563
00:23:51,083 --> 00:23:52,812
that for you to just
throw it back in my face.

564
00:23:52,837 --> 00:23:54,490
I didn't mean
to throw it in your face.

565
00:23:54,624 --> 00:23:58,733
I respect that you let things
take their natural course,

566
00:23:58,868 --> 00:24:02,526
but I want to make things work
with Mike,

567
00:24:02,661 --> 00:24:06,669
and the only way I know how
to do that is to fight for him.

568
00:24:06,821 --> 00:24:08,707
Fight for him all you want,

569
00:24:08,842 --> 00:24:10,595
but don't lie about Harvey
ever again.

570
00:24:35,189 --> 00:24:38,422
You missing it in here already?

571
00:24:38,447 --> 00:24:41,118
Just passing through.

572
00:24:41,237 --> 00:24:42,919
- I lied to you.
- I know you lied to me...

573
00:24:42,924 --> 00:24:45,595
Not that.

574
00:24:45,714 --> 00:24:50,290
Harvey never assigned me
to your case.

575
00:24:50,392 --> 00:24:53,114
I did it
because you left our home,

576
00:24:53,266 --> 00:24:54,785
and you came here.

577
00:24:54,936 --> 00:24:59,746
And all I can think every time
I look at you is how sorry I am.

578
00:25:06,597 --> 00:25:08,327
And the reason
I want you to leave me alone

579
00:25:08,352 --> 00:25:12,861
is all I can think
when I look at you is him.

580
00:25:15,319 --> 00:25:18,124
Then why did you come back?

581
00:25:18,293 --> 00:25:21,799
I was drowning,
and Louis threw me a lifeline.

582
00:25:21,935 --> 00:25:23,971
I'm your lifeline, too.

583
00:25:24,140 --> 00:25:26,338
A lifeline? You're the one
that threw me overboard.

584
00:25:26,362 --> 00:25:29,284
- Mike...
- And why did it have to be him?

585
00:25:34,214 --> 00:25:36,385
I don't need you to keep
telling me that you're sorry

586
00:25:36,535 --> 00:25:39,392
or to be charming
or anything else.

587
00:25:42,266 --> 00:25:45,940
I just need to get that image
out of my head.

588
00:26:11,256 --> 00:26:12,892
- Did you get it?
- No.

589
00:26:13,010 --> 00:26:14,873
A little heads
up would have been nice.

590
00:26:14,898 --> 00:26:16,578
I don't exactly
have a backup plan.

591
00:26:16,603 --> 00:26:18,857
- Well, good thing I do.
- What are you talking about?

592
00:26:18,991 --> 00:26:21,914
It doesn't matter whether we
have proof of our theory or not.

593
00:26:22,065 --> 00:26:24,286
It just matters whether or not
our theory is true.

594
00:26:24,420 --> 00:26:25,421
You typed up a fake list.

595
00:26:25,540 --> 00:26:27,126
Exactly. Brilliant.

596
00:26:27,244 --> 00:26:28,489
It would have
been a little more brilliant

597
00:26:28,514 --> 00:26:30,027
if you didn't get here
at the last second.

598
00:26:30,051 --> 00:26:32,532
It wouldn't work if it doesn't
look real, and that takes time.

599
00:26:32,557 --> 00:26:33,725
Okay, just give it to me.

600
00:26:33,860 --> 00:26:35,730
I got it.

601
00:26:41,411 --> 00:26:42,914
Oh, well, well.

602
00:26:43,049 --> 00:26:44,217
If it isn't the wonder twins.

603
00:26:44,335 --> 00:26:46,221
Form of "douche bag."

604
00:26:46,340 --> 00:26:48,176
Shape of "got you by the balls."

605
00:26:48,312 --> 00:26:49,741
No, no, no, no.
It's got to be an animal.

606
00:26:49,765 --> 00:26:51,518
I don't care what it has to be.

607
00:26:51,653 --> 00:26:54,275
What that is,
is every surveillance request

608
00:26:54,410 --> 00:26:56,113
from the SEC
in the last three months.

609
00:26:56,281 --> 00:26:57,727
Mike, why don't you tell him
what's on there?

610
00:26:57,751 --> 00:27:00,455
Oh, he knows what's on there
and what's not on there,

611
00:27:00,624 --> 00:27:02,822
which would be me and you.

612
00:27:02,846 --> 00:27:04,716
Wait a second,
doesn't that make any evidence

613
00:27:04,851 --> 00:27:06,497
he's planning on using today
inadmissible?

614
00:27:06,522 --> 00:27:09,227
I believe it would.

615
00:27:09,345 --> 00:27:11,481
Save yourself
the embarrassment, Sean.

616
00:27:11,618 --> 00:27:13,989
Withdraw your request
for a warrant, a subpoena,

617
00:27:14,123 --> 00:27:15,158
or anything.

618
00:27:15,327 --> 00:27:17,914
All right.
Let's get this thing going.

619
00:27:18,050 --> 00:27:20,221
What are you two doing
at his table?

620
00:27:20,372 --> 00:27:23,979
You want to tell him
or should we?

621
00:27:24,097 --> 00:27:26,819
Your Honor, I am formally
withdrawing my request

622
00:27:26,937 --> 00:27:28,189
to go through their files.

623
00:27:28,358 --> 00:27:30,077
Then, why are we all here?

624
00:27:30,229 --> 00:27:31,865
Because I want it to be
on the record

625
00:27:32,033 --> 00:27:33,786
that Logan Sanders requests

626
00:27:33,921 --> 00:27:35,540
the release
of all communications

627
00:27:35,675 --> 00:27:38,073
between these two gentlemen
on his behalf.

628
00:27:38,098 --> 00:27:39,717
- What?
- You heard me.

629
00:27:39,885 --> 00:27:42,974
Your Honor, how do we know
that signature isn't fabricated?

630
00:27:43,110 --> 00:27:44,171
Go ahead.

631
00:27:44,195 --> 00:27:45,898
Give Mr. Sanders a call.

632
00:27:46,033 --> 00:27:49,573
He'll tell you it's true.

633
00:27:49,709 --> 00:27:51,462
Because unlike you,
he was more than happy

634
00:27:51,613 --> 00:27:56,307
to sign the request
in exchange for immunity.

635
00:27:56,459 --> 00:27:59,398
Pending verification
of this signature,

636
00:27:59,533 --> 00:28:03,441
you are to give him everything
he asks for immediately.

637
00:28:03,609 --> 00:28:06,866
Your Honor.

638
00:28:07,000 --> 00:28:09,505
I told you I'd get those files
sooner or later.

639
00:28:09,656 --> 00:28:12,513
Guess it's gonna be sooner.

640
00:28:19,179 --> 00:28:20,481
What's that?

641
00:28:20,616 --> 00:28:22,931
It's 50 different ways we can
stop Sean Cahill in his tracks.

642
00:28:22,956 --> 00:28:24,492
- Why did you...
- I told you.

643
00:28:24,626 --> 00:28:26,830
An attack on one of us
is an attack on all of us.

644
00:28:26,998 --> 00:28:29,229
Harvey is my brother, and if
Cahill's coming after him,

645
00:28:29,254 --> 00:28:31,391
he is coming after me.
Louis, it doesn't matter.

646
00:28:31,510 --> 00:28:32,872
There's nothing
we can do about it.

647
00:28:33,013 --> 00:28:34,124
What do you mean there's
nothing we can do about it?

648
00:28:34,148 --> 00:28:35,601
Logan Sanders cut a deal
with Cahill.

649
00:28:35,736 --> 00:28:37,716
We have to release
all communications

650
00:28:37,740 --> 00:28:40,161
between me and Harvey on Gillis.

651
00:28:40,280 --> 00:28:41,726
Just between you and Harvey?
That's it?

652
00:28:41,750 --> 00:28:42,762
None of the Forstman stuff?

653
00:28:42,786 --> 00:28:44,004
That's it.

654
00:28:44,122 --> 00:28:45,424
Thank God. We're in the clear.

655
00:28:45,576 --> 00:28:47,606
Louis, one second ago, you
said that an attack on Harvey

656
00:28:47,631 --> 00:28:49,060
was an attack on you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.

657
00:28:49,084 --> 00:28:50,112
And you just said there's
nothing we can do about it.

658
00:28:50,137 --> 00:28:51,974
But that doesn't make
it a good thing.

659
00:28:52,109 --> 00:28:53,421
- Doesn't it?
- What are you...

660
00:28:53,445 --> 00:28:55,448
Mike, did you
collude with Harvey or not?

661
00:28:55,600 --> 00:28:57,413
- Of course I didn't.
- That's exactly my point,

662
00:28:57,438 --> 00:29:00,294
so as far as I'm concerned,
this matter is done.

663
00:29:10,987 --> 00:29:12,405
Guess what this is?

664
00:29:12,524 --> 00:29:14,410
Louis, I was never really
a Star Trek fan.

665
00:29:14,529 --> 00:29:18,787
It's the resting heart rate
of a happy man.

666
00:29:18,923 --> 00:29:20,157
It's over?

667
00:29:20,293 --> 00:29:21,795
We're sending them files,

668
00:29:21,930 --> 00:29:24,635
but we're not sending
them our files.

669
00:29:24,803 --> 00:29:26,021
I don't understand.

670
00:29:26,173 --> 00:29:28,778
Logan Sanders signed a deal,

671
00:29:28,897 --> 00:29:30,650
blah, blah, blah.

672
00:29:30,818 --> 00:29:33,623
They're not getting
the Forstman document.

673
00:29:33,742 --> 00:29:35,411
And that's the end?

674
00:29:35,546 --> 00:29:38,000
- That's the end.
- Congratulations, Louis.

675
00:29:38,169 --> 00:29:42,512
Thank you, Katrina.

676
00:29:42,646 --> 00:29:44,209
You know what,

677
00:29:44,234 --> 00:29:45,697
why don't take the rest
of the day off and check out

678
00:29:45,721 --> 00:29:47,032
that Mummenschanz retrospective
I've been telling you about.

679
00:29:47,057 --> 00:29:49,612
Thank you, Louis,
though I may do something else.

680
00:29:49,730 --> 00:29:50,925
Suit yourself,
but I'm telling you right now.

681
00:29:50,950 --> 00:29:52,703
It's a game changer.

682
00:29:52,871 --> 00:29:54,708
They...

683
00:30:02,110 --> 00:30:04,759
Am I to understand
Logan Sanders waived privilege?

684
00:30:04,783 --> 00:30:06,652
- Yeah, it's his right.
- Goddamn it, Harvey.

685
00:30:06,788 --> 00:30:09,159
You never should have cut
that man loose as a client.

686
00:30:09,277 --> 00:30:11,609
Well, I cut him loose because
I knew he was the kind of person

687
00:30:11,633 --> 00:30:12,884
who would do what he just did.

688
00:30:13,003 --> 00:30:14,589
Bullshit. You cut him loose

689
00:30:14,723 --> 00:30:16,653
because you knew Mike Ross
was coming back here.

690
00:30:16,678 --> 00:30:17,740
Well, you're damn right I did.

691
00:30:17,765 --> 00:30:19,099
I'm not gonna apologize for it.

692
00:30:19,268 --> 00:30:21,104
You should have
discussed it with me first.

693
00:30:21,273 --> 00:30:24,446
Well, it's easier to ask
for forgiveness than permission.

694
00:30:24,580 --> 00:30:26,116
Forgiveness?

695
00:30:26,252 --> 00:30:28,148
You just said you're not
going to apologize for it.

696
00:30:28,172 --> 00:30:30,760
You know what? I'm not because
I don't want to hear a lecture

697
00:30:30,879 --> 00:30:32,809
on the amount of billings
his company brought in.

698
00:30:32,834 --> 00:30:35,973
You mean the $20 million
going back over two decades.

699
00:30:36,141 --> 00:30:37,811
I don't give a shit
if it's $100 million.

700
00:30:37,979 --> 00:30:40,284
You want to have it
out over which clients we keep,

701
00:30:40,401 --> 00:30:41,463
I'm happy to.

702
00:30:41,488 --> 00:30:43,074
But in this case, I made a call,

703
00:30:43,208 --> 00:30:44,688
and you're either gonna back
me or you're not.

704
00:30:44,712 --> 00:30:46,214
We need to stop fighting.

705
00:30:46,366 --> 00:30:47,367
Excuse me?

706
00:30:47,502 --> 00:30:48,903
- We're not fighting.
- Yes, we are.

707
00:30:49,005 --> 00:30:50,340
I'm not talking about you two.

708
00:30:50,476 --> 00:30:52,596
Then what the hell
are you talking about?

709
00:30:52,732 --> 00:30:54,351
Cahill.

710
00:30:54,485 --> 00:30:55,547
You want us to give in?

711
00:30:55,572 --> 00:30:59,196
No. I'm saying
he wants all the files,

712
00:30:59,331 --> 00:31:02,203
let's give him all the files.

713
00:31:18,815 --> 00:31:20,150
Rachel, what are you doing here?

714
00:31:20,269 --> 00:31:21,580
I told you needed some time.

715
00:31:21,605 --> 00:31:24,160
And then you told me that you
needed to get that image

716
00:31:24,279 --> 00:31:25,831
out of your head.
Which is why I need-

717
00:31:25,949 --> 00:31:29,757
No. No, it isn't

718
00:31:29,876 --> 00:31:33,767
because you'll never completely
get it out of your head.

719
00:31:35,773 --> 00:31:39,898
- Tess.
- Yes, Tess.

720
00:31:40,066 --> 00:31:41,569
And my image isn't made up,

721
00:31:41,737 --> 00:31:46,630
and it wasn't of two people
kissing.

722
00:31:46,782 --> 00:31:48,802
But I got over it
without getting rid of it

723
00:31:48,955 --> 00:31:52,596
because forgiveness
doesn't work that way.

724
00:31:52,730 --> 00:31:55,603
You knew how I felt about him.

725
00:31:57,659 --> 00:31:58,944
You knew what it would do to me,

726
00:31:59,079 --> 00:32:00,280
and you did it anyway.

727
00:32:00,416 --> 00:32:03,288
And I told you I made a mistake.

728
00:32:05,461 --> 00:32:08,467
What do you want from me,
Rachel?

729
00:32:08,602 --> 00:32:11,306
I want you to decide

730
00:32:11,475 --> 00:32:16,201
if you love me
more than you hate what I did.

731
00:32:16,353 --> 00:32:20,997
And if you don't,

732
00:32:21,132 --> 00:32:22,812
then I want you to tell me
that it's over.

733
00:32:22,836 --> 00:32:27,345
And if you do,
then I want you to come home.

734
00:32:51,121 --> 00:32:53,240
- Afternoon, Sean.
- Well, you're in a good mood

735
00:32:53,376 --> 00:32:54,972
for a man who keeps getting
his ass kicked.

736
00:32:54,996 --> 00:32:57,417
Well, at a certain point,
you get tired of fighting.

737
00:32:57,553 --> 00:32:58,564
Well, I wouldn't know,

738
00:32:58,588 --> 00:32:59,950
but after this,
we can grab a beer,

739
00:32:59,975 --> 00:33:03,733
and you can tell me
what it's like to be a loser.

740
00:33:03,851 --> 00:33:05,019
Your Honor.

741
00:33:05,154 --> 00:33:06,271
Mr. Specter,

742
00:33:06,407 --> 00:33:09,195
you better be here
to hand over your clients files.

743
00:33:09,313 --> 00:33:11,117
I'm here to do more than that.

744
00:33:11,285 --> 00:33:13,673
We're handing
over all of the files

745
00:33:13,791 --> 00:33:15,487
in the Gillis Industries
takeover,

746
00:33:15,512 --> 00:33:18,217
but I want the court to catalog
every piece of paper

747
00:33:18,352 --> 00:33:20,974
in there so Sean doesn't "find
one" that was never there

748
00:33:21,109 --> 00:33:22,562
in the first place.

749
00:33:22,696 --> 00:33:26,320
Isn't this what you were
arguing against from day one?

750
00:33:26,488 --> 00:33:29,076
We changed our minds
because we have nothing to hide.

751
00:33:29,212 --> 00:33:30,831
No, no. This is a ploy.

752
00:33:30,966 --> 00:33:33,531
He's trying to get me on record
stating that we have everything,

753
00:33:33,555 --> 00:33:35,091
and if I find nothing,

754
00:33:35,210 --> 00:33:37,514
he's gonna file
malicious prosecution charges.

755
00:33:37,649 --> 00:33:40,771
Actually, Sean, I'm filing
those charges right now.

756
00:33:40,889 --> 00:33:43,527
And when you don't find anything
in the contents

757
00:33:43,696 --> 00:33:45,699
of everything you ever asked
for, this bullshit

758
00:33:45,835 --> 00:33:47,337
search becomes Exhibit A.

759
00:33:47,456 --> 00:33:49,844
Your Honor, he has no basis
to file that action.

760
00:33:49,961 --> 00:33:51,514
I can't stop the man
from giving you

761
00:33:51,633 --> 00:33:55,784
exactly what you were in here
asking me for two days ago.

762
00:33:55,808 --> 00:33:59,399
Now, are you gonna proceed under
threat the malicious prosecution

763
00:33:59,535 --> 00:34:02,574
or not?

764
00:34:02,709 --> 00:34:03,960
What's the matter, Sean?

765
00:34:04,079 --> 00:34:06,250
Afraid you won't find anything?

766
00:34:06,384 --> 00:34:08,137
Just give me the files.

767
00:34:11,731 --> 00:34:14,269
You wanted to see me?

768
00:34:14,403 --> 00:34:17,859
I wanted to give credit
where credit is due.

769
00:34:17,996 --> 00:34:19,114
Cahill went for it.

770
00:34:19,248 --> 00:34:20,867
Yes,

771
00:34:21,003 --> 00:34:24,343
and when he finds nothing,
we'll be done with him.

772
00:34:24,494 --> 00:34:25,546
Good job.

773
00:34:25,680 --> 00:34:28,970
Thank you.

774
00:34:29,139 --> 00:34:32,005
And thank you
for taking me back,

775
00:34:32,029 --> 00:34:33,711
especially since I know
you didn't want to.

776
00:34:33,734 --> 00:34:35,820
Would you have wanted
to if you were me?

777
00:34:35,989 --> 00:34:38,160
I did just come up
with that fix.

778
00:34:38,294 --> 00:34:43,339
A fix for Cahill coming after
you for colluding with Harvey?

779
00:34:43,473 --> 00:34:48,517
A problem I never would have had
if I'd never met you.

780
00:34:48,652 --> 00:34:50,047
Why'd you call me down here?

781
00:34:50,072 --> 00:34:52,995
I want to know
why the hell you came back.

782
00:34:55,735 --> 00:34:57,382
You know, it's funny. If you'd
asked me that this morning,

783
00:34:57,407 --> 00:34:59,628
I would have said because I had
no place else to go.

784
00:34:59,745 --> 00:35:01,933
I didn't ask you this morning.

785
00:35:02,084 --> 00:35:05,107
I'm asking you now.

786
00:35:05,226 --> 00:35:09,234
Then it doesn't matter
why I came back.

787
00:35:09,369 --> 00:35:12,436
What matters is that I'm staying

788
00:35:12,460 --> 00:35:15,382
because this is where I belong.

789
00:35:24,805 --> 00:35:26,942
Hey, just the person
I was looking for.

790
00:35:27,111 --> 00:35:29,030
- You heard?
- I heard that I just

791
00:35:29,166 --> 00:35:31,169
booked a plane ticket
to Boston to surprise Sheila,

792
00:35:31,288 --> 00:35:33,068
and I need you to cover
the McBain hearing tomorrow.

793
00:35:33,093 --> 00:35:37,469
Louis, the McBain hearing
is the least of our worries.

794
00:35:37,603 --> 00:35:39,139
What do you mean?

795
00:35:39,273 --> 00:35:41,811
Harvey went to court
this morning and agreed to hand

796
00:35:41,980 --> 00:35:44,818
over every single document
on the Gillis takeover,

797
00:35:44,954 --> 00:35:46,205
including Forstman.

798
00:35:46,324 --> 00:35:49,045
What? Why would...

799
00:35:49,197 --> 00:35:52,220
Because he thinks
we have nothing to hide.

800
00:35:52,339 --> 00:35:56,397
Shit.
Then it's only a matter of time

801
00:35:56,549 --> 00:35:57,877
before I'm marched
out of here in handcuffs.

802
00:35:57,902 --> 00:35:59,131
I'm not gonna
let it come to that.

803
00:35:59,155 --> 00:36:00,824
Oh, how the hell
are you gonna stop it?

804
00:36:00,943 --> 00:36:04,834
By replacing one document
with another.

805
00:36:04,952 --> 00:36:06,704
I am not framing Harvey.

806
00:36:06,840 --> 00:36:09,595
This isn't framing Harvey.

807
00:36:09,746 --> 00:36:12,134
It's freeing you.
What are you talking about?

808
00:36:12,270 --> 00:36:13,933
This makes it look
like Forstman's payment never

809
00:36:13,957 --> 00:36:15,927
went to any offshore accounts

810
00:36:16,029 --> 00:36:17,511
and that you never took a piece
of it.

811
00:36:17,532 --> 00:36:20,237
No, that's forgery.

812
00:36:20,372 --> 00:36:25,967
Which is less of a crime
than what you did.

813
00:36:26,119 --> 00:36:27,421
I didn't ask you to do this.

814
00:36:27,590 --> 00:36:30,061
Then don't use it,

815
00:36:30,163 --> 00:36:32,461
but you're the one who said that
if we give them those files,

816
00:36:32,485 --> 00:36:34,438
it's only a matter of time.

817
00:36:34,573 --> 00:36:38,281
Louis, Cahill's looking for dirt
on Harvey and Mike,

818
00:36:38,449 --> 00:36:40,285
not you and Forstman.

819
00:36:40,420 --> 00:36:42,006
He won't even give this
a second glance.

820
00:36:42,158 --> 00:36:43,961
But if he does,
it puts Harvey in jeopardy,

821
00:36:44,096 --> 00:36:48,855
and I might as well frame him
just like Forstman wanted me to.

822
00:36:49,007 --> 00:36:51,121
Then you have a decision
to make because they're turning

823
00:36:51,146 --> 00:36:54,035
everything over
first thing tomorrow.

824
00:37:10,910 --> 00:37:14,868
Louis, is everything okay?

825
00:37:15,004 --> 00:37:17,876
Yeah, everything's fine, Mike.

826
00:37:30,240 --> 00:37:32,126
Donna?

827
00:37:32,245 --> 00:37:33,881
What can I do for you, Harvey?

828
00:37:33,999 --> 00:37:35,862
Everything taken care of
for the file transfer tomorrow?

829
00:37:35,887 --> 00:37:38,118
It was taken care of 20
minutes before you asked for it.

830
00:37:38,142 --> 00:37:40,262
Great. Here's Howard, Miller,
and Klein.

831
00:37:40,398 --> 00:37:41,910
I'd like to get a jump
on these right now.

832
00:37:41,934 --> 00:37:43,771
Oh, it's late, Harvey.
We've had a long day.

833
00:37:43,906 --> 00:37:45,274
Maybe we can just... come on.

834
00:37:45,410 --> 00:37:47,697
We can order from that shity
Thai place you love.

835
00:37:47,833 --> 00:37:49,285
Knock this out in two hours.

836
00:37:49,420 --> 00:37:52,843
- Is that an order or a request?
- What are you...

837
00:37:52,961 --> 00:37:54,491
I have a date tonight, Harvey,

838
00:37:54,515 --> 00:37:57,721
so unless you think we're gonna
lose Howard, Miller, or Klein,

839
00:37:57,857 --> 00:37:59,726
I'm leaving.

840
00:38:02,200 --> 00:38:03,820
Have a good night.

841
00:38:03,987 --> 00:38:06,993
Thanks, Harvey.

842
00:38:07,162 --> 00:38:08,173
Don't forget to use
protection...

843
00:38:08,197 --> 00:38:09,215
Stop right there.

844
00:38:09,367 --> 00:38:11,003
Oh, so when I go out
with someone,

845
00:38:11,138 --> 00:38:13,068
you can give me all the shit
in the world, but when you do...

846
00:38:13,093 --> 00:38:15,541
Yep. That's exactly
how it works.

847
00:38:15,566 --> 00:38:20,359
Get used to it.

848
00:38:20,495 --> 00:38:22,591
What's wrong with you? You
look like you just saw a ghost.

849
00:38:22,615 --> 00:38:24,033
I feel like I did.

850
00:38:24,170 --> 00:38:25,933
I think we have a problem.
What do you mean?

851
00:38:25,957 --> 00:38:27,079
We just took step number one

852
00:38:27,210 --> 00:38:29,023
to finally putting
this Cahill bullshit behind us.

853
00:38:29,048 --> 00:38:31,580
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
I don't think it is behind us.

854
00:38:31,604 --> 00:38:33,975
- What?
- I don't know what Louis did,

855
00:38:34,110 --> 00:38:35,563
but I think
he did something wrong.

856
00:38:35,697 --> 00:38:36,899
What are you talking about?

857
00:38:37,034 --> 00:38:39,248
When he came to me yesterday,
he was chomping at the bit

858
00:38:39,272 --> 00:38:40,992
to help fight Cahill.
That's Louis.

859
00:38:41,126 --> 00:38:43,023
He'd take a bullet for
this firm, you know that.

860
00:38:43,048 --> 00:38:45,419
Then why did he immediately
change his tune after I told him

861
00:38:45,588 --> 00:38:48,426
that Logan was only
releasing our communications?

862
00:38:48,595 --> 00:38:49,623
He seemed relieved?

863
00:38:49,647 --> 00:38:51,099
He seemed ecstatic,

864
00:38:51,268 --> 00:38:53,666
and before that, he was pissed
that I was working on your stuff

865
00:38:53,690 --> 00:38:56,245
until he found out
it was to fight Cahill.

866
00:38:56,364 --> 00:38:58,450
What exactly are you
thinking he might have done?

867
00:38:58,586 --> 00:38:59,837
I don't know exactly,

868
00:38:59,989 --> 00:39:04,682
but I think he cut some sort
of deal with Forstman.

869
00:39:04,834 --> 00:39:05,862
He did cut a deal with Forstman.

870
00:39:05,886 --> 00:39:07,164
I'm talking about
an illegal deal.

871
00:39:07,189 --> 00:39:09,644
Mike, I know Forstman's a snake,

872
00:39:09,779 --> 00:39:11,209
but this is Louis
you're talking about.

873
00:39:11,233 --> 00:39:13,346
I know, but you weren't there
when he made me that offer.

874
00:39:13,371 --> 00:39:14,907
I'd never seen him like that.

875
00:39:15,042 --> 00:39:18,081
He was desperate to keep me
from working for "that man."

876
00:39:18,198 --> 00:39:19,477
- Mike...
- And then on top of that,

877
00:39:19,502 --> 00:39:21,806
I found out what he gave up
to get me back here.

878
00:39:21,925 --> 00:39:24,513
Sheila.

879
00:39:24,682 --> 00:39:28,523
But why would he care about us
handling over everything

880
00:39:28,658 --> 00:39:31,362
if he didn't care about
the communications between us?

881
00:39:31,498 --> 00:39:33,617
Because if he did make
a dirty deal with Forstman,

882
00:39:33,753 --> 00:39:35,356
it wouldn't have been
in those documents.

883
00:39:35,458 --> 00:39:38,908
It would have been
in the other documents.

884
00:39:38,933 --> 00:39:40,519
The documents
we just told the court

885
00:39:40,636 --> 00:39:43,224
we're happy to turn over.

886
00:39:43,360 --> 00:39:44,946
What are you gonna do?

887
00:39:45,097 --> 00:39:47,451
I'm gonna find out
what the hell Louis did.

888
00:39:50,209 --> 00:39:51,460
Go home, Mike.

889
00:39:51,579 --> 00:39:54,468
There's nothing
you can do tonight.

890
00:41:58,000 --> 00:42:00,257
I made a huge mistake.

