So you did have the document
from Coastal Motors?
- Objection.
- Harvey, you're the defendant.
I wasn't objecting
to his question.
Just his tie.
I do have to look at it,
you know.
This is fun, isn't it, Harv?
Hanging out, catching up,
learning about your fraud.
I hate to burst your bubble,
Trav,
but there was no fraud.
There was no fraud. What?
You just said,
you had the document.
Yes. We went back through
the case files.
Found the report. Whoops.
That's it. "Whoops"?
Hope, you got that.
"Whoops"?
Your defense is "whoops"?
All right,
you've made your point.
You made us a settlement offer
that we would never take.
Let's talk about
one that we would.
This is a deposition,
not a settlement meeting.
Every meeting
is a settlement meeting.
Fine.
The offer was 5 million,
and Harvey gets disbarred.
How about $100 million?
And Harvey gets disbarred.
Tanner, you want to take
this to court, go right ahead.
I'd rather watch her
cut you down
than see her cut a deal anyway.
You know, I see why hairdo
wants to roll the dice,
but why you?
You just went from
5 million to 100 million,
and you're questioning
why I don't want to settle.
If that's a sticking point,
I might be able to go to
0 million.
But the one thing
I won't budge on is
he gets disbarred.
I think I'm doing you a favor.
And what does he...
cause a headache like this once,
twice a month?
Doesn't matter,
'cause he cures more
than he makes,
like when you stuck your nose
into my case last year,
and he beat you.
Crushed him.
Then he took his ball
and went home.
- Should've stayed there.
- Look at that.
Finishing
each other's sentences.
How cute.
No wonder you won't throw him
under the bus.
Good for you, Harvey.
I mean,
you're throwing her
under the bus.
Watch yourself, Tanner.
Oh, what's the matter, Harv?
Did I offend
your delicate sensibilities?
You want to take
your ball and go home?
I'm gonna take my ball
and shove it up your... Harvey.
Of course.
Your coif ed hair,
your pretty nails.
See? She's the man,
and you're the girl.
You know, it's funny.
I would have thought
she'd prefer someone like...
This deposition is over.
Now what? Is mommy
gonna take you home now?
Wait. That's it.
You got a thing for mommy.
And now it all makes sense.
Because I actually
looked into your mommy,
and it turns out
that the whole time
you were home with daddy,
mommy was out banging...
Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET.
Point, Tanner.
I'll see you in court, Harv.
So when did the plan change
from trying to settle
to punching Tanner in the face?
He didn't seem to want
to do the one,
so I did the other.
That's funny.
But he got under your skin,
and that can't happen
when we go to trial.
- It won't.
- Not if you're prepared.
Are you suggesting a trial run?
I don't want
a trial at all but...
We already know your position
is to cut me loose.
Not you. No.
I'm just one of many partners
who don't know what to think.
And if they don't know
you didn't do it,
how is a jury gonna feel?
You're betting everything
on this trial.
Better make damn sure
you can win.
He's an asshole.
He's right.
All right, what?
If we're gonna do this,
I don't want to waste the chance
to tune you up,
but that means we need
a damn good Tanner.
Are you saying I'm rusty?
When was the last time
you were in the ring?
We don't need a good Tanner.
We need a nasty Tanner.
Someone who will do anything
to beat me.
Someone who makes you want
to punch him in the face.
Oh, you want me to do what?
I just told you four times.
I want you to play Tanner.
No, no, no.
I'm... I was a little distracted
because I was reading.
Can you just repeat it
one more time?
Look, Louis,
you've had your fun.
When I said the ground rules
were to knock me off my game,
I was talking about the trial.
I know what
you're talking about.
You didn't come to me
because I'm an idiot.
No, not because you're one,
in spite of you being one.
I'm the man for the job,
and you know it.
Actually, I had you
at number five on my list.
And what did Jessica
have me at?
Six.
Okay. I get it. I get it.
You're trying to make me mad.
No, I'm trying
to make you good.
You see, the one thing
you have in common
with Tanner
is your hatred of me.
That is true.
But what you don't have
are his skills.
But that's okay.
I'll go to somebody else.
Wait, Harvey. Stop.
You don't think I can win?
I know you can't.
This isn't some bank loan,
junior.
Get out.
I've got a trial to prepare for.
And you know what?
When you lose,
do not come crying to me,
because there's nothing
on this earth
that would be sacred enough
to stop me
from shoving your ass
in the goddamn ground.
Good.
Because those are
the real ground rules.
Oh, I see.
Now, you're asking
to get lit up.
Somebody wants to get lit up.
? See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ?
? Get another piece of pie
for your wife ?
? Everybody wanna know
how it feel ?
? Everybody wanna see
what it's like ?
? Living in a beehive
of your mind ?
? Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ?
? All right
? all that time imagine this ?
? The greenback boogie
Messages,
color coded by urgency.
Has Donna called back?
She would be red, so...
No.
Then those would all be
the same shade
of I-don't-give-a-shit.
Call her again. Yes.
So?
How was it?
- How was what?
- Punching Tanner.
It was awesome, wasn't it?
Tell me it was awesome.
What are you, in middle school?
I'm in the middle of a trial.
A mock trial.
Mock trials are for children.
The adults are doing
an in-house trial run.
Okay. Mock trial, trial run.
Po-tay-to, po-tah-to,
not potato.
What do you need me to do?
What he needs you to do
is help me.
What's this?
You've been drafted.
Okay, what round?
Excuse me?
Sports metaphor.
Oh, it's not tennis. Sports.
You've been assigned
by the judge to help me
in pretty boy's trial.
Oh, look at that,
he thinks I'm pretty.
Wait, what judge?
His honor, Daniel Hardman.
I'll see you in court,
sweet tits.
No, no. He can't.
- He can.
- I'm not...
- You are.
- Harvey...
Listen, Louis is devious,
confident, and intelligent.
You forgot ugly, lazy,
and disrespectful.
Now is not the time to quote
The Breakfast Club.
Oh, you mess with the bully,
you get the horn.
Stop it. This trial is no joke.
Jessica's going against
Muhammad Ali.
She better be able
to beat Joe Frazier.
Louis is no Joe Frazier.
Okay. I get it.
You want me to help
Louis think outside the box.
Exactly. Now, how would
you come after me?
- Well, first of all...
- Don't tell me, tell Louis.
Because you and I
are not discussing
this trial during this trial.
Oh, and you were right.
I know. About what?
Tanner. It was awesome.
Guess you're not going
to let me win.
Have I ever?
Would I know?
Doubtful.
Have you ever? I am right now.
Rule number 27:
Never beat the person
you're trying to close.
I always hated rule number 27.
You couldn't close me
five years ago.
What makes you think
you've got a shot tonight?
Didn't.
Not couldn't.
And five years ago,
it wasn't your legal services
I was interested in.
How does Jessica feel
about an employee
who resigned coming back
to consult?
She's on board.
Do you mean
I have to convince her?
See that?
That's why I want you.
You could've told me
all this on the phone.
Well, I wanted
to see you first.
Make sure things weren't...
awkward.
You know, because...
"I didn't call you back
five years ago"?
Oops.
You think you didn't call me
back five years ago?
Oh, I know I didn't call you
back five years ago.
Well, I hope
your jury consulting
is better than your memory.
I guess we'll have to agree
to disagree.
Because you know I'm right.
Because I'm a bigger person.
Which is why I'm gonna come in.
But I want to know,
why'd you call me
instead of Ted Phillips?
Why do you think?
They had the document.
They kept it to themselves,
and then they destroyed it.
These are the facts of the case,
and they are undisputed.
Aren't you supposed
to be over there?
You know, I'm just working on
something for work. Yeah.
And just quoting A Few Good Men.
- For work.
- I know.
Look, I, um...
I have to ask you.
Do you think that
it's at all possible
that he actually did it?
- No, I don't.
- How do you know?
Because I know Harvey.
I mean, how could you think
he could do it?
Because I don't know Harvey.
All I know is that he thinks
he's above the rules,
and he will do
whatever it takes to win.
Yeah, but that doesn't mean...
you don't think
he has integrity.
Ah. Sorry, I have to go.
Oh, Mike.
What happens to you
if Harvey loses?
I don't know.
But right now, it's not my job
to worry about him losing.
Ladies and gentlemen
of the jury,
guilty is not gray.
You either are or you aren't.
And Harvey Specter is guilty
of concealing that document.
It's a good opening.
It's not good enough.
Says his lap dog.
Says the guy who knows
how to beat him.
I'm listening.
How?
Don't play the odds.
Play the man.
Do you know
how Harvey beat Tanner?
No.
He threatened to commit
perjury to win.
Of course, it's classic Harvey.
He was bluffing.
But Tanner didn't know that,
and Harvey used against him.
What's your point?
My point is you said
classic Harvey
before you even knew
he was bluffing
because you don't think
Harvey has any integrity.
Nobody thinks
Harvey has integrity.
So then use that
against him.
Easier said than done. Thanks.
Yeah. No, you're right.
Maybe it would just be easier
to bug his office
with a dictaphone.
Then use that to get ahead.
I did not use it
for that reason.
Yes, you did, because you are
a devious son of a bitch.
- How dare you...
- Shut up. You know it.
I know it. Everybody knows it.
I did what I did for
the integrity of the firm.
Then why didn't you take it
to the managing partner
of the firm?
Daniel had a right to know.
And Jessica had a right
to tell him,
but you told him.
You sought out Hardman
because if he comes out on top,
you want him to owe you.
He was there when I heard it.
He asked, I told him.
Oh, so he asked
if Harvey had a secret?
- No, he didn't.
- So then you volunteered it.
Which is as good
as seeking it out.
Devious. You weren't there.
You don't know.
You're twisting what happened.
Which is exactly
what you need to do to Harvey.
How long have you been waiting?
How long were
you gonna ignore my calls?
Last I checked,
you haven't called.
I've left you ten voicemails
in the last week.
Huh, that's so weird.
I seem to remember
your assistant
leaving me ten voice mails.
You know I don't know
how to dial out.
Is it eight? Is it nine?
Do you know
how to use your cell phone?
Because if I were
your assistant,
I would have totally programmed
my phone number into it.
Oh, wait.
I did.
When I was your assistant.
Okay, look. I'm an asshole.
Did you come here to
tell me things I already know?
No, I came here to see
how you're doing.
You came to get me
to do the trial run.
Donna, it's important.
Yeah, important for me
to get up there and say
I screwed up
trying to protect you?
You did screw up.
Yes. To protect you.
Which I never asked you to do.
No, you just expected me
to do it.
Like I expected
you to fight for me.
- I did.
- Really?
Like you fought for Mike?
Because that fight,
you somehow managed to win.
Oh, and when you thought
he needed to be fired,
you respected him enough
to do it yourself.
Jessica insisted that
she be the one to let you go.
And since when have you ever
done anything Jessica wanted
if it wasn't
what you wanted too?
Donna, I need you there.
I need you to tell them
that I didn't do this.
I'm sorry, I can't.
I've hired an attorney.
If this thing goes to trial,
I'm gonna be taking the fifth.
So if you need another Donna
at the firm,
just have anybody say,
"I decline to answer,"
because that's all you're
gonna get out of me anyway.
- Donna.
- I decline to answer.
Really? Really?
You don't get
my kind of track record
just by moneyballing people.
She's the me
of jury consulting.
Don't sell me short, Harvey.
I'm trying to close a deal here.
What kind
of jury would you pick?
I already did. You need men.
That's a mistake.
Women love me.
Really?
Because I showed them
your photo,
and they described you
as arrogant,
conceited, cocky...
Oh, and arrogant again.
What about handsome?
Did I not mention arrogant?
It's not bragging if it's true.
- Yes, it is.
Zoe, I'm still not convinced
I should hire you
instead of Ted Phillips.
After all, Harvey never tried
to sleep with Ted Phillips.
Who says I never tried to
sleep with Ted Phillips?
I can do what Ted can't.
Hardman came back.
You're in his chair.
He doesn't like that.
You told her?
I didn't have to.
The partners
don't know what to think.
We don't just need to convince
a jury I'm innocent.
We need to convince
them I'm innocent.
Because if they don't
trust Harvey...
They don't trust me.
And if they don't trust you,
and it ever comes to a vote,
he'll win.
She's worked here.
She knows the other partners.
She can read them.
And I also know Hardman.
I never liked him.
I won't tell Hardman
what I tell you.
Welcome back, Zoe.
Please state your name.
Harvey Specter.
Your full name.
Harvey Reginald Specter.
Do you consider yourself
a liar, Mr. Specter?
Of course not.
Didn't you recently confess
that as an associate
you hid an important file
belonging to a...
ooh, what was his name?
Oh, yeah, a Louis Litt.
That was a prank.
It was a one-time thing.
So you didn't do
anything wrong?
I don't think so.
And when asked,
did you claim that
you knew nothing about it? Yes.
Did you ever do anything
to remedy the situation?
- No.
- Why not?
What was done was done.
"What was done was done."
And like you said,
it was a one-time thing, right?
- Yes.
- Ah. Was it?
Because I think
maybe this is a pattern.
Information was hidden,
you claim
you knew nothing about it,
you did nothing to rectify
the situation,
and years later, you maintain
you've done nothing wrong.
Your Honor, he's testifying.
Sounds exactly the same
as why we're here today.
Except there's
one big difference.
- Your Honor...
- This time...
A man was killed.
No further questions,
Your Honor.
What's done is done, right?
The plaintiff calls
Ms. Donna Paulsen.
Ms. Paulsen, did Harvey Specter
order you to shred
this document?
I decline to answer pursuant
to my fifth amendment rights.
So you don't want
to take this opportunity
to state
your employer's innocence?
- Objection.
- You can't object.
- Jessica will.
- Could you just...
Sorry. Yeah.
Ms. Paulsen, do you consider
yourself good at your job?
I do.
Have you ever stated
to one Rachel Zane
that you are indeed the best
legal secretary in the city?
Mike, you can't.
Donna, I can.
Yes.
Ms. Paulsen,
there was a personal date stamp
from five years ago
on the document
that you're accused
of shredding.
Was it yours?
I decline to answer.
Did it look
like your date stamp?
I decline to answer.
Okay. Then let me ask you this.
Would you believe
that the best legal secretary
in the city
didn't know about a document,
even though it had what appeared
to be her date stamp on it?
I decline to answer.
And would you believe that
that same secretary
would have destroyed
that document
without explicit orders
from her boss?
This is gonna be bad, isn't it?
Donna's gonna be great.
Just follow the script.
Well, Rachel's not Donna.
She's not guilty,
and she can't be rattled.
You see how I rattled Harvey?
The jury listens to words,
but they respond to fear.
And we don't have that...
Yet.
- What's this?
- Subpoena.
You want to depose me?
Okay, let's stop playing
tiptoe through the tulips
around the elephant
in the room.
That's not a thing.
You know some things
about Harvey,
and I need to know them too.
You yourself said
go after the man.
What better way to go after the
man than to question the boy?
But I don't know anything
about this case.
That's an evasive answer, Mike.
You're hiding something,
and I smell fear.
I have to go to the restroom.
Wait a minute. How bad is it?
Is it uncomfortable?
Well, now it is.
Good.
What. Whoa, whoa.
Is that a polygraph?
- Yes.
- Nope.
You are under oath.
And I'll tell the truth.
You bet your ass you will,
or I'll know.
We'll start with an easy one.
What's your name?
Mike Ross.
Where do you work?
Pearson Hardman.
What do you do for a living?
I practice law.
And where did you attend
law school?
What? What's the matter?
Nothing.
- You're lying.
- No, I'm not.
I beg to differ.
Listen to me.
I know why the machine
says you're lying.
You're nervous.
You don't want
to rat out Harvey.
I get that.
But it's time you accept
the situation.
This is happening,
and you're going to have
to tell me some things
about Harvey.
I accept that.
Then answer
the goddamn question.
I'm proud to say that I have
a diploma from Harvard law.
Now it's time that you accept
the situation.
I'm not afraid of you.
I wasn't there,
and I don't know anything
that's gonna help this case.
Do you want fear?
I'll get you Donna.
The answer's no.
I didn't even ask a question
yet.
- Yeah, well you were going to.
- Yeah.
And you were gonna say no, but
instead you're gonna say yes.
Oh. That's funny 'cause I
already said no to Harvey.
And you, my dear, are not...
Are not Harvey.
No, I'm the guy who told you
not to destroy that document,
and you're the girl
who promised me she wouldn't.
- You know that I...
- Broke your promise.
Well, then I guess I just suck.
Because I'm breaking another one
right now.
I told my attorney
that I wouldn't talk to anybody
at the firm
until after this was over.
- You hired an attorney?
- Yeah.
I'd rather not go to jail.
I don't do roommates, and I
definitely don't do orange.
Nobody's going to jail, Donna.
You can't guarantee that.
You dragged me
into Harvey's office once,
and you scold me about how much
he loves his job.
Well, if you don't help him
prep for Tanner,
he's gonna lose in court,
he is gonna get disbarred,
and he is never gonna be able
to do what he loves ever again.
- That is not fair.
- No, what's not fair
is Harvey taking the blame
for your mistake.
You know what, do whatever
your attorney wants.
Come in. Don't come in.
Go to the movies.
Take pilates.
I don't give a shit.
Because whatever you do,
you're gonna regret it
for the rest of your life.
Complainant would like to call.
Ms. Jessica Pearson
to the stand.
Sidebar?
This is just an attempt
to make Harvey's attorney
look bad in front of the jury.
What, you think Tanner's
gonna make you look good?
You're a named defendant.
He has a right to call you.
Louis, will you excuse us
for a moment?
You think I don't see
what you're trying to do?
You want him to undermine me
in front of the partners.
I'm acting
in an unbiased manner.
It sure took you
a while to jump in
when Harvey was up here.
Oh, wait, you never jumped in.
Jessica, you chose
to try this case.
You could have been up here.
Instead, you're down there.
Either take a knee
or take that stand.
Would you say it's important
to win at Pearson Hardman?
You don't get to be one
of the top law firms
in New York by losing.
What about Mr. Specter?
How's his track record?
Exceptional.
He almost always wins.
Almost always.
Is that why he's the youngest
senior partner in firm history?
It's a factor.
And how much
did the firm benefit
with the Coastal Motors win?
I'd say the profits
were somewhere
in the mid 8 figures.
And if Mr. Specter had lost
those 8 figures,
would he have still made
senior partner so young?
- No.
- Mm.
- No, he wouldn't have.
- How much did Mr. Specter
personally gain
as senior partner?
Oh, it's too soon to say.
He hasn't received
his first bonus yet.
- Ballpark.
- No.
Are you that ashamed
of how much you pay him?
No.
Well, then answer the question.
- Millions.
- And a junior partner makes?
Much less.
So win,
and you're rewarded millions.
Win less, and no matter
how much hard work, dedication,
or administrative dominance
is displayed, you get nothing.
Quite the incentive
to do whatever it takes
to "almost always" win.
I have to say, delicious
dinner, fantastic wine...
almost enough to make up
for the mediocre company.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
You're not mediocre.
See, that's funny, because
you were talking about me.
There it is, the Specter smile.
What can I say?
It came with the name.
And you're never fully dressed
without a smile.
Being fully dressed
is overrated.
It is when you look like me.
Mrs. Robinson, are you trying
to seduce me?
Did you just call me
Mrs. Robinson?
Okay, first of all, I'm younger
than Anne Bancroft.
Anne Bancroft was hot.
Which brings me
to second of all.
I'm hotter than Anne Bancroft.
I'm hotter than Dustin Hoffman.
Not inTootsie.
Are you afraid you're gonna lose
this thing?
No.
You should be.
Why, because Louis
had one good direct?
You walk through life like men
want to be you
and women want to sleep
with you.
I don't always walk.
Sometimes I drive fast.
And it's exactly
that kind of response
that make the partners think
you're an ass.
Being an ass doesn't make me
guilty of fraud.
If they're right
about who you are,
what would make them think
they'd be wrong
about what you do?
Well, why don't you tell me?
You're the expert
on warm and fuzzies.
You want to know how I know I
wasn't the one to call you back?
Because I know why I wasn't
the one to call you back.
Let me guess...
you didn't like me.
No, I did.
But in all the time I knew you,
you never once showed me
any vulnerability.
I told you
how I felt about you.
But you never showed me.
So I had no way of knowing
it's the truth.
And you could be telling
the truth now,
but if you don't show
the partners some emotion,
they're not gonna believe you
either.
What do you want me to do?
Manufacture a few tears?
Harvey,
when you're a defendant,
you need the jury
to protect you.
There's no way
they're ever gonna protect you
if they don't care about you.
The plaintiff
would like to call.
Ms. Donna Paulsen to the stand.
You got her to come in?
Just stick to the script.
Harvey won't know what hit him.
Ms. Paulsen,
did Harvey Specter order you
to shred that document?
I decline to answer pursuant
to my fifth amendment rights.
Did you put your date stamp
on that document?
- I decline to answer.
- Um...
I'm not gonna ask questions
that you're just gonna plead
the fifth to, so...
Had Harvey Specter asked you
to bury something
five years ago, would you?
He wouldn't ask me to do that.
That's not what I asked.
If he did, would you do it?
Oh, see, you're pausing, which
means you're hiding something.
No, I'm not.
See, I think
you'd do anything for him,
and I know why.
Is there a question?
Do you love Harvey Specter?
What?
Do you love him?
That has nothing to do with...
It has everything to do with.
Why did your last boyfriend
break up with you?
Ms. Paulsen, why did he
end it with you?
He thought that I prioritized
my work over our relationship.
Your work?
He asked you to choose
between him and Harvey,
didn't he?
- Yes.
- Who did you choose?
- Harvey.
- Because you love him?
Louis, stop.
It is not that simple.
Do you love him, yes or no?
Answer the question. Louis.
You're with him all the time.
Your work revolves around him.
Your life revolves around him.
Objection, badgering.
You don't have a boyfriend,
but the one you did
wouldn't share you with him.
- Your Honor!
- Please, I just need a...
Do you love Harvey Specter?
That's enough!
Donna.
You crossed the line.
Do not do this to me right now.
You humiliated Donna.
You kept pushing and pushing her
for what, for fun?
What, you think I enjoyed that?
That made me sick.
You could have stopped.
You think Tanner
would have stopped?
Travis Tanner does not give
a shit about Donna Paulsen.
- You are not Travis Tanner.
- I don't...
- You did not have to do that.
- I did my job.
You really want to beat me
that badly, huh?
You think
this is about beating you?
This whole thing
is about saving you.
Everyone is trying to help you
because you screwed up.
This is all your fault.
And what just happened
to that beautiful woman
in there...
that's on you...
not me.
Are you kidding me?
Go home. Shoo!
Go the hell home.
Look, I didn't know
he was gonna do that.
And if you had known,
would you have done one thing
differently?
I am so sorry.
Bullshit. Bullshit.
- Okay. Donna, I'm not...
- Harvey.
I know.
But you know what, sweetheart,
maybe you are.
And I do not mean that
as a compliment.
Look, I did what I did
for the same reason
you did what you did,
to help Harvey, that's all.
Well, that worked out the same
for you as it did for me,
because,
in case you hadn't noticed,
in addition to screwing me,
you completely shafted Harvey.
We had a script.
Wait, you trusted Louis?
You trusted Louis?
Yeah, I thought
he would stick to it.
Yes. Well, he didn't.
And you should have known that,
because that is just who he is.
I am sorry. But I'm...
People are who they are.
Thank you. Okay.
I can fix this!
What's all this?
It wouldn't concern you.
Why is that?
Because you want to settle
even if it means
Harvey getting disbarred.
If he loses in court,
he'll get disbarred anyway.
My concern is for the firm.
It's not a personal attack
against Harvey.
This whole thing is a personal
attack against Harvey.
And you're gonna do something
about it?
Tanner's cases, transcripts,
appeals, decisions.
I know he did something illegal,
because that's who he is,
and I'm gonna find it,
because that's who I am.
What are you planning on doing
with it?
Leveraging that
for a settlement?
I'm not against settling.
I'm against Harvey
getting disbarred.
You really admire him.
- I do.
- Loyalty.
You can't buy that.
No. You can't.
What are you doing?
We worked together
all night once.
Let's do it again.
I hope this time turns out
better than the last time.
Now we have them
right where we want them.
Either you're better
than I thought you were,
or you have absolutely no idea
what you're doing.
Trust me, the partners
are starting to believe Harvey.
Why?
Because he protected Donna.
He was also protecting himself.
Yes. But they didn't see that.
They saw a man who cared
about someone else.
His softer side.
And we need to give them more.
He won't want to.
And we both know Harvey
won't do
what he doesn't want to do.
Everybody knows that.
So what do we do?
Permission to treat
the witness as hostile.
Permission granted.
He's hostile.
The day we met,
you were working
in the mail room
of this law firm.
I don't recall that day.
Well, let me refresh
your memory.
An associate
had missed a filing,
so he backdated the postage.
You came to me,
and you said if the firm
did not declare misconduct,
you would report us to the D.A.
I don't like fraud.
It's no secret.
But what you did want
to keep secret
was the fact that you told me.
Why?
I didn't want
to get in trouble.
No, you did it
because if we'd won,
an old woman
would have lost her pension.
And if anyone found out
that he was the one
that told me,
then they'd know that you cared.
Whatever you say.
You pretend like you
don't care, but you do.
You care about the people
you work with,
you care about the people
you work for,
and you care about every one
of your clients.
But you refuse
to let people know.
Is there a question?
I just want to know why.
No answer?
Are you embarrassed?
Nope.
- Afraid?
- No.
Then why?
- Just let it go.
- You are under oath.
Then hold me in contempt.
For God sakes, what the hell
happened to you?
What kind of damage
was done to you?
Caring only makes you...
Weak.
They think you care,
they'll walk all over you.
You weren't weak the day
you walked into my office.
You were a man who believed
that to win fairly
was more important than to win.
And you still are.
And I've never seen anyone
walk all over you.
Is there a question here,
Your Honor?
No, there isn't.
- That whole thing your idea?
- I didn't know that story.
I asked you a question.
Don't give me that coy bullshit.
Excuse me?
You said you wanted to see
through me, you did.
The least you can do is give me
an honest answer.
Yes, it was my idea.
Harvey, your partners
loved what they saw in there.
You're gonna win.
Bravo.
A tour de force.
I mean, that story?
It was so great.
But there isn't one shred
of proof it's true.
Hostile witness, my ass.
I mean, before that story,
we all believed you did it.
And I ask you, ladies
and gentlemen of the jury,
if he did commit that fraud,
how hard is it to believe
that he didn't concoct
some bullshit on the stand
to get himself off the hook?
That's my close.
We have one more witness
to call.
Mr. Litt, do you resent
Harvey Specter?
It's complicated.
No, it's simple.
Do you resent him
for being better than you?
- He's not better than me.
- I understand.
It's so much easier
to criticize someone else
than it is to acknowledge
your own shortcomings.
- Shortcomings?
- Mm.
My billables
are higher than his.
My client list
is better than his.
Yes, but I didn't ask you
about those things.
What are you asking,
Ms. Pearson?
Does the witness
resent my client?
- Yes.
- Your own ambition aside,
do you think Harvey Specter
deserves to be senior partner?
Yes or no?
Yes.
Do you think
he's an excellent attorney?
- Yes.
- And, as much as you hate him,
do you think he committed
this fraud?
No.
Defense rests.
Refusing to admit defeat
even after defeat.
You really are like Harvey.
I'm not so sure
that's a good thing.
Well, who would you rather be?
Someone who believes
it's more important
to win fairly than to win.
Like I said, Harvey.
Yeah. Not in this case.
You both cheated.
Excuse me?
Louie's testimony pushed it
over the top.
But that jury,
they didn't see Louis Litt
believing Harvey's innocence...
they saw Travis Tanner.
And that is never gonna happen
in court.
You do realize that you are
chastising the managing partner.
With all due respect,
it's not gonna matter what you
are if Harvey gets disbarred.
We'll find a way to win.
You should be finding a way
to settle.
There isn't
an acceptable offer.
Yet.
Not just a pretty face.
I hope you brought
a baseball bat.
You want to go another round
with me, you're gonna need it.
It doesn't matter what I have,
you're just gonna sucker punch
me again anyway.
Boohoo.
You baited me.
You wanted to catch me
on that tape, and you know it.
That's not what I'm talking
about, and you know it.
You want to settle?
Let me save you some time.
We pass.
You can pass, you can sign it,
or you could stick it
up your ass,
but this is the best
you're getting.
- This gets me off the hook.
- Nice try.
You think I don't know
this was your doing?
Harvey, next time have the balls
to do it yourself
instead of sending
your errand boy.
Errand boy?
You got what you wanted,
so stop playing dumb.
Daniel Hardman doesn't work you.
You work him.
- What the hell did you do?
- This is a good deal.
A good deal that costs every
partner at this firm $100,000.
Including me.
We share the profits;
We share the losses.
There won't be a loss
when I win this at trial.
The only reason
you weren't willing to settle
was Harvey's disbarment.
That's gone.
And I want to know
how you made it go away.
- I found dirt on Tanner.
- What dirt?
You blackmailed him
into a settlement.
I leveraged a deal
that's good for the firm.
I said, "what dirt?"
Not your concern.
It's my concern.
I don't want what you did
biting me in the ass.
You were already bitten.
And the last time I crossed the
line and you found out about it,
it bit me in the ass.
You cleared Harvey's name
inside the firm.
We both know
that's what you wanted.
Time to move on.
Let's let the partners
put this to a vote.
Hardman got Tanner to settle.
Are you kidding?
It worked?
So it was your idea
to use dirt to get a deal.
No, it was my idea to use
Tanner against Tanner.
Box.
Me.
You're welcome.
I didn't thank you.
It's okay. You don't have to.
And I'm not going to,
'cause we're not
taking the deal.
Because you don't trust Daniel.
This isn't just about me.
Every partner is...
everybody is paying now.
Do you have any idea why Donna
showed up to testify?
Because I convinced her to.
What?
Yeah, I made her do
what I needed
instead of what she wanted.
I did what you do.
And look where that's gotten us,
you, me,
Jessica, Louis, everybody.
Take the deal, Harvey.
What did Hardman find
in those files?
I don't know, and I don't care,
because he just got every single
one of us off the hook.
He can't be trusted,
and you should know that by now.
No, what I know is that if you
take this thing to trial,
it's gonna cost us all a hell
of a lot more than money.
And if you don't know that
by now, after all this,
then I don't think I should be
the one learning from you.
This is your decision.
So, by a show of hands,
those in favor of settling?
Thank you.
Now all those in favor
of going to trial.
Split vote.
And it appears
we have a holdout.
I vote we settle.
Let the record show
we have settled.
Thank you for your time.
In light of recent events,
there is one other issue
I'd like to raise.
This lawsuit has caused
some of you to question.
Jessica's judgment and,
by extension, her leadership.
Allowing this kind of dissention
to fester hurts the entire firm.
Therefore, I am calling
a partners' meeting,
at which point we will vote:
Either Jessica will retain her
position as managing partner,
or I will resume control
of Pearson Hardman.