- Okay.
- Bye.
The least you can do
is be honest with Jenny.
- That's what this is all about.
- Yeah.
You always liked her.
You kept flirting with me
long after you started dating her.
Yeah, well,
that's going to stop.
And while you're at it,
no more running to me
for favors or asking me for help.
How about you find yourself
some other paralegal?
Because as far
as I'm concerned, we're done.
You haven't even gone
to any law school.
- I'm working there.
- Oh, yeah. What, as a lawyer?
It's a long story, okay?
But you can't tell anyone, ever.
This guy is not your friend.
He is an anchor.
He is my oldest friend.
You were there.
What would you do?
I'd tell them everything.
Watch Cameron go down.
Sleep like a baby
after I did it.
Harvey would never use it, and he'd kill
me if he knew I had it.
But can you use this?
To help him?
Clifford Danner.
He was 18.
I put him in jail
12 years ago.
He's innocent.
Cameron buried the evidence.
- Do you have enough to overturn?
- I don't know.
- So, what are you going to do?
- I'm going to get him out.
Go. Go.
9224-4930-754229.
No. That's not right.
Right. I gave it
to you backwards.
I have to keep it
interesting for myself.
Security code.
You know I know it.
Why are you wasting our time?
Because I want to
make you work for it.
Oh, really? Well, maybe I don't
feel like working for it.
- Okay. All right. I'll just...
- 8767. Stop.
No, no.
What are you doing?
Showering.
Oh, you don't trust me
being here without you.
No. I...
I trust you. I just... You know, I like
everything just so.
What?
Okay. "Just so"
doesn't mean clean. It means just so.
Got you.
- Have a good day.
- Bye.
Trevor. Jesus.
Surprise.
- Can I come in?
- No.
You... Well, I'm late. So, we should,
you know, grab a coffee on the way.
Well, let me just
take a piss first.
No, don't.
Trevor, stop.
Stop.
You've got a girl
in there, don't you?
Let's go.
I'm just going
to take a peek.
Trevor, stop it.
No, no. Stop.
Stop. It's not even funny.
Get your hand off the knob.
We're going.
I'll buy you breakfast.
You're so serious.
- He loves you!
- Go.
I got a job. Law firm mail room,
of all places.
Oh.
I was wondering, think I could stay with
you for a couple of days?
Uh...
I don't really know
if that's such a good idea.
You know, I could
have died that day.
If it hadn't been for
you and your boss.
And I don't want to
live that life anymore. I really don't.
I don't have anybody else.
- Okay.
- And I was thinking, you know,
maybe I'll try
and call Jenny.
Yeah. Yeah. You should.
What are you doing
here, Prosecutor?
I believe you're innocent.
You just find out you've only got
six months to live?
Because today isn't the day you get your
conscience cleared.
That's not the
reason that I'm...
You know, I've been
in here a dozen years.
While Jason Black and Matt Bailey are
out there living it up.
You think I give a shit
what you believe?
- You want to hit me?
- I want to kill you.
But I lay a finger on you and they put
me in the hole for 48 hours,
extend my sentence.
I got four years left.
I ain't doing another minute than that.
Good.
Because I'm not here
for your absolution.
I'm here for your redemption.
This is the letter
I told you Jill wrote me.
I know.
The one you didn't
believe existed.
I believe it now. You were involved with
her. This is the proof.
Involved with her?
I loved her.
And she loved me.
Then why did you keep this
relationship a secret?
Look at me, man.
They gave me a scholarship
to that school,
but nobody wanted me dating anybody
at that school.
I had a record.
If her father ever found out,
I would have been done.
They wouldn't have cared.
Like you didn't care.
Where did this come from?
It was buried,
but it got found.
And this is why
you believe I'm innocent.
Yes.
And this is enough
to get me out?
No. But that wasn't
the only thing they buried.
Jill's dress had
your DNA on it.
But there was another piece of clothing
that had blood on it.
A camisole.
And they buried that
because that DNA wasn't hers
and it wasn't yours.
Let me guess.
It was Jason Black's.
Unfortunately, I don't have
access to his DNA.
So, you finally going to go after him
and Matt Bailey?
I'm not a prosecutor
anymore.
Then what the hell
are you here for?
I want you to let me
represent you.
You think I'm going to trust you after
what you did to me?
I don't see anyone else lining up to get
your ass out of here.
See the money, wanna stay
for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
What's that?
It's an article where Clifford Danner
took his plea.
- Do you want me to read it to you?
- No.
"Clifford Danner had
a history of violence.
"This poor girl was brutally murdered at
a high-end private school.
"And quote, 'This doesn't sound like the
work of the squash team captain to me."'
I don't know, Harvey.
This article makes a pretty compelling
case that he's guilty.
Well, he's not.
- It's quoting you.
- I was wrong.
Jessica, I don't think you should let
Harvey take this case.
Louis. We're talking
about a man's life.
And if Harvey thinks the kid didn't do
it, then so do I.
I understand that. But what Harvey
thinks and what Harvey can prove
are two different things.
In my experience with Harvey,
it's one and the same.
Listen to me.
He was set up.
Jill Hodgkins went to him
and said that she was gonna turn in
these two other guys for selling coke.
They killed her
and planted the coke
in Clifford's room.
I didn't buy his story
because his DNA was on her.
He claimed that it was because they were
having this secret relationship,
but he had no proof.
And now, he does.
Okay. I hate to disagree
with you here,
but I took a little poll
of the partners...
Whoa. You did what?
I was discreet.
I assure you.
And they feel, as I do, that Harvey's
actions will hurt this firm.
This firm?
You mean my firm.
And when you're running the firm of
Litt, Nothing, and Nobody,
then you can make
whatever call you'd like.
Until then, you can
just get back to work.
I'm telling you
those guys did it.
And as far
as his violent history is concerned,
you of all people
are gonna tell me
that a person can't change
if they get a second chance?
What do you
need me to do?
Hey.
I need your help.
I thought I made it clear that I don't
expect to hear those words
from your mouth ever again.
- It's important.
- It's always important.
- It's for Harvey.
- It's always for Harvey.
He specifically
asked for you.
By name?
He said
he wanted the best.
Well, if he didn't
specifically name me
and you didn't
specifically tell him,
then I am going
to specifically decline.
Rachel.
Are you kidding me?
Okay. I know that
you're mad at me,
but we are talking about a guy
roughly our age
who spent over a decade in prison for a
murder that he didn't commit,
and we are trying
to get him out.
Don't you think that's more important
than our little... Whatever?
- "Whatever"?
- You know what I mean.
Problems of two people,
hill of beans.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Casablanca.
- Oh, I've never seen that movie.
- You...
No, it's old.
Old. Oh, my God.
Okay. What's your basis
for getting him out?
- Prosecutorial misconduct?
- Buried evidence.
Okay. Then, you need
precedents to overturn.
- I already got those.
- Then what?
I need to find out everything I can
about the former DA's cases.
Okay.
- Gone With the Wind?
- No.
- Citizen Kane?
- Dirty Dancing?
- "Nobody puts Baby in the corner."
- I can't believe you.
- I'm helping you.
Come on, let's go.
You thought to do
this on your own?
I decided
to think like you.
This is a high-profile
murder case
against the new
District Attorney himself.
- You know that, right?
- I know.
And you think I'm going to let you come
with me for this, don't you?
I know you are.
You know, I don't want you thinking
like me anymore.
- Now, you know how the rest of us feel.
- A-ha! Right there.
- I always would have said that.
- No, you wouldn't.
Yes, I would.
Harvey Specter.
Terrance Wolf.
That your case?
I thought it best
to cut a deal.
Let him out
for time served.
High-profile murder
at a prep school.
No, I don't think
I'll be cutting any deals.
Miguel Ruiz, Lawrence Baker,
Ray Jenkins, Calvin Reynolds.
And who are
these gentlemen?
They're other cases with improprieties
that we'll be forced to cite
if we have to file
to reopen.
You of all people
don't want that.
Really? Why not?
Because it will
make you look bad.
Didn't happen on my watch.
You're supposed to be
cleaning up the office.
I find sunshine
is the best disinfectant.
Your mother teach you that?
No, Harvey,
life taught me that.
This man is innocent.
Then he should
have gone to trial.
Evidence was buried.
Then dig it up
and make your case.
Mike. Give me a minute.
Terrance, you're forcing me to do
something that I'd rather not do.
- And what is that?
- Take this case on.
I win. It's what I do.
It will send a message
around your entire office
that you can't
handle your business.
Well, if I lose, I lose.
That's the way the law works.
But, Harvey, don't think
I can't send a message or two myself.
Rumor has it, you're the traitor who
sold out his former boss.
Wasn't me.
Those rumors are wrong.
So, mysterious evidence
from back in the day
of your old boss
just appeared.
You didn't know.
Maybe it wasn't you.
But it had to be somebody.
Right, Harvey?
Have a nice day.
My office. Now.
I have never thought
about firing you.
You took something when we quit
the DA's office?
Come clean right now
or I'll let you go.
Not give it
a minute's thought.
I knew it.
You were in trouble.
You had no right.
I don't care.
What did you do with it?
She did what she had to do.
She gave it to me.
And the two of you saw fit
to fight my battles for me?
We did what you would have done
for either one of us.
So, get off your high horse.
Leave the woman alone.
We work because I've always known
that I can trust you.
Don't ever go behind
my back again.
You're welcome.
Wait.
He called you?
Yeah.
He left a message.
What did he say?
That he wanted
to see me.
And what did you do?
I texted him and I told him
I wasn't interested.
We've got to tell him.
- No, we don't.
- Yeah, we do.
I am already
living a lie at work.
I can't live one
at home, too.
Do you think that
if you tell Trevor about us,
he's going to keep
your secret to himself?
I know Trevor. If I tell him, he will
take it up with me.
- If he hears it from someone else...
- Who's gonna tell him?
I don't know. Okay? I just... I know
that he's over there right now
and it's drilling
a hole in my brain.
- Then stay here.
- I can't.
- Why not?
- Because he came to me for help.
Okay.
- Okay, what?
- Tell him.
But please wait until he has his life
back together.
What do you mean?
He came to you for help.
How much help do you think hearing about
us is going to be for him?
- Okay.
- Okay, what?
Okay, I'll stay.
Could you just
not touch anything?
Because
I like my place just so.
What?
This place is a mess.
What are you...
The court finds sufficient misconduct
to warrant a new trial.
Any pretrial motions
at this time?
Yes, Your Honor.
The State advises that we will be
seeking the maximum sentence
of life in prison.
What?
Your Honor, my client
has four years left.
Mr. Specter, the state has every right
to seek that penalty.
Would you like to
confer with your client
before I vacate
his conviction?
Or you could just withdraw
your motion right now.
I'll confer with
my client, Your Honor.
Get the message?
Four more years.
Or you get out now.
Or stay in
the rest of my life.
September 19th, 2007.
What?
His halfway point.
I realized
I could make it.
You never said
this could happen.
He is sending a message.
It's got nothing
to do with you.
It's got everything
to do with me.
What do you wanna do?
What do you think?
If we win, I want in.
- If we lose, I don't.
- We'll win.
- How do you know?
- Because I know.
The same way
you knew I was guilty?
What do you think?
I think Harvey
wins his cases.
What would you do?
I'd trust him.
Harvey, can you
give us a minute?
Clifford,
I don't know you
and you don't know me.
But I'm going to tell you a story about
what that man did for me
and why I think
you should trust him.
Court is now in session.
Mr. Specter.
You going to withdraw
your motion?
Your Honor, my client wishes
to proceed to trial.
Gensync Chemical.
They dropped us today.
Louis' client?
Louis' Fortune 500 client.
You want to guess why?
His ears?
They freak a lot of people out.
That was one client.
His teeth?
The fidgeting?
- It could be anything.
- Okay, stop it.
Let me guess. One of the board members
has a kid who went to this school.
A daughter.
And Louis correctly
pointed out
that they might not
be the only clients
that will punish us
for taking this case.
- Which costs us money.
- Mmm.
Louis is in the
majority this time.
Which hurts your position
with the partners.
You telling me
to drop this?
I'm telling you to win.
But that's not why I called you in here.
Have a seat.
- Donna.
- Mmm-hmm.
You need to get over it.
I'm trying.
It's not that easy.
Yes, it is.
- Tell me.
- Okay.
Think about what your life
would be like without her.
Now, I know.
Know what?
How you always
forgive me.
Oh, it's nowhere near
as easy to forgive you.
Think about it.
Oh, I do.
Every goddamn day.
- Hey.
We're starting
trial today.
I know.
You've got five minutes.
I've never started a trial
without doing our thing.
Well, you don't have time.
There's plenty of time.
You don't have time.
I'm sorry.
- For what?
- Don't push it.
Okay, let's go.
We've got three minutes.
- Okay. Here or in my office?
- Here's good.
Okay. On three.
One, two...
Wait, let's go
in your office.
- I'll get the can opener.
- Yeah.
You left that
in the kitchen.
Thanks. I hate it
when I do that.
You don't have any numbers
in your speed dial.
I don't need them.
And yet,
you forgot your phone.
- It's not the same thing.
- Okay.
Hey, Rachel.
Thank you. For before.
Sure. I mean,
it was for Harvey.
Yes. Yeah.
Hey.
Today's your first trial.
What? I've been
to trial before.
Yeah, but not when
you've been with me.
Fair enough.
Okay, I want to start
a ritual with you.
What do you want to do?
We're on the phone.
Remember that gymnastics video
we saw?
Yeah. I can
get behind that.
Feeling good?
Never better. You?
Oh, I'm ready to roll.
Don't think I didn't
see that can opener.
What do you think you're doing,
re-opening this case?
Making sure an innocent man doesn't
suffer for the crimes of others.
What about Jill? Don't you care
how she suffered?
You two would know more about that
than anyone, right?
Excuse me?
I bought the devastated friend act
12 years ago.
But I know better now.
Mike, meet Jason Black
and Matt Bailey.
Just don't
shake their hands.
They've got Jill Hodgkins'
blood all over them.
Look, I don't know what you think you
know, but when I'm done testifying,
the jury's going to know
that Clifford killed Jill.
Just because you switched sides doesn't
mean the rest of the world did.
- We just lost the letter.
- What?
I didn't realize he'd have
the nerve to lie on the stand.
It's not exactly a giant leap from
killing someone.
Perjury and murder,
they aren't the same thing.
Yeah. Murder's worse.
It's easier.
Nobody's watching.
Let's go.
Mr. Black, what exactly did Jill tell
you regarding the defendant?
She told me
she felt trapped.
I thought she was
talking about school.
But now, I know
what she meant.
That letter was dated a week before
she was killed.
She must have
broken up with him
and this is how
he paid her back.
Mr. Black, you said you didn't see Jill
Hodgkins at all
on the day of the murder.
Is that correct?
Correct.
So, there'd be no reason for your blood
to be on any of her clothing at all.
No, there'd be no reason.
Would you be willing
to have a DNA test, Mr. Black?
Objection, Your Honor.
Prejudicial.
We'll pay for it,
if that's a problem.
Mr. Specter.
It's about the DNA
and they can't spin that.
Detective Packel.
The dress wasn't the only article of
clothing that you submitted, was it?
No. There was a camisole.
Was it in your report?
Yeah. If you
bothered to read it.
I did read it, Detective.
And what was the DNA analysis
on that camisole?
- I never picked it up.
- Why is that?
Well, it wasn't ready
until two days later.
And we already had enough
from the dress.
Enough?
A man's life is at stake.
Enough for what?
Enough for you to put him away without
bringing it up for 12 years.
Well, I did pick up that test, along
with the camisole.
Your Honor, I'd like
to request a sidebar.
On what grounds?
The camisole and any evidence connected
to it are inadmissible.
- This is bullshit.
- Easy.
- What?
- Your Honor,
in between picking up the camisole
at the precinct
and dropping it off
at the lab,
you can see here
the document is flawed.
Therefore,
the chain of possession
with respect
to the camisole was broken.
You have to be kidding me.
It's inadmissible.
First six.
What?
The first six months
are the hardest.
In your mind.
I don't know if
I can do that again.
Mr. Specter.
You are accusing a police officer of
tampering with evidence.
Yes, I am.
When the results of the DNA test came
back, they didn't line up.
And Detective Packel changed
the custody documents.
Even if Mr. Specter's
assertions were true,
it would automatically
taint the evidence, anyway.
He's got a point.
That camisole was what allowed us to
reopen this case in the first place.
That camisole was proof
that evidence was buried.
That's why the
case was reopened.
An entirely separate issue
from whether that evidence
can be used in this trial.
Clifford,
I don't know what's
going on in there,
but no matter
what they rule,
he's not going
to lose this one.
You sure?
Yeah. I am.
Your Honor.
That's enough.
I'm instructing the jury
to disregard all testimony
relating to either the camisole or
the resulting DNA test.
Oh, my goodness. I'm so sorry.
Are you okay?
Get out of my face.
What the hell are you doing,
reopening this?
You worried about getting caught
intentionally tainting evidence?
I didn't taint anything.
What I did was
help you put away a guilty man
for brutally killing
a young girl.
And I'm not going to let you drag my
reputation through the gutter.
Not without consequences.
Are you threatening me?
Because the truth is,
you wouldn't even be here
if you hadn't done
something wrong.
Me. Yeah.
It's all well and good for you to drag
up shit from the past, huh?
You're protected
by your shiny suit, right?
What are you talking about?
Lawyers never go
after their own.
What is that Denzel movie?
Tell it to me
like I'm a five-year-old.
Sometimes, the good guys
got to do bad things
to make the bad guys pay.
It's time to start painting
outside the lines.
How?
If Muhammad won't come
to the mountain,
we need to bring the
mountain to Muhammad.
Really?
The mountain to Muhammad?
- It's a thing.
- Yeah. I know.
It just has no meaning to me
in this situation.
You said you could think like me.
Figure it out.
- Okay. Yeah. I got it.
- What is it?
- You tell me. I'll confirm.
- Nice try.
Damn it.
Why did you
text me, Matty?
We've got nothing
to talk about.
I didn't text you.
You texted me.
- We've got to go.
- Yes.
Come on.
Does it really matter who texted who?
Why not take advantage
of the fact you get to see each other?
Catch up.
Talk about old times.
Yeah, like that time
that you murdered that girl
and framed
an innocent man.
We didn't do anything.
- You're wasting your time.
- Am I?
We know the truth.
It's just a matter of time until one of
you turns on the other one.
The question is,
who's it going to be?
We were there today. You're the ones
running out of time.
Asshole.
Looks like the rattlesnakes are starting
to commit suicide.
Holy shit. That's from
Mississippi Burning.
This whole idea is from
You know that movie? I was trying to
stump you with that one.
Front to back.
Give me a break.
The problem is those two don't seem like
they're going to break.
They know we don't have anything.
Only now, we do.
So, by the mountain
to Muhammad, you meant...
DNA coming to Mr. Wolf.
That's good.
- Hi, Donna.
- Hi, Louis.
- You're never...
- I know.
- Why?
- I need a favor.
You mean Harvey
needs a favor.
Oh, that's very
astute of you.
A big one.
You know your cousin
in the DNA lab?
- We need something today.
- No.
- It's for...
- I know what it's for.
What do you want?
- I don't want anything.
- I will fill in for Norma.
Okay.
I'm not being vindictive.
I'm sorry. Do I have
the right office?
Listen to me. I want you,
God damn it.
And I would throw that secretary
right out the window
if I knew you were going to be
my secretary.
But I have a reputation
that I value,
and I'm not going to be putting
my reputation on the line
for something that
I do not believe in...
American Ballet Theatre?
No.
Followed by a one-on-one dinner
with Baryshnikov.
Oh, mommy.
No, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
No, no. Mmm-mmm.
- Nope. I'm sorry.
- Okay.
- Can't do it.
- Got it.
- Okay?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Do you understand why?
- It's very clear to me.
Do you know?
Because...
- Do you understand why I said no?
- I hear you, Louis.
- Louis... Shh.
- I want to. But I can't.
- What?
- Let go.
Jessica would like to see you
in her office.
Oh, that phony bitch.
Call your cousin.
- It is not that simple.
- Yes, it is.
You've compromised your principles
before. Do it now.
Like I told Donna,
this isn't for me.
This is for Harvey.
Wrong. It's for me.
Okay. You know,
you want this so bad,
why don't you maybe
compromise your principles a little bit?
- Excuse me?
- Yeah.
You know my billables. You talk about it
all the time.
"Louis, you've got
big billables."
You've seen my loyalty.
Yet, you refuse
to acknowledge my value.
- Where is this going?
When you said Litt,
Nothing, and Nobody,
you know what
that said to me?
That said, "Louis, you're never going to
make senior partner."
Well, Harvey's running out of time.
This is my leverage.
I wanna make senior partner and I wanna
make senior partner now.
Louis, I do not
respond to threats.
I make them.
So, if you ever want to be senior
partner, you call your cousin.
Now.
All right.
I don't need to see the results.
I saw their faces.
They did it.
What happened
to the letter?
They made it seem
like it didn't matter.
Like, he was jealous.
And so, he killed her.
- Well, I...
- What?
I'm just wondering,
what would have happened
if they hadn't kept their
relationship a secret.
I have to make
a phone call.
Okay.
Jenny, hey. It's me.
I can't keep this a secret
from Trevor anymore.
I need to tell him.
Call me.
DNA results. Jason Black
and Matt Bailey.
They match samples of the DNA taken
from that camisole.
They did it.
- Where did you get that?
- I found it.
That doesn't
prove anything.
- It's their blood on her.
- So, what?
They could have had
a gym class together
or played flag football or any one of
a hundred other reasons.
Jason Black said
he didn't see her that day.
It's two specks of blood
from what could easily be
- any other day.
- What's wrong with you?
Me? You come in here with
some unauthorized DNA test
and right away,
you expect me
to just release a convicted felon into
the streets.
He didn't do it.
And how can you allow him to sit in
there
while these two other murderers go free?
Let me explain
something to you.
My job is to prosecute.
Your job is to defend.
I didn't bury any evidence.
I didn't toss that DNA.
The judge did that,
based on fact.
You're coming
after me for the sins of someone else.
This piece of paper here
means nothing.
So, unless one of those two boys
just up and volunteer
that they killed that girl,
your client is going to go back to
prison for the rest of his life.
Terrance,
you have a reputation as a fair man.
I don't give a damn what
other people think of me.
I care about what
I think of me.
- It didn't work.
- What's next?
What's next is we have to
put on a defense tomorrow.
We got nothing.
So, what are we
going to do?
I don't know.
Ooh, Rachel.
What are you
doing in here?
You have access
to the Partners' kitchen.
Yeah. I like to keep
my finger on the pulse.
Plus, they don't
have Cheetos.
Actually, I don't care
about the pulse.
Hmm.
Okay. Either I am losing it or you are
upset about something.
So, what are you
upset about?
- I don't want to talk about it.
- Got it.
Mike Ross.
How do you know that?
I'm Donna. I know.
Donna, what am
I going to do?
There's only
one thing to do.
Quit.
- Kill her?
- Well...
You need a drink.
Yes.
Two?
We should barf.
Take them off.
Huh?
He's not an animal.
I want to talk to him
like a man.
What happened?
Wolf won't drop
the charges.
What?
I tried everything.
You tried.
Look, we can cut a deal.
We can ask for more time.
- He already said no way.
- We have got to...
Try?
Try like you did
with the DNA?
I had four years.
Four years of 16 that I only had in the
first place because of you.
- Clifford, we...
- Shut up.
Why don't you
take it out on me?
What did you say?
- I said take it out on me.
- Harvey.
I put you in there.
I let you rot.
I didn't give it a minute's thought
for over a decade.
- Don't push me.
- Why not?
I deserve it. It's my fault.
You said it yourself.
Harvey.
They'll put me back in the hole.
That's why not.
- Harvey, come on.
- And increase your sentence?
- It's going to happen, anyway.
- Guard.
Come on.
You know, Jason Black...
- I said don't push me.
...and Matt Bailey,
- they killed Jill.
- Guard, get in here!
And they are out there
laughing their asses off...
- Knock it off!
- You know what?
No, come here!
Get off of him!
You tried?
- Let's go.
- You said you would
- get me out of here!
- Let's go.
You said
you'd get me out!
What just happened?
I just bought us 48 hours.
Now, what?
I'm going to beat the shit out of one
of those guys
and get him to rat
on the other one.
- Which one?
- The weaker one.
- Which one is that?
- The one who didn't testify.
You're serious.
You can't do that.
Who's going to stop me?
Harvey, it wouldn't
be admissible.
You'll never get
them that way.
- But it will get Clifford out.
- How?
Wolf won't be able to deny
that he's innocent anymore.
Harvey, you don't do this.
You can't beat people.
- That's not what you do.
- It is today.
Harvey, stop.
Listen, I've got
another idea.
- What?
- You'll like it.
It's from Mississippi Burning.
Come on.
So, all of these
things are from clients?
Yeah, pretty much.
This pen.
Remember that big Trump scandal you
heard about last year?
- No.
- Exactly.
Oh! Don't touch that.
Signed by Patrick Ewing.
He'll know. I'll never hear
the end of it.
All right. This one?
- Bird.
- He's from Boston.
- White man's hero.
- Hmm.
Yeah, it's Kobe.
He won't care.
You really know him.
I really do.
- No.
- Never?
No.
Ever?
- Never ever?
- No.
Why not?
Because you can
never go back.
I got to pee.
Hey, man.
I got your message.
What did you
want to talk about?
It can wait.
Do you remember when you said you would
have died that day
- if it hadn't been for Harvey?
- Yeah.
Well,
he needs your help.
Wake up, Matt.
Shh!
Who are you?
What do you want?
It's not who I am.
It's who I represent.
Jason Black.
He knows you talked
to the police.
No, I didn't. I swear.
Yeah, that's not
my department.
Now, Matt, you're going
to retract what you said,
you're going to leave town,
and you're never going
to talk to them again.
Or next time,
that's going to
be your head.
Somebody call the police?
You. You... What are you
doing here?
Hey, Matt.
Relax. The detective was across
the street the whole time.
We knew Jason
would send somebody.
What?
Who do you think told Jason you went to
the police in the first place?
I did.
Harvey showed me the results
of the DNA test.
Two splotches.
Jason Black's and yours.
Okay. Um... Uh...
I want to file a report.
Oh.
Sure. I'll take
you downtown.
You look through the books.
Maybe you find something.
Maybe you don't.
But your real problem
isn't that guy.
It's Jason Black.
Somebody was going
to turn him in once before.
And I think you know
the lengths he'll go to
to shut somebody up.
No, I don't.
We were here this time.
We won't be here next time.
Next time. What would have happened if
he would have killed me this time?
Well, you'd be dead and we'd have
caught the guy
and used him to put
Jason away for murder.
- Shit, we should have done that.
- Yeah.
Harvey, behave.
What do you want?
What do you want from me?
Confess to the crime.
Turn in Jason Black.
No. I can't do that.
Yes, you can.
I'll tell you why.
You were 16.
A juvenile.
That's three years maximum.
Less if you're the one
who comes forward.
We'll get you a deal.
You can't make that promise.
You're not the DA.
You'd rather
negotiate with Jason?
Because he'll kill you
and you know it.
It was his idea. I didn't want to do it.
I didn't want to do it.
Okay. Get dressed.
You're coming with me. Go.
Hey, by the way,
how did you get that bruise?
Sometimes, the good guys
got to do bad things
- to make the bad guys pay.
- To make the bad guys pay.
That's right.
- What?
- "What?"
You should have
let me do the talking.
Wouldn't work.
You're not ready, yet.
Not ready?
This whole thing was my idea.
You lost in housing court.
You think you could
handle a murderer?
Mississippi Burning.
You're welcome.
I let you say
the juvenile thing.
That was pretty badass,
wasn't it?
Really?
I thought I nailed it.
Shower girl.
Hey, Mike. It's Rachel.
I know I shouldn't
be doing this,
and I know
you're seeing Jenny
but I can't stop
thinking about the kiss.
And I can't go back.
Looks like one of them
up and confessed.
We'll get your client out. I'll back
your motion to expunge his record.
I'll facilitate his release.
You don't seem very happy.
You think I don't know you set those
boys up and coerced that whole thing?
Set him up?
How would I do that?
I don't know. What difference
does that make?
- I know you did it.
- You know?
The same way you knew
Clifford was guilty?
No. You don't
get to tell me
it's one way in court
and another out here.
You can't prove it,
you don't know anything.
Well, you broke the law. Tell yourself
whatever you want.
I'll tell myself
I got an innocent man out
and I put two
guilty ones in.
Then, I'll close my eyes
and I'll sleep like a baby.
One other thing.
You've got a little something
right over here.
I like you.
By the way, how did you
make those guys
think that they were
texting each other?
I bought a prepaid phone.
Set it to private. I texted each one
it was the other.
- Who else would it be?
- You.
Yeah, but they're not
going to think that.
That's cool. You'd make
a good criminal.
Yeah. Better than you.
Uh, excuse me.
I was an amazing criminal.
You don't remember?
Briefcase popping open?
Drugs spilling everywhere?
Okay. That was
a mechanical failure,
and that could have
happened to anybody.
Weed was all
over the floor.
Oh, shit! I forgot my phone again. Here,
can I borrow yours?
How do you have this memory and keep
forgetting your phone?
It's not the same thing.
Trevor, it's Mike.
I need you to call me back.
Remember that thing
that I said could wait?
It can't anymore.
There's something
I've got to tell you.
Ms. Pearson. I'm Trevor Evans.
I'm a friend of Mike Ross.
Yes?
I wish I didn't
have to do this.
There's something you need to
know about him.
Something Harvey Specter
hasn't told you.
What is it?