I want to, uh...
taupe.
- Is that...?
- Justice Thomas.
I knew it.
What can I do for you, Louis?
Ah, to the point. Of course.
I wanted t...
I wanted to congratulate you
on bringing in Pfister Insurance
and let you know
I've taken the liberty
of putting together
the initial paperwork.
Excellent. Leave it there.
I wanted to follow it through.
I would relish
the opportunity to...
Nonsense.
Louis, it's beneath you.
Oh, I think you'll find
nothing's beneath me.
Are you offering
something untoward to me?
I'm simply saying that
I'm not oblivious to the fact
that there's change afoot,
firm dynamic-wise.
We used to be... huh.
Now, we're kinda... hmm.
We might need a little... hmm.
You know? Louis.
I'd like things to operate with
a certain integrity around here.
Oh, I admire that philosophy.
I actually try
to live by it myself.
Good.
Now, can you do me a favor?
Anything.
Send Mike Ross to me.
Ross?
You want to work with Ross?
He's actually
working for me right now
on the Liquid Water litigation,
and he's been on it for weeks,
and I wish I could do it,
but I cannot.
I can't do it right now.
Then forget I said anything.
But I can give you Dickinson.
Okay.
Let me know how that works out.
With Ross.
Okay.
Um, I am taking Mike exclusively
for the next two weeks.
Excuse me?
I'm calling in my chip.
Our wager? The Price sisters?
My triumph?
Does that ring a bell?
Can't have him.
Oh, well,
then I guess you'd rather
that I announce
to the entire office
that the mighty Harvey Specter
is a welcher.
I didn't welch.
You passed on him.
Okay, please.
I'm begging you. I need him.
Okay, tell you what, Louis.
Just say out loud that I am
the best closer in New York,
and you can have him. Fine.
To Donna.
- No.
- Then we don't have a deal.
Welcher.
That was fun. Morning.
If that's a big check,
I want another Marni bag.
Hands off the vinyl, junior.
10:00, nice of you to join us.
I was closing Cranston
this morning.
Oh, yeah? Couldn't get it done
by 9:00, huh?
You're a little lippy
for a Monday.
- What the hell?
- What? What is it?
"Draft of complaint
from Smith and Devane,
threatening to reopen
Randall v. CM,"
a case I won 4 years ago.
Randall v. CM?
Ah, accident
on the Merritt Parkway.
They claimed it was
Coastal Motors' hood,
you killed it in court
by saying it was the driver.
This can't be surprising
to you anymore.
They're saying
there's new evidence.
New evidence?
It's product liability.
The statute of limitations
is expired.
Which means it's a shakedown.
You gotta quash that shit.
I do, and I will.
Whoa.
Come on. The Spinners? Really?
For your information,
the Spinners were
one of the defining pop bands
of their time.
Oh. Oh, wow, sorry.
Yeah, that's cool, like, uh,
like, the Jonas Brothers
or Hanson or 'NSYNC
or Selena Gomez, yeah.
Come here, lippy.
I want to show you something.
Yeah?
What, you got Bieber fever?
Prepare motions to dismiss
by end of day Thursday,
and don't puss out
when Judge Edelstein
tries to stifle my brilliance.
- He's all yours.
- What?
Why the sudden change of mind?
Does it matter?
You're punishing him,
aren't you?
- Yes.
- So you're saying
working for me is punishment?
As far as I'm concerned,
this whole conversation's
punishment.
Oh, here we go.
- Duration?
- One case.
- Jurisdiction?
- Exclusive.
- What can I do to him?
- What do you want to do to him?
Harvey.
Things.
That is not
a legitimate answer.
Honor the boundaries
of labor law?
I prefer the Geneva Convention.
- Then we have a deal.
- We...
I think I need a sick day.
Careful there, Harv.
That's high-end
Brazilian cherry
from the South American
rainforest.
Tanner.
You selling furniture now?
No, but if we both did,
I'd sell more than you.
I thought I told you
to stay out of my city.
Can't. I'm the newest senior
partner at Smith and Devane.
Don't get too comfortable.
If all you're bringing
is the Boston shakedown,
you're not gonna be here long.
Oh, I'm bringing
more than that, Harvey.
Randall versus CM is a winner.
That case was litigated.
- Not by me.
- Well, let me
bring you up to speed.
Frank Randall had a history
of substance abuse.
His family tried to blame
Coastal Motors,
but his death had nothing to do
with the carmaker or its design.
Yeah, well,
we've got new evidence
that contradicts
that assertion.
Oh, look at that,
you learned some new words.
Even if it were true, the
statute of limitations ran out.
Well, what you call
a shakedown,
I call a sure thing.
This is an internal memo.
Showing that CM
knew about engineering defects.
You're on the wrong side
of this one, Harvey.
I never saw this thing
in my life.
Sure looks like you did,
and that statute of limitations
doesn't apply
to fraudulent concealment.
I didn't conceal jack shit.
Harvey, that's for your client.
We want $46 million
and not a penny less,
and this, well, that's for you
because we're suing you
and your entire firm for fraud.
You really
want to come after me again?
I'm not moving down here
for the Sushi.
0 and 2 doesn't look good
on a resume.
You know, I'm thinking
Upper East Side.
Well, why don't you check out
the corner of
81st and kiss-my-ass?
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right
♪ all that time imagine this ♪
♪ The greenback boogie
This looks bad, Harvey.
I don't care how it looks,
it's bullshit.
Then tell me what's bullshit
because I'm looking at
a document that undermines
your entire defense.
An anonymous memo with names
and dates blacked out.
It's damning, and it
implicates you in a cover-up.
Never crossed my desk.
I'm not saying it did.
I'm saying it looks bad.
I don't want Daniel
knowing about this.
I got nothing to hide.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I believe you, but you're not
my only concern at the moment.
You know full well
what Daniel will do
if he finds out
you're being accused of fraud
and it happened on my watch.
He'll use it against us,
but I also know
that he's familiar
with the people at CM,
and he's bound to find out
sooner or later.
Then make it go away
before it gets to sooner.
Durham Foods v. Liquid Water.
I need motions to dismiss,
compel,
strike, and change venue.
Why are they not finished yet?
Okay, Louis,
I might be a quick study,
but I'm gonna need a tad
more information than that.
Have you heard of Liquid Water?
Yeah, sure. Liquid Water.
"We put the I.Q. in liquid."
You see?
You already know the client.
- What did they do?
- They didn't do anything.
They're being accused
of coming up with
a deceptive slogan.
- By Durham Foods.
- Exactly.
They have their own line
of bottled water, which,
by the way,
tastes like a stagnant pond.
So how do we
defend against their claim?
Who said anything about "we,"
white man?
My defense is puffery.
Oh, you're gonna
stick out your chest?
No, Mike, "puffery" is...
A big, bold, empty statement
not meant to be taken as fact,
therefore
not subject to deceptive
advertising litigation.
Touche.
See? It's a solid case.
I agree.
No one would actually believe
that drinking Liquid Water
would raise your I.Q.
I mean, who would be
that stupid?
I mean, other than people
who actually drink...
Liquid Water.
You know what? Whatever.
Just don't mention that
last part in the deposition,
okay? Yeah, okay.
Wait, Louis?
Um, if we're claiming puffery,
why do I need to waste
all my time with these motions?
All right, let me
explain something to you.
We're at war,
and in times of war,
a private does not question
his commanding officer.
If I ask you to wipe out
a village, you say, "how high?"
- That...
- Which brings me
to my next point.
You report to me and me only.
You don't talk about
our business with anyone else.
You're in by 7:00,
you're out no sooner than 10:00,
and here's the most important
thing, no sex of any kind.
Weakens legs,
clouds your judgment. Got it?
- I'm not sure I do.
- Good.
Okay.
No sex.
No sex. Got it.
Oh, my God.
Well?
- Oh, my God.
- Donna,
I need to know
if you ever saw this.
Yes, Harvey,
I saw the smoking gun
in a multimillion-dollar
liability claim,
and I hid it from you.
I also know where Amelia
Earhart's living, and I have
the missing 18 minutes
from the Watergate tapes.
All right, take it easy.
I don't like
having my competence questioned.
Yeah, and I don't like
being sued for fraud.
That document
never came into this office,
or you would have seen it.
Donna, two dozen people
worked on this case,
and any one of them could have
seen it and missed it.
I need to know
that didn't happen,
or I need to know who to fire.
Give me an order.
Go through every file
in the original case
and make sure
that document isn't in them,
and do it
without anyone knowing.
Done.
Okay, ha ha, joke's on me.
Aren't you Louie's boy?
Yes, I get it.
No more fondling the vinyl.
Or besmirching
the good name of the Spinners.
Yes, I totally deserve
to be handed over
to the poor man's Lex Luthor
for that.
Please, Harvey,
you have to get me back.
- Have to?
- Will you?
He thinks we're going to war.
He give you the
"burn down the village" speech?
Yes. What is it with him?
It's like the pony thing
all over again.
He's, like, the captain
of mixed metaphors.
Look, I can't
take you back now.
I have to honor my bet,
especially since
my honor's in question.
Okay, why are you strangely
emphasizing the word "honor?"
This letter of complaint.
I'm being accused of fraud
by Travis Tanner.
Isn't that like the pot
accusing the kettle of... fraud?
I'm going to the airport
to talk to CM right now.
I'm want to reassure
Lawrence Kemp
that we're all over this.
Please, Harvey, come on.
Take me with you.
I can do this.
I can work for both of you.
It's too risky.
I'm solo on this.
Besides, I've got
a relationship with Kemp.
I should talk to him alone.
Not a word to Louis.
Understand?
Yeah. Hey, he said
that I can't have sex
while I'm working with him.
Is that really his call?
Well, he is
your commanding officer.
You looking for Civil Torts,
Volume Three?
People put that in criminal law.
I hate that.
Yeah, I know. Me too.
Oh, I knew we had something
in common.
You need my help?
Ah no, I've actually
got it right... there.
I'm sorry.
I was just trying to help you.
Harold, you're the associate,
and I'm the paralegal.
It's my job to help you,
not the other way around.
I don't see us that way.
Okay, um, you want to help me?
My... my stapler is broken.
Could you get me a new one?
I'll get you three.
Harold.
Thank you.
Good to see you, Lawrence.
Harvey, good to see you.
Sorry this had to be
on the fly.
It's not a problem.
I want to start
by giving you my word
that we crushed this suit once,
we're gonna to crush it again.
I should hope so.
I was hoping to have
this discussion privately.
Well, this is our new
general counsel, Matt Lasker.
He insisted on being
part of the discussion.
Forgive me,
I'm just getting up to speed.
- Then you should know that...
- Out of curiosity,
why did you receive
a draft of the complaint
before we did, Mr. Specter?
Travis Tanner gave me
an advanced copy.
Must like you.
We have a special relationship.
- Which I've looked into.
- Harvey,
he really seems to have
a bone to pick with you.
That's not gonna be a problem.
May be for us.
Tanner came to see you,
didn't he?
- At our request.
- Lawrence, I'm telling you,
we can handle this.
We just need to stick together.
Look, if I'm going to defend us
against this suit...
"If" being the operative word.
A-am I being fired?
Ww... we're keeping you
on retainer
while we evaluate our options.
Don't you see, Tanner's trying
to put a wedge between us?
What Lawrence is reluctant
to tell you is,
your relationship with this man
has put us
directly in his crosshairs.
There is a wedge between us.
Maybe Lawrence's reluctance
stems from the fact
that I also have
a relationship with him.
Harvey, I have
a corporate responsibility here.
Well, while you're evaluating
your options,
why don't you think about
who was there for your company
four years ago and what happened
to your stock price after I won.
Oh, you got paid
very well for that.
As were you.
You had a huge bonus that year,
and I don't actually
recall it ever going back down.
There's no need
to get personal.
You... our asses
are on the line,
and you're trying
to cut me loose... it's personal.
- Harvey...
- Save the "it's not you,"
"it's me" speech, okay?
Be a man and make a clean break.
- Fine.
- No.
You're fired.
He's on record.
Remember I told you it was
to work with me and Louis
at the same time?
Yes.
We have to take that risk.
I need you to go through
every file in this case.
You mean you want me to find
what you missed?
I didn't miss anything.
I need you to go through
those files
and tell me what's not in there.
Shit, I gotta go.
What happened?
Well, I got good news
and bad news.
- What's the bad news?
- I got us fired.
What's the good news?
Anything we find
from here on out
is no longer covered
by attorney client privilege.
Did you find
what you're not looking for?
No, did you find
Nope. Oh, my God,
it is so stuffy in here.
What are the symptoms
of carbon dioxide poisoning?
Uh, headaches, dizziness,
mental confusion,
mental confusion.
Kevin, trusts and estates?
No, it's too meek.
It's gotta be a woman.
Who is it?
- Harold. I need a stapler.
- I was right.
Okay, there are files
everywhere.
He's gonna be suspicious.
What do we do?
Don't worry, I got it.
I got th... what are you-?
Come here.
Ow! Oh, come on, you pussy.
- Ow. Okay, what are you...?
- Shh.
What's going on?
Come in.
Hi, Harold, honey.
Is this why it says,
"Do not enter?"
We're kind of busy in here.
Do you mind if, um...
You know,
you just don't bother us
anymore?
Sure. No problem.
Yeah, he didn't notice
the files.
Oh, sh..., I'm late for
Louie's settlement conference.
Uh, and... thanks.
You're welcome.
And then I take the shuttle
to Grand Central,
and then I take the local
from there.
I think you'll find that...
pleasurable, actually.
Sorry, restroom.
No, that's okay.
This is my associate, Mike Ross.
He was busy, uh, drafting
some pertinent documents.
Motion to dismiss,
motion to compel,
motion to strike,
motion to change venue,
and we have another half dozen
in the pipeline.
- No, they're here.
- Oh.
What is this?
This was supposed to be
a settlement conference.
Oh, we're not here to settle.
We're proceeding to trial.
You want to take this case
to trial?
Um, unless I can't hear
the sound of my own voice,
I believe that's
what I just frickin' said.
We're the little guy.
Your parent company's
a behemoth.
A jury's gonna hate you.
Well, thanks to your
disgusting smears in the media,
that might be true,
which is why we're also filing
a countersuit for libel,
slander, and anything else
that might be appropriate
in this case.
Tortious interference?
This is... you got... this is not
good faith, Mr. Litt.
Sir, you have besmirched
the good name of Liquid Water,
and if you think that we're here
for a settlement conference,
well, let me just correct
that one for you right now.
We are not settling.
We will not be settling.
In fact, the only thing
that's settling here
is the sediment at the bottom
of your putrid water. Get me?
Now be sure to take
that Grand Central shuttle
like I told you, okay?
I think you're gonna love it.
- Uh, that was...
- Amazing? I know.
- I'm sorry, Louis, that I, uh...
- Questioned my orders? I know.
I thought it was
just busy work.
Well, it wasn't. For every
hour you spent drafting them,
they're gonna spend ten hours
figuring out
how to argue it back in court.
You're gonna bury them
in paperwork.
Look at you.
You catch on quick.
What happens next?
They squirm for a day or two,
reevaluate,
and come back to us
on our terms.
Like... tomorrow, maybe?
Tomo...
Mike. Sweet,
impressionable, young Mike.
You see,
unlike what Harvey believes,
going to trial is a good thing,
especially when the other side
can't afford it.
Durham Foods,
their financials are soft,
but it's gonna take a trial
to put 'em down,
so you better
lace up your bootstraps
'cause this battle
could take months.
Uh, where you going?
Uh, I just have to go back...
to, uh, the bathroom.
You just went.
Are you keeping track?
I may start.
I don't mean to intrude,
but Donna's not at her desk.
Do you have a minute?
I overstepped last week.
I want to make up for it.
It's not necessary, Daniel.
Pfister Insurance. I thought
maybe we could handle them
together.
I'm gonna to have
to take a rain check.
It's a peace offering, Harvey.
Take it.
You know, I'm sorry,
but my plate's just
a little full at the moment.
Do you mind if I ask with what?
Uh, the usual.
I have six situations,
all in need
of immediate attention.
Which begs the question,
why not add one more?
I'll see if I can free up
some time next week, okay?
Um... I think
I didn't find something.
Let me not have it then.
During the two years
before our car was manufactured,
there was this mid-level
quality control manager
named Sarah Layton,
who wrote several reports
on other CM car models
but never on ours.
So she's not relevant
to our case.
It would appear that way,
but after May 5th, 2006,
she never wrote
another report ever again.
That's kind of a coincidence,
isn't it?
That on the exact date that
our car went into production,
she disappeared
from CM's records?
She could've just been fired.
Never filed for unemployment.
- Could've quit.
- No exit interview.
Permanent unpaid leave.
Gets out of any records.
And nothing to tie her
to our car.
She wrote that memo.
- Very smart.
- Thank you.
I meant them, not you.
But I found it.
That makes me even smarter.
Don't be cocky.
It's unbecoming.
On you. I can pull it off.
You better be nice to me
because I know where she lives.
Where who lives?
My high school sweetheart.
We connected on Facebook.
Oh. Bullshit,
you're not that sentimental.
- Yes, I am.
- She was his first.
Deposition tomorrow. Be ready.
- First?
- I had to sell it.
Give me the address
and tell Donna to hurry up.
I'm naked to the world
down here.
Harvey, there is one problem.
If this woman was involved
in the original cover-up,
she's not gonna want
to talk to a lawyer
who isn't on her side anymore.
Well, I better think of
something on my way down there.
I went to the file room
to get you the good stapler,
but there was a bit of a snafu.
- In the file room?
- I don't want to get into it.
In the meantime, I brought you
my own personal stapler,
a two-hole punch, three-hole
punch, old-school wite-out,
and enough highlighters
to last you till kingdom come.
Look, Harold, I-I know
that you don't see us
as paralegal and associate,
but I think it's best
from now on
that I just help you.
Because the truth...
the truth is,
you are far too valuable
to be wasting your time on this.
I am?
You're right. Yeah.
And besides, you probably
don't want all this stuff,
anyway. Well, there's that.
Except for the stapler,
of course.
You got it. Of course.
Thank you.
Sarah Layton?
You recognize me.
I do.
Then you know who I work for.
Coastal Motors.
I'm not gonna deny that.
What do you want?
We have a problem.
I need you to tell me everyone
you've ever shown this to.
I never showed it to anyone.
Ms. Layton,
I don't care that you wrote it.
You made a deal
to keep your mouth shut,
and I believe you kept it.
All I care about
is who else read it.
I don't know
who else read it...
'Cause I didn't write it.
- Ms. Layton...
- I brought my concerns
to Mr. Kemp.
He told me not to put anything
in writing, and I never did.
Good.
I need you to swear to me
that you never told anyone
other than Lawrence Kemp
about the flaws in his hood.
You listen to me.
He promised he'd fix
the problems on the line
if I kept quiet. He did,
but he never went back and fixed
the ones we already made,
and that man died.
I have been living with that
ever since.
Now get off my property,
and leave me the hell alone.
Furniture salesman
to limo driver.
You're stepping up
in the world.
Well, it's nice to know
you still have a sense of humor,
Harvey, considering you just
learned you defended a murderer.
I should've known
you'd have me followed.
Follow you?
I've been waiting for you.
I told you,
you're on the wrong side.
I don't defend murderers.
That's not
what that woman just told you.
You wanted me to find her.
You have the document.
No proof of fraud.
Can't admit it without fraud.
Now that you know
Kemp lied on the stand...
I'm obligated to come forward
and tell the court. Otherwise...
Even if you weren't
guilty of fraud then,
you'll be guilty of fraud now.
Of course,
when you do come forward,
it's going to be awfully hard
for people to believe
you didn't know about it
at the time.
You know I didn't know.
I don't know
anything of the kind.
What I do know is,
you're in a bind.
I wouldn't wait too long now.
I'd hate to have to report you
to the bar.
Lawrence goddamn Kemp.
Harvey, I need this suit
quashed, and I need it done now,
so channel your anger
and find a way out.
I mean, I knew I had an enemy
in Tanner, but...
Did you ever think that
the person you should be mad at
is yourself? Excuse me?
Law 101.
Don't ask your client
if he committed murder,
but sure as hell find out
if there's a smoking gun.
Jessica, I'm sorry,
I wasn't born yesterday,
but he swore to me there was
nothing wrong with that car,
and I believed him.
Well, he lied to you.
It's not the first time,
and it won't be the last,
but now Tanner knows it.
I guess
it's time to tell Daniel.
What? Now? No.
I just had the chance
to tell him, and I didn't.
- Why not?
- Because you told me not to.
The one time you listen to me.
No, no, no, no.
You can't lay into me
every time I go against you
and then flip it around now.
We're not telling.
I'm gonna fix it.
Well, the one way to fix it
is to negotiate a settlement.
Oh, wait, we can't
because you got us fired.
I did, which means
there's nothing stopping us
from strong-arming them.
I gotta go.
Just admit it.
Your research suggests
that consumers believe
your water tastes like shit.
Do I have to answer that?
What exactly
are you getting at, Mr. Litt?
What I'm getting at is,
Mr. Kessler is aware of the fact
that his company's product
can't compete with ours
'cause it tastes like shit,
and they resorted
to filing a bogus lawsuit
against us in a desperate
attempt to hide that fact.
No, you don't
have to answer that.
Hey, Mike...
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
Kevin, right?
How long have you
worked at Durham Foods?
22 years.
I started right out of college.
That's dedication.
I admire that.
What's your current title?
Vice president
of Market Research.
It says here, three years ago,
you applied
for senior vice president,
but they gave the job
to an Alan Stansby instead,
a man who had been at the
company far shorter than you.
Correct.
Well, how'd that make you feel?
Yes or no questions.
My client's not here
to discuss feelings.
Okay, truthfully,
you were hoping to be
further up the corporate ladder
by now, weren't you?
Maybe.
Thank you, Mike.
And once again,
recently you applied
for a senior VP position
and were turned down.
Is that correct?
- Yes.
- You do know that
management is going outside the
company to fill the job, right?
Objection. Lack of foundation.
You know what?
I am so sorry. That was...
that's off the record.
That's just because of
a headhunter friend of mine...
That's not... no,
we object to that too.
I'm warning you, Mr. Litt.
I'm sorry. Statement withdrawn.
You know, you can tow
the party line, Kevin...
but I know exactly
what it's like to bust your ass
every day at a company
and be overlooked for
a promotion time and time again.
It just...
hurts.
Just physically hurts.
Right here.
Give 110% every day,
and for what?
So they can just...
chip away at your dignity?
You can be the, uh,
loyal soldier today,
be the cannon fodder
for your bosses,
or you can turn the guns on 'em
right now,
and you can just
tell me the truth.
We're done here.
- It's true.
- Kevin.
- Our product sucks.
- No, objection.
You can't object
to your own witness.
We're suing 'cause
we're losing market share.
- Kevin.
- There's nothing wrong
with your ad campaign,
and that's the truth.
Thank you, Kevin.
Uh, Louis, that was awesome.
That was pretty spectacular,
wasn't it?
His testimony
is gonna be amazing.
I got him to admit
some damning things, didn't I?
You know, we should subpoena
the outside company
that put together
the focus groups.
- Yes.
- We should get
all their records... Like it.
And the names and addresses
of the people who took part.
They're protected
in civil actions
under the privacy statute
of '74.
No, that was overturned
by Kressler v. Symtech.
Not if they'd been compensated,
as is this case right here.
We're gonna win this thing.
"If I can't win, I won't run."
- What?
- "If I can't win,
I won't ru..."
that's Chariots of Fire.
Come on. Do you... don't tell me
you don't know that film.
You know,
like what you and Harvey do,
the... the movie quotes.
I forgot. It's... yeah.
Well, it's been a long time
since I saw it,
you know. It's a great,
great flick though.
Yeah.
Anyway, all right. So, um,
make sure the subpoenas
are on my desk in the morning.
Oh, Mike, uh,
make it the afternoon
'cause you've earned it.
Good night, Tommy.
Lawrence, what a coincidence,
me running into you
in your own building.
I certainly
wasn't waiting for you.
Harvey.
Ah, it's better this way.
Your new lawyer
won't hear what I have to say
and be put in a position
to commit fraud,
like you did to me.
I don't know what you think
you know, but it's wrong.
I know about Sarah Layton.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
But whatever you know, Harvey,
is privileged information.
Not if I found out yesterday,
and definitely not
if you conspired
for me to commit fraud.
There's no fraud.
She found a problem,
and you tried to...
And I fixed it,
and there's no record!
That's what a solid front end
feels like,
but you didn't make one,
so when Frank Randall's car
hit the divider
at 50 times the force
that you just felt,
it crumpled
and split him in half.
Then I savaged his reputation,
all because
you looked me in the eye
and told me that your hood
was rock solid.
What do you want, Harvey?
What you should have done
in the first place.
Pay these people
and make this thing go away.
If you don't,
I'm coming forward
and telling the court
what I know.
Even if I didn't want to,
I'd have to, but I want to,
and when I do, Coastal Motors
is gonna cut you loose
exactly the same way
you did to me,
so either you make it right
on your own, or I will.
Hey, I got the subpoenas.
I said the afternoon.
It's the first thing
in the morning.
War doesn't wait
for the afternoon.
Sweeter words
have never been spoken.
Gentlemen,
before you do any more work,
Durham Foods
is declaring bankruptcy.
- Yes.
- Damn.
- Damn? We win.
- No, now if there's a judgment
on the countersuit,
we're gonna be
in the back of the line
behind a dozen lenders.
Sorry. I know you've been
working on this for weeks.
Uh, yeah. Yeah, well,
what are you gonna do?
We can still get a win-win out
of this whole thing.
- How?
- Well, you said that
their other products are
worth real money, right?
So why don't we just
advise Liquid Water
to buy the whole company
and then just give up the suit?
We kill the competition
and get their other products
at a discount to market value.
- Win.
Why'd you cover for me?
What do you mean?
With Hardman out there.
You let him think
that we were working together.
In the deposition yesterday
when you were...
you know, when you were
talking about not...
I've just really enjoyed
working with you, Louis.
- You have?
- Yeah, sure.
Well, I thought Harvey
might have poisoned the well
in regards to any relationship
between the two of us.
Louis,
can I be honest with you?
- Yeah, I can keep it real.
- As far as
poisoning the well goes,
Harvey didn't really
have anything to do with it.
That's pretty much
all been you.
What are you talking about?
Among other things,
you tried to sabotage
my relationship with Jenny.
After you laughed
at that video of me.
You stuck me in housing court.
'Cause you stole a client
from me.
You tried to blackmail me
with a fake drug test.
Yeah, but it didn't work.
You defeated me. So?
So it's water under the bridge.
No, no, no.
Not water under the bridge.
Louis, you can't do that
to people and expect them
to forget about it and move on.
Don't you get that?
- They should.
- Would you?
Okay.
Mike, I will take
your thoughts...
on my behavior
under advisement.
Wait, Mike? Yeah?
Something's in the air still.
Like a pall of secrecy
or a layer of unease.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Mm, my spider parts
are tingling.
Please don't ever
say things like that.
Harvey's up to something.
I know it. What is he up to?
I don't know.
- You sure?
- Yes.
Um, Louie's parts are tingling.
I don't want to know what
that means or how you know that.
It means he knows
you're hiding something.
Well, if everything goes
like I expect,
there won't be
anything to hide.
Good, because it just
doesn't feel right lying.
You know, I actually kind of
like working with him.
He's not a bad lawyer.
I mean, you know, we have fun.
You guys thinking about
moving in together?
Jealous?
Where's your gatekeeper?
Any Tom, Dick, or Harry
can just waltz right in.
Well, I don't see
any Toms or Harrys here, but...
Okay, can we just please
cut the small talk
and you let me know
what I'm not privy to?
I don't know
what imaginary world
you're skipping through
right now, Louis,
but you're there
all by yourself.
Right.
So first you hand me Ross
on a silver platter,
then Donna's not at her desk
for days.
You think that I don't know
that there's a power struggle
going on
between Jessica and Hardman?
Harvey, look,
I admit I haven't
always been, um...
well-behaved,
but I can help you on this.
You just gotta trust me.
Louis, go away.
- That was harsh.
- You kidding me?
He came hat in hand, Harvey.
Have you met him?
This guy gets one whiff
of what we've been hiding
from Hardman,
I guarantee you it's his office
he's in, not ours.
I know, we can't trust him.
Still, you should have seen him
in this deposition.
I mean, all he wants
is to be you.
Isn't that
what everybody wants?
- I'm serious, Harvey.
- Well, I'm sorry.
That's just pathetic.
I know, but what I'm...
Harvey Specter.
Harvey, it's Lawrence Kemp.
Give 'em what they want.
- Good.
- Is that it?
You want a medal?
For what it's worth,
I never meant
to put your reputation
on the line,
and that memo
never crossed my desk.
Goodbye, Lawrence.
They're settling?
You wanted that?
Wanted it?
I goddamn orchestrated it.
CM pays what they should have
in the first place.
And the suit against us
goes away.
And Daniel Hardman's
none the wiser.
Where the hell's Donna?
She's in the file room.
Hasn't found that document yet.
There is no document.
So you believe him?
Not really. I just remember
who we're dealing with.
Harvey.
What are you doing here?
Nothing. Just delivered
CM's settlement offer to Smith.
Or Devane.
I can't remember,
I can't tell those guys apart.
It's not their case.
No, but it is their firm,
and I don't trust you.
Our offer
was take it or leave it.
Well, we took it.
And now we're done.
Hmm, well,
I'm afraid there's still
the little matter
of our fraud claim against you.
Tanner, I'm glad you did
what you did.
The Randall family
deserved that money,
but let's not pretend
you've got shit on me.
Excuse me?
You used that memo
to get what you wanted,
but it never would have held up
in court because you wrote it.
That's
a scintillating argument.
Too bad
not a word of it's true.
Well, let's take a look
at your resume.
Witness tampering,
extortion, bribery.
Forgery fits right in.
That document's
the real deal, Harv,
and as far as reputations go,
I know all about your dirty
dealings in the D.A.'s office.
Unlike your theories about me,
you were actually investigated
for the very thing you're being
accused of, burying evidence...
a point I can't wait
to bring up in court.
You're the one
with the problem, Harv.
You know I didn't do this.
Hey, thanks for settling
the case for me, buddy,
but I said I wanted
a pound of flesh
from CM and you,
and I meant it.
- That was harsh.
- You kidding me?
He came hat in hand, Harvey.
Have you met him?
This guy gets one whiff
of what we've been hiding
from Hardman,
I guarantee you it's his office
he's in, not ours.
I know, we can't trust him.
Still, you should have seen him
in this deposition.
I mean, all he wants
is to be you.
Isn't that
what everybody wants?
I'm serious, Harvey.
I'm sorry,
that's just pathetic.
I know, but what I'm...
Bothering you?
No. No, not at all.
I heard about your proposal
to buy Durham Foods
out of bankruptcy.
Impressive.
Well, the way I see it
is a win-win.
Way to think outside the box.
It was actually
Mike Ross's idea.
I'm glad to see
it all worked out.
Louis...
you seem upset about something.
Is there anything
you want to tell me?
Jessica Pearson,
leading by example.
Spare me the charm, Harvey.
Give it to me straight.
CM settled. $46 million.
1/3 to Frank Randall's widow,
the rest into a blind trust
for his children.
You're pleased with that?
Damn straight I am.
When's the other shoe
gonna drop?
What makes you think
there's another shoe?
It's Tanner.
There's always another shoe.
They're still
coming after us for fraud.
It's time to pay the Piper.
You want to tell him,
or shall I?
Well, we'll worry
about that tomorrow.
What the hell gives you two
the right
to hide a lawsuit
against my firm from me?
- Daniel...
- I am not done yet.
When were you planning on
telling me this?
When the case went to court?
When our malpractice insurance
ran out?
Are the two of you
so shortsighted
that you would allow
your distaste of me
to impair your ability
to run this firm?
When you came five years ago
to blackmail me, I was furious.
You told me that I was
blaming you for my own actions.
I wasn't just embezzling,
but I also tried to cover it up.
Well, that's what you were
so busy doing
the other morning,
covering it up.
You had the chance to tell me,
and you didn't.
- No, I didn't.
- Why?
I don't trust you.
That's not true.
He didn't tell you
because I don't trust you.
Tell me you're not gonna
use this as some power play.
That's exactly
what I should do,
but I am gonna
give you the chance
I have been asking you
to give me,
the chance to redeem yourself.
How?
They're not just
coming after you.
They're coming after all of us.
Pearson. Hardman.
What are you proposing?
We fight them together.
Okay.
You trust him?
At the moment,
we don't really have a choice.
Looking good, Louis.
You're supposed to say,
"feeling good, Billy Ray."
You know, Trading Places.
Movie quotes, it's what we do.
You want something?
Uh, well, I just heard
that you ran with my idea
about buying out Durham Foods,
and Hardman told me
you gave me the credit,
so... Team Litt-Ross.
I told him because I don't
like to owe anyone anything.
You covered for me with him
earlier, so I threw you a bone.
Now we're even.
Where's this coming from?
I'll tell you
where it's coming from.
You were right.
Actions have impact.
So you want to remember
the marijuana and tennis thing?
Well, I'm gonna
remember things too.
How's your budding bro-mance
with Louis?
Evidently, it's over.
So fickle is the heart.
What's going on with you?
Why are you being so... weird?
Tanner took the deal.
So it's done.
No. He's still
coming after me for fraud,
and a lot of people are gonna
think I buried that document.
How can you bury
what doesn't exist?
Doesn't matter.
They'll think it happened once,
it could happen again.
So why are you smiling?
Because I know what they don't.
You're gonna beat Tanner.
I'm not just gonna beat him.
When I'm done with him,
his own mother
won't even recognize him.
Ah, that's where you are.
I've been looking for you.
You okay? You look like
you're gonna be sick.
Oh, God, you know,
actually, I do,
I feel like
I'm coming down with something.
Do you think that maybe
you could grab me a water?
Yeah. Yeah, of course.