Previously on... Suits
Katrina Bennett said she'd put
the deal through
if you offered her a job.
You bribed her.
You bet your ass I did.
I decided to farm out the case.
Let me guess... Daniel Hardman.
[Whispering] He's baiting you
into breaching confidentiality.
And I'm ready to bite down
and drag him in with me.
She was younger than you,
prettier than you,
and of child-bearing age...
all of the things you are not,
and you fired her for it.
You can't be
the named defendant
on a gender-discrimination case
while we're suing Folsom Foods
for the same thing.
I am not capitulating
to that man.
You have 45 cases
you can't afford.
Any way you slice it,
I'm going to bleed you dry.
I put my reputation
on the line to close Maria.
- Sheila, please.
- I think you should go.
Meet Ms. Dana Scott.
- Scottie.
- Harvey.
Oh, you two know each other?
We went to Harvard Law
together.
I've been here longer
than 75% of our associates,
and I love it,
and that's what I told them
in my essay.
I'm going to Harvard.
When I get back to London,
I'm getting married, Harvey.
What would you like me to say?
I'm Hanley Folsom,
President of Folsom Foods.
Recently we've been victim
to terrible allegations
that we've been discriminating
against women.
We're in places
like Marysville,
places where women want
more than just jobs.
They want homes, families,
and we support that.
And if they want advancement,
we support that too.
Got to give it to him.
His food might suck,
but he makes
a mean bullshit pie.
Okay, please don't put
that image in my mind.
I'm eating. Thank you.
What've you got there...
vomit bagel...
Feces pancakes?
Look, I don't care
what he says.
This is a man
who won't promote women.
I want to steal a page
from your book.
I already checked. There's
no hot-mic footage from this.
Then interview the cameraman
or the sound guy,
whatever it takes.
We need to catch this guy
in a lie.
I already tried
to hire an investigator.
The authorization
got kicked back.
Do it anyway.
I'll take care of it.
We need to talk
about resources.
We do.
I hear clients' calls
aren't being returned.
Hardman put seven cases
on the fast track.
The rest have to take
a backseat.
We can't just hang our clients
out to dry.
We won't.
At 10:00 a.m.,
the library will be packed.
Instead of returning 113 calls,
I'm going to take an hour
and give them
the state of the union.
- Oh, good.
- Not good enough.
I need 40 more
contract lawyers,
a dozen paralegals,
and Mike Ross just told me
he couldn't even hire
an investigator.
That's right. He can't.
- We have to.
- No.
- We need to invest in this.
- Did you hear me?
We bit this off.
We need to chew.
You're like a toddler. No.
All of these are bills.
We knew what we were
getting into.
And then we took a hit
from Monica Eton
and hired the contract lawyers.
We are out of money.
Use the line of credit.
It's gone.
What?
They have evaluated
the situation,
and they know we're bleeding.
So we've got seven cases
in seven cities
over the next two months.
So what are you proposing I do?
Okay, what do you have for me?
Rachel.
Rachel?
What's going on?
What are you doing?
- I'm working.
- On what?
One of the seven cases
is in Massapequa,
so I'm seeing
if one of the cities nearby
might have
a private investigator.
Okay, so that's a map
of Boston.
You're on what we commonly
refer to as the Internet.
And then, up here,
you would just write
"private investigator."
But then
I wouldn't be able to see
what part of town
I want to live in
when I go to Harvard.
Okay, so basically
you haven't been working
for the last, what, 15 minutes?
Half hour...
45 minutes.
- Come on.
- I am sorry.
I don't deal well with waiting.
You've done everything
that you can do, all right?
You killed the LSATs.
You had a great interview.
You're a legacy.
You're smoking hot.
They don't let people in
because they're hot.
I would.
You do realize we're working
on a gender-discrimination case.
That's what I'm doing...
working.
And hopefully that's
what you'll be doing now too.
Change of plans.
Welcome to the team, hottie.
We're consolidating resources.
Jessica didn't approve
the investigator?
Jessica approved
anything we want,
for one case.
What?
No, we have to fight them all.
And we will.
By letting six of them go?
Do you know
how we won World War II?
Yeah, of course. Spock didn't
let Kirk save Joan Collins
from getting hit by that car.
Wrong. We'd already won.
Kirk just would have changed
the course of history.
I accept that.
Eisenhower had 156,000 men
for 8 possible invasion points,
which means...
- 19,500 men per point.
- Otherwise known as nothing.
He had to put everything
that he had into one attack...
[Snaps fingers] Normandy.
So the question is,
where the hell is our Normandy?
That's easy. Bakersfield.
Lowest percentage
of female promotions...
Highest percentage
of female applicants.
And Hanley Folsom's
brother-in-law runs the plant.
Exactly.
You want to launch an attack,
you launch it from Bakersfield.
Hey, am I Spock or Kirk?
Uhura.
Walked right into it.
I got you an espresso,
quad shot.
- I don't need coffee.
- You might.
I'm fine.
What?
Oh, your suit's a little...
It's a client meeting,
not a bachelor auction.
Yeah, about that...
What, are there too many
clients to fit in the library?
We're using
the conference room.
- They won't all fit.
- They will.
There's been
a slight complication.
Donna...
You will understand
when you get there.
Now you're ready.
Donna.
Scottie? Harvey.
- How's married life?
- I wouldn't know.
Divorced so soon?
I never took the plunge.
Oh, get over yourself.
I know I came here last time
with cold feet
and blubbered over you
like a 15-year-old,
but it wasn't about you.
It was about me.
So what's it about this time?
Bakersfield.
You are not taking
my clients, Scottie.
We already did.
Like taking candy
from a little Harvard baby.
You just said
it wasn't about me.
Harvey,
Bakersfield is everything,
and I've got them.
I've also got appointments
with the rest.
So I can spend time going
after them and get 20 more,
or you could let me have 10
and we call it a day.
Well, why don't I just
give it all to you?
My cases, office,
my wallet, my keys...
It's not personal.
It's just business.
- Yeah, my business.
- Good business.
The answer is no.
Well, there's no harm
in asking.
It's good to see you, though.
[Laughs] You look great.
A bit overworked, but...
Not bad for a guy your age.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All that time imagine this ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
You've got to be kidding me.
She took Bakersfield?
And she's looking for ten more.
A woman that goes after
what she wants.
- You sound impressed.
- You don't.
I already work with a woman
like that every day.
Maybe I should have hired her
when I had the chance.
What chance?
There was one opening
that year,
and she was the best on paper,
but I had already
invested so much in you
that I decided to get a return
on my investment.
Which is what I'm going
to give you right now,
even though you don't have
any more money to invest.
Are you back to resources?
Because I've had enough
of hearing about our weaknesses.
I'm talking about turning it
into one of our strengths.
I'm listening.
Hardman knows we're tapped out.
He's counting on it.
What if we're not?
What if we're flush?
Are you talking
about joining forces with her?
With her firm...
Her infinitely
deep-pocketed firm.
Harvey, she wanted ten cases.
You're talking
about sharing 45,
and I've never known you
to share.
They're based in London,
so we'll be running the show.
They'll just be signing
the checks.
And taking a cut
of the winnings.
Exactly. Winnings.
It's the best way
to beat Hardman.
And the side benefit is
you don't lose to Scottie.
Nothing wrong
with a side benefit.
Fine. Don't lose to her.
But you better make damn sure
that you don't lose with her.
Good. You're here.
I'm taking the personnel files,
you go through
the corporate minutes, and...
Excuse me?
Bakersfield.
We don't have all day.
[Scoffs]
I'm... I'm sorry. I didn't know
you were on Bakersfield.
Well, I am. Let's go.
The minutes are over there,
and they're not going
to read themselves.
Okay, well, you may be
on Bakersfield,
but I'm the lead
and we're not going to do any
of that stuff
until we get Harvey
some up-to-date statistics.
4.7% female executives...
up to date.
That's a number.
We need the probability
of that ratio being chance
across 22 divisions
in 45 states, which is one...
One in 8.3 billion.
How did you know that?
I checked
with the statistician.
Yeah, well, he's wrong,
because he didn't...
Adjust for outliers,
which takes it to...
One in 6.4 billion.
- How did you know that?
- I did it in my head.
It's what I do.
It's why I'm lead,
and if you don't know,
you better ask somebody.
I don't need to ask anybody
to know that if we use
the 8.3 billion number,
it's defensible,
and it skews the results
in our favor.
Oh, what a shock.
You want to skew the results
at the expense
of our credibility.
We're not doing it.
- I am a fifth year, Mike.
- And I work for Harvey.
Well, Jessica assigned me.
And if you don't like that,
why don't you go talk to her?
I don't want to work
with Katrina.
She comes in. She takes over.
She acts like everything
is her idea.
Then we're in the same boat,
'cause I don't want
to work with Scottie.
- We're working with Scottie?
- I'm working with Scottie.
She's coming
to Bakersfield with us?
to Bakersfield with me.
How can you do that to me?
I didn't do it to you.
She did. She stole them.
- Wait. What?
- Relax, okay?
You're going to go
on another road trip someday.
No, Harvey,
you're not getting it.
We're going
to lose World War II.
What do you want?
Coffee? Tea?
I'm good, thanks.
A woman who wants nothing...
I distrust that.
Who said I want nothing?
Oh, no one's ever said that
about you.
Oh, what have they said?
"They"?
You.
My opinion matters to you?
Your opinion matters to him.
I've only ever said
good things about you, Scottie.
But what have you thought?
Just don't screw with him.
Don't screw with him,
or don't screw him?
Are you able to do one
without the other?
The other what?
I'll leave you two to business.
So are you going
to take me up on my offer,
or are you going to fight me?
You tell me.
I think neither.
I think you want us
to try the cases together
and let my firm
bankroll the litigation.
Which is exactly
what you wanted the whole time.
You got me.
We'll start with Bakersfield.
You couldn't just go
for the direct approach?
You don't respond
to the direct approach, Harvey.
You like to feel you can come
to things on your own.
Which is why we're not
starting with Bakersfield.
- It's the clear choice.
- Exactly.
You knew it,
my first year knew it,
and so will Hardman.
- I'm not afraid of Hardman.
- You should be.
And that's why
we're going to Parkville.
You mean the one division
with a female manager
and the best ratio
of women executives
in the entire company?
No, I mean the one division
where Hardman will never think
to find us.
Because it's
the dumbest place to start
and the hardest place to win.
And when we win it,
all the others will surrender.
What a surprise...
Harvey Specter wants
to do things the hard way.
What a surprise...
Dana Scott's looking
for the shortcut.
And what makes you think
that he's not going to find out
that we're not still going
to Bakersfield?
We're still going
to Bakersfield.
We book a plane, a hotel,
line up depositions there
and in all seven cities.
That plan isn't worthy
of our kind of money.
If you want
to overwhelm Hardman...
We go to all 45 cities...
Which is exactly
what you wanted the whole time.
You got me.
Hey, um, I just wanted
to say I'm sorry
and that you were right.
Jessica assigned you,
so you should take the lead
on Bakersfield.
What are you going to do?
I've got other things.
I'll be fine.
Good. You're both here.
Change of plan.
Uh, no need.
I already know, so...
This isn't about Parkville.
I'm deposing Hanley Folsom
in 36 hours,
and I need to know more
about him than his mistress does
before he gets here.
He has a mistress?
That would help, wouldn't it?
And you should already know,
since you asked on this case.
Now find me something.
What are you pissed about now?
Jessica assigned you?
No, you asked.
I asked, and she assigned me.
That's how it works.
When you phrased it to me,
you picked language
that skewed a little bit
in your favor.
Like you just said,
"I've got other things,"
instead of telling me
the focus of the entire case
apparently just moved
to Parkville,
which I don't have
a problem with,
but clearly
you have a problem with me.
My problem with you
is how you got here.
That's funny,
because my problem with you
is how I got here.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Harvey offered me a job,
and I thought it was
because I'd impressed him.
Then you showed up,
ready to break privilege,
and I knew the real reason.
He was hiring me
to protect you.
Right, and then
after you found out
the real reason for the offer,
you went to Harvey,
and you said,
"I can't possibly accept
employment
under those circumstances."
Oh, wait. No, you didn't.
You're damn right I didn't,
because I couldn't,
because I had already
given notice.
Stop taking everything
so personally
and get over it.
Tell me you're
not having "Lear" envy.
It's nice.
"Nice"?
Should we have taken your jet?
Oh, wait. You don't have a jet.
It's hard to park them
in Manhattan.
Oh, right. I forgot how
provincial Pearson Hardman was...
one office, one city.
One office, the city.
What?
It just occurred to me.
Oh, let me guess.
There's an advantage
to being on the same side.
Well, we don't have to get
the business out of the way
before getting to the pleasure.
There's also a disadvantage.
Oh, let me guess.
You have some rule.
I don't cook in my own kitchen.
- You cook?
- It's a metaphor.
Yeah, I got that.
But you're in luck.
We are not in the same kitchen.
We are on this case.
Somebody didn't read
the paperwork.
When do I ever read
the paperwork?
We're still separate entities.
It's just a combined
legal action.
Mm, I like the sound of that.
I was hoping you would.
Are you going to litigate me
into sleeping with you?
I'm going to lead you
right where you're dying to go.
[Laughs]
How long until we land?
Long enough.
- Combined legal action.
- Mm-hmm.
You know, wait.
We didn't decide who's taking
the lead on the deposition.
Well, we could
rock, paper, scissors for it.
[Laughs]
Or we can do this.
How will we know who won?
Oh, we'll know.
Hey, sweetpants.
I feel like
I never see you anymore,
so I was wondering
if you want...
oh, my God. What happened?
You didn't get in.
I don't want to talk about it.
I understand.
[Knocks on glass]
Hey, Rachel, I need your help.
Um, yes. What do you need?
I'm ready to work.
Listen, if you need help
with any of it,
I'm going to be at my desk.
Thanks, Donna.
Don't take it so personally.
What?
That's what someone said to me.
And whenever someone says
something's not personal,
it is, because everything
is personal.
I know.
What do you think
Hanley Folsom's
personal opinion is
on hiring women?
Uh, that he doesn't think
we're good enough,
but, I mean, it's not
like he would say it out loud.
Not at work.
Which is why you need access
to his personal correspondence.
- Exactly.
- That's outside the scope.
Well, let's find a way
to put it inside the scope.
Do you have any ideas?
No, but I have 62 boxes
and 12 hours to find an idea.
Exactly what I need to do...
let's go.
- I told you I'd win.
- Maybe I let you win.
You've never let anybody
win anything in your whole life.
Why would you start now?
Now I get to demand a rematch.
And I get
to lead the deposition.
Parkville, Missouri...
of all the places
to run into you, Harvey.
Glad you could make it.
I almost didn't.
I was on my way
to Bakersfield...
after all, Harvey Specter
had a flight booked there...
when, suddenly,
I had a thought.
What would Harvey do?
So I checked,
and Dana Scott's flight plan
was here.
Can't get around those pesky
F.A.A. regulations, can you?
I hope you've got
all the cities covered,
'cause we've got
people everywhere.
Deep pockets.
Dana Scott. A pleasure.
I can't say the same.
You do like
strong women, Harvey.
And you don't like women
at all.
[Cell phone ringing]
Oh, she's cute.
This should be fun.
Oh, I'm just getting a call
from my niece
who needs help
with her homework.
What do you got?
I know why
they promoted Cathleen Mitchell.
What is your title,
Ms. Mitchell?
Vice President,
Regional Services.
And how many
management positions are there
in your region? 612.
And how many of those
are women?
41.
41 out of 612...
that's, uh, 6.6%.
- 6.7%, if you round up.
- Let's not.
And who sets the hiring policy?
The hiring policy
is that we hire
the best applicant
for each job.
I'm confused.
Are women inherently
inferior, then?
No.
Well, then why is it
that your company
doesn't want to promote women
into positions of power?
I am in a position of power.
Yes, but you're not exactly
like other women, are you?
Harvey?
You applied four times
for management,
and you've been rejected
every time,
due to reviews
containing the terms
"aggressive," "hostile,"
and "overly ambitious."
And then, suddenly,
you were "dedicated,"
"hardworking,"
and "a team player."
People change, Harvey.
And the last I checked,
you have to ask a question.
I will,
and it's about that change.
Were you diagnosed
with uterine cancer in 2009?
- That is not relevant.
- Are you married?
- What does that...
- Do you have any children?
- No.
- Can you have any children?
This is beyond the pale,
Harvey, even for you.
Should I read your deposition
of Jessica Pearson
from two weeks ago?
That's a different case
and inadmissible here.
Did you or did you not
have a hysterectomy
that rendered you unable
to have children
nine months
before you were promoted?
- She is not going to answer.
- Maybe not today.
But it will become part
of the record.
Hanley Folsom only promotes
women whose attention to home
and family isn't in question.
Except for one thing.
Mr. Folsom didn't know.
So you say.
He didn't know
because I didn't tell anybody,
because it's my business.
Still, he found out,
and that's why
you were promoted.
[Whispering]
Harvey, that's enough.
Will you look at that, Harvey?
Even Ms. Scott understands
that being childless
and unmarried
doesn't make you damaged goods.
But if that's how you're framing
your argument,
good luck.
We'll see you in Bakersfield...
And everywhere else.
How could you not tell me
that she'd had a hysterectomy?
Because I just got
the information
on my way into the room.
You could have taken
five seconds to fill me in.
I didn't fill you in
because I wasn't sure
you could play good cop.
Because you weren't sure
that I could play it,
or because even when we're
on the same side,
you still want to win?
If I told you,
you wouldn't be pissed off.
Now you can go to her
and call me an asshole
with conviction.
You're an asshole.
Wait a second.
You're accusing me
of still trying to win?
You're the one who's still
trying to win something.
You know, I should have known.
It's never the whole story
with you.
What the hell's
really going on?
You beat me last time.
And ever since then,
Edward Darby hasn't seen me
as worthy
of being a name partner.
Cooke would never allow that
to happen, anyway.
He can't stand Americans.
Cooke retired,
and he decided there's more
to life than work.
So, if you deliver
a huge win...
I get my name on the door.
Why didn't you
just tell me that?
You always respond to strength,
not weakness.
Look at that.
You really did fool me.
If I had known that you
were that good a performer,
I would've let you be good cop.
[Both laugh]
Stop.
Cooke really decided
there's more to life than work?
Yep.
Both: Pussy.
Um, where have you been?
- I've been right here.
- I've been waiting for you.
I finished
going through everything.
Me too. It's all catalogued.
It's right there.
Okay, good,
'cause I got to get it to...
where's 15 through 20?
I thought that was you.
The boxes
are right there, Rachel.
What's the matter with you?
Come on.
You're late.
Katrina handed me her briefs
an hour ago.
Um, yeah, I've, uh...
I got most of mine.
Most? [Chuckles]
If I can't count on you
for the effort,
how the hell am I supposed
to count on you for the results?
I'm sorry. It was my fault.
Um, I'll get it done. Too late.
Now I have to call
Daniel Hardman
and postpone
and look like a fool.
Thank you, Mr. Ross.
- Mike...
- I don't want to hear it.
Get it done.
Rachael?
Yes.
Katrina Bennett.
We haven't met yet.
Oh, I-I know who you are.
Welcome.
Louis says you're
the best paralegal around.
Thank you.
I need 40 copies of these,
and if you can duplicate
the tabs
and have it back to me
within in an hour,
I will be eternally
in your debt.
Uh, Katrina, I'm so sorry.
I just can't.
I'm too busy right now.
Too busy on what?
I'm going back
through discovery
to see if I can find a door
into Folsom's
personal correspondence.
That's a wild-goose chase.
Who put you on that?
Mike Ross.
Well, I'm sorry you're busy
working on something
for a first year.
But the managing partner
asked me to do something,
and I didn't tell her
I was too busy.
Right.
This is for the same
managing partner.
Yes, but she didn't ask for it.
Mike Ross did.
Look, I know
you've taken your LSATs,
and you may well be ready
to be a lawyer.
But right now you're not.
You're a paralegal.
I'm doing my job,
and I need you to do yours.
Rachel, do me a favor?
Can you just put that on pause
for a sec?
'Cause I need to make a copy.
No, Louis, I can't.
I'm busy doing my job.
Excuse me?
What, do you want to fire me
like you fired Harold?
Because honestly,
I-I-I don't give a shit.
I get it. [Chuckles]
Rachel, listen, I know
about the Harvard thing.
And I think it's great. What?
Yeah, Norma told me.
Rachel, I know
the waiting is hard,
but you're not going to be here
for much longer.
I got 100% faith in you.
[Voice breaking]
I didn't get in.
What?
I don't understand.
I had everything...
my grades, the LSATs,
I'm a legacy,
and I don't even
puff myself up,
but I killed it
at that interview.
That doesn't make any sense.
And do you remember that woman
who came from Harvard?
She didn't like anyone,
but I swear, she loved me.
Sheila?
Yeah. Sheila... Sheila Sazs.
You remember.
Yeah, I remember.
Is there something wrong?
Yep, there is something wrong.
I believe you were wronged.
I believe you suffered
the slings and arrows
of outrageous wrongness.
And I will not have it.
What does that mean?
That means that I'm going
to rectify this situation,
because you, Miss Zane,
you're going to Harvard.
[Telephone ringing]
Looks like somebody
had a good trip.
- Not exactly.
- Though the plane ride was fun.
As long as you didn't hit
any turbulence.
Jessica wants to see you.
I'll be right back.
Actually, she wants
to see both of you.
Jessica wants to see me too?
Not exactly.
Your boss wants to see you.
I'll just ask the concierge
to find something...
- Hello.
- Ah, Dana.
And this must be
the man himself.
Edward Darby.
He doesn't seem stodgy at all,
or that old.
You should see me
in my altogether.
Pass.
Fair enough.
[Jessica and Harvey chuckle]
Edward stopped in
to take stock of his investment.
So how are we?
We're right on schedule.
Dana?
We've dropped a grenade.
We're just waiting
for it to go off.
- Meaning it hasn't.
- Rome wasn't built in a day.
Excellent point.
I needn't have crossed the pond.
And yet, here you are.
[Sighs]
Well, as I confessed
to Jessica,
I have an ulterior motive
in our little venture.
Daniel Hardman.
I've had
the distinct displeasure.
So I have asked him
to step it up a notch.
Nice. Attack him on all fronts.
We have clients everywhere.
Finding a bone
of contention with him
seemed the least
I could contribute.
Along with 12 million pounds.
I hate talking numbers.
I prefer raking them in.
Well, I've done
what I came to do.
Now I'm going to get
out of your way.
Nice to put a face to all this.
And a lovely face,
it turns out.
Thank you, Edward.
I was referring to your man.
[Both chuckle]
I'll be waiting
for that detonation.
I trust it will come through.
Mmhmm.
[Knocks on glass]
You wanted to see me?
Yeah.
I wanted to explain
about earlier.
You don't have to. It's fine.
I overreacted.
Okay, then I won't.
I will just tell you
I found what you needed.
What, like you went
through the rest of the files?
No. I found what you needed.
- Access?
- Hanley Folsom.
- Personal?
- Bingo.
Oh, my God, that couldn't
have come at a better time.
I would have found them
for you sooner,
but I had to copy
some bullshit for Katrina.
Why didn't you just tell her
you were working for me?
I told her exactly
what I was doing for you.
And she didn't... oh, God.
Never mind. I get it.
She did the same thing to me.
She pulls that fifth-year crap,
and then you don't feel
like dealing.
You have no idea.
What do we have?
Enough for you
to write a motion.
- He seems nice.
- He was pissed.
That was pissed?
What does happy look like?
He's British...
pretty much the same thing.
Then how'd you know
he was pissed?
- Wouldn't you be?
- I am.
We haven't turned
Cathleen Mitchell yet.
Your good cop failed.
No, your move failed.
Well, Jessica took it well.
Because she had company.
I'll hear about it later.
Does he do that...
just pop in for a spot of tea?
It's 12 million pounds.
You weren't expecting him.
No...
I wasn't.
But this is a big investment
for him, Harvey.
His investment is only money.
For me, it's my whole firm.
Excuse me.
Harvey, do you have a minute?
[Keys clacking]
You got here just in time.
I'm getting us access.
- Hanley Folsom?
- Bingo.
Well, if you're talking
about the July 29th reference
in his business email
to his personal email,
then you're too late. What?
Katrina gave me the subpoena
an hour ago.
I guess it's a good thing
Jessica put her
on the case after all.
When people steal from me,
I take it personally.
- Are you subpoenaing me?
- You diverted Rachel.
And then you pursued
my idea yourself.
Your idea?
Are you denying it?
No, you said we needed to fly,
so I built an airplane.
And then flew it
right into Harvey's office
just in time to take credit.
I offered you a chance
to work together.
You didn't want to take it.
You've always got an answer.
And you've always got
an accusation.
So either run to Harvey
and tell him
your little tale of woe,
or get to work
prepping for Folsom, like I am.
[Elevator bell dings]
[Knock at door]
Louis.
Sheila.
- Where's my interviewee?
- I dispatched him.
That's unacceptable.
- You are unacceptable.
- Excuse me?
You behaved unprofessionally.
I never behave
unprofessionally.
Okay, fine.
Ski mask and coconut oil?
That was personal.
But you let the personal
color the professional,
and Rachel Zane
will not be a casualty
of your misplaced anger.
"Misplaced"?
You made me look the fool.
I looked the fool.
You were collateral damage...
not my fault.
And it certainly
wasn't Ms. Zane's fault.
So you're here to be
her knight in shining armor.
I'm here to right a wrong.
- How very...
- Very what?
Noble.
Yeah, it is.
And you're going to undo this.
I am.
That's not what I meant.
But it's what you've caused.
I...
Will not be denied.
Then come reap
what you've sowed.
- Have at you.
- Joust me.
I don't care what it takes.
We need to get to that
smoking gun before Katrina does.
She already found it.
Katrina gave it
to Missy Dietler to make copies.
I'm sure it's already
in Jessica's hands by now.
Wait a minute. Missy Dietler?
She's going to take four coffee
breaks before she's done.
She's going to take
four coffee breaks
before she finishes
her coffee break.
Which means it's probably still
in the copy machine right now.
Missy's not going to leave
the documents
just sitting
in the copy machine.
No, but she probably
already scanned them.
So all we need is her code.
You're talking about
stealing someone's work.
Mm, someone who lied to you,
stole from me,
and made us both
look like fools.
Look, if you have any qualms,
think about it.
We're all on the same team.
The faster this gets done,
the better for everyone.
Oh, you got an answer
for everything.
Well, so does she.
Are you sure
you want to do this?
Yes.
Uh, whoa. What are you doing?
Manningham's had a crush
on me since the day I got here.
He would give me his mother's
social security number
if I asked him for it.
Okay, Rachel, we don't
have much time.
I need a sure thing here.
Mike...
I am a sure thing.
Yeah, I mean, give it a shot.
It probably won't work,
but, um...
That was brutal,
deliciously brutal.
And your act of vengeance
raised my ire.
You, sir, are a knight.
And now it is time
to right what is wrong.
Look, Sheila, I'm flattered
by what you did,
but this is not fair,
and you know it can't stand.
Louis, pull a resume
from the stack... any one.
Read it. [Sighs]
Sure.
Magna cum laude, Yale, 3.9 GPA.
Another one.
Summa cum laude,
Georgetown, 4.3. GPA.
Listen, I get it.
I know what you're trying...
That's my reject pile.
I am a professional.
I would never let
my feelings for you
sway me against a candidate.
Okay, but you have to let them
sway you for a candidate.
You can't ask me that.
Rachel Zane
is the best paralegal
in the best law firm
in New York.
She is relied upon
by the best lawyers
who have graduated
from the best university.
The woman is crimson.
So who do I knock out?
I promised her.
Louis, I liked her. I did.
You're just going to have
to tell her the truth.
Sometimes
good isn't good enough.
So how's
that detonation coming?
Long fuse.
Is that your way of telling me
that it's never going off?
Well, if it doesn't,
you could always have James Bond
take care of it for you.
That reminds me.
How are things going
with Pussy Galore?
Um, I believe, at this point,
she's still flying missions
for Goldfinger.
"No, Mr. Bond,
I expect you to die."
What the hell
are you doing here?
We can win Parkville.
This is the key to everything.
Well, then we need to get
Pussy Galore back on that plane.
[Elevator bell dings,
telephone rings]
Just remember what I told you.
No matter what happens...
well, if it isn't
the three stooges.
Oh, dibs on Curly.
Would you gentlemen mind
accompanying us
to the conference room?
What is she doing here?
Dana Scott?
She's the attorney of record
on the case.
He's referring to my employee.
Oh, well, at the moment,
she's reading this.
An email you wrote
from your personal account
on the subject
of hiring Ms. Mitchell.
And next,
we'll show her the attachment.
It wasn't on your copy.
Oddly enough,
it wasn't on ours either.
Mike managed
to find the original.
We'll need time to review this.
Review it? He wrote it.
You knew
she couldn't have children.
That's why you
changed her review,
and that's why you
promoted her.
And when she sees it,
she'll join the suit,
and you won't stand a chance.
That email
doesn't prove a pattern.
- It proves what he did to her.
- It's one case.
We'll see you at the next 44.
In the meantime,
we won't be participating
in that deposition
until you put Ms. Mitchell
back on a plane.
[Elevator bell dings]
How'd it go?
It's not over yet.
But you're out of the doghouse
with Jessica?
Out.
What?
You never said how it went
with Manningham.
[Laughs] And I never will.
Well, if it isn't
Bonnie and Clyde.
What are you doing
in my office?
Well, I didn't think you cared
to respect what's yours
or, more to the point,
what's mine.
Your problem's not with her.
It's with me.
Okay.
You stole my discovery,
and you know it.
Oh, you mean
that piece of paper
that I turned into a strategy?
Or, as you like to call it,
an airplane.
Okay, fine.
I put my toe over the line.
You obliterated it.
Yeah. I'm so sorry.
But yesterday you were
the fifth-year authority
on right and wrong, so I...
I was just taking your advice.
And which side
of right and wrong
does sleeping
with the paralegals fall on?
Get the hell out of my office.
You're right.
That's none of my business.
But it's a good thing
you're going to law school,
because they may sleep
with the paralegals,
but they end up
with the lawyers.
Of course, when you called,
I popped straight over,
but I must say,
you do keep uncivilized hours
in the little apple.
It's the Big Apple.
Well, then someone's just
sold me a counterfeit T-shirt.
A sense of humor...
I love that in a man,
which is why
I'm prepared to consider
taking you up on your offer.
Might I inquire
what changed your mind?
What's this?
Our books
from the last five years.
If we're going to do this,
I want you to know
exactly what it is
you're getting yourself into.
Now, start at the beginning.
It's a great read.
You are an impressive woman.
Oh, you don't know the half.
Well, here's
to my further education.
You're late.
That's not going to get you
out of buying me a drink first.
No more bullshit.
What?
I just left Jessica
and your boss,
and I know what I saw.
They're in bed together,
and I don't mean having sex.
They're talking merger.
It's not what it looks like.
Hardman can check a plane,
and I can check a plane.
Edward Darby flew here
the day you did.
He didn't just pop in.
He wasn't supposed to do that.
You don't want your name
on the door.
You want your name on my door.
I want to see our names
on the same door.
Yeah, like I said,
it's never the full story
with you.
I wanted to be able
to tell you myself.
Then why didn't you tell me?
Because he wouldn't let me
until he decided.
Well, evidently,
he decided without you.
Okay, okay. He jumped the gun.
But I have his promise, Harvey.
If we merge,
he names me as partner,
and Jessica's only choice
is you.
I don't need you
to get my name on the door
any more than I need you
to win this case.
You know what, Harvey?
You have been outgunned
ever since Hardman left.
I am bringing the guns.
This is exactly
what you've always wanted.
Get over your pride.
I'm not getting over anything.
And this merger
isn't happening.
Jessica. Edward.
Daniel, haven't seen you
since that business in Milan.
- Beautiful weather.
- Oh, enough.
We are not
friendly adversaries, Daniel.
And you're about to lose.
My client already said no.
He may no longer listen to you
when I inform him
of your prior embezzlement.
You told him.
I didn't tell him anything.
I found it on my own.
Edward and I are merging.
I had to show him the books.
Legally required
to show me her books.
And unlike you,
I don't break the law.
A fact that Hanley Folsom
could be made acutely aware of.
You do break the law, Jessica.
Not reporting embezzlement
is a crime.
Why don't you bring that up
at your sentencing hearing?
Why don't I sue you?
You could.
Anybody could sue anybody.
But you still don't have proof
that I told him.
And our firms combined
have ten times
the resources that yours d...
[chuckles] Oh, wait.
You don't have a firm.
You're just here,
living in Zane's offices,
working on those cases
that will no longer be yours
when we're done with you.
Good-bye, Daniel.
Oh...
Get your client
to sign those papers, will you?
[Knocks on glass]
What is it, Louis?
Got a hard truth to tell you.
- I'm not going to Harvard.
- No, you're not.
I get it.
I'm not good enough.
I never have been.
That is not the hard truth.
You are an amazing candidate,
and you need to know this
in your heart.
The truth is,
you did not get in...
Because I let you down.
What are you talking about?
Sheila and I
had a relationship.
I hurt her, and...
And she took it out on me?
I'm going to write you
a recommendation for anywhere,
any law school.
It just...
Won't be Harvard.
I'm really sorry.