1
00:00:01,770 --> 00:00:03,415
- Jeff.
- Jessica, you were right.

2
00:00:03,440 --> 00:00:06,204
We either need to have both,
or it's not going to work.

3
00:00:06,229 --> 00:00:09,378
Effective immediately,
I'm tendering my resignation.

4
00:00:09,402 --> 00:00:11,154
Forstman
doesn't throw money around

5
00:00:11,289 --> 00:00:12,935
without getting something
in return.

6
00:00:12,960 --> 00:00:14,973
He's gonna get money in return.

7
00:00:14,997 --> 00:00:15,975
Money is third on his list.

8
00:00:16,000 --> 00:00:17,779
The first two are
getting back at people

9
00:00:17,803 --> 00:00:19,304
and getting control of people.

10
00:00:19,423 --> 00:00:20,306
You son of a bitch,
you didn't bring me here

11
00:00:20,425 --> 00:00:21,570
for you to sign on the arrows.

12
00:00:21,594 --> 00:00:23,073
You brought me here
for me to sign on the arrows.

13
00:00:23,098 --> 00:00:24,683
Yep.

14
00:00:24,818 --> 00:00:25,913
After Woodall lost his job,

15
00:00:25,937 --> 00:00:27,772
Forstman got him installed
at the SEC.

16
00:00:27,907 --> 00:00:28,969
Where's the proof?

17
00:00:28,993 --> 00:00:30,277
In Eric Woodall's bank accounts.

18
00:00:30,413 --> 00:00:31,424
This is ridiculous.

19
00:00:31,448 --> 00:00:33,618
I'm your boss.

20
00:00:33,754 --> 00:00:34,875
Gentlemen, give me a minute.

21
00:00:35,006 --> 00:00:36,317
You're forcing me to turn you in

22
00:00:36,341 --> 00:00:37,687
for what you did 12 years ago.

23
00:00:37,712 --> 00:00:38,796
You're not gonna do that.

24
00:00:38,930 --> 00:00:40,693
Because you did it too, pal.

25
00:00:40,718 --> 00:00:44,691
Anyone else
ever loses faith in me,

26
00:00:44,809 --> 00:00:46,538
it doesn't matter.

27
00:00:46,563 --> 00:00:48,175
With you, it's different.

28
00:00:48,200 --> 00:00:49,951
I should go.

29
00:00:50,070 --> 00:00:51,215
Why?

30
00:00:51,239 --> 00:00:53,659
You know I love you, Donna.

31
00:01:00,008 --> 00:01:07,906
♪ ♪

32
00:01:20,382 --> 00:01:21,410
To Harvey.

33
00:01:21,435 --> 00:01:25,108
To Harvey. Cheers.

34
00:01:25,227 --> 00:01:33,125
♪ ♪

35
00:01:46,938 --> 00:01:48,523
Jay, can I get a Macallan 18?

36
00:01:50,913 --> 00:01:53,116
You know, usually when someone
wins their first trial,

37
00:01:53,251 --> 00:01:55,121
they at least pretend
to finish the drink

38
00:01:55,255 --> 00:01:56,673
their fellow ADAs bought them.

39
00:01:56,791 --> 00:01:57,792
I'm sorry, do we...

40
00:01:57,793 --> 00:01:59,461
Know each other? Not yet.

41
00:01:59,630 --> 00:02:00,608
But today's your lucky day.

42
00:02:00,633 --> 00:02:01,851
And why is that?

43
00:02:01,969 --> 00:02:03,999
Because it's the day
you get to meet Donna.

44
00:02:04,023 --> 00:02:05,869
And let me guess. You're Donna.

45
00:02:05,894 --> 00:02:09,149
Oh, you have no idea
how Donna I am.

46
00:02:09,284 --> 00:02:11,704
- Well, Donna, I'm Harvey...
- Harvey Specter.

47
00:02:11,822 --> 00:02:12,850
You really think
I'd be talking to you

48
00:02:12,875 --> 00:02:13,853
if I didn't know who you were?

49
00:02:13,877 --> 00:02:15,662
And how exactly
do you know about me?

50
00:02:15,831 --> 00:02:16,664
I know about everybody.

51
00:02:16,800 --> 00:02:19,003
What I don't know is

52
00:02:19,137 --> 00:02:21,034
why this is the first case
you ever took to trial.

53
00:02:21,058 --> 00:02:22,486
Because it was
a white-collar crime,

54
00:02:22,511 --> 00:02:23,846
not some drug dealer
on a corner,

55
00:02:23,981 --> 00:02:25,292
which makes it
the kind of case...

56
00:02:25,317 --> 00:02:27,748
That puts your name
in the paper.

57
00:02:27,773 --> 00:02:29,335
You're not just a pretty face,
are you?

58
00:02:29,359 --> 00:02:31,862
No, I'm not.

59
00:02:31,998 --> 00:02:33,309
So maybe you should
buy me a drink,

60
00:02:33,334 --> 00:02:35,376
and we can continue
this conversation in the corner.

61
00:02:37,125 --> 00:02:38,627
Jay?

62
00:02:38,761 --> 00:02:46,643
♪ ♪

63
00:02:54,244 --> 00:02:55,806
Sean, what are you doing
in my building

64
00:02:55,831 --> 00:02:57,142
in the middle of the night?

65
00:02:57,166 --> 00:02:58,395
I thought we were done
with you following me.

66
00:02:58,419 --> 00:03:00,137
I'm not following you.

67
00:03:00,256 --> 00:03:02,142
I'm waiting for you.

68
00:03:02,260 --> 00:03:03,488
I need your help.

69
00:03:03,513 --> 00:03:05,516
You need my help,
or the SEC needs my help?

70
00:03:05,650 --> 00:03:06,662
We both do.

71
00:03:06,686 --> 00:03:08,081
But at the moment,
I care more about me

72
00:03:08,106 --> 00:03:09,992
than I do about the SEC.

73
00:03:10,110 --> 00:03:11,638
I can't find the money.

74
00:03:11,663 --> 00:03:12,975
What do you mean
you can't find the money?

75
00:03:12,999 --> 00:03:14,594
What the hell have you been
doing for the last three months?

76
00:03:14,619 --> 00:03:15,620
Looking for the money.

77
00:03:15,621 --> 00:03:16,672
Then look harder,

78
00:03:16,790 --> 00:03:18,652
because Woodall isn't
in the charity business.

79
00:03:18,677 --> 00:03:19,856
Forstman buys people,

80
00:03:19,880 --> 00:03:21,799
and we handed them to you
on a silver platter.

81
00:03:21,968 --> 00:03:23,163
And I stuck my neck out for you,

82
00:03:23,187 --> 00:03:25,357
and I accused my friend
of being on the take.

83
00:03:25,475 --> 00:03:27,538
Now, if I can't follow through
with that, Eric Woodall walks.

84
00:03:27,563 --> 00:03:28,624
Charles Forstman walks.

85
00:03:28,648 --> 00:03:30,044
Well, what makes you think
I can find the money

86
00:03:30,068 --> 00:03:31,069
when you couldn't?

87
00:03:31,070 --> 00:03:32,311
I don't know if you can or not,

88
00:03:32,406 --> 00:03:34,102
but they're gonna shut me down
in five days,

89
00:03:34,127 --> 00:03:35,545
and I need all the help
I can get.

90
00:03:43,679 --> 00:03:45,566
Okay, enough about me.
Let's talk about you.

91
00:03:45,683 --> 00:03:46,912
Ooh, my favorite subject.

92
00:03:46,936 --> 00:03:49,322
- You know what I think?
- Hmm?

93
00:03:49,441 --> 00:03:51,338
I think your favorite subject
didn't come up to me

94
00:03:51,362 --> 00:03:52,840
just to find out
why I went to trial.

95
00:03:52,865 --> 00:03:54,845
You want something.

96
00:03:54,869 --> 00:03:56,014
I sure do.

97
00:03:56,038 --> 00:03:59,604
And I think I might be ready
to give it to you.

98
00:03:59,629 --> 00:04:02,110
It's not sex.

99
00:04:02,135 --> 00:04:03,886
Then never mind.

100
00:04:05,474 --> 00:04:07,309
Wow, you're gonna be
that honest about it.

101
00:04:07,445 --> 00:04:09,948
Saves time.

102
00:04:10,067 --> 00:04:13,550
Well, in that case,
I want to move to your desk.

103
00:04:13,575 --> 00:04:14,626
And why is that?

104
00:04:14,743 --> 00:04:16,305
Because it's no secret
that in a few years,

105
00:04:16,330 --> 00:04:18,059
you're going back to Gordon,
Schmidt, and Van Dyke.

106
00:04:18,084 --> 00:04:20,448
And let me guess, you want to
come with me when I do.

107
00:04:20,472 --> 00:04:21,890
No, I don't.

108
00:04:22,009 --> 00:04:23,621
Then why?

109
00:04:23,646 --> 00:04:25,291
Because I'm gonna be an actress,

110
00:04:25,315 --> 00:04:26,743
and I want somebody
who understands

111
00:04:26,768 --> 00:04:29,990
that there's more to life
than just the DA's office.

112
00:04:30,109 --> 00:04:31,444
And that I can give my all
to them

113
00:04:31,578 --> 00:04:33,498
but still step out
for the occasional audition.

114
00:04:33,616 --> 00:04:35,061
So you're stepping out
on me already?

115
00:04:35,086 --> 00:04:36,848
Yes, but the important thing is,

116
00:04:36,873 --> 00:04:38,853
I'm telling you about it
in advance.

117
00:04:38,877 --> 00:04:40,629
Macallan 36.

118
00:04:40,764 --> 00:04:42,266
I didn't order a Macallan 36.

119
00:04:42,384 --> 00:04:45,640
It's from the gentleman
over there.

120
00:04:45,774 --> 00:04:47,295
Okay, I don't know who that is,

121
00:04:47,311 --> 00:04:50,199
but I'm telling you right now,
he is bad news.

122
00:04:56,162 --> 00:04:58,726
You look different.

123
00:04:58,751 --> 00:05:00,837
I will take that
as a compliment.

124
00:05:00,973 --> 00:05:02,818
I meant I wasn't expecting
to see you like that...

125
00:05:02,843 --> 00:05:04,178
I-I know what you meant.

126
00:05:04,313 --> 00:05:06,315
What you really meant is that
you weren't expecting

127
00:05:06,317 --> 00:05:07,685
to see me at all.

128
00:05:07,853 --> 00:05:09,238
Excuse me?

129
00:05:09,357 --> 00:05:10,742
Oh, come on, Harvey.

130
00:05:10,859 --> 00:05:12,340
Ever since Mike came back
to the firm,

131
00:05:12,363 --> 00:05:15,895
I've basically been
nonexistent to you.

132
00:05:15,920 --> 00:05:16,932
What's going on?

133
00:05:16,956 --> 00:05:18,936
Cahill can't find the money.

134
00:05:18,960 --> 00:05:20,739
What do you mean
he can't find the money?

135
00:05:20,764 --> 00:05:22,242
What's he been doing
this whole time?

136
00:05:22,266 --> 00:05:24,446
- Yeah, that's what I said.
- And what did he say?

137
00:05:24,471 --> 00:05:26,272
He said he's in trouble
and he needs our help.

138
00:05:26,275 --> 00:05:28,037
And I'm gonna tell you
what I couldn't tell him.

139
00:05:28,062 --> 00:05:29,280
He can't find the money

140
00:05:29,398 --> 00:05:31,210
because he's been looking
in the wrong place.

141
00:05:31,235 --> 00:05:33,238
So where's the right place?

142
00:05:33,406 --> 00:05:35,459
I don't know exactly.

143
00:05:35,578 --> 00:05:38,332
But somewhere, there's a person
Eric Woodall cares about,

144
00:05:38,467 --> 00:05:39,645
and that's where the money went.

145
00:05:39,669 --> 00:05:41,481
And why can't we tell
Cahill that?

146
00:05:41,506 --> 00:05:43,285
Because I don't know him to know
how I know it.

147
00:05:43,310 --> 00:05:45,513
- How do you know it?
- Because I know.

148
00:05:47,986 --> 00:05:49,605
You want a chance to exist?

149
00:05:49,740 --> 00:05:51,575
Figure out a way
to get this done.

150
00:05:56,671 --> 00:06:00,260
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪

151
00:06:00,379 --> 00:06:03,600
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪

152
00:06:03,719 --> 00:06:06,774
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪

153
00:06:06,892 --> 00:06:10,531
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪

154
00:06:10,650 --> 00:06:13,455
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪

155
00:06:13,572 --> 00:06:17,463
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪

156
00:06:17,581 --> 00:06:18,976
♪ All right ♪

157
00:06:19,000 --> 00:06:20,555
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪

158
00:06:20,557 --> 00:06:24,561
♪ Suits 4x16 ♪ Not Just a Pretty Face
Original Air Date on March 4, 2015

159
00:06:24,562 --> 00:06:26,247
♪ The greenback boogie ♪

160
00:06:26,272 --> 00:06:28,274
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man

161
00:06:32,037 --> 00:06:39,979
♪ ♪

162
00:06:51,694 --> 00:06:52,695
Louis, I got your note,

163
00:06:52,829 --> 00:06:54,558
and I know that Norma's
still out,

164
00:06:54,583 --> 00:06:56,035
but I really
don't have time to...

165
00:06:56,170 --> 00:06:58,423
Norma's dead.

166
00:06:58,541 --> 00:06:59,542
What?

167
00:06:59,678 --> 00:07:01,608
She died this morning
taking care of her sister.

168
00:07:01,632 --> 00:07:04,747
Oh, Louis, I'm so sorry.

169
00:07:04,771 --> 00:07:05,949
You don't need to fake it,
Donna.

170
00:07:05,973 --> 00:07:06,974
I'm not faking it.

171
00:07:06,975 --> 00:07:08,037
She was a sweet woman.

172
00:07:08,062 --> 00:07:09,897
She was a frickin' battle-ax
is what she was.

173
00:07:10,032 --> 00:07:12,212
There wasn't a day that went by
that I didn't want to rip out

174
00:07:12,236 --> 00:07:14,267
one of her varicose veins
and strangle her with it.

175
00:07:14,291 --> 00:07:15,686
Okay, I don't think
you're in touch

176
00:07:15,711 --> 00:07:17,312
with how you're really feeling
right now.

177
00:07:17,331 --> 00:07:19,311
How I'm feeling
is that she left me high and dry

178
00:07:19,335 --> 00:07:20,419
just like she always did.

179
00:07:20,554 --> 00:07:22,283
You expect her to keep working?

180
00:07:22,308 --> 00:07:23,809
Look at this.

181
00:07:23,928 --> 00:07:25,623
It's her entire estate
laid out on paper.

182
00:07:25,647 --> 00:07:26,959
She couldn't manage my calendar,

183
00:07:26,984 --> 00:07:29,186
but this crap fest she plans
within an inch of her life.

184
00:07:29,188 --> 00:07:30,166
And you want me to make sure

185
00:07:30,190 --> 00:07:31,418
these things
are bequeathed properly?

186
00:07:31,443 --> 00:07:33,840
You can stuff them in
a giant piñata for all I care.

187
00:07:33,864 --> 00:07:35,093
I have to go find
the perfect urn

188
00:07:35,118 --> 00:07:36,680
to throw her ashes
off the top of the building.

189
00:07:36,704 --> 00:07:37,705
She requested that?

190
00:07:37,706 --> 00:07:39,351
No, she wanted them
to be in here with me,

191
00:07:39,376 --> 00:07:40,657
but like hell I'm gonna do that.

192
00:07:40,796 --> 00:07:42,716
Okay, Louis, I will
take care of this for you,

193
00:07:42,850 --> 00:07:44,947
but you're not throwing
her ashes anywhere without me.

194
00:07:44,971 --> 00:07:46,189
Okay, fine.

195
00:07:46,307 --> 00:07:47,786
Do you want me to smooth things
over with Harvey for you?

196
00:07:47,810 --> 00:07:49,622
No.

197
00:07:49,647 --> 00:07:52,368
Harvey will be just fine
on his own.

198
00:07:55,626 --> 00:07:58,163
I know who you are,
and I'm not interested.

199
00:07:58,331 --> 00:08:00,478
Just 'cause I got
a bad reputation?

200
00:08:00,503 --> 00:08:01,838
Because I'm not accepting
a drink

201
00:08:01,972 --> 00:08:03,534
for putting your rival
behind bars.

202
00:08:03,559 --> 00:08:04,977
You got the wrong idea, pal.

203
00:08:05,096 --> 00:08:07,683
I didn't buy you that
for putting my enemy away.

204
00:08:07,852 --> 00:08:11,051
I bought you that
for how you put my enemy away.

205
00:08:11,075 --> 00:08:12,526
Okay, you got me.

206
00:08:12,662 --> 00:08:15,393
What are you talking about?

207
00:08:15,418 --> 00:08:16,429
You.

208
00:08:16,453 --> 00:08:18,873
You've got something special.

209
00:08:19,008 --> 00:08:20,570
And I want people
with something special

210
00:08:20,594 --> 00:08:21,929
working for me.

211
00:08:22,048 --> 00:08:23,109
Why exactly would I want
to work for you?

212
00:08:23,133 --> 00:08:24,551
I can think of
a million reasons,

213
00:08:24,720 --> 00:08:26,784
'cause that's the signing bonus
I'm gonna give you,

214
00:08:26,808 --> 00:08:28,036
and that's a hell of
a lot more money

215
00:08:28,060 --> 00:08:29,371
than you're ever gonna make
as a lawyer.

216
00:08:29,396 --> 00:08:30,397
And what if I told you

217
00:08:30,398 --> 00:08:31,794
I don't practice law
to make money?

218
00:08:31,818 --> 00:08:34,966
Then I'd ask you,
what do you practice it for?

219
00:08:34,991 --> 00:08:36,961
To bend people to my will.

220
00:08:37,079 --> 00:08:40,417
Then bend people to your will
for me

221
00:08:40,553 --> 00:08:42,900
and make a lot of money
on top of it.

222
00:08:42,924 --> 00:08:45,571
Well, here's the thing,
Mr. Forstman.

223
00:08:45,596 --> 00:08:46,991
Not that
it's any of your business,

224
00:08:47,016 --> 00:08:50,105
but I'll be making 1/2 million
a year in no time.

225
00:08:50,239 --> 00:08:51,858
1/2 million a year is dick.

226
00:08:51,993 --> 00:08:53,973
My gardener makes that.

227
00:08:53,997 --> 00:08:55,425
Then go offer your gardener
a job,

228
00:08:55,450 --> 00:08:57,119
because I'm not interested.

229
00:08:57,253 --> 00:09:00,759
Just so you know, if you change
your mind and come back to me,

230
00:09:00,878 --> 00:09:03,358
it's not gonna be
the same conversation.

231
00:09:03,383 --> 00:09:06,688
Thanks for the drink.
Good luck, Mr. Forstman.

232
00:09:10,865 --> 00:09:12,711
Okay.

233
00:09:12,736 --> 00:09:13,737
What are you doing?

234
00:09:13,738 --> 00:09:15,156
What do you think I'm doing?

235
00:09:15,291 --> 00:09:17,471
If Forstman gave the money
to someone Woodall's close to,

236
00:09:17,495 --> 00:09:19,715
we need to start
by compiling a family tree.

237
00:09:19,834 --> 00:09:22,471
I meant why aren't you
at school today?

238
00:09:22,590 --> 00:09:26,095
Because I'm gonna prove
to Harvey that I exist.

239
00:09:26,230 --> 00:09:27,408
Okay.

240
00:09:27,433 --> 00:09:29,162
Now that you mention it,
what was that last night?

241
00:09:29,187 --> 00:09:30,498
Ever since you came back,

242
00:09:30,522 --> 00:09:32,776
it's like you and Harvey
speak this secret language,

243
00:09:32,911 --> 00:09:33,838
and I'm not a part of it.

244
00:09:33,863 --> 00:09:35,331
Rachel, come on.
We have history.

245
00:09:35,449 --> 00:09:37,691
I'm not talking about history.
I'm talking about respect.

246
00:09:37,704 --> 00:09:39,016
Okay, you don't know
what you're talking about

247
00:09:39,040 --> 00:09:40,402
if you think
Harvey doesn't respect you.

248
00:09:40,427 --> 00:09:41,521
Are you gonna tell me
that last night

249
00:09:41,545 --> 00:09:42,774
he didn't give you a look
that said,

250
00:09:42,798 --> 00:09:44,360
"You don't need to tell her
the full story

251
00:09:44,385 --> 00:09:45,746
because she doesn't need
to know"?

252
00:09:45,770 --> 00:09:47,165
Rachel, he didn't give me
that look

253
00:09:47,190 --> 00:09:48,369
because he doesn't respect you.

254
00:09:48,393 --> 00:09:52,115
He gave me that look
because he's ashamed.

255
00:09:52,234 --> 00:09:53,568
What are you talking about?

256
00:09:56,493 --> 00:09:58,022
Let's just say that
I'm not the only one

257
00:09:58,047 --> 00:09:59,308
that Charles Forstman duped.

258
00:09:59,332 --> 00:10:01,779
- Harvey got taken by Forstman?
- Yes.

259
00:10:01,804 --> 00:10:03,199
And he only told me
because he had to

260
00:10:03,223 --> 00:10:05,237
when we were in the middle
of that takeover battle.

261
00:10:05,261 --> 00:10:08,766
That's why Harvey's so slow
to care about anybody.

262
00:10:08,935 --> 00:10:11,750
Forstman used somebody
he cared about.

263
00:10:11,774 --> 00:10:13,971
Holy shit.
I never even thought about that.

264
00:10:13,996 --> 00:10:15,174
Who do you think it was?

265
00:10:15,198 --> 00:10:18,287
I don't know,
but I have a pretty good guess.

266
00:10:18,421 --> 00:10:20,791
Well, what do you think?

267
00:10:20,927 --> 00:10:22,990
I think this place is a dump,
and I'm busy,

268
00:10:23,014 --> 00:10:25,328
so why don't you tell me
why we're here?

269
00:10:25,353 --> 00:10:26,698
I want to open
a restaurant here.

270
00:10:26,722 --> 00:10:28,474
Marcus, there's already
a restaurant here.

271
00:10:28,642 --> 00:10:30,121
And it isn't working.

272
00:10:30,146 --> 00:10:32,793
Which is why they're gonna
lose their lease.

273
00:10:32,818 --> 00:10:34,203
Take a look.

274
00:10:34,321 --> 00:10:36,374
I've got a chef.

275
00:10:36,493 --> 00:10:37,888
I've got a liquor license.

276
00:10:37,912 --> 00:10:39,330
I've got renovation plans.

277
00:10:39,465 --> 00:10:42,136
I have everything I need.

278
00:10:42,254 --> 00:10:44,341
Except the money.

279
00:10:44,475 --> 00:10:45,820
I need $150,000.

280
00:10:45,845 --> 00:10:47,491
- Are you crazy?
- Come on, Harvey.

281
00:10:47,515 --> 00:10:48,733
This is my dream.

282
00:10:48,851 --> 00:10:50,069
I know I can make this work.

283
00:10:50,187 --> 00:10:51,248
And I'm not saying you can't,

284
00:10:51,273 --> 00:10:52,301
but I don't have
that kind of money.

285
00:10:52,325 --> 00:10:54,422
What are you talking about?

286
00:10:54,446 --> 00:10:56,843
You're the big-time lawyer who
just got his name in the paper.

287
00:10:56,868 --> 00:10:59,539
My name in the paper
doesn't pay me extra money.

288
00:10:59,674 --> 00:11:01,571
I make $50,000 a year.

289
00:11:01,595 --> 00:11:03,525
And you said you were gonna be
a corporate lawyer.

290
00:11:03,549 --> 00:11:05,612
Yeah, and when I am,
I can help you, but right now...

291
00:11:05,636 --> 00:11:07,939
I don't give a shit
about right now.

292
00:11:08,057 --> 00:11:09,836
I give a shit about when
you were supposed to be

293
00:11:09,861 --> 00:11:11,206
my big brother, but instead,
what did you do?

294
00:11:11,231 --> 00:11:12,292
I know what I did.

295
00:11:12,316 --> 00:11:13,962
Then you know
I can never get a loan

296
00:11:13,987 --> 00:11:15,321
for as long as I live.

297
00:11:15,456 --> 00:11:16,717
Marcus, when are you gonna
take responsibility

298
00:11:16,742 --> 00:11:17,937
for your own shit?

299
00:11:17,961 --> 00:11:19,883
What the hell does it look like
I'm trying to do?

300
00:11:24,893 --> 00:11:28,827
I came to you first because
I know you'd want me to,

301
00:11:28,851 --> 00:11:31,632
but if you don't come through,

302
00:11:31,657 --> 00:11:33,075
I'm gonna go to Mom.

303
00:11:33,193 --> 00:11:34,360
You don't mean Mom.

304
00:11:34,496 --> 00:11:35,780
You mean him.

305
00:11:35,915 --> 00:11:37,760
And you're not taking
a nickel from that man.

306
00:11:37,785 --> 00:11:39,337
Taking his money
isn't gonna make

307
00:11:39,456 --> 00:11:40,957
what he did to Dad any worse.

308
00:11:41,093 --> 00:11:42,794
That's bullshit,
and you know it,

309
00:11:42,963 --> 00:11:44,933
and I'm not gonna let you do it.

310
00:11:45,051 --> 00:11:46,696
Hey, Harvey.

311
00:11:46,721 --> 00:11:48,724
How the hell
are you gonna stop me?

312
00:11:56,040 --> 00:11:57,041
Am I crazy,

313
00:11:57,159 --> 00:11:58,721
or is that the same dress
you were wearing

314
00:11:58,746 --> 00:12:00,331
the last time I saw you?

315
00:12:00,466 --> 00:12:01,478
You must be crazy,

316
00:12:01,502 --> 00:12:03,197
because I don't wear
the same dress ever.

317
00:12:03,222 --> 00:12:05,903
Then you must spend a fortune
on wardrobe.

318
00:12:05,927 --> 00:12:09,349
But I have to say,
it's worth it.

319
00:12:09,484 --> 00:12:12,249
I suddenly get the feeling
this isn't just a drop-by.

320
00:12:12,274 --> 00:12:14,025
I want to move up our timeline.

321
00:12:14,194 --> 00:12:15,890
Harvey, we have a deal.

322
00:12:15,915 --> 00:12:17,226
I put myself on the line
for you,

323
00:12:17,251 --> 00:12:19,705
and our deal
is not going to change.

324
00:12:19,839 --> 00:12:21,518
I could just pay you
the money back and move on.

325
00:12:21,543 --> 00:12:23,523
And if you could do that,
you wouldn't be here

326
00:12:23,547 --> 00:12:24,681
asking to come back.

327
00:12:24,800 --> 00:12:27,030
How much money
did Marcus lose this time?

328
00:12:27,054 --> 00:12:29,285
He didn't lose anything.
He wants to start a restaurant.

329
00:12:29,309 --> 00:12:31,445
He doesn't want to start shit.

330
00:12:31,564 --> 00:12:32,732
He owes somebody something.

331
00:12:32,866 --> 00:12:34,902
You don't know that.
He's turned his life around.

332
00:12:35,071 --> 00:12:37,051
What I know is,
he has a problem,

333
00:12:37,075 --> 00:12:40,130
and he's looking
to get money from you.

334
00:12:40,248 --> 00:12:42,946
And you're not gonna get it
from me.

335
00:12:42,971 --> 00:12:46,259
Then I'll get it somewhere else.

336
00:12:46,395 --> 00:12:48,123
And what's that
supposed to mean?

337
00:12:48,148 --> 00:12:51,687
I got a job offer
from Charles Forstman.

338
00:12:51,823 --> 00:12:53,909
Look at me.

339
00:12:54,027 --> 00:12:55,612
I don't care
what he's offering you.

340
00:12:55,781 --> 00:12:56,614
Don't take it.

341
00:12:56,749 --> 00:12:58,311
Because he's got
a bad reputation?

342
00:12:58,336 --> 00:12:59,431
You think I don't know that?

343
00:12:59,455 --> 00:13:00,650
I think there are
a lot of things

344
00:13:00,674 --> 00:13:01,769
you think you know
that you don't.

345
00:13:01,793 --> 00:13:03,438
What I know is,
you're either gonna help me

346
00:13:03,463 --> 00:13:04,798
or Charles Forstman is.

347
00:13:04,933 --> 00:13:06,997
It's up to you.

348
00:13:07,021 --> 00:13:09,618
Harvey, I can't make you
listen to me,

349
00:13:09,643 --> 00:13:12,230
but what I'm not going to do
is let you come here

350
00:13:12,365 --> 00:13:13,960
and leverage me
with some bullshit offer

351
00:13:13,984 --> 00:13:16,789
from a shady banker,
so do what you're gonna do.

352
00:13:16,907 --> 00:13:19,044
But don't say I didn't warn you.

353
00:13:32,902 --> 00:13:35,072
You can buy all the Wonder Bread
you want, Eric,

354
00:13:35,206 --> 00:13:36,718
but you can't take it with you
to prison.

355
00:13:36,743 --> 00:13:38,044
What are you doing here?

356
00:13:38,162 --> 00:13:40,465
I'm here to remind you
that once they find the money,

357
00:13:40,584 --> 00:13:42,396
it's all gonna come
tumbling down.

358
00:13:42,421 --> 00:13:43,983
Well, they're not gonna
find the money,

359
00:13:44,007 --> 00:13:46,094
'cause there is no money.

360
00:13:46,229 --> 00:13:49,651
Not in your accounts,
but I know what Cahill doesn't.

361
00:13:49,770 --> 00:13:51,667
Forstman gave it to somebody
you care about,

362
00:13:51,691 --> 00:13:53,252
and if I tell him that,
it'll be too late.

363
00:13:53,276 --> 00:13:54,611
I know what you're trying to do.

364
00:13:54,747 --> 00:13:57,311
You're trying to bait me
into moving the body.

365
00:13:57,336 --> 00:13:59,505
We both know you're not
dumb enough to do that.

366
00:13:59,623 --> 00:14:01,102
I'm here to get you
to cut a deal

367
00:14:01,127 --> 00:14:02,355
and turn Forstman in.

368
00:14:02,379 --> 00:14:04,943
You don't have the authority
to cut a deal.

369
00:14:04,968 --> 00:14:07,973
No, but I can get Cahill to

370
00:14:08,107 --> 00:14:10,694
after you hire me
to represent you.

371
00:14:10,813 --> 00:14:14,035
You mean hire the fox
to watch the henhouse?

372
00:14:14,154 --> 00:14:15,155
Not a chance.

373
00:14:15,156 --> 00:14:17,709
Eric, they're closing in,

374
00:14:17,828 --> 00:14:20,392
and when they do,
you're gonna want to call me.

375
00:14:20,416 --> 00:14:22,986
So why don't you take my card?

376
00:14:34,028 --> 00:14:35,914
This is ridiculous.

377
00:14:36,032 --> 00:14:37,433
Woodall's got 30 people
it could be,

378
00:14:37,452 --> 00:14:38,430
or it could be none of them.

379
00:14:38,454 --> 00:14:40,540
I know that,
but this is our job.

380
00:14:40,675 --> 00:14:44,598
No, our job is to help Harvey
get Forstman.

381
00:14:44,716 --> 00:14:46,679
If you're thinking
what I think you're thinking...

382
00:14:46,704 --> 00:14:47,705
I am, and you are too.

383
00:14:47,706 --> 00:14:48,851
Rachel, we are never
gonna get Harvey

384
00:14:48,875 --> 00:14:50,917
to go after Forstman
for what they did 12 years ago.

385
00:14:50,929 --> 00:14:52,214
Why, because of his brother?

386
00:14:52,349 --> 00:14:54,930
Yes, because of his brother,
or because he's ashamed.

387
00:14:54,954 --> 00:14:56,699
Either way, he knows
it's a possibility.

388
00:14:56,724 --> 00:14:58,611
He doesn't need me
to tell him about it.

389
00:14:58,728 --> 00:15:01,199
No, he just doesn't need me
to tell him about it.

390
00:15:01,334 --> 00:15:03,237
- Rachel...
- This is not about that.

391
00:15:03,421 --> 00:15:05,625
Look, I can't tell him

392
00:15:05,743 --> 00:15:07,723
because I'm not supposed
to know, but you can.

393
00:15:07,747 --> 00:15:09,667
And I just told you,
he doesn't want to hear it.

394
00:15:09,802 --> 00:15:11,447
And when has that ever
stopped you before?

395
00:15:11,472 --> 00:15:12,784
- This is different.
- Why?

396
00:15:12,808 --> 00:15:15,846
Because he's ashamed.

397
00:15:15,981 --> 00:15:18,401
Then he's not thinking right,

398
00:15:18,520 --> 00:15:21,442
and he needs your help
more than ever.

399
00:15:23,997 --> 00:15:25,365
Then we're both telling him.

400
00:15:25,501 --> 00:15:26,813
Mike, I don't need the credit.

401
00:15:26,837 --> 00:15:29,267
No, this isn't about credit.
This is about us.

402
00:15:29,292 --> 00:15:31,962
He can't tell me something
and expect me not to tell you.

403
00:15:36,557 --> 00:15:37,619
You wanted to see me?

404
00:15:37,643 --> 00:15:39,027
Yes.
Where have you been all day?

405
00:15:39,146 --> 00:15:41,293
Why? Is there something
you want to talk about?

406
00:15:41,317 --> 00:15:42,318
Yeah, where you've been.

407
00:15:42,319 --> 00:15:43,904
Sean Cahill was at my door
last night...

408
00:15:44,039 --> 00:15:45,384
Harvey, Norma passed away.

409
00:15:45,408 --> 00:15:46,877
I've been helping Louis.

410
00:15:46,995 --> 00:15:49,059
Norma died?

411
00:15:49,083 --> 00:15:50,718
That's terrible.

412
00:15:50,836 --> 00:15:52,148
I thought
you couldn't stand her.

413
00:15:52,173 --> 00:15:55,645
I couldn't, but I assume
Louis loved her, so...

414
00:15:55,780 --> 00:15:57,064
- Do what you need to do.
- Oh.

415
00:15:57,200 --> 00:15:59,453
Because she was his secretary,
he must have loved her.

416
00:16:01,659 --> 00:16:04,056
- That's not what I meant.
- But it is what you said.

417
00:16:04,080 --> 00:16:05,749
Okay, Donna. What's wrong?

418
00:16:05,884 --> 00:16:07,202
How about we start with the fact

419
00:16:07,371 --> 00:16:09,557
that I have been wondering
for the last ten hours

420
00:16:09,692 --> 00:16:11,979
if you're going to acknowledge
what happened last night.

421
00:16:12,114 --> 00:16:13,743
But you're you,
so of course you're not.

422
00:16:13,768 --> 00:16:14,889
I'm not gonna acknowledge it

423
00:16:14,903 --> 00:16:16,382
because nothing happened
last night.

424
00:16:16,407 --> 00:16:18,553
Why?
And don't tell me I know why.

425
00:16:18,577 --> 00:16:20,699
Because it would have been
a mistake, and you know it.

426
00:16:20,715 --> 00:16:22,979
What I know is
something happened,

427
00:16:23,004 --> 00:16:25,424
and you ran away, but not before
you told me you loved me.

428
00:16:25,558 --> 00:16:29,409
I did that because I wanted
to make you feel better.

429
00:16:29,433 --> 00:16:30,984
What did you just say to me?

430
00:16:31,103 --> 00:16:32,748
That's not what I meant.
I didn't say that...

431
00:16:32,773 --> 00:16:34,168
Because you pity me?
Yeah, you did.

432
00:16:34,193 --> 00:16:36,307
No, I said it
because I love you,

433
00:16:36,331 --> 00:16:37,309
and I wanted you to know it.

434
00:16:37,333 --> 00:16:38,617
Love me how?

435
00:16:38,752 --> 00:16:41,456
- Why does that have to...
- Love me how?

436
00:16:44,180 --> 00:16:45,798
That's what I thought.

437
00:16:45,967 --> 00:16:47,585
You either can't answer
or you won't,

438
00:16:47,721 --> 00:16:49,456
which is bullshit,
because obviously,

439
00:16:49,625 --> 00:16:50,936
you don't just look at me
this way.

440
00:16:50,961 --> 00:16:52,864
You're capable of looking at me
that way,

441
00:16:52,965 --> 00:16:54,794
but you don't want to let
those worlds collide

442
00:16:54,819 --> 00:16:56,348
because you're afraid
to risk anything.

443
00:16:56,372 --> 00:16:57,473
Because we have everything.

444
00:16:57,608 --> 00:16:59,354
No, Harvey. You have everything.

445
00:16:59,379 --> 00:17:00,980
So you're saying
you want everything?

446
00:17:01,148 --> 00:17:02,883
I don't know, Harvey,

447
00:17:02,985 --> 00:17:06,708
but what I do know is
I don't want your pity.

448
00:17:09,850 --> 00:17:17,749
♪ ♪

449
00:17:22,126 --> 00:17:24,930
What are you doing here?
Nobody finds out where I live.

450
00:17:25,048 --> 00:17:26,266
I do.

451
00:17:33,482 --> 00:17:35,402
Hold on a second.
Let me turn this off.

452
00:17:35,536 --> 00:17:37,600
You got to be kidding me.
You're watching Wall Street?

453
00:17:37,624 --> 00:17:39,554
A monthly ritual
to remind myself.

454
00:17:39,579 --> 00:17:40,730
Of what?

455
00:17:40,914 --> 00:17:43,067
Of what a pussy Gordon Gekko is.

456
00:17:43,202 --> 00:17:47,103
Now, you want to tell me
what changed your mind?

457
00:17:47,128 --> 00:17:48,512
I decided I wanted the money.

458
00:17:48,630 --> 00:17:49,931
And you turned me down,

459
00:17:50,067 --> 00:17:54,307
so now you're gonna tell me
why you want the money.

460
00:17:54,425 --> 00:17:57,089
My brother needs $150,000
for a restaurant.

461
00:17:57,114 --> 00:17:59,784
Hmm.
Now we're getting somewhere.

462
00:18:01,123 --> 00:18:02,258
Let's have it.

463
00:18:02,375 --> 00:18:03,877
Okay, you want it?

464
00:18:04,012 --> 00:18:07,051
Here it is.

465
00:18:07,185 --> 00:18:11,442
It's not just a restaurant.
It's a second chance.

466
00:18:11,561 --> 00:18:14,900
Marcus has a gambling problem,

467
00:18:15,035 --> 00:18:16,180
and I gave it to him.

468
00:18:16,204 --> 00:18:17,806
Mm-hmm.

469
00:18:17,941 --> 00:18:19,978
And you think
this is his way out?

470
00:18:20,112 --> 00:18:21,039
I know it is.

471
00:18:21,064 --> 00:18:23,869
Hmm.

472
00:18:23,987 --> 00:18:25,715
We're not a good fit,

473
00:18:25,740 --> 00:18:27,519
'cause restaurants fail,

474
00:18:27,544 --> 00:18:30,192
and when this one does,
you'll leave.

475
00:18:30,217 --> 00:18:34,674
So you might as well leave
right now.

476
00:18:34,859 --> 00:18:35,971
Then how about we bet on it?

477
00:18:35,995 --> 00:18:37,363
You're gonna gamble on something

478
00:18:37,498 --> 00:18:39,579
to get your brother
out of a gambling problem?

479
00:18:39,603 --> 00:18:42,524
- I didn't say I had a problem.
- I think maybe you do.

480
00:18:42,659 --> 00:18:45,530
When you always win,
it's not a problem.

481
00:18:50,091 --> 00:18:51,292
I think I might like you, pal.

482
00:18:59,393 --> 00:19:00,394
Louis.

483
00:19:00,529 --> 00:19:01,874
I got your message.
What's going on?

484
00:19:01,899 --> 00:19:03,544
What's going on is,
they're trying to screw me,

485
00:19:03,568 --> 00:19:04,451
and I need you to be bad cop.

486
00:19:04,571 --> 00:19:05,572
What?

487
00:19:05,573 --> 00:19:06,974
Have you made a decision, sir?

488
00:19:07,076 --> 00:19:10,164
No, I haven't made a decision,
you shyster dealer of death.

489
00:19:10,300 --> 00:19:12,446
Okay, I think maybe
we're gonna need another minute.

490
00:19:12,470 --> 00:19:13,672
No, we don't.

491
00:19:13,806 --> 00:19:15,127
I don't need another minute
to see

492
00:19:15,143 --> 00:19:16,738
that this looks like a pot
from Home Depot,

493
00:19:16,763 --> 00:19:18,164
this looks like a lamp
from Motel 6,

494
00:19:18,182 --> 00:19:20,629
and this looks like
a goddamn howitzer shell.

495
00:19:20,654 --> 00:19:22,500
You are lucky that I don't take
this mockery

496
00:19:22,525 --> 00:19:24,972
of a final resting place
and shove it up your ass.

497
00:19:24,996 --> 00:19:26,831
- Louis, that's enough.
- No, it's not enough.

498
00:19:26,951 --> 00:19:28,837
I've been handling this bullshit
for two days

499
00:19:28,955 --> 00:19:31,208
for a woman who's supposed to be
handling things for me.

500
00:19:31,343 --> 00:19:32,521
Louis, this isn't about the urn.

501
00:19:32,545 --> 00:19:34,441
Oh, please don't give me
that touchy-feely shit.

502
00:19:34,466 --> 00:19:35,745
And why the hell
are you not being bad cop?

503
00:19:35,769 --> 00:19:37,114
Because that's not
what's needed.

504
00:19:37,138 --> 00:19:38,700
Oh, bullshit
it's not what's needed.

505
00:19:38,725 --> 00:19:40,203
- Louis.
- You don't care about me.

506
00:19:40,228 --> 00:19:41,696
You never cared about me.

507
00:19:41,814 --> 00:19:44,151
All you care about
is yourself...

508
00:19:44,286 --> 00:19:47,185
and your stupid sister
and your Hummel figurines

509
00:19:47,209 --> 00:19:48,827
and your Murder, She Wrote
reruns.

510
00:19:48,962 --> 00:19:50,497
Louis, I'm not Norma.

511
00:19:52,670 --> 00:19:54,840
She's gone...

512
00:19:55,009 --> 00:19:56,010
and it's gonna be okay.

513
00:19:56,144 --> 00:19:58,014
She was a battle-ax!

514
00:20:04,027 --> 00:20:08,201
But she was my battle-ax.

515
00:20:08,369 --> 00:20:10,923
I know. I know.

516
00:20:11,042 --> 00:20:12,928
Oh, she didn't just leave me
high and dry.

517
00:20:13,046 --> 00:20:14,547
She left me for good.

518
00:20:14,683 --> 00:20:16,351
I'm so sorry.

519
00:20:16,470 --> 00:20:18,556
It's okay.

520
00:20:21,062 --> 00:20:22,707
Both of you?

521
00:20:22,732 --> 00:20:23,927
We both work for you.

522
00:20:23,952 --> 00:20:25,380
Which is why we're both here
to say

523
00:20:25,404 --> 00:20:28,637
maybe it's time
we explore other options.

524
00:20:28,662 --> 00:20:29,663
You got to be kidding me.

525
00:20:29,664 --> 00:20:30,692
You spent two days on this,

526
00:20:30,716 --> 00:20:32,237
and you're ready
to throw in the towel?

527
00:20:32,252 --> 00:20:33,730
We've spent two
of our five days on it,

528
00:20:33,755 --> 00:20:34,900
and we still don't have a name,

529
00:20:34,924 --> 00:20:36,927
so we think
it's time to consider...

530
00:20:37,062 --> 00:20:38,074
What?

531
00:20:38,098 --> 00:20:39,933
Going after Forstman

532
00:20:40,102 --> 00:20:41,663
for whatever he did to you
12 years ago.

533
00:20:43,776 --> 00:20:45,088
- You told her?
- Yes, I did.

534
00:20:45,112 --> 00:20:47,031
Because like I said,
we both work for you.

535
00:20:47,166 --> 00:20:48,511
Which means
we both want to help.

536
00:20:48,536 --> 00:20:50,618
You think I haven't wondered
how to go after Forstman

537
00:20:50,623 --> 00:20:51,944
100 times
in the last dozen years?

538
00:20:51,960 --> 00:20:52,961
Then why don't you?

539
00:20:53,095 --> 00:20:54,536
Because I'm not the only one
at risk.

540
00:20:54,548 --> 00:20:57,185
You mean your brother.

541
00:20:57,304 --> 00:20:58,499
Yes, I do.

542
00:20:58,524 --> 00:20:59,952
And I'm not gonna bring him
into this,

543
00:20:59,976 --> 00:21:01,454
because he didn't do
anything wrong.

544
00:21:01,479 --> 00:21:03,041
Harvey, I'm not saying...

545
00:21:03,065 --> 00:21:05,129
Did you hear me?

546
00:21:05,154 --> 00:21:06,799
He doesn't just have a gun
to my head, okay?

547
00:21:06,823 --> 00:21:07,968
He's got one to my brother's.

548
00:21:07,993 --> 00:21:09,305
And how many times
have you told me

549
00:21:09,329 --> 00:21:10,857
that when someone has
a gun to your head,

550
00:21:10,882 --> 00:21:11,809
you figure a different way out?

551
00:21:11,834 --> 00:21:13,569
This is Charles Forstman.

552
00:21:13,671 --> 00:21:15,500
- There is no other way out.
- Harvey, there's...

553
00:21:15,525 --> 00:21:17,678
I gave you a job to do.
Now do your goddamn job.

554
00:21:28,964 --> 00:21:29,965
Well, that was a bust.

555
00:21:29,966 --> 00:21:31,346
- We had to try.
- Did we?

556
00:21:31,348 --> 00:21:32,610
I told you he'd be pissed off,
and he was.

557
00:21:32,634 --> 00:21:34,112
Yeah, and you also told me
he needed to hear things

558
00:21:34,137 --> 00:21:35,021
that he didn't want to hear.

559
00:21:35,139 --> 00:21:36,501
Okay, well, now all he heard is,

560
00:21:36,525 --> 00:21:38,539
not only can't he trust me,
he can't trust you either.

561
00:21:38,563 --> 00:21:40,124
That's not what he heard,
and you know it.

562
00:21:40,149 --> 00:21:42,046
What he heard was that
you're the closest person

563
00:21:42,070 --> 00:21:43,071
in the world to me,

564
00:21:43,072 --> 00:21:44,517
I am never gonna
keep things from you,

565
00:21:44,542 --> 00:21:46,221
and I'm not the only one
in his corner.

566
00:21:46,246 --> 00:21:48,249
I'm the closest person
in the world to you.

567
00:21:48,383 --> 00:21:49,361
Of course you are.
How can you even...

568
00:21:49,385 --> 00:21:50,480
I'm not questioning it.

569
00:21:50,504 --> 00:21:53,235
I'm the closest person
in the world to you,

570
00:21:53,260 --> 00:21:56,348
and I wouldn't be
on your family tree.

571
00:21:56,484 --> 00:21:57,411
You're talking about Woodall.

572
00:21:57,436 --> 00:21:58,687
Yes, I'm talking about Woodall.

573
00:21:58,855 --> 00:22:00,567
Woodall's married.
We checked his wife. Nothing.

574
00:22:00,592 --> 00:22:02,027
That's the thing.
We're not married.

575
00:22:02,195 --> 00:22:03,641
Okay, I really don't think this
is the time to bring that up.

576
00:22:03,665 --> 00:22:04,916
I'm being serious.

577
00:22:05,035 --> 00:22:06,513
We've exhausted every person
that's related to him.

578
00:22:06,537 --> 00:22:09,174
Maybe it's time
we found someone who isn't.

579
00:22:12,049 --> 00:22:13,935
- That's genius.
- Thank you.

580
00:22:14,053 --> 00:22:17,475
Now I really don't understand
why Harvey doesn't respect you.

581
00:22:17,610 --> 00:22:18,622
It's too soon.

582
00:22:18,646 --> 00:22:21,450
It's too soon for that joke.

583
00:22:21,568 --> 00:22:22,953
Too soon.

584
00:22:26,244 --> 00:22:29,060
I can have any one?

585
00:22:29,084 --> 00:22:30,612
Take your pick.

586
00:22:30,637 --> 00:22:32,422
It doesn't matter,
'cause you're gonna lose.

587
00:22:32,591 --> 00:22:33,653
That's funny.

588
00:22:33,677 --> 00:22:35,455
I look at it like
I'm gonna win twice.

589
00:22:35,480 --> 00:22:38,663
I get to drive a badass car,
and I get to kick your ass.

590
00:22:38,688 --> 00:22:40,489
Cocky. I like that.

591
00:22:40,608 --> 00:22:42,387
A guy like you,
I'm surprised you could stand

592
00:22:42,412 --> 00:22:44,532
working for Cameron Dennis
in the first place.

593
00:22:44,666 --> 00:22:46,428
- What do you mean?
- He doesn't like cocky.

594
00:22:46,453 --> 00:22:48,673
Take, for instance,
what's-his-name... DuPont?

595
00:22:48,792 --> 00:22:50,310
What's he up for? Tax evasion?

596
00:22:50,461 --> 00:22:51,873
- Insider trading.
- Yeah, whatever.

597
00:22:51,898 --> 00:22:54,797
The point is, after
what you did the other day,

598
00:22:54,821 --> 00:22:56,139
why aren't you leading that?

599
00:22:56,291 --> 00:22:57,502
Because this is Cameron's case.

600
00:22:57,526 --> 00:23:00,147
If I were him, it'd be yours.

601
00:23:00,249 --> 00:23:02,886
Harvey, you are his star player,

602
00:23:02,988 --> 00:23:05,158
and he's not even putting you
in the game.

603
00:23:05,309 --> 00:23:07,161
And on top of that,
he didn't have the balls

604
00:23:07,313 --> 00:23:09,716
to announce whether
he's going after DuPont or not.

605
00:23:09,852 --> 00:23:11,293
Don't you worry
about Cameron Dennis.

606
00:23:11,405 --> 00:23:15,723
DuPont's gonna get
what's coming to him.

607
00:23:15,747 --> 00:23:17,499
That's exactly what
I wanted to hear.

608
00:23:17,617 --> 00:23:20,065
What are you talking about?

609
00:23:20,090 --> 00:23:21,234
Well, you're loyal to the guy
you work for.

610
00:23:21,258 --> 00:23:23,211
I like that.

611
00:23:23,347 --> 00:23:24,868
So you were just
talking shit about him

612
00:23:24,883 --> 00:23:25,944
to see if I'd jump on board?

613
00:23:25,968 --> 00:23:28,783
And you didn't...

614
00:23:28,807 --> 00:23:31,706
which is why
we don't have to race anymore.

615
00:23:31,731 --> 00:23:32,792
You're saying I got the job?

616
00:23:32,816 --> 00:23:35,888
I'm saying welcome to the team.

617
00:23:36,022 --> 00:23:37,774
Well, that's all
well and good, Charles,

618
00:23:37,893 --> 00:23:39,622
but we're still racing.

619
00:23:39,647 --> 00:23:40,781
We sure as hell are.

620
00:23:40,899 --> 00:23:42,985
We just have to find
something else to bet on.

621
00:23:45,242 --> 00:23:46,320
Hey, Sean. Good to see you.

622
00:23:46,344 --> 00:23:47,545
Don't give me that shit.

623
00:23:47,680 --> 00:23:49,583
Did you confront Eric Woodall
yesterday morning

624
00:23:49,768 --> 00:23:50,584
at his supermarket?

625
00:23:50,736 --> 00:23:52,298
I ran into him by accident.

626
00:23:52,323 --> 00:23:53,591
I like the produce there.

627
00:23:53,742 --> 00:23:55,238
I'm not in the mood, Harvey.

628
00:23:55,263 --> 00:23:58,078
Did you approach the subject
of an SEC investigation

629
00:23:58,102 --> 00:24:00,799
with the express purpose
of intimidating him?

630
00:24:00,824 --> 00:24:02,827
I approached him
with the express purpose

631
00:24:02,945 --> 00:24:04,140
of hiring me as his lawyer.

632
00:24:04,164 --> 00:24:05,365
Why the hell would you do that?

633
00:24:05,367 --> 00:24:06,648
You're supposed to be
helping me.

634
00:24:06,669 --> 00:24:08,338
And if he's willing to
admit what he did,

635
00:24:08,456 --> 00:24:09,457
that is helping you.

636
00:24:09,458 --> 00:24:10,699
And instead, he's claiming that

637
00:24:10,761 --> 00:24:12,462
I sent you there
to intimidate him.

638
00:24:12,598 --> 00:24:14,277
Then I guess
that's the way it's breaking.

639
00:24:14,302 --> 00:24:15,663
What the hell
are you talking about?

640
00:24:15,688 --> 00:24:17,200
He's either gonna buy
what I'm selling

641
00:24:17,224 --> 00:24:18,536
or cover his tracks.

642
00:24:18,561 --> 00:24:21,482
And if he covers his tracks,
you need to be there.

643
00:24:21,617 --> 00:24:23,035
Are you asking me to follow him?

644
00:24:23,154 --> 00:24:24,883
No, I'm telling you
to follow him.

645
00:24:24,907 --> 00:24:26,708
I can't do that.
I don't have authorization.

646
00:24:26,828 --> 00:24:28,380
Didn't stop you following me.

647
00:24:28,497 --> 00:24:30,299
Enough.

648
00:24:30,418 --> 00:24:33,256
He's filing charges
of harassment against me.

649
00:24:33,392 --> 00:24:34,843
We do this, nothing sticks.

650
00:24:34,978 --> 00:24:37,181
Then we might not get him,
because I have nothing.

651
00:24:37,350 --> 00:24:39,232
Well, let me give you
a little extra motivation.

652
00:24:39,237 --> 00:24:40,855
Remember,
Woodall knows all about

653
00:24:40,991 --> 00:24:43,027
Louis Litt's
little Forstman transgression.

654
00:24:43,161 --> 00:24:45,415
So if he gets exonerated,

655
00:24:45,533 --> 00:24:48,622
who do you think's gonna be
the first person he goes after?

656
00:24:48,756 --> 00:24:50,793
So, instead of going to Jersey
for your produce,

657
00:24:50,927 --> 00:24:52,462
go get me something I can use.

658
00:25:05,741 --> 00:25:07,553
You're having a drink
by yourself?

659
00:25:07,578 --> 00:25:09,748
What's going on?

660
00:25:09,884 --> 00:25:11,218
What's going on is,

661
00:25:11,336 --> 00:25:16,429
I just finished having them
scrape Jeff's name off his door.

662
00:25:16,564 --> 00:25:18,486
So why don't you tell me
why you're here, Harvey?

663
00:25:18,601 --> 00:25:20,320
Cahill's having trouble
getting evidence

664
00:25:20,439 --> 00:25:21,667
against Forstman and Woodall.

665
00:25:21,691 --> 00:25:22,969
I'm aware of that.

666
00:25:22,994 --> 00:25:25,258
Then you should also be aware
that if Woodall keeps his job,

667
00:25:25,282 --> 00:25:26,583
he's likely to go after Louis.

668
00:25:26,702 --> 00:25:29,005
I could've done that math,
and so could you, so...

669
00:25:29,123 --> 00:25:33,047
I might be able to
help them get Forstman...

670
00:25:33,182 --> 00:25:35,519
on something else.

671
00:25:35,636 --> 00:25:37,115
Does this have something to do

672
00:25:37,140 --> 00:25:39,477
with when he offered you
that job 12 years ago?

673
00:25:39,611 --> 00:25:42,008
Yes.

674
00:25:44,204 --> 00:25:45,516
I told you that man was trouble.

675
00:25:45,541 --> 00:25:47,961
And I told you
I wouldn't abandon Marcus

676
00:25:48,079 --> 00:25:50,332
and you were wrong about him.

677
00:25:50,467 --> 00:25:52,052
So this has something to do
with Marcus.

678
00:25:52,171 --> 00:25:55,726
Yes, it does.

679
00:25:55,845 --> 00:25:58,733
Well, if you are asking me
to choose

680
00:25:58,851 --> 00:26:01,321
between your brother and Louis,
you know who I'm choosing.

681
00:26:01,440 --> 00:26:03,052
I'm not asking you to do that.

682
00:26:03,077 --> 00:26:04,089
Then what are you asking?

683
00:26:04,113 --> 00:26:07,930
I want your help
to get my mind right.

684
00:26:07,954 --> 00:26:11,938
Here's the thing, Harvey.

685
00:26:11,962 --> 00:26:14,777
Jeff's gone,

686
00:26:14,801 --> 00:26:17,722
and he's gone
because of the choices I made.

687
00:26:20,062 --> 00:26:23,128
So I'm not sure if I can
help you get your mind right,

688
00:26:23,152 --> 00:26:25,449
'cause right now...

689
00:26:25,474 --> 00:26:27,593
mine's not right.

690
00:26:33,006 --> 00:26:36,261
Hang on a sec.

691
00:26:36,395 --> 00:26:37,396
Hey.

692
00:26:37,397 --> 00:26:39,744
Hey.

693
00:26:39,769 --> 00:26:42,250
You didn't come down here
just to give me my start date.

694
00:26:42,274 --> 00:26:43,492
I came down here to tell you

695
00:26:43,611 --> 00:26:44,972
I think
you have something special,

696
00:26:45,114 --> 00:26:47,144
and I'd love nothing more
than to have you on my desk,

697
00:26:47,168 --> 00:26:50,517
but I'm leaving the DA's office.

698
00:26:50,541 --> 00:26:52,623
Does this have something to do
with that Forstman guy

699
00:26:52,630 --> 00:26:54,025
buying you a drink
the other night?

700
00:26:54,049 --> 00:26:55,694
I thought you didn't know
who he was.

701
00:26:55,719 --> 00:26:56,880
Well, I looked him up

702
00:26:56,888 --> 00:26:59,502
because I thought
I was gonna be working for you.

703
00:26:59,527 --> 00:27:01,697
And I'm telling you, he's shady.

704
00:27:01,814 --> 00:27:03,176
Because he's got
a bad reputation?

705
00:27:03,201 --> 00:27:06,373
I don't care
what his reputation is.

706
00:27:06,491 --> 00:27:09,713
You don't know this about me
yet, but I know people...

707
00:27:09,831 --> 00:27:11,527
usually better
than they know themselves.

708
00:27:11,552 --> 00:27:14,557
And the same way
I know you are a good person,

709
00:27:14,675 --> 00:27:16,811
I can tell you that man
is rotten to the core.

710
00:27:16,930 --> 00:27:18,331
You're just trying
to get me to stay

711
00:27:18,349 --> 00:27:19,430
so you can work at my desk.

712
00:27:20,353 --> 00:27:22,165
Listen to me.

713
00:27:22,190 --> 00:27:25,172
I don't care whether
I work on your desk or not.

714
00:27:25,196 --> 00:27:27,343
You're making a mistake
if you take a job with that man.

715
00:27:27,368 --> 00:27:28,730
Then I guess
I'm making a mistake,

716
00:27:28,754 --> 00:27:30,623
because I already did.

717
00:27:30,758 --> 00:27:33,428
It was nice knowing you, Donna.

718
00:27:40,895 --> 00:27:42,782
So you're keeping her here
after all.

719
00:27:46,407 --> 00:27:47,885
Yeah, I couldn't throw her
off the roof

720
00:27:47,910 --> 00:27:48,972
after you got me to cry.

721
00:27:48,996 --> 00:27:50,464
I'm glad.

722
00:27:50,583 --> 00:27:51,894
Donna, I can't thank you enough
for what you did.

723
00:27:51,918 --> 00:27:54,984
Oh, you're welcome, Louis.

724
00:27:55,008 --> 00:27:58,730
The truth is, I needed this
more than you know.

725
00:27:58,849 --> 00:28:00,494
Well, I get it.

726
00:28:00,519 --> 00:28:01,581
You needed a distraction

727
00:28:01,605 --> 00:28:03,968
after everything
you just went through.

728
00:28:03,993 --> 00:28:06,497
Uh, yeah. Something like that.

729
00:28:06,616 --> 00:28:08,952
Truth is,

730
00:28:09,120 --> 00:28:11,290
I could use a distraction
myself.

731
00:28:11,426 --> 00:28:13,322
Well, there is one thing
that you still need to do.

732
00:28:13,346 --> 00:28:17,437
You need to start thinking
about a new secretary.

733
00:28:17,554 --> 00:28:21,003
Donna, I know
I've asked you this before,

734
00:28:21,028 --> 00:28:23,198
but we're so much closer now
than we were then, and...

735
00:28:23,317 --> 00:28:25,012
Louis, I work for Harvey.

736
00:28:25,036 --> 00:28:26,548
You know
I can't be your secretary.

737
00:28:26,573 --> 00:28:30,858
But we have this bond...

738
00:28:30,883 --> 00:28:32,551
you and I.

739
00:28:32,670 --> 00:28:35,223
Shakespeare, the gun club.

740
00:28:35,342 --> 00:28:37,504
We've always spoken the same
language, and you know it.

741
00:28:37,513 --> 00:28:38,848
Louis, I can't.

742
00:28:38,982 --> 00:28:40,484
I get it.

743
00:28:43,910 --> 00:28:45,077
We're better as friends.

744
00:28:45,195 --> 00:28:47,916
Hey.

745
00:28:48,034 --> 00:28:50,956
How about I set up
a little farewell for Norma

746
00:28:51,090 --> 00:28:54,212
as my last official act
as your interim secretary?

747
00:28:57,554 --> 00:28:58,722
Thank you, Donna.

748
00:29:11,685 --> 00:29:12,913
Are you sure
we've got the right address?

749
00:29:12,938 --> 00:29:14,273
I'm positive.

750
00:29:14,407 --> 00:29:15,448
I'll be right back.

751
00:29:15,827 --> 00:29:17,078
Can I help you?

752
00:29:17,196 --> 00:29:19,646
Uh, yes, is there
a Mary Ann McGrath here?

753
00:29:19,648 --> 00:29:20,815
Who can I say is asking?

754
00:29:20,933 --> 00:29:22,244
We're with Pearson Specter Litt.

755
00:29:22,269 --> 00:29:24,500
We'd like to speak with her
in regards to an ongoing case.

756
00:29:24,524 --> 00:29:26,002
I'm afraid
that won't be possible.

757
00:29:26,027 --> 00:29:28,091
You just said she was here.
I don't understand...

758
00:29:28,115 --> 00:29:30,034
Mary Ann has
advanced Alzheimer's.

759
00:29:30,169 --> 00:29:31,620
But she's 55.

760
00:29:31,756 --> 00:29:34,627
It's early onset, and hers is
particularly aggressive.

761
00:29:34,762 --> 00:29:35,773
I'm sorry.

762
00:29:35,797 --> 00:29:36,942
Can I ask how long
she's been a patient?

763
00:29:36,966 --> 00:29:38,367
We're not supposed to
disclose any...

764
00:29:38,386 --> 00:29:41,391
Please. It's really important.

765
00:29:41,525 --> 00:29:43,371
She was moved her
about a year and a half ago.

766
00:29:43,396 --> 00:29:44,397
And before that?

767
00:29:44,398 --> 00:29:46,233
I don't really know,

768
00:29:46,370 --> 00:29:48,823
but I don't think
she was getting the best care.

769
00:29:48,991 --> 00:29:51,661
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.

770
00:29:58,678 --> 00:30:02,495
My mother's 55.

771
00:30:02,519 --> 00:30:04,966
You know, and if she's only here
because Forstman pays for it...

772
00:30:04,990 --> 00:30:05,991
I know.

773
00:30:05,993 --> 00:30:07,245
Harvey wants us to find

774
00:30:07,362 --> 00:30:08,724
the person Woodall's close to.

775
00:30:08,749 --> 00:30:09,761
That's all we can do.

776
00:30:09,785 --> 00:30:10,919
Well, "all we can do"

777
00:30:11,037 --> 00:30:12,983
is gonna send her back
to some horrible facility.

778
00:30:13,007 --> 00:30:14,688
- We don't exactly know that.
- Yes, we do.

779
00:30:14,711 --> 00:30:18,383
Rachel, it's terrible.

780
00:30:18,519 --> 00:30:19,864
I don't like it
any more than you do,

781
00:30:19,888 --> 00:30:22,085
but it's not up to us.

782
00:30:22,110 --> 00:30:24,925
I know.

783
00:30:24,949 --> 00:30:28,404
It just sucks.

784
00:30:28,540 --> 00:30:31,388
You goddamn liar.

785
00:30:31,412 --> 00:30:33,392
Oh, don't be mad.

786
00:30:33,416 --> 00:30:35,586
Yeah, Conchita tells everybody
I'm not home.

787
00:30:35,754 --> 00:30:37,172
You know what I'm talking about.

788
00:30:37,308 --> 00:30:39,311
DuPont Investments
dropped through the floor today,

789
00:30:39,428 --> 00:30:40,596
and you sold short

790
00:30:40,732 --> 00:30:43,412
based on something
that I told you in confidence.

791
00:30:43,437 --> 00:30:45,407
I don't recall you telling me
anything at all.

792
00:30:45,525 --> 00:30:46,526
You son of a bitch.

793
00:30:46,660 --> 00:30:48,339
You made over $100 million
on that trade.

794
00:30:48,364 --> 00:30:49,832
Yeah, I did.

795
00:30:49,951 --> 00:30:51,619
Welcome to the real world, pal.

796
00:30:51,755 --> 00:30:54,258
My real world doesn't involve
befriending young attorneys

797
00:30:54,376 --> 00:30:55,844
to get inside information.

798
00:30:55,963 --> 00:30:58,300
Maybe you're not the right man
for me after all.

799
00:30:58,435 --> 00:31:00,281
You think I still want
to work for you after this?

800
00:31:00,306 --> 00:31:01,951
You wanted competition
and money.

801
00:31:01,975 --> 00:31:04,874
You got the competition.

802
00:31:04,899 --> 00:31:05,983
Here's your money.

803
00:31:06,117 --> 00:31:08,181
You can shove that $1 million
up your ass,

804
00:31:08,205 --> 00:31:10,385
because I'm not only
not taking your job,

805
00:31:10,410 --> 00:31:11,545
I'm gonna prosecute you.

806
00:31:11,662 --> 00:31:13,784
Then you might as well
add your name to the indictment

807
00:31:13,800 --> 00:31:15,836
since you've already
shared in the profits.

808
00:31:16,005 --> 00:31:17,400
What are you talking about?

809
00:31:17,424 --> 00:31:18,903
Take a look at this check.

810
00:31:18,928 --> 00:31:20,729
It's not $1 million.

811
00:31:20,848 --> 00:31:23,518
It's 850,000.

812
00:31:23,654 --> 00:31:26,358
Bet you can guess where
the other $150,000 went.

813
00:31:26,493 --> 00:31:27,494
What did you do?

814
00:31:27,495 --> 00:31:30,226
You know what I did.

815
00:31:30,251 --> 00:31:32,036
Marcus had nothing to do
with this.

816
00:31:32,171 --> 00:31:34,268
He wouldn't have had you said
yes right away.

817
00:31:34,292 --> 00:31:35,320
But you didn't.

818
00:31:35,344 --> 00:31:37,190
We're giving you the money back.

819
00:31:37,215 --> 00:31:39,050
You're gonna break
his little heart.

820
00:31:39,185 --> 00:31:41,082
He thinks that money
came from you.

821
00:31:41,106 --> 00:31:44,395
And you snatch cash out
of an addicted gambler's hands,

822
00:31:44,530 --> 00:31:46,042
take away his dream,

823
00:31:46,067 --> 00:31:47,879
only one way that story ends.

824
00:31:47,904 --> 00:31:50,792
So you can either
pout about it...

825
00:31:50,910 --> 00:31:53,976
or you can embrace it and
prove to everyone I was right

826
00:31:54,000 --> 00:31:57,138
when I said I saw
something special in you.

827
00:31:57,257 --> 00:32:00,155
Someday the shoe's gonna be
on the other foot, Charles.

828
00:32:00,179 --> 00:32:02,910
Words spoken by every loser
I've ever met.

829
00:32:02,935 --> 00:32:05,072
See you around, pal.

830
00:32:13,340 --> 00:32:15,654
It's Woodall's first wife.

831
00:32:15,678 --> 00:32:17,513
Her name's Mary Ann.
They grew up together.

832
00:32:17,631 --> 00:32:19,634
They got married
when they were 21

833
00:32:19,803 --> 00:32:21,282
and had it annulled
six months later.

834
00:32:21,306 --> 00:32:23,192
And what's the money for?

835
00:32:23,311 --> 00:32:25,146
- She has Alzheimer's.
- Don't tell me.

836
00:32:25,281 --> 00:32:26,642
He moved her
to a high-end facility

837
00:32:26,650 --> 00:32:27,985
and pays
for round-the-clock care.

838
00:32:28,154 --> 00:32:29,683
And the problem is,
we called the company

839
00:32:29,707 --> 00:32:30,908
that handles the billing, and...

840
00:32:30,910 --> 00:32:32,305
And everything's in cash
up front,

841
00:32:32,329 --> 00:32:33,914
probably paid five years
in advance.

842
00:32:34,049 --> 00:32:37,054
And Mary Ann couldn't tell you
because she doesn't speak.

843
00:32:37,172 --> 00:32:41,229
Which mean we don't have
any proof.

844
00:32:41,348 --> 00:32:42,349
Where are you going?

845
00:32:42,517 --> 00:32:45,270
I'm gonna go get us some proof.

846
00:32:45,406 --> 00:32:46,417
You did this?

847
00:32:46,441 --> 00:32:47,526
Mike and I both did.

848
00:32:47,661 --> 00:32:49,056
Then why isn't he here?

849
00:32:49,080 --> 00:32:50,281
You know why.

850
00:32:50,417 --> 00:32:53,004
Because it was more you
than him.

851
00:32:53,122 --> 00:32:54,203
You did a good job, Rachel.

852
00:32:57,631 --> 00:33:01,749
Shopping, renting videos.

853
00:33:01,774 --> 00:33:04,227
You must be going stir-crazy.

854
00:33:04,361 --> 00:33:06,030
That's all right.

855
00:33:06,149 --> 00:33:08,879
My suspension
is about to expire.

856
00:33:08,904 --> 00:33:10,385
Yeah, I wouldn't count on it.

857
00:33:10,491 --> 00:33:11,742
We found Mary Ann.

858
00:33:11,911 --> 00:33:13,831
I'm told she's doing well
at the new facility...

859
00:33:13,965 --> 00:33:15,835
You know,
the one Forstman's paying for.

860
00:33:19,059 --> 00:33:22,347
You son of a bitch.

861
00:33:22,483 --> 00:33:24,413
I'm not here to exploit
your tragedy, Eric.

862
00:33:24,437 --> 00:33:25,799
I'm here to tell you it's over.

863
00:33:25,823 --> 00:33:26,857
Well, if this were over,

864
00:33:26,992 --> 00:33:29,162
you'd be with Sean Cahill
right now,

865
00:33:29,280 --> 00:33:31,310
which means you're still looking
for me to cut a deal.

866
00:33:31,334 --> 00:33:33,119
I'm looking for you
to turn on Forstman.

867
00:33:33,288 --> 00:33:35,208
You accost me
for the second time

868
00:33:35,343 --> 00:33:37,847
in three days
and throw Mary Ann's name around

869
00:33:37,964 --> 00:33:39,799
like a bargaining chip,

870
00:33:39,936 --> 00:33:41,771
and you think
I'm gonna help you?

871
00:33:41,890 --> 00:33:42,891
Drop dead.

872
00:33:46,065 --> 00:33:48,201
Eric, please.

873
00:33:48,320 --> 00:33:50,517
The reason I knew to look
for someone that you cared about

874
00:33:50,541 --> 00:33:51,886
was that Forstman did
the same thing to me.

875
00:33:51,910 --> 00:33:54,859
He finds your weakness
and presses down

876
00:33:54,884 --> 00:33:57,053
until you don't have
the will to stand up to him.

877
00:33:57,171 --> 00:34:00,143
With you, it was an ex-wife
with Alzheimer's.

878
00:34:00,261 --> 00:34:02,981
With me...

879
00:34:03,100 --> 00:34:06,021
it was a little brother
addicted to gambling.

880
00:34:06,157 --> 00:34:08,170
I don't care.

881
00:34:08,194 --> 00:34:09,579
You don't have proof,

882
00:34:09,697 --> 00:34:11,677
and you're not gonna get it
in the next 24 hours.

883
00:34:11,702 --> 00:34:12,730
You're right. I don't.

884
00:34:12,754 --> 00:34:14,539
But here's the thing.

885
00:34:14,708 --> 00:34:17,546
Cahill may have a deadline,
but I don't,

886
00:34:17,680 --> 00:34:19,215
and I don't care
how long it takes,

887
00:34:19,351 --> 00:34:20,852
because I'm gonna find
that proof

888
00:34:20,970 --> 00:34:22,388
if you don't turn on Forstman.

889
00:34:37,902 --> 00:34:39,063
A lot of you don't know this,

890
00:34:39,131 --> 00:34:42,303
but the truth is, I hated Norma.

891
00:34:42,472 --> 00:34:45,142
I hated her clogs,

892
00:34:45,278 --> 00:34:47,147
her mustache,

893
00:34:47,282 --> 00:34:49,902
her stupid seasonal sweaters.

894
00:34:50,037 --> 00:34:52,909
But the thing
I hated most about her

895
00:34:53,043 --> 00:34:54,829
was her favorite story

896
00:34:54,964 --> 00:34:58,838
about how Abe Vigoda asked her
to marry him in 1975.

897
00:34:59,005 --> 00:35:00,223
I mean, we get it.

898
00:35:00,342 --> 00:35:01,727
You were hot.

899
00:35:01,845 --> 00:35:02,929
You turned him down,

900
00:35:03,064 --> 00:35:04,900
and it was the biggest regret
of your life.

901
00:35:05,018 --> 00:35:07,322
And like everything
you ever said,

902
00:35:07,439 --> 00:35:09,493
I couldn't stand it at the time.

903
00:35:09,611 --> 00:35:12,950
But now that you're gone,

904
00:35:13,084 --> 00:35:16,456
I understand what you meant.

905
00:35:16,592 --> 00:35:20,549
Don't let the moment pass.

906
00:35:20,717 --> 00:35:22,519
Don't let the people you love
walk by you

907
00:35:22,638 --> 00:35:25,192
without letting them know
how you feel about them,

908
00:35:25,310 --> 00:35:28,565
because life slips by,
and then it's over.

909
00:35:28,700 --> 00:35:30,964
And I'm not gonna let
another minute pass me by

910
00:35:30,988 --> 00:35:34,243
without letting you know
how much you mean to me.

911
00:35:38,337 --> 00:35:40,723
I love you, Norma.

912
00:35:46,103 --> 00:35:48,300
Thank you, Louis.

913
00:35:48,324 --> 00:35:50,109
That was a lovely ceremony.

914
00:36:06,144 --> 00:36:08,114
That was beautiful, Louis.

915
00:36:08,232 --> 00:36:09,633
I couldn't have done it
without you.

916
00:36:09,652 --> 00:36:11,822
- Oh, that's not true.
- Yeah, it is.

917
00:36:11,956 --> 00:36:15,890
I couldn't even see how I felt
without you showing me.

918
00:36:15,915 --> 00:36:16,916
And the truth is, Donna,

919
00:36:17,051 --> 00:36:21,068
you know me better
than I know myself.

920
00:36:21,092 --> 00:36:25,984
Like I said, Harvey has no idea

921
00:36:26,102 --> 00:36:27,654
how lucky he is to have you.

922
00:36:30,778 --> 00:36:38,677
♪ ♪

923
00:36:56,047 --> 00:37:03,929
♪ ♪

924
00:37:16,423 --> 00:37:17,735
Looking for the money

925
00:37:17,760 --> 00:37:19,128
I supposedly gave Eric Woodall?

926
00:37:19,262 --> 00:37:22,968
You want to save me the trouble
and just admit what you did?

927
00:37:23,137 --> 00:37:24,865
Now, where would be the fun
in that?

928
00:37:24,890 --> 00:37:27,527
Fine. Keep playing your games,

929
00:37:27,646 --> 00:37:28,927
but this time,
you're gonna lose.

930
00:37:29,033 --> 00:37:31,203
Why, because you think
you convinced Woodall

931
00:37:31,320 --> 00:37:34,051
to give me up?

932
00:37:34,076 --> 00:37:35,878
Yeah, he came to see me.

933
00:37:35,997 --> 00:37:37,692
Said you tried to get him
to turn me in.

934
00:37:37,717 --> 00:37:40,732
What I said was,
you're an arrogant bastard

935
00:37:40,756 --> 00:37:43,728
who's spent his life
manipulating people.

936
00:37:43,847 --> 00:37:47,580
And you're the loser who
only cares about competition.

937
00:37:48,607 --> 00:37:50,025
Not my fault you can't beat me.

938
00:37:50,159 --> 00:37:51,588
I can this time.

939
00:37:51,613 --> 00:37:55,419
Oh, I don't think so, pal,
because...

940
00:37:55,537 --> 00:37:58,258
he turns on me, I turn on you.

941
00:37:58,376 --> 00:38:00,523
If you're talking about
12 years ago, let me remind you.

942
00:38:00,548 --> 00:38:01,693
We were both part of that deal.

943
00:38:01,717 --> 00:38:03,269
Yes, we were.

944
00:38:03,387 --> 00:38:06,226
All three of us were...
You, me, and your brother.

945
00:38:06,360 --> 00:38:07,641
You leave my brother
out of this.

946
00:38:07,646 --> 00:38:08,780
Not a chance.

947
00:38:08,898 --> 00:38:11,128
And you don't leave
this Woodall thing alone,

948
00:38:11,153 --> 00:38:13,073
by the time I'm done,

949
00:38:13,207 --> 00:38:15,271
all anybody will know
about 12 years ago

950
00:38:15,295 --> 00:38:16,462
is you gave me a tip

951
00:38:16,581 --> 00:38:18,885
and made sure your little
brother profited from it.

952
00:38:19,002 --> 00:38:20,889
I didn't give you shit.

953
00:38:21,006 --> 00:38:23,310
You tricked me into giving you
inside information

954
00:38:23,428 --> 00:38:24,730
and then blackmailed me

955
00:38:24,848 --> 00:38:27,319
by giving Marcus money
he didn't even know was dirty.

956
00:38:27,436 --> 00:38:29,667
That may be the truth,

957
00:38:29,692 --> 00:38:33,114
but they're never gonna
hear it from me.

958
00:38:33,283 --> 00:38:36,788
I'm afraid they just did.

959
00:38:36,923 --> 00:38:37,924
Hi, Charles.

960
00:38:37,926 --> 00:38:39,855
Sean Cahill. Nice to meet you.

961
00:38:39,879 --> 00:38:41,514
Who the hell are you?

962
00:38:41,633 --> 00:38:44,187
I'm the guy from the SEC
that isn't in your pocket.

963
00:38:44,305 --> 00:38:45,606
I asked Sean to follow Woodall.

964
00:38:45,725 --> 00:38:48,005
Couldn't. No authorization.

965
00:38:48,029 --> 00:38:49,731
But I had no problem
getting authorization

966
00:38:49,866 --> 00:38:50,900
to follow you.

967
00:38:51,036 --> 00:38:54,352
Which is how I knew
when to turn this on.

968
00:38:54,376 --> 00:38:56,545
You're wearing a goddamn wire?

969
00:38:56,664 --> 00:38:59,028
For someone whose favorite movie
is Wall Street,

970
00:38:59,052 --> 00:39:00,697
that's got to be
pretty embarrassing.

971
00:39:00,722 --> 00:39:02,007
Son of a bitch.

972
00:39:02,141 --> 00:39:04,728
You may have gotten the better
of me 12 years ago, Charles,

973
00:39:04,847 --> 00:39:06,900
but this time, you didn't.

974
00:39:07,019 --> 00:39:10,241
So remember what it feels like,
because I know I will.

975
00:39:10,359 --> 00:39:13,497
Harvey, this isn't over.

976
00:39:13,616 --> 00:39:16,230
Words spoken by every loser
I've ever met.

977
00:39:16,255 --> 00:39:18,007
See you around, pal.

978
00:39:23,386 --> 00:39:25,137
Two for two.

979
00:39:29,866 --> 00:39:32,202
He didn't touch my balls.

980
00:39:36,379 --> 00:39:38,549
Black, two sugars,
splash of vanilla.

981
00:39:38,668 --> 00:39:40,397
How do you know
that's how I take my coffee?

982
00:39:40,421 --> 00:39:42,233
The same way I know
you're not taking that job.

983
00:39:42,258 --> 00:39:44,738
You know I'm not taking that job
because I came into work today.

984
00:39:44,763 --> 00:39:45,791
No, Mr. Specter.

985
00:39:45,815 --> 00:39:47,210
I knew you weren't taking
that job

986
00:39:47,235 --> 00:39:49,822
the second you walked away
from me the other night.

987
00:39:49,941 --> 00:39:52,244
I told you I know people better
than they know themselves.

988
00:39:52,362 --> 00:39:54,499
Well, what did you do with Tina?

989
00:39:54,617 --> 00:39:56,169
Oh, I had Big Bertha
reassign her.

990
00:39:56,287 --> 00:39:58,840
- To who?
- Do you really care?

991
00:39:58,959 --> 00:40:00,177
- Not a bit.
- Good.

992
00:40:00,296 --> 00:40:02,349
Here's the deal.

993
00:40:02,467 --> 00:40:04,947
I will take a bullet for you.

994
00:40:04,972 --> 00:40:06,784
And I don't mean that literally.

995
00:40:06,809 --> 00:40:08,478
But what you do for me is,

996
00:40:08,613 --> 00:40:10,125
when I need something,
you give it to me.

997
00:40:10,149 --> 00:40:12,486
It's not just a one-way street.

998
00:40:12,621 --> 00:40:14,824
Will you also do some actual
secretarial work?

999
00:40:14,959 --> 00:40:17,914
Take a look at what I did with
your calendar there, hotshot.

1000
00:40:18,049 --> 00:40:19,134
Holy shit.

1001
00:40:19,251 --> 00:40:20,863
When'd you get that done?

1002
00:40:20,888 --> 00:40:23,675
I told you I'm not like
every other secretary.

1003
00:40:23,811 --> 00:40:26,348
I'm Donna.

1004
00:40:26,483 --> 00:40:28,045
Then let's get to work.

1005
00:40:28,069 --> 00:40:32,053
But for the record, I don't take
vanilla with my coffee.

1006
00:40:32,078 --> 00:40:34,281
You will after you taste that.

1007
00:40:34,416 --> 00:40:36,502
Oh, my God, this is awesome.

1008
00:40:36,621 --> 00:40:38,591
When will they learn?

1009
00:40:53,154 --> 00:40:54,299
Perfect timing.

1010
00:40:54,324 --> 00:40:55,803
And what are we celebrating?

1011
00:40:55,827 --> 00:40:58,882
Our win.

1012
00:40:59,001 --> 00:41:01,638
"Our win."

1013
00:41:01,756 --> 00:41:03,903
- I like the sound of that.
- Me too.

1014
00:41:03,927 --> 00:41:05,406
Where were you?

1015
00:41:05,430 --> 00:41:06,981
I'll get into that in a minute.

1016
00:41:07,100 --> 00:41:08,652
I want to talk to you
for a second.

1017
00:41:08,770 --> 00:41:10,082
What is it?

1018
00:41:10,106 --> 00:41:13,278
Rachel, you know I told you
I loved you

1019
00:41:13,413 --> 00:41:14,498
from the second I met you.

1020
00:41:14,616 --> 00:41:16,979
Well, you loved my pencil skirt.

1021
00:41:17,004 --> 00:41:18,005
I loved your face.

1022
00:41:22,966 --> 00:41:24,111
♪ ♪

1023
00:41:24,135 --> 00:41:28,286
You're the most amazing woman
I have ever met,

1024
00:41:28,311 --> 00:41:32,462
and you're not just beautiful,

1025
00:41:32,486 --> 00:41:37,137
but you're sweet
and caring and kind

1026
00:41:37,162 --> 00:41:39,499
and brilliant and tenacious.

1027
00:41:39,634 --> 00:41:42,472
Mike, are...

1028
00:41:42,590 --> 00:41:45,845
Are you doing
what I think you're doing?

1029
00:41:48,520 --> 00:41:51,358
I called your father today.

1030
00:41:51,492 --> 00:41:53,673
And then I went to get
Grammy's ring cleaned.

1031
00:41:53,697 --> 00:41:54,864
Oh, my...

1032
00:41:54,999 --> 00:41:56,083
I don't want to go 40 years

1033
00:41:56,202 --> 00:41:58,706
wondering why I didn't do this
one day sooner.

1034
00:42:04,553 --> 00:42:08,285
Rachel Elizabeth Zane...

1035
00:42:08,310 --> 00:42:10,758
I love you...

1036
00:42:10,782 --> 00:42:13,964
and I always will.

1037
00:42:13,989 --> 00:42:16,603
You're my whole life.

1038
00:42:18,548 --> 00:42:19,893
Will you marry me?

1039
00:42:19,917 --> 00:42:22,087
Yes.

1040
00:42:22,223 --> 00:42:23,891
- Yes?
- Yes.

1041
00:42:29,437 --> 00:42:30,270
Oh, my God.

1042
00:42:30,406 --> 00:42:32,275
All right, here...

1043
00:42:34,782 --> 00:42:36,617
Oh.

1044
00:42:36,786 --> 00:42:38,621
Oh, my God.

1045
00:42:41,629 --> 00:42:44,684
It's beautiful.

1046
00:42:44,803 --> 00:42:47,774
She wore it every day
for almost 60 years.

1047
00:42:47,892 --> 00:42:50,279
So will I.

1048
00:43:05,060 --> 00:43:06,181
What's up, dickhead?

1049
00:43:06,347 --> 00:43:07,348
What's up, loser?

1050
00:43:07,349 --> 00:43:09,067
Hey, Harvey.
Good to hear from you.

1051
00:43:09,186 --> 00:43:11,048
What's going on?
Everything okay?

1052
00:43:11,073 --> 00:43:12,358
Yeah, everything's okay.

1053
00:43:12,493 --> 00:43:13,971
I just haven't talked to you
in a while

1054
00:43:13,996 --> 00:43:15,391
and wanted to see
how you were doing.

1055
00:43:15,416 --> 00:43:16,701
I'm great. Katie's good.

1056
00:43:16,869 --> 00:43:18,922
The kids are good.
Everything's good.

1057
00:43:19,039 --> 00:43:20,341
Great.

1058
00:43:20,459 --> 00:43:22,713
That's exactly what
I wanted to hear.

1059
00:43:22,848 --> 00:43:24,610
You sure
there's nothing going on?

1060
00:43:24,634 --> 00:43:25,969
Nothing.

1061
00:43:26,104 --> 00:43:28,391
Like I said, I just haven't
talked to you in a while,

1062
00:43:28,560 --> 00:43:30,111
and I miss you.

1063
00:43:30,229 --> 00:43:32,459
I miss you too, Harvey, but
unless you got something else,

1064
00:43:32,484 --> 00:43:33,513
I've got to go.

1065
00:43:33,537 --> 00:43:34,821
The kids are in the bath.

1066
00:43:34,956 --> 00:43:36,240
Nothing else.

1067
00:43:36,376 --> 00:43:38,712
Love you, Harvey.

1068
00:43:38,831 --> 00:43:40,333
I love you too.

1069
00:43:47,766 --> 00:43:48,961
- Hey.
- Hey.

1070
00:43:48,986 --> 00:43:51,132
Listen, I was thinking about
what you said,

1071
00:43:51,156 --> 00:43:53,170
about me pitying you.

1072
00:43:53,194 --> 00:43:54,305
And I don't.

1073
00:43:54,329 --> 00:43:56,499
Nothing could be further
from the truth.

1074
00:43:56,618 --> 00:43:58,765
I think you're one of
the most amazing women

1075
00:43:58,789 --> 00:44:01,125
I've ever met,
and just because I don't...

1076
00:44:01,261 --> 00:44:03,297
- I'm leaving you, Harvey.
- What?

1077
00:44:03,465 --> 00:44:08,116
This isn't working
for me anymore.

1078
00:44:08,141 --> 00:44:10,505
Donna, I know
how you're feeling,

1079
00:44:10,530 --> 00:44:12,483
but you just went
through something huge,

1080
00:44:12,618 --> 00:44:16,718
with being on trial, and, uh...

1081
00:44:16,742 --> 00:44:19,831
you need to give it time.

1082
00:44:19,966 --> 00:44:21,334
You can't just quit.

1083
00:44:21,502 --> 00:44:23,899
I'm not quitting.

1084
00:44:23,924 --> 00:44:25,175
I'm going to work for Louis.

1085
00:44:28,267 --> 00:44:29,401
Donna.

1086
00:44:33,327 --> 00:44:35,580
Donna, please.

1087
00:44:35,699 --> 00:44:38,036
I love you, Harvey.

1088
00:44:57,448 --> 00:45:03,954
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man

