1
00:00:02,324 --> 00:00:04,973
Professor Gerard, I came
to ask for a favor.

2
00:00:04,997 --> 00:00:05,998
The answer's no.

3
00:00:06,000 --> 00:00:07,596
Which is why I brought this.

4
00:00:07,620 --> 00:00:08,838
You know.

5
00:00:08,956 --> 00:00:10,151
And you talk a big game,

6
00:00:10,176 --> 00:00:12,129
but you're just as human
as everyone else,

7
00:00:12,264 --> 00:00:13,382
you smug son of a bitch.

8
00:00:13,516 --> 00:00:15,519
Louis.

9
00:00:15,638 --> 00:00:17,274
- What are you doing here?
- Leaving.

10
00:00:17,392 --> 00:00:19,896
That way, I don't have to look
at either one of you two liars.

11
00:00:21,986 --> 00:00:24,206
Oh, my God. He knows.

12
00:00:24,324 --> 00:00:26,712
He doesn't just know.

13
00:00:26,830 --> 00:00:28,048
He's a name partner.

14
00:00:28,167 --> 00:00:29,813
She came to me
and lied to my face.

15
00:00:29,837 --> 00:00:31,756
She did it to protect me.

16
00:00:31,892 --> 00:00:33,561
I'm gonna keep hammering on her

17
00:00:33,679 --> 00:00:34,930
until you break.

18
00:00:35,066 --> 00:00:37,019
With a new name
comes a new beginning.

19
00:00:37,154 --> 00:00:39,074
Here's to our newest
name partner,

20
00:00:39,192 --> 00:00:40,193
Louis Litt.

21
00:00:41,247 --> 00:00:42,748
Louis has something on you.

22
00:00:42,867 --> 00:00:47,019
Daniel Hardman embezzled
money from the firm,

23
00:00:47,044 --> 00:00:48,345
and I covered it up.

24
00:00:48,463 --> 00:00:50,576
Why couldn't you trust me
with this before?

25
00:00:50,601 --> 00:00:52,364
Because I didn't know
how you'd react.

26
00:00:52,388 --> 00:00:55,611
Jessica, your secret
is safe with me.

27
00:01:04,500 --> 00:01:12,400
♪ ♪

28
00:01:17,580 --> 00:01:20,418
I thought we were done
with rooftop conversations.

29
00:01:20,537 --> 00:01:22,183
Some things require privacy.

30
00:01:22,207 --> 00:01:24,271
I haven't heard you say that
since the midnight coup

31
00:01:24,296 --> 00:01:25,630
of Schmidt, Gordon,
and Van Dyke.

32
00:01:25,766 --> 00:01:26,694
You done?

33
00:01:26,718 --> 00:01:27,746
It wasn't a joke.

34
00:01:27,770 --> 00:01:28,781
Well, neither is this.

35
00:01:28,805 --> 00:01:30,808
I told Jeff Malone
I helped cover up

36
00:01:30,944 --> 00:01:33,365
Daniel Hardman's embezzlement.

37
00:01:33,483 --> 00:01:35,370
Why the hell would you
open that time capsule?

38
00:01:35,487 --> 00:01:36,789
Because he knew the explanation

39
00:01:36,907 --> 00:01:38,910
we gave the partners about
Louis was bullshit,

40
00:01:39,046 --> 00:01:40,224
and I had to tell him something.

41
00:01:40,248 --> 00:01:42,312
You could've told him
it was none of his business.

42
00:01:42,337 --> 00:01:43,922
Harvey, I didn't bring you here

43
00:01:44,057 --> 00:01:45,342
to get relationship advice.

44
00:01:45,477 --> 00:01:46,872
I brought you here
to tell you what I did

45
00:01:46,897 --> 00:01:47,898
in case it ever came up.

46
00:01:47,899 --> 00:01:48,900
No, you didn't.

47
00:01:48,901 --> 00:01:49,963
You brought me here because now

48
00:01:49,988 --> 00:01:51,309
you have to get Louis
to back you,

49
00:01:51,324 --> 00:01:52,836
and you knew you'd be mad at me

50
00:01:52,861 --> 00:01:54,641
when I told you what
you didn't want to hear.

51
00:01:54,665 --> 00:01:56,177
You're right.
I don't want to hear it.

52
00:01:56,202 --> 00:01:57,403
How do you think it's gonna go

53
00:01:57,505 --> 00:01:58,546
when I tell Louis he holds

54
00:01:58,707 --> 00:02:00,904
the fate of my relationship
in his hands?

55
00:02:00,929 --> 00:02:02,130
How do you think it's gonna go

56
00:02:02,216 --> 00:02:04,269
the first time Malone
brings up Louis' blackmail?

57
00:02:04,387 --> 00:02:05,438
I don't care.

58
00:02:05,556 --> 00:02:06,584
Well, I'll tell you
how it's gonna go.

59
00:02:06,608 --> 00:02:08,087
Louis is gonna look back

60
00:02:08,112 --> 00:02:10,794
with his beady little eyes
and say, "Embezzlement?"

61
00:02:10,819 --> 00:02:12,799
That's not how I got
my name on the wall."

62
00:02:12,823 --> 00:02:14,909
And the shit's gonna
hit the fan anyway.

63
00:02:15,045 --> 00:02:16,079
You know what?

64
00:02:16,214 --> 00:02:17,393
You can be a real
son of a bitch.

65
00:02:17,417 --> 00:02:19,303
Yeah, but instead
of being pissed at me,

66
00:02:19,422 --> 00:02:20,566
why don't you take
a look in the mirror?

67
00:02:20,590 --> 00:02:22,454
Because we held out
an olive branch,

68
00:02:22,479 --> 00:02:23,930
and after Louis hears this,

69
00:02:24,066 --> 00:02:25,494
he's gonna take that branch

70
00:02:25,519 --> 00:02:27,105
and beat the shit
out of us with it.

71
00:02:36,794 --> 00:02:38,524
Louis.

72
00:02:38,549 --> 00:02:40,469
Professor Gerard?
What are you doing here?

73
00:02:40,603 --> 00:02:41,804
I've got a small legal matter

74
00:02:41,940 --> 00:02:43,024
to attend to.

75
00:02:43,142 --> 00:02:44,978
Well, is it anything
I can help you with?

76
00:02:45,114 --> 00:02:46,676
Actually, I'm here
to speak with Harvey.

77
00:02:46,700 --> 00:02:48,129
Ah, ah, I understand.

78
00:02:48,154 --> 00:02:49,549
You're looking
for a name partner.

79
00:02:49,574 --> 00:02:50,802
Well, you can't quite
see it from here,

80
00:02:50,826 --> 00:02:51,938
but if you walk back
about ten feet,

81
00:02:51,963 --> 00:02:53,141
take a gander to your left,

82
00:02:53,165 --> 00:02:54,560
you'll see I've gotten
a little recognition...

83
00:02:54,585 --> 00:02:56,338
I appreciate that,
but as I said,

84
00:02:56,507 --> 00:02:58,560
I'm here to speak with Harvey.

85
00:03:02,571 --> 00:03:04,467
So are we gonna talk about
that little welcome speech

86
00:03:04,491 --> 00:03:05,692
that Jessica made for Louis?

87
00:03:05,828 --> 00:03:07,056
We don't have to talk about it

88
00:03:07,080 --> 00:03:09,060
because Louis isn't
going to accept it.

89
00:03:09,085 --> 00:03:10,263
Why not?

90
00:03:10,288 --> 00:03:11,683
Because it'll be
a cold day in hell

91
00:03:11,707 --> 00:03:13,710
when he can accept being
Maverick to my Iceman.

92
00:03:13,879 --> 00:03:16,109
Don't... don't you mean
Iceman to your Maverick?

93
00:03:16,134 --> 00:03:17,553
No, I don't.

94
00:03:17,688 --> 00:03:20,193
You actually want to be
Iceman over Maverick?

95
00:03:20,310 --> 00:03:21,923
- Who got the trophy?
- Who's the better pilot?

96
00:03:21,948 --> 00:03:23,210
- The one who got the trophy.
- Wrong.

97
00:03:23,234 --> 00:03:25,237
Because in the end,
Maverick saved Iceman,

98
00:03:25,372 --> 00:03:26,884
and if he hadn't, trophy boy
would be sitting

99
00:03:26,909 --> 00:03:29,046
on the bottom
of the Indian Ocean right now.

100
00:03:29,164 --> 00:03:31,028
- Where he'd still be the man.
- According to you.

101
00:03:31,052 --> 00:03:33,423
According to me is the only
"according to" that matters.

102
00:03:33,558 --> 00:03:34,486
Here we go.

103
00:03:34,510 --> 00:03:37,098
Maybe, but according to me,

104
00:03:37,233 --> 00:03:39,831
Viper was the real hero
of that film.

105
00:03:39,856 --> 00:03:41,334
What?

106
00:03:41,359 --> 00:03:42,972
You think I'm too old
to know Top Gun?

107
00:03:42,996 --> 00:03:44,448
What I think is,
you have no business

108
00:03:44,617 --> 00:03:45,668
being in my office.

109
00:03:45,785 --> 00:03:47,732
Are we gonna do this
in front of your associate?

110
00:03:47,757 --> 00:03:49,604
We don't have to do anything
in front of anybody.

111
00:03:49,628 --> 00:03:51,547
You just have to go.

112
00:03:54,105 --> 00:03:56,201
Harvey...

113
00:03:56,226 --> 00:03:57,478
I need a lawyer.

114
00:03:57,613 --> 00:03:58,875
Louis' office is down the hall.

115
00:03:58,899 --> 00:04:00,818
I don't want Louis.

116
00:04:00,987 --> 00:04:02,238
- I want you.
- That's funny.

117
00:04:02,374 --> 00:04:04,020
The last time you saw me,
you told me I wasn't fit

118
00:04:04,044 --> 00:04:05,974
to practice law
in your ivory tower.

119
00:04:05,999 --> 00:04:07,167
What I told you was,

120
00:04:07,302 --> 00:04:09,565
is that you'll sacrifice
ethics for wins,

121
00:04:09,590 --> 00:04:12,205
and right now
I'm not in my ivory tower,

122
00:04:12,230 --> 00:04:13,231
and I need a win.

123
00:04:13,349 --> 00:04:14,350
I knew it.

124
00:04:14,351 --> 00:04:15,496
You're just like everybody else.

125
00:04:15,521 --> 00:04:16,799
The ends don't justify the means

126
00:04:16,823 --> 00:04:18,251
until it's your ass on the line.

127
00:04:18,276 --> 00:04:20,246
Do you think I like
asking you for help?

128
00:04:20,365 --> 00:04:23,013
I think this Liberty Rail thing
must have you by the balls.

129
00:04:23,038 --> 00:04:24,100
So you know.

130
00:04:24,124 --> 00:04:25,235
I know after their
train derailed,

131
00:04:25,259 --> 00:04:26,354
you were appointed to assess

132
00:04:26,379 --> 00:04:28,215
the victims'
compensation formula,

133
00:04:28,383 --> 00:04:29,434
and I know after you did,

134
00:04:29,553 --> 00:04:31,021
some of those victims
hired a lawyer

135
00:04:31,140 --> 00:04:32,753
and opened an investigation.

136
00:04:32,777 --> 00:04:34,205
Then you also know
they found nothing.

137
00:04:34,230 --> 00:04:36,210
Then the question is,
why are you here?

138
00:04:36,235 --> 00:04:39,100
The TSA found $25,000
in my luggage

139
00:04:39,124 --> 00:04:41,996
the day I announced I was
changing the formula.

140
00:04:42,131 --> 00:04:43,416
So now you're being accused

141
00:04:43,551 --> 00:04:44,636
of accepting a bribe.

142
00:04:44,755 --> 00:04:46,233
Which I did not do.

143
00:04:46,258 --> 00:04:48,261
Well, good luck proving
that, Professor,

144
00:04:48,396 --> 00:04:50,265
because it won't be
with my help.

145
00:04:52,405 --> 00:04:55,003
I was wrong about you,
Mr. Specter.

146
00:04:55,028 --> 00:04:56,758
I never thought that you
wouldn't represent somebody

147
00:04:56,782 --> 00:04:57,926
just because you
didn't like them.

148
00:04:57,951 --> 00:04:59,119
Well, you're wrong again.

149
00:04:59,287 --> 00:05:01,290
I don't like you,
but I'm not representing you

150
00:05:01,459 --> 00:05:02,927
because you did something shady,

151
00:05:03,046 --> 00:05:04,598
and I'm not screwing over
crash victims

152
00:05:04,716 --> 00:05:05,828
for the likes of you.

153
00:05:05,853 --> 00:05:06,937
You know I didn't do this.

154
00:05:07,055 --> 00:05:09,024
What I know is
you showed yourself in.

155
00:05:09,143 --> 00:05:10,863
You can show yourself out.

156
00:05:16,744 --> 00:05:20,334
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪

157
00:05:20,470 --> 00:05:23,676
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪

158
00:05:23,810 --> 00:05:26,849
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪

159
00:05:26,984 --> 00:05:30,607
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪

160
00:05:30,743 --> 00:05:33,531
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪

161
00:05:33,666 --> 00:05:37,541
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪

162
00:05:37,675 --> 00:05:39,010
♪ All right ♪

163
00:05:39,013 --> 00:05:40,634
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪

164
00:05:40,635 --> 00:05:44,640
♪ Suits 4x12 ♪ Respect Original
Air Date on February 4, 2015

165
00:05:44,641 --> 00:05:46,311
♪ The greenback boogie ♪

166
00:05:46,335 --> 00:05:52,575
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man.

167
00:05:52,576 --> 00:05:53,721
Hey, I didn't want
to say anything

168
00:05:53,746 --> 00:05:55,475
in front of Gerard,
but has it occurred to you

169
00:05:55,499 --> 00:05:57,669
that you're an idiot
if you don't take this case?

170
00:05:57,805 --> 00:05:59,484
Last year, you were
shitting yourself

171
00:05:59,508 --> 00:06:00,559
he'd find out about you,

172
00:06:00,678 --> 00:06:02,375
and now you think
we should work with him?

173
00:06:02,399 --> 00:06:03,900
No, I wasn't worried
he'd find out.

174
00:06:04,019 --> 00:06:05,605
I was worried about Louis.

175
00:06:05,739 --> 00:06:07,492
Gerard didn't bat
an eye at me back then,

176
00:06:07,611 --> 00:06:08,945
and he didn't just now.

177
00:06:09,080 --> 00:06:10,121
But we get him out of this

178
00:06:10,250 --> 00:06:11,751
and he ever does
find out about me,

179
00:06:11,870 --> 00:06:12,954
he's gonna owe us.

180
00:06:13,090 --> 00:06:15,628
Mike, that man is never
gonna compromise his ethics

181
00:06:15,762 --> 00:06:17,203
just because we got him
out of a jam.

182
00:06:17,216 --> 00:06:18,611
Never gonna compromise
his ethics?

183
00:06:18,636 --> 00:06:19,854
You just said he took a bribe.

184
00:06:19,972 --> 00:06:21,654
So what does that
have to do with anything?

185
00:06:22,945 --> 00:06:24,466
It has everything
to do with everything

186
00:06:24,482 --> 00:06:26,903
because you don't
think he did it.

187
00:06:28,876 --> 00:06:30,160
- So what?
- So what?

188
00:06:30,296 --> 00:06:31,607
That means you're not
turning him down

189
00:06:31,632 --> 00:06:32,834
because you think he's shady.

190
00:06:32,968 --> 00:06:34,086
You're...

191
00:06:34,221 --> 00:06:35,566
You're turning him down
because you have

192
00:06:35,591 --> 00:06:37,655
a Henry Gerard-sized chip
on your shoulder.

193
00:06:37,679 --> 00:06:39,265
I do not have a chip
on my shoulder.

194
00:06:39,400 --> 00:06:40,735
You sure sound like you do,

195
00:06:40,854 --> 00:06:42,049
which makes you
worse than an idiot.

196
00:06:42,073 --> 00:06:43,134
It makes you a jackass.

197
00:06:43,159 --> 00:06:44,577
- Excuse me?
- You heard me.

198
00:06:44,696 --> 00:06:46,342
You know that he divided
that money fairly,

199
00:06:46,366 --> 00:06:47,344
which means that you're just...

200
00:06:47,368 --> 00:06:48,753
I don't care what it means,

201
00:06:48,872 --> 00:06:50,150
and I don't need
a lecture from you.

202
00:06:50,175 --> 00:06:51,236
Apparently you do,

203
00:06:51,260 --> 00:06:52,355
because you're about
to screw over

204
00:06:52,379 --> 00:06:53,691
a bunch of innocent people

205
00:06:53,716 --> 00:06:56,437
just to stick it to some guy
who hurt your feelings.

206
00:06:56,556 --> 00:06:58,024
That's not something
I ever thought

207
00:06:58,143 --> 00:06:59,528
I'd be saying to you.

208
00:07:02,537 --> 00:07:04,467
Well, look who it is,

209
00:07:04,491 --> 00:07:06,460
the woman who put me
in my place.

210
00:07:06,579 --> 00:07:07,640
What now?

211
00:07:07,664 --> 00:07:08,726
You want me to sign
a piece of paper

212
00:07:08,751 --> 00:07:10,397
admitting that I was the man
on the grassy knoll?

213
00:07:10,421 --> 00:07:12,257
I meant what I said
at the ceremony, Louis.

214
00:07:12,392 --> 00:07:13,913
You mean the ceremony
that you only had

215
00:07:13,929 --> 00:07:15,147
in order to trick me?

216
00:07:15,265 --> 00:07:17,101
I had it because
you demanded it,

217
00:07:17,237 --> 00:07:19,106
but I'm not here
to talk about that.

218
00:07:19,241 --> 00:07:20,636
I'm here to talk
about Jeff Malone.

219
00:07:20,661 --> 00:07:21,672
What about him?

220
00:07:21,696 --> 00:07:23,058
You may be aware
that he and I are...

221
00:07:23,083 --> 00:07:24,763
Fifty Shades of Grey? I'm aware.

222
00:07:24,787 --> 00:07:27,124
I'm gonna let that go

223
00:07:27,259 --> 00:07:29,439
because you may
also not be aware

224
00:07:29,464 --> 00:07:30,765
that I had to lie to him.

225
00:07:35,562 --> 00:07:37,114
He doesn't know
about Mike, does he?

226
00:07:37,232 --> 00:07:38,710
No.

227
00:07:38,735 --> 00:07:40,288
But he does know
you committed a crime

228
00:07:40,406 --> 00:07:41,467
and that you resigned

229
00:07:41,492 --> 00:07:43,055
and now your name
is up on the wall.

230
00:07:43,079 --> 00:07:44,140
What'd you tell him?

231
00:07:44,164 --> 00:07:46,813
I told him you found out
that I covered up

232
00:07:46,838 --> 00:07:48,484
Daniel Hardman's embezzlement

233
00:07:48,508 --> 00:07:50,906
and that you used it
to strong-arm me.

234
00:07:50,930 --> 00:07:53,351
And now you want me to protect
another one of your secrets.

235
00:07:53,519 --> 00:07:55,656
It's the same secret, Louis,

236
00:07:55,774 --> 00:07:57,588
and you have just as much
invested in it as I do.

237
00:07:57,613 --> 00:07:58,924
No, I don't,
because I don't care

238
00:07:58,948 --> 00:08:00,918
if your relationship
with Jeff survives or not.

239
00:08:02,958 --> 00:08:04,093
What do you want, Louis?

240
00:08:04,210 --> 00:08:06,213
I want something for
continuing to cover your ass.

241
00:08:06,349 --> 00:08:08,987
You got something.
You got your name on the wall.

242
00:08:09,089 --> 00:08:10,752
Now I want the respect
that comes with it.

243
00:08:10,776 --> 00:08:11,954
Meaning?

244
00:08:11,978 --> 00:08:14,733
I want one of Harvey's clients.

245
00:08:14,868 --> 00:08:15,869
Which one?

246
00:08:18,744 --> 00:08:20,245
That's between me and Harvey.

247
00:08:23,421 --> 00:08:31,271
♪ ♪

248
00:08:41,714 --> 00:08:43,350
Okay.

249
00:08:43,467 --> 00:08:45,698
I agreed to meet.

250
00:08:45,723 --> 00:08:47,452
I hope it's not just
so you can tell me more

251
00:08:47,476 --> 00:08:49,947
about what a horrible
person I am.

252
00:08:50,065 --> 00:08:52,513
I came here to tell you
that I changed my mind.

253
00:08:52,538 --> 00:08:55,460
So you admitted to yourself
that I didn't do this?

254
00:08:55,579 --> 00:08:57,225
I've admitted to myself
that you came to me

255
00:08:57,249 --> 00:08:59,647
because this case
needs rule-bending,

256
00:08:59,671 --> 00:09:03,873
and you're gonna tell me
why right now.

257
00:09:03,897 --> 00:09:05,483
The money.

258
00:09:05,602 --> 00:09:06,936
Yes, the money.

259
00:09:07,071 --> 00:09:08,189
If you weren't bribed,

260
00:09:08,324 --> 00:09:10,672
where the hell did you
get that $25,000 from?

261
00:09:10,696 --> 00:09:12,393
You know where it came from.

262
00:09:12,417 --> 00:09:13,645
It's the same thing
you tried to use

263
00:09:13,670 --> 00:09:15,289
to blackmail me last year.

264
00:09:15,424 --> 00:09:17,427
Let me get this straight.

265
00:09:17,545 --> 00:09:18,824
You have an explanation
for the money

266
00:09:18,849 --> 00:09:20,194
that would get you
out of this whole thing.

267
00:09:20,218 --> 00:09:24,420
But I can't use it.

268
00:09:24,445 --> 00:09:25,896
Where are you going?

269
00:09:26,031 --> 00:09:27,951
To get you out of this.

270
00:09:28,070 --> 00:09:30,039
Welcome to the real world,
Professor.

271
00:09:33,164 --> 00:09:38,057
♪ ♪

272
00:09:39,813 --> 00:09:41,376
I need you to find out
everything you can

273
00:09:41,400 --> 00:09:42,462
on Garrett Brady.

274
00:09:42,486 --> 00:09:44,272
Absolutely. Who's Garrett Brady?

275
00:09:44,407 --> 00:09:46,089
The guy on the other side
of Gerard's suit.

276
00:09:48,115 --> 00:09:49,116
Wait a second.

277
00:09:49,118 --> 00:09:50,229
Does this mean
you took his case?

278
00:09:50,253 --> 00:09:52,100
You know that means
I took his case,

279
00:09:52,125 --> 00:09:53,270
and I don't want to hear
any gloating.

280
00:09:53,294 --> 00:09:54,461
Gloating? No, no, no, no, no.

281
00:09:54,630 --> 00:09:55,751
I'm not... I'm not gloating.

282
00:09:55,849 --> 00:09:57,552
I'm merely recognizing
the fact that you

283
00:09:57,687 --> 00:09:58,889
completely changed your mind

284
00:09:59,024 --> 00:10:01,060
based entirely on what I said.

285
00:10:01,195 --> 00:10:03,041
- Which is gloating.
- "Po-tay-to," "po-tah-to."

286
00:10:03,066 --> 00:10:04,796
But as long as you're
gonna think of it that way,

287
00:10:04,820 --> 00:10:05,955
I might as well point out

288
00:10:06,073 --> 00:10:07,793
that since you listened
to my lecture,

289
00:10:07,911 --> 00:10:10,024
maybe you should start
calling me Professor.

290
00:10:10,049 --> 00:10:11,718
I'm gonna start
calling you unemployed

291
00:10:11,836 --> 00:10:14,735
if you don't figure out a way
around using Gerard's alibi.

292
00:10:14,760 --> 00:10:16,873
Wait, we can't say where
the money came from?

293
00:10:16,898 --> 00:10:19,580
No, we can't, because
he was playing backroom poker,

294
00:10:19,604 --> 00:10:20,999
and if that comes out,
Harvard fires him.

295
00:10:21,024 --> 00:10:22,409
Are you kidding me?

296
00:10:22,527 --> 00:10:24,926
He's an ethics professor,
and he's breaking the law?

297
00:10:24,950 --> 00:10:26,919
Where the hell do you think
my chip comes from?

298
00:10:28,290 --> 00:10:29,531
Well, if we can't use his alibi,

299
00:10:29,543 --> 00:10:30,905
how are we supposed
to get him out of this?

300
00:10:30,930 --> 00:10:32,526
I don't know, Professor,
but you're the one

301
00:10:32,550 --> 00:10:33,829
who wanted us to take this case,

302
00:10:33,854 --> 00:10:35,366
so why don't you use
that big brain of yours

303
00:10:35,390 --> 00:10:36,976
and find a solution?

304
00:10:40,452 --> 00:10:41,933
You're giving me Henry Gerard.

305
00:10:42,039 --> 00:10:43,040
What?

306
00:10:43,041 --> 00:10:44,202
I saw him. I want him.

307
00:10:44,210 --> 00:10:45,245
You got him. He's mine.

308
00:10:45,413 --> 00:10:46,557
That's not the way
it works, Louis.

309
00:10:46,582 --> 00:10:47,861
I'm afraid you'll have
to find yourself

310
00:10:47,886 --> 00:10:48,897
another boyfriend.

311
00:10:48,921 --> 00:10:51,809
Oh, this is exactly
how it works.

312
00:10:51,928 --> 00:10:53,481
You talked to Jessica,
didn't you?

313
00:10:53,598 --> 00:10:55,328
Sure did, and she used me
to cover her ass,

314
00:10:55,352 --> 00:10:57,132
so I get one
of your clients in return.

315
00:10:57,157 --> 00:10:59,254
You want one of my clients,
we can talk about that,

316
00:10:59,278 --> 00:11:00,663
but Gerard's staying with me.

317
00:11:00,781 --> 00:11:02,116
Oh, please, don't pretend

318
00:11:02,285 --> 00:11:03,596
like you actually care
about him.

319
00:11:03,621 --> 00:11:04,983
He can't even stand you.

320
00:11:05,008 --> 00:11:07,155
Louis, I just offered
to consider giving you

321
00:11:07,180 --> 00:11:08,191
one of my clients,

322
00:11:08,215 --> 00:11:10,018
so I suggest you let Gerard go.

323
00:11:10,136 --> 00:11:11,448
No, I'm not letting anything go,

324
00:11:11,473 --> 00:11:13,119
because it doesn't make
any sense.

325
00:11:13,143 --> 00:11:14,528
Not only can't he stand you.

326
00:11:14,646 --> 00:11:16,568
He doesn't respect you
because he's got things...

327
00:11:16,651 --> 00:11:18,036
What did you just say to me?

328
00:11:18,155 --> 00:11:20,052
I said he doesn't respect you.

329
00:11:20,076 --> 00:11:21,104
Well, you know what?

330
00:11:21,129 --> 00:11:23,142
He definitely
doesn't respect you,

331
00:11:23,166 --> 00:11:25,504
because when he told me
he needed a lawyer,

332
00:11:25,638 --> 00:11:27,535
I tried to send him your way,

333
00:11:27,560 --> 00:11:29,206
and his exact words were,

334
00:11:29,230 --> 00:11:31,684
"I don't want Louis.
I want you."

335
00:11:34,576 --> 00:11:35,693
Fine.

336
00:11:35,862 --> 00:11:37,341
Then I'll just take
another one of your clients.

337
00:11:37,366 --> 00:11:39,563
- You're not taking a thing.
- You just said that I could...

338
00:11:39,587 --> 00:11:41,567
Look, I don't give a shit
what I just said, okay?

339
00:11:41,592 --> 00:11:43,070
My clients are my clients.

340
00:11:43,095 --> 00:11:44,190
And you don't get
out of my office

341
00:11:44,214 --> 00:11:45,382
in the next three seconds,

342
00:11:45,517 --> 00:11:47,164
something's gonna happen
between you and me,

343
00:11:47,188 --> 00:11:49,224
and I guarantee
it won't end with you

344
00:11:49,359 --> 00:11:51,814
keeping all of your teeth.

345
00:11:57,462 --> 00:11:58,580
No.

346
00:11:58,714 --> 00:12:00,477
Just turn around and walk
right back out that door.

347
00:12:00,501 --> 00:12:01,729
- Harvey.
- Did you hear what I said?

348
00:12:01,754 --> 00:12:03,066
I did, but apparently,
you didn't hear

349
00:12:03,091 --> 00:12:04,977
what Jessica said
about wiping the slate clean.

350
00:12:05,095 --> 00:12:06,708
And apparently, you didn't
hear what I said,

351
00:12:06,732 --> 00:12:08,912
because I just told Louis
he could have one of my clients.

352
00:12:08,937 --> 00:12:10,584
And three seconds later,
you told him he couldn't.

353
00:12:10,608 --> 00:12:12,053
Yeah, because I realized
that I'm paying

354
00:12:12,078 --> 00:12:13,256
for Jessica's mistake.

355
00:12:13,281 --> 00:12:15,284
No, Harvey, you were willing
to pay for her mistake

356
00:12:15,453 --> 00:12:17,650
right up until Louis said
Gerard doesn't respect you.

357
00:12:17,675 --> 00:12:19,036
Oh, that has nothing
to do with it.

358
00:12:19,044 --> 00:12:20,596
You can lie to yourself
all you want,

359
00:12:20,715 --> 00:12:21,943
but I'm not gonna
let you bullshit me.

360
00:12:21,967 --> 00:12:23,279
What the hell
are you talking about?

361
00:12:23,304 --> 00:12:25,117
Henry Gerard is the one
person you respect

362
00:12:25,141 --> 00:12:27,311
who never respected you,
and Louis touched that nerve.

363
00:12:27,446 --> 00:12:29,784
And I told you that
has nothing to do with it.

364
00:12:29,902 --> 00:12:30,963
You really think that?

365
00:12:30,988 --> 00:12:32,069
I don't think it. I know it.

366
00:12:32,074 --> 00:12:33,185
Then you know what, Harvey?

367
00:12:33,210 --> 00:12:34,472
You're no different than Louis,

368
00:12:34,496 --> 00:12:36,418
because you have a chance
to help us all move on,

369
00:12:36,551 --> 00:12:38,281
and you are blowing it off
out of pettiness,

370
00:12:38,305 --> 00:12:39,891
which is exactly
what Louis would do.

371
00:12:40,008 --> 00:12:40,893
What do you want from me, Donna?

372
00:12:41,011 --> 00:12:42,263
I want you to be a grown-up

373
00:12:42,398 --> 00:12:45,019
and do what you said you'd do
in the first place.

374
00:12:51,629 --> 00:12:52,890
You got something?

375
00:12:52,915 --> 00:12:54,699
Yeah, we've been
overlooking the obvious.

376
00:12:54,700 --> 00:12:56,282
Yeah, I'm not in the mood
for 20 questions.

377
00:12:56,283 --> 00:12:57,344
Give it to me.

378
00:12:57,369 --> 00:12:58,765
Unless you're traveling
internationally

379
00:12:58,790 --> 00:13:00,553
and don't report it,
carrying cash on board a plane

380
00:13:00,577 --> 00:13:01,638
isn't a crime.

381
00:13:01,662 --> 00:13:02,880
Great, except for the fact

382
00:13:02,999 --> 00:13:04,562
that Gerard's not being
charged with smuggling.

383
00:13:04,586 --> 00:13:05,587
He's being sued.

384
00:13:05,589 --> 00:13:06,617
Right, but my point is,

385
00:13:06,641 --> 00:13:08,243
how did Garrett Brady
even find that out?

386
00:13:08,344 --> 00:13:10,264
Well, he found out
because Gerard

387
00:13:10,399 --> 00:13:11,628
was detained by the TSA.

388
00:13:11,652 --> 00:13:13,248
Who talked to him
for five minutes

389
00:13:13,272 --> 00:13:14,523
and then sent him on his way.

390
00:13:14,659 --> 00:13:15,943
Those searches aren't a matter

391
00:13:16,079 --> 00:13:17,140
of public record.

392
00:13:17,164 --> 00:13:18,582
- Exactly.
- Holy shit.

393
00:13:18,701 --> 00:13:19,763
Brady bribed the TSA.

394
00:13:19,788 --> 00:13:20,816
Which isn't only illegal.

395
00:13:20,840 --> 00:13:23,020
It makes that report
totally inadmissible.

396
00:13:23,045 --> 00:13:24,440
You figured this out
on your own?

397
00:13:24,465 --> 00:13:26,361
Well, I would've done it faster,
but I had to order some sushi.

398
00:13:26,385 --> 00:13:28,472
"Would've done it faster."

399
00:13:28,574 --> 00:13:29,919
That's what you said
your first week here,

400
00:13:29,944 --> 00:13:31,530
except it was pizza
instead of sushi.

401
00:13:31,648 --> 00:13:32,649
Yeah, I'm growing.

402
00:13:32,818 --> 00:13:34,987
You mean Rachel
taught you how to eat.

403
00:13:35,123 --> 00:13:36,876
Like I said, I'm growing.

404
00:13:39,917 --> 00:13:42,338
Hey, Donna, I'm a little
busy at the moment.

405
00:13:42,472 --> 00:13:44,175
Too busy to take on this?

406
00:13:44,311 --> 00:13:45,372
What's that?

407
00:13:45,396 --> 00:13:46,959
Just the first client
that Jessica gave Harvey

408
00:13:46,983 --> 00:13:48,351
when he made name partner.

409
00:13:48,486 --> 00:13:50,133
Harvey said he wouldn't
let me have any of his clients.

410
00:13:50,157 --> 00:13:51,552
No. He said he would.

411
00:13:51,577 --> 00:13:53,140
But then instead
of taking him up on it,

412
00:13:53,164 --> 00:13:54,559
you went ahead
and shit on his feelings.

413
00:13:54,584 --> 00:13:55,979
Please.
Harvey doesn't have feelings.

414
00:13:56,004 --> 00:13:57,567
That's not true,
and you know it.

415
00:13:57,591 --> 00:13:58,986
And you of all people
should know that a person

416
00:13:59,011 --> 00:14:00,346
can overreact when they're hurt.

417
00:14:00,463 --> 00:14:01,514
If you're referring to me,

418
00:14:01,633 --> 00:14:02,778
I do not overreact when...

419
00:14:02,802 --> 00:14:04,388
Okay, whatever you say,
Fatty-Baldy.

420
00:14:04,557 --> 00:14:07,696
Okay, get the hell
out of my office and...

421
00:14:07,814 --> 00:14:10,369
Fine, you have a small,
legitimate point.

422
00:14:10,486 --> 00:14:11,514
I really hurt his feelings?

423
00:14:11,539 --> 00:14:12,885
Yeah, you really did.

424
00:14:12,909 --> 00:14:14,521
But then he realized
he was overreacting

425
00:14:14,546 --> 00:14:15,892
and that this was
a chance for us all

426
00:14:15,916 --> 00:14:17,551
to get back to where we were.

427
00:14:17,670 --> 00:14:19,088
You swear that is
the first client

428
00:14:19,257 --> 00:14:21,321
that Jessica gave him
after me made name partner?

429
00:14:21,345 --> 00:14:23,231
I swear.

430
00:14:23,350 --> 00:14:25,236
Leave me the file.

431
00:14:38,467 --> 00:14:40,664
You two go ahead.
I haven't decided yet.

432
00:14:40,689 --> 00:14:42,117
Actually, we're not here
for the falafel.

433
00:14:42,142 --> 00:14:43,728
We're here to introduce
ourselves.

434
00:14:43,863 --> 00:14:44,864
Mike Ross.

435
00:14:44,866 --> 00:14:45,794
Harvey Specter.

436
00:14:45,818 --> 00:14:47,202
We represent Henry Gerard.

437
00:14:47,321 --> 00:14:48,572
Ah.

438
00:14:48,708 --> 00:14:50,494
Well, in that case,
let me buy you two lunch,

439
00:14:50,628 --> 00:14:52,859
because I'm about to come
into an unexpected windfall.

440
00:14:52,884 --> 00:14:54,229
Well, I guess
that's your thing...

441
00:14:54,254 --> 00:14:55,505
Paying people off.

442
00:14:55,640 --> 00:14:57,821
I hope the TSA got more
than some shitty falafel.

443
00:14:57,846 --> 00:14:59,207
What the hell
are you talking about?

444
00:14:59,231 --> 00:15:00,649
I'm talking about this.

445
00:15:03,775 --> 00:15:05,695
Oh. Bribery?

446
00:15:05,830 --> 00:15:07,032
Ironic, isn't it?

447
00:15:07,167 --> 00:15:09,788
You suing Professor Gerard
for accepting a bribe

448
00:15:09,923 --> 00:15:11,926
when you're the one
paying off federal employees.

449
00:15:12,045 --> 00:15:13,379
Allegedly paying, Counselor.

450
00:15:13,515 --> 00:15:14,526
Tsk, tsk, tsk.

451
00:15:14,550 --> 00:15:15,885
You don't want to slander me.

452
00:15:16,020 --> 00:15:17,773
- So you admit it.
- I don't admit a thing.

453
00:15:17,891 --> 00:15:19,670
Your client sold out victims
of a train derailment.

454
00:15:19,695 --> 00:15:20,780
He's going to pay.

455
00:15:20,898 --> 00:15:22,700
You may not be willing
to admit anything here,

456
00:15:22,819 --> 00:15:24,382
but you'll have to
in front of the judge.

457
00:15:24,406 --> 00:15:25,468
Because I've drafted subpoenas

458
00:15:25,492 --> 00:15:28,080
for every TSA employee
on duty that night.

459
00:15:28,215 --> 00:15:30,228
Drop the case, Mr. Brady.

460
00:15:30,252 --> 00:15:31,397
Are you threatening me?

461
00:15:31,422 --> 00:15:33,402
No, we're informing you.

462
00:15:33,426 --> 00:15:34,928
Well, let me inform you.

463
00:15:35,098 --> 00:15:36,399
In case you forgot,
the TSA falls

464
00:15:36,517 --> 00:15:38,159
under the Department
of Homeland Security,

465
00:15:38,271 --> 00:15:39,834
which makes this
a national security issue.

466
00:15:39,858 --> 00:15:40,886
This has nothing to do

467
00:15:40,910 --> 00:15:42,840
with national security,
and you know it.

468
00:15:42,865 --> 00:15:44,250
All I know is
the government found

469
00:15:44,369 --> 00:15:45,647
a large sum of cash
on a passenger.

470
00:15:45,671 --> 00:15:46,766
Now, how they came to know that,

471
00:15:46,791 --> 00:15:48,069
how they proceeded
to investigate that,

472
00:15:48,093 --> 00:15:49,321
or what they did
with that information

473
00:15:49,346 --> 00:15:50,525
is the government's business.

474
00:15:50,550 --> 00:15:51,661
And that's what
you're going with?

475
00:15:51,685 --> 00:15:52,780
That's not what I'm going with.

476
00:15:52,805 --> 00:15:54,641
That's what they're
going to go with.

477
00:15:54,775 --> 00:15:57,707
So you can call up as many
TSA agents as you like,

478
00:15:57,732 --> 00:15:59,128
but they're not gonna be
saying a thing.

479
00:15:59,153 --> 00:16:01,991
And you can buy
your own damn falafel.

480
00:16:10,144 --> 00:16:11,229
I need Cutie Pie Cosmetics.

481
00:16:11,346 --> 00:16:12,658
You want to try that again?

482
00:16:12,683 --> 00:16:13,995
I have a meeting
with Joan Walsh tonight,

483
00:16:14,020 --> 00:16:15,248
and I need her files.

484
00:16:15,273 --> 00:16:16,274
Joan is Harvey's client.

485
00:16:16,408 --> 00:16:17,910
- Not anymore.
- Since when?

486
00:16:18,029 --> 00:16:19,497
Since it doesn't matter,

487
00:16:19,616 --> 00:16:20,950
because I'm name partner,

488
00:16:21,086 --> 00:16:23,423
which means when I say
I need something,

489
00:16:23,541 --> 00:16:24,603
your response should either be,

490
00:16:24,628 --> 00:16:26,597
"How high?"
or "Can I have another?"

491
00:16:28,352 --> 00:16:29,363
Fine.

492
00:16:29,388 --> 00:16:30,750
There are a few things
that you should know...

493
00:16:30,775 --> 00:16:32,287
You see, what I know is

494
00:16:32,312 --> 00:16:33,563
your boss seems to think

495
00:16:33,698 --> 00:16:35,377
all it takes
to impress Joan Walsh

496
00:16:35,402 --> 00:16:37,907
is getting Donna to make
a fancy dinner reservation,

497
00:16:38,041 --> 00:16:40,379
but I'm going to impress her
with so much legal domination

498
00:16:40,497 --> 00:16:41,725
that by the end of the night,

499
00:16:41,750 --> 00:16:42,861
all she's gonna be able
to say is,

500
00:16:42,885 --> 00:16:44,555
"Harvey Specter who?"

501
00:16:44,674 --> 00:16:46,069
- Okay, that's a mistake...
- A mistake?

502
00:16:46,093 --> 00:16:47,154
Oh, I get it.

503
00:16:47,179 --> 00:16:48,347
You're trying to impress me

504
00:16:48,481 --> 00:16:49,826
with your legal domination

505
00:16:49,851 --> 00:16:51,854
to prove that you're not
just a paralegal

506
00:16:51,990 --> 00:16:53,001
but an associate.

507
00:16:53,025 --> 00:16:54,160
No, Louis. I'm...

508
00:16:54,279 --> 00:16:55,841
See, I don't care
what you call yourself.

509
00:16:55,865 --> 00:16:57,785
So unless you did
such a shitty job,

510
00:16:57,920 --> 00:16:59,255
the files are unreadable,

511
00:16:59,373 --> 00:17:01,176
hand 'em over to me right now.

512
00:17:24,013 --> 00:17:25,816
That's more like it.

513
00:17:41,387 --> 00:17:42,438
What's this?

514
00:17:42,555 --> 00:17:43,750
I know you have to work tonight,

515
00:17:43,775 --> 00:17:45,120
but you also need to eat.

516
00:17:45,145 --> 00:17:46,624
I wouldn't call this
just eating.

517
00:17:46,649 --> 00:17:48,485
Well, you deserve better
than paper plates.

518
00:17:48,619 --> 00:17:50,322
I don't mind paper plates.

519
00:17:50,457 --> 00:17:52,243
Oh, I know you don't.

520
00:17:52,378 --> 00:17:53,796
I just said you deserve better.

521
00:17:53,915 --> 00:17:55,584
Is that ropa vieja?

522
00:17:55,719 --> 00:17:56,803
Hmm.

523
00:17:56,922 --> 00:17:58,725
I made it myself.

524
00:17:58,843 --> 00:18:00,512
Which means you got it
at the Cuban place

525
00:18:00,647 --> 00:18:03,129
that I love on 40th and Lex.

526
00:18:03,153 --> 00:18:04,187
By myself.

527
00:18:04,322 --> 00:18:06,608
What did I do to deserve this?

528
00:18:06,745 --> 00:18:09,343
I don't know.

529
00:18:09,367 --> 00:18:11,504
I'm just...

530
00:18:11,622 --> 00:18:13,792
feeling closer.

531
00:18:13,928 --> 00:18:15,129
Because I confided in you.

532
00:18:15,264 --> 00:18:16,861
Because the walls
are coming down,

533
00:18:16,885 --> 00:18:18,804
and I can feel it.

534
00:18:21,946 --> 00:18:24,511
What did I do to deserve you?

535
00:18:24,535 --> 00:18:26,036
Mm, well, we can talk about that

536
00:18:26,156 --> 00:18:30,798
over this delicious meal
that I made all by myself.

537
00:18:33,924 --> 00:18:41,022
♪ ♪

538
00:18:41,156 --> 00:18:42,157
To us.

539
00:18:46,869 --> 00:18:48,872
And then I said, "Helen",

540
00:18:49,008 --> 00:18:50,571
"that's no Pomeranian.

541
00:18:50,595 --> 00:18:52,180
"That's a Pomimo.

542
00:18:52,298 --> 00:18:54,184
You've been had."

543
00:18:54,303 --> 00:18:57,392
Oh-ho-ho, that is hilarious.

544
00:18:57,527 --> 00:18:59,123
Really, dogs, they are...

545
00:18:59,147 --> 00:19:00,593
They are so fascinating.

546
00:19:00,618 --> 00:19:01,902
Do you have many dogs, Louis?

547
00:19:02,071 --> 00:19:03,072
Hell, no.

548
00:19:05,328 --> 00:19:08,216
Building regulations...
It's a clusterf-f-f...

549
00:19:08,335 --> 00:19:09,837
I've been fighting them
for years.

550
00:19:09,972 --> 00:19:11,424
- Oh, that's horrible.
- Yes.

551
00:19:11,593 --> 00:19:13,656
As is what's going on
with your stock.

552
00:19:13,681 --> 00:19:14,742
Oh, Louis, we're having dinner.

553
00:19:14,766 --> 00:19:15,984
- Put that away.
- No, no, no.

554
00:19:16,103 --> 00:19:17,465
But I just thought you'd
be interested to know

555
00:19:17,490 --> 00:19:18,635
that we could skyrocket
the share price...

556
00:19:18,659 --> 00:19:20,305
Right now what I'm interested in

557
00:19:20,330 --> 00:19:21,508
is having another Manhattan

558
00:19:21,532 --> 00:19:23,061
and hearing what's
on the dessert list.

559
00:19:23,086 --> 00:19:24,514
Oh, you don't need a list.
Get the crème brûlée.

560
00:19:24,539 --> 00:19:25,567
Now, this stock issue, I have...

561
00:19:25,591 --> 00:19:27,020
Fax the papers to my office,

562
00:19:27,045 --> 00:19:28,490
and I'll review them
when I get home.

563
00:19:28,515 --> 00:19:29,526
When you get home?

564
00:19:29,550 --> 00:19:31,470
What the f-f...

565
00:19:31,639 --> 00:19:33,502
What the hell did we come
to dinner for, then?

566
00:19:33,527 --> 00:19:34,561
For this.

567
00:19:34,696 --> 00:19:35,697
What this?

568
00:19:35,698 --> 00:19:37,367
This.

569
00:19:39,039 --> 00:19:40,491
Okay.

570
00:19:40,626 --> 00:19:42,856
I don't know how Harvey handled
these quarterly reviews, but I...

571
00:19:42,881 --> 00:19:44,193
Oh, Harvey...

572
00:19:44,217 --> 00:19:45,646
was magnificent.

573
00:19:47,224 --> 00:19:48,870
Truth be told,
I was a little disappointed

574
00:19:48,894 --> 00:19:50,457
when I heard that
you'd be handling this

575
00:19:50,482 --> 00:19:51,494
instead of him,

576
00:19:51,518 --> 00:19:53,187
but I haven't seen
your cha-cha yet,

577
00:19:53,321 --> 00:19:54,489
so the jury's still out.

578
00:19:54,608 --> 00:19:56,778
- That was a lawyer joke.
- Yep. Got it.

579
00:19:56,913 --> 00:19:58,031
Yep.

580
00:19:58,166 --> 00:20:00,369
Listen, Joan,

581
00:20:00,504 --> 00:20:02,207
I think you're
gonna be really glad

582
00:20:02,342 --> 00:20:03,627
that it was me here tonight,

583
00:20:03,763 --> 00:20:05,743
because I already sent
a letter to your board.

584
00:20:05,767 --> 00:20:07,101
- You did what?
- And I...

585
00:20:07,220 --> 00:20:08,939
I notified them of this.

586
00:20:09,058 --> 00:20:10,086
That's what...

587
00:20:10,110 --> 00:20:11,896
What I'm trying to tell you.

588
00:20:16,541 --> 00:20:17,909
Why the hell
would you do something

589
00:20:18,045 --> 00:20:19,496
so patently stupid?

590
00:20:19,632 --> 00:20:20,966
Stupid?

591
00:20:21,085 --> 00:20:23,399
Hey, I didn't become
name partner being stupid.

592
00:20:23,424 --> 00:20:24,425
Didn't you?

593
00:20:24,426 --> 00:20:25,427
Two members of my board

594
00:20:25,429 --> 00:20:27,292
are about to reach
their term limits.

595
00:20:27,316 --> 00:20:29,379
At least one is being circled
by Glamour Cosmetics.

596
00:20:29,404 --> 00:20:32,253
You have just notified
that person of a product

597
00:20:32,278 --> 00:20:34,164
that I've had in R & D
for years,

598
00:20:34,282 --> 00:20:36,620
and now they can trade
information

599
00:20:36,754 --> 00:20:39,877
for a seat on the board
of my biggest competitor.

600
00:20:40,011 --> 00:20:41,106
Joan, I didn't know...

601
00:20:41,131 --> 00:20:43,184
Tell me, Mr. Litt,

602
00:20:43,303 --> 00:20:46,118
did you actually graduate
from law school,

603
00:20:46,142 --> 00:20:48,814
or did you just buy your way
onto the letterhead?

604
00:21:08,862 --> 00:21:10,487
Yeah, you better put
that bag down,

605
00:21:10,488 --> 00:21:11,790
because we're staying all night.

606
00:21:14,444 --> 00:21:15,725
Didn't go well with Joan,
did it?

607
00:21:15,731 --> 00:21:17,460
No, it didn't, because
you sandbagged me.

608
00:21:17,484 --> 00:21:18,652
I didn't sandbag you.

609
00:21:18,788 --> 00:21:20,099
Well, then what do you call
not telling me

610
00:21:20,123 --> 00:21:21,552
that Glamour was circling
her board members?

611
00:21:21,577 --> 00:21:22,805
I tried to tell you,

612
00:21:22,830 --> 00:21:24,393
but you couldn't hear me
through all of your rage.

613
00:21:24,417 --> 00:21:25,468
What I'm not hearing

614
00:21:25,586 --> 00:21:27,339
is the sound of you
putting your bag down,

615
00:21:27,474 --> 00:21:29,454
because the board members
are meeting tomorrow afternoon,

616
00:21:29,478 --> 00:21:31,531
and I only have until then
to fix this.

617
00:21:31,633 --> 00:21:32,818
And you want me to help you?

618
00:21:32,936 --> 00:21:34,465
You're the associate
on this case, aren't you?

619
00:21:34,490 --> 00:21:36,372
- So now I'm an associate?
- Hey, you know what?

620
00:21:36,494 --> 00:21:37,505
Now is not the time
to get into it.

621
00:21:37,530 --> 00:21:39,093
No, now is exactly the time
to get into it,

622
00:21:39,117 --> 00:21:42,122
because you have taken
every opportunity possible

623
00:21:42,258 --> 00:21:44,010
to make me feel like
I am nothing,

624
00:21:44,128 --> 00:21:46,108
and now, even though
you want something,

625
00:21:46,133 --> 00:21:47,775
you're still treating me
like I'm nothing.

626
00:21:47,887 --> 00:21:49,500
I'm treating you like
every other associate.

627
00:21:49,524 --> 00:21:50,585
That is bullshit,
and you know what?

628
00:21:50,610 --> 00:21:51,622
Even if it were true,

629
00:21:51,646 --> 00:21:53,232
you didn't used to
treat me that way.

630
00:21:54,986 --> 00:21:58,136
I didn't used to know you
lied to me on a daily basis.

631
00:21:58,160 --> 00:22:01,383
Louis, it would serve you right

632
00:22:01,502 --> 00:22:04,725
if I take my bag
and leave you here

633
00:22:04,843 --> 00:22:06,729
and go home to the man
that I love.

634
00:22:06,848 --> 00:22:07,849
So you're not gonna help.

635
00:22:07,983 --> 00:22:09,546
No, I'm gonna help you,

636
00:22:09,570 --> 00:22:11,500
but not because you deserve it.

637
00:22:11,525 --> 00:22:13,839
I'll do it because I am
an associate,

638
00:22:13,864 --> 00:22:17,431
and I am a professional,
which means I am capable

639
00:22:17,455 --> 00:22:20,376
of putting the personal aside
in order to do my job.

640
00:22:25,390 --> 00:22:26,391
And one of those, please.

641
00:22:26,476 --> 00:22:28,278
Just what I was in the mood for.

642
00:22:28,396 --> 00:22:29,541
Ah, you're getting a bagel.

643
00:22:29,566 --> 00:22:30,761
That means you kicked ass.

644
00:22:30,786 --> 00:22:32,622
Which I did.

645
00:22:32,740 --> 00:22:33,824
You called up the TSA,

646
00:22:33,960 --> 00:22:35,629
busted up their
national security defense?

647
00:22:35,747 --> 00:22:37,443
No, I used their defense.

648
00:22:37,467 --> 00:22:38,946
Gerard's gonna testify
under seal

649
00:22:38,971 --> 00:22:40,924
because it's a matter
of national security.

650
00:22:41,059 --> 00:22:42,143
And the judge bought that?

651
00:22:42,261 --> 00:22:43,289
What's not to buy?

652
00:22:43,314 --> 00:22:44,732
The TSA made
the argument for us.

653
00:22:44,851 --> 00:22:45,796
And what did Brady say?

654
00:22:45,820 --> 00:22:48,000
That's the best part about it.

655
00:22:48,025 --> 00:22:49,778
He doesn't even know it.

656
00:22:49,912 --> 00:22:52,009
It's a matter
of national security.

657
00:22:52,034 --> 00:22:53,312
We testify under seal,

658
00:22:53,337 --> 00:22:56,009
the judge realizes that Gerard
is a degenerate gambler...

659
00:22:56,126 --> 00:22:57,127
But a fair mediator.

660
00:22:57,129 --> 00:22:58,993
The case gets dismissed,
and Garrett Brady

661
00:22:59,017 --> 00:23:00,970
and Harvard Law
never know it happened.

662
00:23:01,105 --> 00:23:02,668
You thought of all
of that on your own?

663
00:23:02,692 --> 00:23:04,288
You think you're the only
one who can come up

664
00:23:04,312 --> 00:23:05,948
with an intelligent solution?

665
00:23:06,066 --> 00:23:07,150
You are 1 for 400

666
00:23:07,286 --> 00:23:08,798
in the time
we've worked together.

667
00:23:08,823 --> 00:23:11,136
Okay, smart guy, since
I did your job for you,

668
00:23:11,161 --> 00:23:12,747
you're gonna do my job for me.

669
00:23:12,882 --> 00:23:14,000
You want me to prep Gerard

670
00:23:14,135 --> 00:23:15,230
because you don't
want to sit in a room

671
00:23:15,254 --> 00:23:16,649
and listen to him talk
for two hours.

672
00:23:16,674 --> 00:23:18,320
I didn't want to 15 years ago,

673
00:23:18,344 --> 00:23:19,562
and I don't want to now.

674
00:23:19,681 --> 00:23:21,828
We only get one shot at this,

675
00:23:21,853 --> 00:23:24,000
and his testimony
better be rock solid.

676
00:23:24,024 --> 00:23:25,025
Thanks.

677
00:23:25,160 --> 00:23:28,248
Oh, yeah, sure, help yourself!

678
00:23:28,367 --> 00:23:29,585
Dick.

679
00:23:36,218 --> 00:23:38,055
I see you haven't slept.

680
00:23:38,190 --> 00:23:39,786
I have a lot of work
that needs attending to.

681
00:23:39,810 --> 00:23:41,780
I bet you do, considering
the phone call

682
00:23:41,898 --> 00:23:43,259
I got from Joan Walsh
this morning.

683
00:23:43,284 --> 00:23:44,987
She called you?

684
00:23:45,123 --> 00:23:47,019
She wanted to know what
the other name partners

685
00:23:47,043 --> 00:23:49,391
were going to do about the one
that screwed the pooch.

686
00:23:49,415 --> 00:23:50,727
Oh, come on, that is not fair.

687
00:23:50,752 --> 00:23:51,947
I didn't have all
the information...

688
00:23:51,971 --> 00:23:53,389
You had enough information

689
00:23:53,508 --> 00:23:55,060
to make a deal
to get her from Harvey,

690
00:23:55,179 --> 00:23:56,959
and part of that deal was
you backing me with Jeff.

691
00:23:56,983 --> 00:23:58,184
Oh, so that's why you're here.

692
00:23:58,269 --> 00:23:59,498
You don't trust
I'm still gonna do it?

693
00:23:59,522 --> 00:24:00,856
Because you haven't done it yet,

694
00:24:00,992 --> 00:24:02,834
and you have a history
of making poor decisions

695
00:24:02,947 --> 00:24:04,281
when things aren't
going your way.

696
00:24:04,417 --> 00:24:05,929
The only poor decision
I've made is agreeing

697
00:24:05,954 --> 00:24:07,182
to cover for you
in the first place.

698
00:24:07,206 --> 00:24:08,518
You didn't think that
was such a bad idea

699
00:24:08,543 --> 00:24:10,021
when you were using it
to get what you wanted.

700
00:24:10,046 --> 00:24:11,776
And now you're threatening
to take that thing away.

701
00:24:11,800 --> 00:24:13,386
Louis, you want to keep Joan,

702
00:24:13,520 --> 00:24:14,532
that's on you,

703
00:24:14,557 --> 00:24:16,860
but I held up my end
of the bargain.

704
00:24:16,979 --> 00:24:18,480
You better hold up yours.

705
00:24:24,162 --> 00:24:26,583
I just want to go over it
one more time, Professor.

706
00:24:26,717 --> 00:24:28,146
How much money was in that pot?

707
00:24:28,171 --> 00:24:30,869
I'm tried of going over it.

708
00:24:30,894 --> 00:24:32,574
Why do we have to keep replaying

709
00:24:32,598 --> 00:24:34,043
every moment of this game?

710
00:24:34,068 --> 00:24:35,998
Because your entire case
depends on it.

711
00:24:36,022 --> 00:24:39,255
My case depends on the fact
that I won that money gambling,

712
00:24:39,280 --> 00:24:41,033
not whether I won it
with a flush.

713
00:24:41,167 --> 00:24:43,087
Your case depends on
the judge believing you,

714
00:24:43,206 --> 00:24:45,236
and if he finds any holes
in your testimony, then we...

715
00:24:45,260 --> 00:24:47,714
I gave you the names of
everyone I knew at that game.

716
00:24:47,850 --> 00:24:50,163
But none of those men were
there when you won that money.

717
00:24:50,188 --> 00:24:52,776
I can't help it if I didn't
get the name of the guy I beat.

718
00:24:52,894 --> 00:24:55,782
Which is why your story
needs to be rock solid.

719
00:24:59,376 --> 00:25:01,079
Okay.

720
00:25:01,213 --> 00:25:02,748
Go ahead.

721
00:25:02,884 --> 00:25:04,503
So I ask you again, Professor,

722
00:25:04,637 --> 00:25:06,317
how much money
was in the final pot?

723
00:25:06,342 --> 00:25:08,178
Roughly $12,000.

724
00:25:08,313 --> 00:25:09,314
And you won that hand.

725
00:25:09,432 --> 00:25:10,995
As I said before, I won,

726
00:25:11,019 --> 00:25:12,081
and then I cashed out.

727
00:25:12,105 --> 00:25:13,186
And what did you have again?

728
00:25:13,190 --> 00:25:14,218
A queen-high flush.

729
00:25:14,243 --> 00:25:15,638
And who did you beat?

730
00:25:15,663 --> 00:25:17,115
I told you,
I didn't get his name.

731
00:25:17,284 --> 00:25:18,451
Okay, so what did he have?

732
00:25:18,586 --> 00:25:21,374
Two pair, queens over sixes.

733
00:25:24,935 --> 00:25:25,946
Wait a second.

734
00:25:25,970 --> 00:25:28,308
You said before that
the man next to you

735
00:25:28,442 --> 00:25:29,620
folded with two queens up,

736
00:25:29,645 --> 00:25:30,924
and now this guy has two queens,

737
00:25:30,948 --> 00:25:32,009
and you had a queen-high flush?

738
00:25:32,034 --> 00:25:34,372
I said that the man next to me

739
00:25:34,489 --> 00:25:35,490
folded with two kings.

740
00:25:35,625 --> 00:25:36,553
No, you didn't.

741
00:25:36,578 --> 00:25:37,629
You heard me wrong.

742
00:25:37,747 --> 00:25:39,526
No, I didn't.

743
00:25:39,550 --> 00:25:41,062
Is this part of prepping me,

744
00:25:41,087 --> 00:25:42,505
or are you accusing me
of something?

745
00:25:42,641 --> 00:25:43,953
I'm trying to get
your story to line up.

746
00:25:43,978 --> 00:25:46,326
- My story does line up.
- Not to me, it doesn't.

747
00:25:46,350 --> 00:25:48,046
Look, young man, if you're
gonna sit over there

748
00:25:48,070 --> 00:25:49,131
and call me a liar...

749
00:25:49,156 --> 00:25:50,241
I'm not calling you a liar,

750
00:25:50,359 --> 00:25:52,081
but if you say tomorrow
what you said today,

751
00:25:52,197 --> 00:25:53,342
we're gonna be
in a lot of trouble,

752
00:25:53,366 --> 00:25:54,427
because where I come from,

753
00:25:54,452 --> 00:25:56,065
there are only
four queens in a deck.

754
00:25:56,089 --> 00:25:57,925
I said two kings,

755
00:25:58,043 --> 00:26:00,608
and I'm gonna say that
again tomorrow.

756
00:26:00,633 --> 00:26:03,438
So you do your job,

757
00:26:03,555 --> 00:26:05,108
and I'm gonna do mine.

758
00:26:11,908 --> 00:26:12,970
He's lying.

759
00:26:12,995 --> 00:26:14,129
What are you talking about?

760
00:26:14,247 --> 00:26:15,608
Gerard's story about
winning all that money

761
00:26:15,633 --> 00:26:16,778
playing poker is bullshit.

762
00:26:16,803 --> 00:26:18,589
All right, slow down.
What the hell happened?

763
00:26:18,724 --> 00:26:20,487
I did the math,
and the hands don't add up.

764
00:26:20,511 --> 00:26:21,906
What do you mean
you did the math?

765
00:26:21,931 --> 00:26:23,878
I mean first he said that he
drew a queen on fourth street,

766
00:26:23,903 --> 00:26:25,248
and then when I pressed
him about it, he...

767
00:26:25,272 --> 00:26:26,323
Wait a second.

768
00:26:26,442 --> 00:26:28,088
This conclusion is based
on him recalling hands

769
00:26:28,112 --> 00:26:29,507
under cross-examination?

770
00:26:29,532 --> 00:26:30,593
Harvey, I got kicked out

771
00:26:30,617 --> 00:26:32,018
of Atlantic City
for counting cards.

772
00:26:32,121 --> 00:26:33,599
- I know this shit.
- It doesn't mean he's lying.

773
00:26:33,624 --> 00:26:35,153
I got a little experience
with that too,

774
00:26:35,178 --> 00:26:36,596
and I'm telling you, he was.

775
00:26:36,715 --> 00:26:38,851
- Or maybe he's tired.
- Or maybe I'm right.

776
00:26:38,970 --> 00:26:40,950
Or maybe you don't know what
the hell you're talking about.

777
00:26:40,975 --> 00:26:43,563
- Why are you defending him?
- Because you asked me to.

778
00:26:48,408 --> 00:26:50,545
Look, Harvey,

779
00:26:50,663 --> 00:26:52,249
I'm not saying that
he took a bribe.

780
00:26:52,384 --> 00:26:56,151
I'm just saying that he didn't
get that money playing poker.

781
00:26:56,176 --> 00:26:59,399
Well, unless he admitted that,
he's testifying tomorrow.

782
00:27:01,021 --> 00:27:04,528
Since when do you stick
your head in the sand?

783
00:27:04,695 --> 00:27:06,665
- Did he admit it?
- No, he didn't.

784
00:27:06,784 --> 00:27:08,931
But he screwed up the details,
and he shouldn't have,

785
00:27:08,956 --> 00:27:11,760
because people who are telling
the truth get it right.

786
00:27:11,879 --> 00:27:14,049
And you know it.

787
00:27:28,823 --> 00:27:29,834
What's that?

788
00:27:29,858 --> 00:27:31,193
Jacks full of fours.

789
00:27:31,329 --> 00:27:32,998
I can see that, but why...

790
00:27:33,116 --> 00:27:34,812
Why is it staring you
in the face?

791
00:27:34,836 --> 00:27:37,518
It's what I threw down
the last time I won a huge hand.

792
00:27:37,543 --> 00:27:41,828
It was six weeks ago,
and I can remember every hand

793
00:27:41,852 --> 00:27:43,615
that every player
at that table had.

794
00:27:43,640 --> 00:27:45,169
Now, if you won money
the other night,

795
00:27:45,194 --> 00:27:46,228
you'd remember it too.

796
00:27:46,363 --> 00:27:47,480
I do remember,

797
00:27:47,649 --> 00:27:49,170
and as I explained
to your associate...

798
00:27:49,286 --> 00:27:51,707
Yeah, stop bullshitting me.

799
00:27:51,825 --> 00:27:54,095
Where the hell did that
money really come from?

800
00:27:54,214 --> 00:27:55,392
'Cause if you don't
tell me the truth,

801
00:27:55,417 --> 00:27:56,858
I'm canceling
that hearing right now.

802
00:27:59,593 --> 00:28:01,873
It came...

803
00:28:01,898 --> 00:28:03,684
from a student of mine.

804
00:28:03,820 --> 00:28:04,987
For what?

805
00:28:05,089 --> 00:28:07,526
In exchange
for changing his grade.

806
00:28:07,662 --> 00:28:10,033
Jesus Christ. For $25,000?

807
00:28:10,167 --> 00:28:11,930
He was going to fail my class,

808
00:28:11,954 --> 00:28:13,818
and that would've stopped him
from getting an offer from...

809
00:28:13,843 --> 00:28:15,439
You goddamn hypocrite.

810
00:28:15,463 --> 00:28:17,884
You preach about ethics,
and you do this?

811
00:28:18,052 --> 00:28:19,938
This is about ethics.

812
00:28:20,057 --> 00:28:21,893
And you don't have
any idea why I did it.

813
00:28:22,027 --> 00:28:23,897
I don't care why you did it.

814
00:28:24,032 --> 00:28:25,712
I care about what
you're making me do,

815
00:28:25,736 --> 00:28:27,289
because I am not
suborning perjury.

816
00:28:27,407 --> 00:28:30,328
Well, you tell me that you've
never done anything worse.

817
00:28:32,251 --> 00:28:34,304
I knew it.

818
00:28:34,423 --> 00:28:37,071
You would do it
for someone else...

819
00:28:37,096 --> 00:28:38,397
but not for me.

820
00:28:38,516 --> 00:28:40,579
You know what, Professor?

821
00:28:40,603 --> 00:28:42,656
There's a small part of me
that actually thought

822
00:28:42,775 --> 00:28:45,173
that you came to me because
you thought I'm the best,

823
00:28:45,197 --> 00:28:47,367
but you just think I'll do
whatever it takes to win.

824
00:28:47,503 --> 00:28:49,706
Isn't that what
makes you the best?

825
00:28:51,261 --> 00:28:52,782
Get someone else
to do your dirty work,

826
00:28:52,798 --> 00:28:54,684
because I'm not
suborning perjury.

827
00:29:10,422 --> 00:29:11,567
What are you doing?

828
00:29:12,727 --> 00:29:13,929
Getting my blood flowing.

829
00:29:14,064 --> 00:29:15,349
I've been sitting here
all night,

830
00:29:15,483 --> 00:29:18,321
and restless leg syndrome
kills 14 people every hour.

831
00:29:18,440 --> 00:29:19,635
I don't think that's accurate.

832
00:29:19,660 --> 00:29:21,423
I don't care what you think.
What do you have?

833
00:29:21,447 --> 00:29:23,083
I found a way to fix
things with Joan.

834
00:29:28,798 --> 00:29:30,279
Okay, you're arguing
anything in R & D

835
00:29:30,300 --> 00:29:31,445
is the intellectual property

836
00:29:31,470 --> 00:29:32,832
of the person
who suggested the product?

837
00:29:32,857 --> 00:29:34,943
Until such time that
the results become public.

838
00:29:35,062 --> 00:29:36,792
Which they did the second
I sent the board that letter.

839
00:29:36,816 --> 00:29:37,877
Except board members are subject

840
00:29:37,901 --> 00:29:39,046
to the nondisclosure agreement.

841
00:29:39,071 --> 00:29:40,299
Well, the board members
haven't signed

842
00:29:40,323 --> 00:29:41,301
a nondisclosure agreement.

843
00:29:41,326 --> 00:29:43,440
Yet.

844
00:29:43,464 --> 00:29:44,892
What's to stop them
from refusing?

845
00:29:44,917 --> 00:29:45,945
Nothing, but if they do,

846
00:29:45,970 --> 00:29:47,138
then the noncompete kicks in.

847
00:29:47,256 --> 00:29:49,152
Preventing them from revealing
the contents of my letter

848
00:29:49,177 --> 00:29:50,489
under threat of prosecution.

849
00:29:50,514 --> 00:29:52,294
Specifically
corporate espionage.

850
00:29:52,318 --> 00:29:54,271
Oh, my God.
You got this idea from...

851
00:29:54,406 --> 00:29:55,751
- Our bylaws.
- My bylaws.

852
00:29:55,775 --> 00:29:58,591
Rachel, holy shit, this is...

853
00:29:58,616 --> 00:30:00,034
acceptable.

854
00:30:02,174 --> 00:30:04,294
I think the word you're
looking for is "awesome."

855
00:30:04,463 --> 00:30:06,683
Well, the word I'm saying
is, "Get out",

856
00:30:06,801 --> 00:30:08,113
because I have a meeting
to prepare for."

857
00:30:08,137 --> 00:30:10,334
You know what, Louis?
I have been working all night.

858
00:30:10,359 --> 00:30:12,673
And this gets your ass
out of a major sling,

859
00:30:12,698 --> 00:30:14,377
so instead of dismissing me,

860
00:30:14,401 --> 00:30:15,880
you should be asking me
to come with you.

861
00:30:15,905 --> 00:30:17,206
Excuse me, Miss Professional.

862
00:30:17,325 --> 00:30:18,971
You wanted me to treat you
like every other associate.

863
00:30:18,995 --> 00:30:20,775
- Now I am.
- By acting as if I did nothing?

864
00:30:20,800 --> 00:30:22,897
No, by acknowledging
you did acceptable work.

865
00:30:22,921 --> 00:30:24,149
Letting you come with me
is something

866
00:30:24,174 --> 00:30:26,094
that I would only do for you
if we were friends,

867
00:30:26,229 --> 00:30:27,230
which we are not.

868
00:30:38,924 --> 00:30:41,512
You canceled the hearing.

869
00:30:41,631 --> 00:30:43,267
You were right.

870
00:30:43,385 --> 00:30:46,450
He was lying.

871
00:30:46,475 --> 00:30:48,779
I'm sorry.

872
00:30:48,897 --> 00:30:50,209
You know, I knew
he was a hypocrite

873
00:30:50,234 --> 00:30:51,702
after I found out
about the gambling.

874
00:30:51,821 --> 00:30:54,626
I never thought
he'd sell out Harvard.

875
00:30:56,965 --> 00:30:58,167
What are you talking about?

876
00:30:58,302 --> 00:30:59,564
He did take the bribe,

877
00:30:59,589 --> 00:31:01,619
but it had nothing to do
with the accident victims.

878
00:31:01,643 --> 00:31:03,813
He did it to change
someone's grade.

879
00:31:05,986 --> 00:31:06,998
Why would he do that?

880
00:31:07,022 --> 00:31:08,183
What difference does it make?

881
00:31:08,275 --> 00:31:10,328
Either way, he was gonna
let me suborn perjury.

882
00:31:10,447 --> 00:31:12,677
It makes a difference because
we still have to win this case.

883
00:31:12,702 --> 00:31:14,649
Oh, I don't give a shit
about winning this case.

884
00:31:17,296 --> 00:31:19,299
I've never heard you say
anything like that before.

885
00:31:19,433 --> 00:31:22,617
You... you care
about winning every case,

886
00:31:22,642 --> 00:31:23,703
every game, every argument.

887
00:31:23,727 --> 00:31:24,728
Did you hear me?

888
00:31:24,863 --> 00:31:26,459
He was gonna let me
suborn perjury.

889
00:31:26,484 --> 00:31:28,180
And so would
every client you have

890
00:31:28,204 --> 00:31:29,549
if they thought
they'd get away with it.

891
00:31:29,574 --> 00:31:30,659
He's not every client.

892
00:31:30,793 --> 00:31:32,356
No, he's the one you hated
in the first place.

893
00:31:32,380 --> 00:31:34,143
- I didn't hate him.
- Harvey, what is going on here?

894
00:31:34,167 --> 00:31:38,007
I thought he was better than us.

895
00:31:38,144 --> 00:31:40,147
I sat in that class
and listened to him talk

896
00:31:40,265 --> 00:31:43,320
about what kind
of lawyers we should be,

897
00:31:43,438 --> 00:31:45,860
and I always let him down
because I knew

898
00:31:45,995 --> 00:31:48,677
that wasn't the kind
of lawyer that wins.

899
00:31:48,701 --> 00:31:50,370
And I wanted to win.

900
00:31:50,505 --> 00:31:52,375
So I'd argue with him,

901
00:31:52,509 --> 00:31:54,596
and he'd look down on me.

902
00:31:56,435 --> 00:32:00,537
And now instead of you
letting him down,

903
00:32:00,562 --> 00:32:01,813
he let you down.

904
00:32:01,948 --> 00:32:04,869
He turned out to be
no better than any of us.

905
00:32:11,754 --> 00:32:15,310
So then let's make him
better than us.

906
00:32:25,919 --> 00:32:26,954
Miss Walsh.

907
00:32:27,089 --> 00:32:28,842
You are not on my schedule
today.

908
00:32:28,960 --> 00:32:31,524
Ah, ah, Miss Walsh,
please take a look at this.

909
00:32:31,549 --> 00:32:32,634
What is it?

910
00:32:32,768 --> 00:32:33,947
It's a chance
to make things right.

911
00:32:33,972 --> 00:32:35,356
Ha.

912
00:32:36,979 --> 00:32:39,400
You cannot call
board members employees

913
00:32:39,534 --> 00:32:41,848
based on them having access
to an expense account.

914
00:32:41,873 --> 00:32:43,636
Not just an expense account.

915
00:32:43,660 --> 00:32:45,974
They have corporate cards
and standing offices,

916
00:32:45,999 --> 00:32:48,029
which, as defined
by section 14.2

917
00:32:48,054 --> 00:32:49,773
of the Internal Revenue Code,

918
00:32:49,874 --> 00:32:51,309
makes them employees.

919
00:32:51,428 --> 00:32:53,097
Well, Mr. Litt,

920
00:32:53,232 --> 00:32:56,154
seems I won't be demanding
a new point person after all.

921
00:32:56,273 --> 00:32:58,409
I'm glad to hear that.

922
00:32:58,527 --> 00:32:59,555
Are you?

923
00:32:59,580 --> 00:33:00,614
Of course I am.

924
00:33:00,749 --> 00:33:02,284
You're my first client
as name partner.

925
00:33:02,419 --> 00:33:03,620
You're very important to me.

926
00:33:05,293 --> 00:33:06,856
Well, I suppose
we'll find out the truth

927
00:33:06,880 --> 00:33:08,381
when someone else
makes name partner.

928
00:33:08,517 --> 00:33:09,885
What are you talking about?

929
00:33:10,020 --> 00:33:11,438
I'm not an idiot.

930
00:33:11,557 --> 00:33:13,587
I know that no one in your firm
wants to deal with me.

931
00:33:13,612 --> 00:33:14,613
That's not true.

932
00:33:14,731 --> 00:33:15,792
In fact, I fought for you.

933
00:33:15,817 --> 00:33:17,547
You may have thought
you were fighting for me,

934
00:33:17,571 --> 00:33:19,574
but I know that Jessica
dumped me on Harvey,

935
00:33:19,709 --> 00:33:22,391
and it seems that the second
you made name partner,

936
00:33:22,415 --> 00:33:23,883
Harvey did the same thing
to you.

937
00:33:26,842 --> 00:33:29,156
Oh, you didn't know that,
did you?

938
00:33:29,181 --> 00:33:31,579
Then maybe we were
meant for each other,

939
00:33:31,603 --> 00:33:33,941
since we're both
left out of the club.

940
00:33:42,678 --> 00:33:43,846
You betrayed me.

941
00:33:43,965 --> 00:33:45,828
You make this big speech
about repairing our friendship,

942
00:33:45,853 --> 00:33:46,864
and all it was was more words.

943
00:33:46,888 --> 00:33:47,866
What are you talking about?

944
00:33:47,890 --> 00:33:49,693
You convinced me to take Joan,

945
00:33:49,812 --> 00:33:51,508
while conveniently
leaving out the fact

946
00:33:51,532 --> 00:33:54,320
you're doing Harvey a favor.

947
00:33:54,456 --> 00:33:55,717
That's not why I did it, Louis.

948
00:33:55,741 --> 00:33:57,972
Well, just tell me right now,
can he stand her?

949
00:33:57,997 --> 00:33:59,498
No, but he was gonna keep her

950
00:33:59,634 --> 00:34:00,668
because you...

951
00:34:00,803 --> 00:34:01,948
Hurt his precious feelings.
I know.

952
00:34:01,972 --> 00:34:02,900
I felt so awful about that.

953
00:34:02,925 --> 00:34:04,206
You know what, Louis?
You should.

954
00:34:04,228 --> 00:34:05,824
And while you're at it,
you should feel pretty awful

955
00:34:05,848 --> 00:34:07,209
about being a dick to me
right now.

956
00:34:07,318 --> 00:34:08,319
You lied to me again.

957
00:34:08,321 --> 00:34:10,859
No, Louis.
I fought for you... again.

958
00:34:10,993 --> 00:34:11,994
No.

959
00:34:11,995 --> 00:34:13,197
You made Joan sound important.

960
00:34:13,365 --> 00:34:15,007
"The first client
that Jessica gave Harvey

961
00:34:15,119 --> 00:34:16,264
when he made name partner."

962
00:34:16,289 --> 00:34:17,817
She is important, Louis,
but you can't see that

963
00:34:17,842 --> 00:34:19,021
because you didn't
want a client.

964
00:34:19,045 --> 00:34:20,824
You just wanted to take
something away from Harvey.

965
00:34:20,849 --> 00:34:21,777
What I want is respect.

966
00:34:21,801 --> 00:34:22,936
Then get out of your own way

967
00:34:23,055 --> 00:34:25,559
and get on the goddamn team.

968
00:34:27,314 --> 00:34:28,960
You mean the team that kept
Mike's secret from me?

969
00:34:28,984 --> 00:34:30,096
No, Louis!

970
00:34:30,121 --> 00:34:31,957
I mean the team that
protected its own,

971
00:34:32,075 --> 00:34:34,629
because that's what teams do.

972
00:34:36,135 --> 00:34:37,731
And, you know, I shouldn't
even be telling you this

973
00:34:37,755 --> 00:34:38,900
because she wasn't going to,

974
00:34:38,924 --> 00:34:40,236
but if you need
a little bit more evidence

975
00:34:40,261 --> 00:34:41,729
of what we do for each other,

976
00:34:41,847 --> 00:34:42,732
then take a look at Rachel,

977
00:34:42,849 --> 00:34:44,151
because she got Katrina a job.

978
00:34:44,270 --> 00:34:45,321
- What?
- That's right.

979
00:34:45,439 --> 00:34:46,824
Your former associate,

980
00:34:46,942 --> 00:34:49,112
and you've been treating
Rachel like shit.

981
00:34:49,247 --> 00:34:50,665
So, if you're done
yelling at me,

982
00:34:50,784 --> 00:34:52,837
then I suggest you go fix
one of the thousand things

983
00:34:52,956 --> 00:34:54,257
that you have screwed up lately,

984
00:34:54,376 --> 00:34:58,384
because the rest of us,
we are done fighting for you.

985
00:35:11,955 --> 00:35:13,323
Mr. Ross.

986
00:35:13,492 --> 00:35:14,603
Ah, you must be Ian.

987
00:35:14,627 --> 00:35:16,028
And, please,
don't call me Mr. Ross.

988
00:35:16,047 --> 00:35:17,332
- Mike is fine.
- Ah, sure.

989
00:35:17,467 --> 00:35:19,137
Hey, thanks for your call, Mike.

990
00:35:19,255 --> 00:35:20,841
Pearson Specter is a great firm.

991
00:35:20,975 --> 00:35:22,393
Ah, well, you're
a great candidate.

992
00:35:22,512 --> 00:35:24,292
I'm a little curious why
you're still interviewing.

993
00:35:24,317 --> 00:35:26,069
I heard you had
a solid offer at Skadden.

994
00:35:26,187 --> 00:35:28,919
I do, but Skadden Arps
is no Pearson Specter.

995
00:35:28,944 --> 00:35:30,245
Are you sure it's not

996
00:35:30,364 --> 00:35:32,427
because you're worried
they'll find out that you failed.

997
00:35:32,451 --> 00:35:34,231
Professor Gerard's
legal ethics class?

998
00:35:34,256 --> 00:35:36,353
- What?
- Oh, shit.

999
00:35:36,377 --> 00:35:37,378
You don't know.

1000
00:35:37,380 --> 00:35:38,909
He hasn't changed your grade,

1001
00:35:38,934 --> 00:35:41,939
but he still has your $25,000.

1002
00:35:43,360 --> 00:35:44,288
Who the hell are you?

1003
00:35:44,313 --> 00:35:45,708
I'm exactly who I said I was.

1004
00:35:45,732 --> 00:35:46,733
The only thing I left out

1005
00:35:46,735 --> 00:35:48,621
is that Professor Gerard
is my client.

1006
00:35:48,739 --> 00:35:50,458
Well, he can't be
in trouble for this.

1007
00:35:50,577 --> 00:35:51,578
I'd know.

1008
00:35:51,579 --> 00:35:52,640
He's not.

1009
00:35:52,664 --> 00:35:54,059
He's being accused
of accepting a bribe

1010
00:35:54,084 --> 00:35:55,647
while conducting
a federal mediation

1011
00:35:55,671 --> 00:35:57,006
because of this.

1012
00:35:57,141 --> 00:35:58,286
That's not my problem.

1013
00:35:58,311 --> 00:35:59,479
It's your problem now,

1014
00:35:59,597 --> 00:36:02,101
which is why you're
gonna sign this.

1015
00:36:04,859 --> 00:36:05,860
What is that?

1016
00:36:05,861 --> 00:36:06,973
It's a sworn affidavit

1017
00:36:06,998 --> 00:36:09,385
stating the money that
you paid Gerard is a loan.

1018
00:36:11,792 --> 00:36:13,176
Well, what happens to my grade?

1019
00:36:13,295 --> 00:36:15,181
It stays the same
because Henry Gerard

1020
00:36:15,300 --> 00:36:17,447
doesn't take money
to change grades.

1021
00:36:17,471 --> 00:36:18,866
That's bullshit. We had a deal.

1022
00:36:18,891 --> 00:36:21,289
Yeah, well, consider this your
first lesson in the real world.

1023
00:36:21,313 --> 00:36:22,960
Deals change.

1024
00:36:22,985 --> 00:36:25,656
I don't care what world it is.

1025
00:36:25,790 --> 00:36:27,353
I'm not signing anything.

1026
00:36:27,377 --> 00:36:28,378
That's too bad,

1027
00:36:28,380 --> 00:36:30,500
because the truth will come out.

1028
00:36:30,634 --> 00:36:32,865
And this way,
you're failing a class

1029
00:36:32,890 --> 00:36:34,318
instead of getting thrown
out of school

1030
00:36:34,343 --> 00:36:35,946
for bribing a professor.

1031
00:36:36,047 --> 00:36:37,492
It's up to you, Ian.

1032
00:36:37,517 --> 00:36:38,568
You want an F,

1033
00:36:38,687 --> 00:36:40,823
or do you want to not have
a legal career at all?

1034
00:36:48,175 --> 00:36:51,213
So I sign this, and the
bribery allegations are gone?

1035
00:36:51,349 --> 00:36:54,220
And no one ever knows a thing.

1036
00:36:54,356 --> 00:36:57,706
But I still have to pay
Ian back the money.

1037
00:36:57,730 --> 00:36:59,499
That's the way loans work.

1038
00:36:59,635 --> 00:37:01,438
You say that like
I am a monster.

1039
00:37:01,539 --> 00:37:03,375
I say it like it's true.

1040
00:37:06,417 --> 00:37:09,005
You know...

1041
00:37:09,140 --> 00:37:11,988
you never let me tell you
what the money was for.

1042
00:37:12,013 --> 00:37:14,367
You didn't listen to me
when I told you I don't care.

1043
00:37:14,502 --> 00:37:15,670
Who's the monster now?

1044
00:37:15,772 --> 00:37:17,541
I don't care
because you always said

1045
00:37:17,642 --> 00:37:20,531
the circumstances don't matter.

1046
00:37:20,666 --> 00:37:22,479
Well, do you care
that after Mike grilled me,

1047
00:37:22,503 --> 00:37:23,704
I was so impressed with him

1048
00:37:23,840 --> 00:37:25,459
that I wonder why
I'd forgotten him.

1049
00:37:25,594 --> 00:37:28,800
So I looked through
my old records,

1050
00:37:28,935 --> 00:37:30,638
just to see how he did,

1051
00:37:30,772 --> 00:37:33,059
but I couldn't find
any record of him

1052
00:37:33,195 --> 00:37:35,341
ever being in my class.

1053
00:37:35,366 --> 00:37:37,203
Just like they're not
gonna find any record

1054
00:37:37,321 --> 00:37:39,742
of you accepting a bribe
from a student.

1055
00:37:42,299 --> 00:37:43,383
You saying we're even?

1056
00:37:43,502 --> 00:37:45,149
I'm saying you got
a two-for-one,

1057
00:37:45,173 --> 00:37:46,701
because they're also
not gonna find any record

1058
00:37:46,726 --> 00:37:48,061
of you gambling last year.

1059
00:37:48,180 --> 00:37:50,517
That's why you came to see me
back then, isn't it?

1060
00:37:50,652 --> 00:37:53,083
You didn't want anyone
to find out about him.

1061
00:37:53,107 --> 00:37:54,552
I'm not gonna tell you
why I came

1062
00:37:54,577 --> 00:37:56,413
to see you last year, Henry,

1063
00:37:56,531 --> 00:37:59,063
because the circumstances
don't matter.

1064
00:38:01,008 --> 00:38:04,692
You really did pay
attention in my class.

1065
00:38:04,717 --> 00:38:07,940
A lot more than you think.

1066
00:38:08,058 --> 00:38:10,529
I'm sorry I let you down,
Mr. Specter.

1067
00:38:14,907 --> 00:38:16,660
Professor...

1068
00:38:18,916 --> 00:38:21,254
Don't worry about
paying back that loan.

1069
00:38:21,422 --> 00:38:22,757
I got it.

1070
00:38:25,932 --> 00:38:33,782
♪ ♪

1071
00:39:03,819 --> 00:39:04,903
Louis...

1072
00:39:05,022 --> 00:39:06,741
what can I do for you?

1073
00:39:06,859 --> 00:39:08,505
The question isn't what
you can do for me, Jeff,

1074
00:39:08,529 --> 00:39:09,974
but it's a matter
of what you're gonna do,

1075
00:39:09,999 --> 00:39:11,585
which is cut the bullshit
right now.

1076
00:39:11,703 --> 00:39:13,589
- What?
- You heard me.

1077
00:39:13,708 --> 00:39:15,344
I know Jessica told you
about Hardman.

1078
00:39:15,462 --> 00:39:16,523
Yeah, she did tell me,

1079
00:39:16,548 --> 00:39:18,245
and I have refrained
from coming to see you

1080
00:39:18,269 --> 00:39:19,888
about blackmailing her
out of courtesy.

1081
00:39:20,022 --> 00:39:21,251
Courtesy?

1082
00:39:21,276 --> 00:39:24,030
You haven't so much as
wished me a congratulations.

1083
00:39:24,149 --> 00:39:25,344
You want me to kiss
the ring, Louis,

1084
00:39:25,368 --> 00:39:26,380
after what you did?

1085
00:39:26,404 --> 00:39:27,432
You're damn right I do,

1086
00:39:27,457 --> 00:39:29,460
because I don't care
how it got up there.

1087
00:39:29,578 --> 00:39:31,298
My name is on that wall.

1088
00:39:31,416 --> 00:39:36,092
And if I had a crowbar handy...

1089
00:39:36,226 --> 00:39:37,405
I would pry it off.

1090
00:39:37,430 --> 00:39:38,825
Well, Jeff, you don't.

1091
00:39:38,850 --> 00:39:40,496
So the question you got
to ask yourself is,

1092
00:39:40,520 --> 00:39:42,667
"Do you want to stick
with the team?"

1093
00:39:42,692 --> 00:39:44,422
Because my name
is up there to stay

1094
00:39:44,446 --> 00:39:45,780
whether you like it or not.

1095
00:39:45,916 --> 00:39:53,799
♪ ♪

1096
00:40:19,576 --> 00:40:21,389
Hey.

1097
00:40:21,414 --> 00:40:23,700
Thanks for meeting me.

1098
00:40:23,836 --> 00:40:25,849
What's going on?

1099
00:40:25,873 --> 00:40:28,878
I wanted to thank you
for making me take Gerard.

1100
00:40:30,685 --> 00:40:31,686
What happened?

1101
00:40:31,687 --> 00:40:32,949
What makes you think
something happened?

1102
00:40:32,973 --> 00:40:34,307
Because I know you,

1103
00:40:34,443 --> 00:40:36,206
and I know you don't have
moments of self-reflection,

1104
00:40:36,231 --> 00:40:37,459
let alone have a drink
with someone

1105
00:40:37,483 --> 00:40:40,098
to tell them about it
unless something happened.

1106
00:40:40,123 --> 00:40:41,769
You know what?
Something did happen.

1107
00:40:41,793 --> 00:40:42,911
I dealt with some shit,

1108
00:40:43,046 --> 00:40:44,581
and I'm trying
to thank you for it

1109
00:40:44,717 --> 00:40:47,923
because it turned out
to be a good thing.

1110
00:40:48,058 --> 00:40:50,456
I think the word you're
looking for is "closure."

1111
00:40:50,480 --> 00:40:51,481
That's your word.

1112
00:40:51,482 --> 00:40:52,543
The word I'm looking for is,

1113
00:40:52,568 --> 00:40:53,603
"You're welcome, Harvey.

1114
00:40:53,737 --> 00:40:55,356
That's nice of you to say."

1115
00:40:55,492 --> 00:40:57,840
Thanks, Harvey.

1116
00:40:57,864 --> 00:40:59,282
Good.

1117
00:40:59,417 --> 00:41:00,452
Now listen to me.

1118
00:41:00,586 --> 00:41:01,731
For a minute there, I thought

1119
00:41:01,756 --> 00:41:03,519
you were gonna tell me
that he knows.

1120
00:41:03,543 --> 00:41:05,022
What?

1121
00:41:05,047 --> 00:41:06,442
Maybe I'm crazy,

1122
00:41:06,467 --> 00:41:09,555
but when I was prepping him,
for a second, he looked at me,

1123
00:41:09,691 --> 00:41:11,560
and I thought,

1124
00:41:11,695 --> 00:41:14,008
"He's suspicious."

1125
00:41:14,034 --> 00:41:15,346
And then you called,

1126
00:41:15,370 --> 00:41:17,657
and after everything
that's happened already, I...

1127
00:41:21,000 --> 00:41:24,340
It's fine, Mike.
He doesn't know.

1128
00:41:24,474 --> 00:41:32,358
♪ ♪

