1
00:00:03,000 --> 00:00:04,778
It's not Woodall
coming after us.

2
00:00:04,802 --> 00:00:06,012
It's... Sean Cahill.

3
00:00:06,036 --> 00:00:08,515
Welcome to the new S.E.C.

4
00:00:08,539 --> 00:00:10,183
We target law firms.

5
00:00:10,207 --> 00:00:12,069
- Mr. Forstman.
- No.

6
00:00:12,093 --> 00:00:14,955
You'll miss the opportunity
to get back at Harvey Specter.

7
00:00:14,979 --> 00:00:16,406
You've got my 230 mil.

8
00:00:16,430 --> 00:00:19,793
Once the deal closes,
you cut Sidwell out.

9
00:00:19,817 --> 00:00:22,329
What happened to "You think
I'm staying if you leave"?

10
00:00:22,353 --> 00:00:23,413
Yeah, that was before I knew

11
00:00:23,437 --> 00:00:24,831
you were gonna
screw over Sidwell.

12
00:00:24,855 --> 00:00:26,366
Forstman doesn't throw
money around

13
00:00:26,390 --> 00:00:27,890
without getting something
in return.

14
00:00:27,908 --> 00:00:29,252
I have no other choice!

15
00:00:29,276 --> 00:00:31,727
So we're just gonna go
back and forth trading favors?

16
00:00:31,746 --> 00:00:33,373
Are you my lawyer or not?

17
00:00:33,397 --> 00:00:36,876
Seriously, Rachel, I couldn't
have done it without you.

18
00:00:36,900 --> 00:00:39,619
Logan, I should go.

19
00:00:59,089 --> 00:01:02,068
Mike?

20
00:01:02,092 --> 00:01:03,092
Right here.

21
00:01:03,093 --> 00:01:04,704
- Did you turn off my alarm?
- I did.

22
00:01:04,728 --> 00:01:06,072
It's after 9:00.

23
00:01:06,096 --> 00:01:07,073
I have been sleeping for...

24
00:01:07,097 --> 00:01:08,175
Almost six hours.

25
00:01:08,199 --> 00:01:09,199
I know.

26
00:01:09,200 --> 00:01:10,410
And the truth is, you need more.

27
00:01:10,434 --> 00:01:11,678
Why would you do that?

28
00:01:11,702 --> 00:01:13,246
Rachel, you've been
running back and forth

29
00:01:13,270 --> 00:01:14,914
between school and the firm
like a maniac.

30
00:01:14,938 --> 00:01:15,966
I don't even remember
the last time

31
00:01:15,990 --> 00:01:17,250
you got a good night's sleep.

32
00:01:17,274 --> 00:01:18,718
It doesn't give you
the right to do that.

33
00:01:18,742 --> 00:01:20,137
Plus, Harvey's gonna kill me.
He'll get over it.

34
00:01:20,161 --> 00:01:21,354
And I've got three briefs
to write,

35
00:01:21,378 --> 00:01:22,378
plus a paper for torts

36
00:01:22,379 --> 00:01:24,591
and a contracts exam tomorrow.

37
00:01:24,615 --> 00:01:26,092
I don't have the luxury
to sleep in.

38
00:01:26,116 --> 00:01:28,928
Then you need to ask Harvey
for a day off this week.

39
00:01:28,952 --> 00:01:31,721
Did he ever give you time off
because you were overworked?

40
00:01:33,891 --> 00:01:35,458
- No, he didn't.
- Exactly.

41
00:01:35,476 --> 00:01:39,939
I don't want to be
any different.

42
00:01:39,963 --> 00:01:42,209
Mr. Jamieson,
you are hereby remanded

43
00:01:42,233 --> 00:01:45,685
to the federal penitentiary
in Danbury, Connecticut.

44
00:01:51,275 --> 00:01:53,753
You might want to call me
about an appeal.

45
00:01:53,777 --> 00:01:57,480
The prosecutor has a reputation
for bending the rules.

46
00:01:57,498 --> 00:01:59,982
You must be
the infamous Harvey Specter.

47
00:02:00,000 --> 00:02:02,962
And you must be the chump
Eric Woodall ordered

48
00:02:02,986 --> 00:02:04,231
to come after me.

49
00:02:04,255 --> 00:02:05,682
Chump's my name
on my mother's side.

50
00:02:05,706 --> 00:02:06,850
I do prefer Cahill.

51
00:02:06,874 --> 00:02:08,518
And I prefer you stop
manufacturing bullshit

52
00:02:08,542 --> 00:02:09,936
to get my clients to turn on me.

53
00:02:09,960 --> 00:02:12,161
I'm sorry, I'm not in
the manufacturing business.

54
00:02:12,179 --> 00:02:13,940
I'm just a humble civil servant.

55
00:02:13,964 --> 00:02:15,331
And if you're as clean
as you say you are,

56
00:02:15,349 --> 00:02:16,976
your clients won't have anything
to give us.

57
00:02:17,000 --> 00:02:18,778
Unless you bully them
into making things up.

58
00:02:18,802 --> 00:02:20,480
Oh, see, now I think
you've got us confused,

59
00:02:20,504 --> 00:02:22,032
because that sounds like
something that you might do.

60
00:02:22,056 --> 00:02:24,618
The point is, Sean,
you had a secret little plan,

61
00:02:24,642 --> 00:02:26,819
and I've taken away
your element of surprise.

62
00:02:26,843 --> 00:02:27,843
Have you?

63
00:02:27,844 --> 00:02:28,872
You may know I'm coming,

64
00:02:28,896 --> 00:02:30,924
but do you know where or when?

65
00:02:30,948 --> 00:02:33,660
See, while you're battening down
the hatches at B-4,

66
00:02:33,684 --> 00:02:35,295
I might be at D-12 or H-3,

67
00:02:35,319 --> 00:02:38,598
and before you know it,
I have sunk your battleship.

68
00:02:38,622 --> 00:02:40,022
That's a cute game.

69
00:02:40,040 --> 00:02:43,436
I was more of a rock 'em
sock 'em robots guy.

70
00:02:43,460 --> 00:02:45,505
So you think you can knock
my block off, Harvey?

71
00:02:45,529 --> 00:02:48,725
I know I can, because I had
Eric Woodall fired.

72
00:02:48,749 --> 00:02:50,866
So stay the hell away
from my clients,

73
00:02:50,885 --> 00:02:54,281
or I'll pave
the same career path for you.

74
00:02:54,305 --> 00:02:57,317
Okay, your hands weren't full
with Eric.

75
00:02:57,341 --> 00:03:00,787
They will be full with me.

76
00:03:00,811 --> 00:03:02,812
Harv.

77
00:03:09,103 --> 00:03:10,553
You want to talk about it?

78
00:03:10,571 --> 00:03:11,748
Talk about what?

79
00:03:11,772 --> 00:03:15,502
That 10,000-pound weight
on your shoulders.

80
00:03:15,526 --> 00:03:16,869
Mike, if you feel this way now,

81
00:03:16,893 --> 00:03:18,922
what are you gonna feel like
when you cut Sidwell out?

82
00:03:18,946 --> 00:03:22,008
If I cut him out.

83
00:03:22,032 --> 00:03:23,343
What are you talking about?

84
00:03:23,367 --> 00:03:24,711
I've been thinking about it.

85
00:03:24,735 --> 00:03:28,348
I haven't actually
taken Forstman's money yet.

86
00:03:28,372 --> 00:03:30,934
If I can get Harvey
to back off before I do,

87
00:03:30,958 --> 00:03:32,819
then I might not even need it.

88
00:03:32,843 --> 00:03:35,221
You want to use the idea
of Forstman's money

89
00:03:35,245 --> 00:03:36,245
to cut a deal.

90
00:03:36,263 --> 00:03:38,558
But, Mike, they have money too.

91
00:03:38,582 --> 00:03:40,893
Yeah, which they can't spend
until their T.R.O. expires.

92
00:03:40,917 --> 00:03:42,696
Yeah, but that's next week,
and it's not like

93
00:03:42,720 --> 00:03:45,805
there's some huge block
of shares available now.

94
00:03:54,982 --> 00:03:56,876
Wexler's merging
two of their funds.

95
00:03:56,900 --> 00:03:58,077
So what?

96
00:03:58,101 --> 00:04:00,102
So their investment parameters
don't allow

97
00:04:00,120 --> 00:04:01,441
for more than 4%
of their holdings

98
00:04:01,455 --> 00:04:04,050
in any one industry.

99
00:04:04,074 --> 00:04:06,586
They have to sell
a block of something.

100
00:04:06,610 --> 00:04:08,254
But how do you know
it's gonna be Gillis Industries?

101
00:04:08,278 --> 00:04:10,890
Because I did the math.
That's what I would do.

102
00:04:10,914 --> 00:04:12,392
You think Harvey will go for it?

103
00:04:12,416 --> 00:04:15,301
There's only one way
to find out.

104
00:04:20,507 --> 00:04:22,124
Hey, I don't have
any cash on me,

105
00:04:22,142 --> 00:04:23,603
but if you want
to bring my luggage up,

106
00:04:23,627 --> 00:04:24,748
I'll get you on the way back.

107
00:04:24,762 --> 00:04:26,489
Nah, you know what? That's okay.

108
00:04:26,513 --> 00:04:28,274
I don't need a tip
now that I have enough money

109
00:04:28,298 --> 00:04:29,326
to buy your whole building.

110
00:04:29,350 --> 00:04:31,467
Yeah, what are you doing here,
Mike?

111
00:04:31,485 --> 00:04:33,380
Well, you came to give me
some friendly advice.

112
00:04:33,404 --> 00:04:34,881
I thought
I would return the favor.

113
00:04:34,905 --> 00:04:36,449
I don't remember asking.

114
00:04:36,473 --> 00:04:39,052
Mm, yeah, neither did I.

115
00:04:39,076 --> 00:04:41,421
Walk away, Harvey.

116
00:04:41,445 --> 00:04:42,445
Excuse me?

117
00:04:42,446 --> 00:04:44,123
You're gonna lose.

118
00:04:44,147 --> 00:04:47,344
If you think you getting
a little loan is gonna stop me,

119
00:04:47,368 --> 00:04:48,795
I didn't teach you much.

120
00:04:48,819 --> 00:04:51,130
It's not a little loan.

121
00:04:51,154 --> 00:04:53,183
I've got one of the most
powerful players in the world

122
00:04:53,207 --> 00:04:54,300
behind me.

123
00:04:54,324 --> 00:04:55,769
Which is exactly
where he needs to be

124
00:04:55,793 --> 00:04:58,160
to stab you in the back.

125
00:04:58,178 --> 00:05:00,473
Well, wherever he's standing,

126
00:05:00,497 --> 00:05:04,500
this is what I'm prepared to
offer Logan Sanders to go away.

127
00:05:04,518 --> 00:05:06,001
I know I don't
need to remind you

128
00:05:06,020 --> 00:05:10,023
that you're legally required
to run that by your client.

129
00:05:12,226 --> 00:05:13,753
I just ran it by him.

130
00:05:13,777 --> 00:05:15,344
No deal. Harvey.

131
00:05:15,362 --> 00:05:17,323
You haven't taken
Forstman's money yet.

132
00:05:17,347 --> 00:05:19,181
He's got some kind of gun
to your head,

133
00:05:19,199 --> 00:05:21,928
and you're just trying to use
his promise of cash

134
00:05:21,952 --> 00:05:23,352
as leverage against me.

135
00:05:24,988 --> 00:05:26,099
This isn't a bluff, Harvey.

136
00:05:26,123 --> 00:05:27,600
I came here to give you
a way out.

137
00:05:27,624 --> 00:05:28,718
Bullshit.

138
00:05:28,742 --> 00:05:31,054
You came here to give yourself
a way out.

139
00:05:31,078 --> 00:05:34,964
But I wasn't born yesterday,
and I'm not giving it to you.

140
00:06:13,064 --> 00:06:15,325
Did you go to see Sean Cahill
in court this morning?

141
00:06:15,349 --> 00:06:17,183
I'm not in the mood
for a lecture.

142
00:06:17,201 --> 00:06:19,185
I'm not lecturing.
I'm asking you a question.

143
00:06:19,203 --> 00:06:21,354
Yes, I did,
and before you tell me

144
00:06:21,372 --> 00:06:22,892
this is what we brought
Malone in for...

145
00:06:22,907 --> 00:06:23,884
I'm not going to tell you that.

146
00:06:23,908 --> 00:06:25,135
Good, because...

147
00:06:25,159 --> 00:06:26,136
Now Cahill's coming
directly after you.

148
00:06:26,160 --> 00:06:27,160
Exactly.

149
00:06:27,161 --> 00:06:28,171
And you're on your way

150
00:06:28,195 --> 00:06:29,723
to tell Malone
to concoct some bullshit

151
00:06:29,747 --> 00:06:31,475
to legally get us
that Wexler block.

152
00:06:31,499 --> 00:06:33,199
Look who's been
reading the papers.

153
00:06:33,217 --> 00:06:35,297
I'm not the only one
who can read the papers, Harvey.

154
00:06:35,302 --> 00:06:37,870
So can you. So can Mike Ross.

155
00:06:37,888 --> 00:06:39,205
He's gonna go
after those shares.

156
00:06:39,223 --> 00:06:41,318
- He is now.
- What are you talking about?

157
00:06:41,342 --> 00:06:43,070
- He tried to buy us off.
- And you turned him down.

158
00:06:43,094 --> 00:06:44,854
Yes, which is why
I'm going to see Malone.

159
00:06:44,878 --> 00:06:46,790
- No, you're not.
- Jessica, we have to...

160
00:06:46,814 --> 00:06:48,158
I'm not saying we don't.

161
00:06:48,182 --> 00:06:51,411
I'm saying I'm going to be
the one to do it.

162
00:06:51,435 --> 00:06:52,579
You know he's not gonna like it.

163
00:06:52,603 --> 00:06:54,164
He doesn't have to like it.

164
00:06:54,188 --> 00:06:56,322
He has to do it.

165
00:06:57,608 --> 00:07:00,504
Therefore, prepare thee
to cut off the flesh.

166
00:07:00,528 --> 00:07:04,397
Shed thou no blood,
nor cut thou less nor more.

167
00:07:04,415 --> 00:07:07,310
But just a pound of flesh if...

168
00:07:07,334 --> 00:07:10,403
Louis, how long have you been
standing there?

169
00:07:10,421 --> 00:07:12,182
Long enough
to become part of you.

170
00:07:12,206 --> 00:07:13,573
Okay, you know what?

171
00:07:13,591 --> 00:07:15,051
I don't have time
for you to be creepy.

172
00:07:15,075 --> 00:07:16,576
So does this mean
you're doing theater again?

173
00:07:16,594 --> 00:07:18,271
Yes, I am playing Portia
in merchant of Venice.

174
00:07:18,295 --> 00:07:19,439
Now, can you please just
let me get back to...

175
00:07:19,463 --> 00:07:21,224
Holy shit, Donna,
that is a meaty part.

176
00:07:21,248 --> 00:07:24,611
Yeah, it's 588 lines,
which I have yet to memorize.

177
00:07:24,635 --> 00:07:25,635
Wait.

178
00:07:25,636 --> 00:07:26,636
So you're not off book?

179
00:07:26,637 --> 00:07:28,064
Louis, if I were off book,

180
00:07:28,088 --> 00:07:29,533
would I be pacing around
the copy room

181
00:07:29,557 --> 00:07:30,557
with a script in my hand?

182
00:07:30,558 --> 00:07:31,598
All right, just calm down.

183
00:07:31,609 --> 00:07:32,609
No need to panic.

184
00:07:32,610 --> 00:07:33,703
When do you open? Tonight.

185
00:07:33,727 --> 00:07:35,071
Tonight,
and you're not off book?

186
00:07:35,095 --> 00:07:36,339
What the hell's wrong with you,
Donna?

187
00:07:36,363 --> 00:07:37,430
- Okay, this isn't helping.
- I'm sorry.

188
00:07:37,448 --> 00:07:38,575
I didn't mean to be...
I knew it.

189
00:07:38,599 --> 00:07:39,793
I bit off
more than I could chew.

190
00:07:39,817 --> 00:07:41,711
No, no, no, no, no, no,
just relax, okay?

191
00:07:41,735 --> 00:07:42,963
I don't care
if it takes all day.

192
00:07:42,987 --> 00:07:46,416
We are gonna memorize
these lines together.

193
00:07:46,440 --> 00:07:48,718
- Thank you, Louis.
- No need.

194
00:07:48,742 --> 00:07:50,554
For one canst choke
on the joy of life

195
00:07:50,578 --> 00:07:52,139
without thy mouth full.

196
00:07:52,163 --> 00:07:53,640
Is that the bard?

197
00:07:53,664 --> 00:07:54,664
Nope, it's the Litt,

198
00:07:54,665 --> 00:07:56,560
and roughly translated,
it means,

199
00:07:56,584 --> 00:08:00,086
when we're done, you're gonna
kick Shakespeare's ass.

200
00:08:02,789 --> 00:08:04,757
Milady.

201
00:08:08,395 --> 00:08:09,656
I take it it didn't go well.

202
00:08:09,680 --> 00:08:11,074
What gave it away?

203
00:08:11,098 --> 00:08:12,742
Because I know you,
and you don't have your usual

204
00:08:12,766 --> 00:08:15,712
"I'm super cool Mike Ross" face.

205
00:08:15,736 --> 00:08:16,802
If you knew me that well,

206
00:08:16,821 --> 00:08:20,116
you'd know I'm not in the mood.

207
00:08:20,140 --> 00:08:21,334
Mike, I'm not your enemy,

208
00:08:21,358 --> 00:08:24,888
and I don't appreciate
being treated like I am.

209
00:08:24,912 --> 00:08:25,912
I know.

210
00:08:25,913 --> 00:08:28,091
I'm sorry.

211
00:08:28,115 --> 00:08:29,676
So what did Harvey say?

212
00:08:29,700 --> 00:08:31,261
It's not what he said.
It's what he did.

213
00:08:31,285 --> 00:08:33,396
He knew what I was trying to do,

214
00:08:33,420 --> 00:08:35,182
and he called my bluff
right there.

215
00:08:35,206 --> 00:08:37,323
He didn't even share the offer
with Logan?

216
00:08:37,341 --> 00:08:38,341
No, he didn't.

217
00:08:38,342 --> 00:08:39,436
But you said he had to.

218
00:08:39,460 --> 00:08:41,271
You want me to sue him for that?

219
00:08:41,295 --> 00:08:42,405
So what are you gonna do?

220
00:08:42,429 --> 00:08:43,473
You know what I'm gonna do.

221
00:08:43,497 --> 00:08:44,858
- Mike.
- I don't want to hear it.

222
00:08:44,882 --> 00:08:46,443
I wasn't disapproving.

223
00:08:46,467 --> 00:08:49,835
I just want to make sure you've
exhausted all your options.

224
00:08:49,854 --> 00:08:51,364
- I have.
- Then maybe you can...

225
00:08:51,388 --> 00:08:53,783
Amy, the second I bid
on that block of shares,

226
00:08:53,807 --> 00:08:55,341
I've already taken
Forstman's money.

227
00:08:58,195 --> 00:09:01,324
Mike Ross' office.

228
00:09:01,348 --> 00:09:03,126
I'll tell him.

229
00:09:03,150 --> 00:09:04,827
Sidwell?

230
00:09:04,851 --> 00:09:07,320
He wants to see you.

231
00:09:16,530 --> 00:09:17,530
You look good.

232
00:09:17,531 --> 00:09:19,392
This isn't a social call.

233
00:09:19,416 --> 00:09:21,177
All right, I take it back.

234
00:09:21,201 --> 00:09:22,479
Wexler is divesting

235
00:09:22,503 --> 00:09:24,147
a huge block
of Gillis Industries,

236
00:09:24,171 --> 00:09:25,899
and I need you to find
a creative way

237
00:09:25,923 --> 00:09:27,350
to buy them for Logan Sanders.

238
00:09:27,374 --> 00:09:29,686
If I'm not mistaken,
Logan Sanders has a T.R.O.

239
00:09:29,710 --> 00:09:32,355
that actually prohibits him from
buying any additional shares.

240
00:09:32,379 --> 00:09:33,623
Which is why
you're going to set up a trust

241
00:09:33,647 --> 00:09:34,741
for us to buy it for him.

242
00:09:34,765 --> 00:09:36,215
That's called parking, Jessica.

243
00:09:36,233 --> 00:09:37,410
I know what it's called.

244
00:09:37,434 --> 00:09:38,995
Then maybe you also know
it's illegal.

245
00:09:39,019 --> 00:09:40,720
I know it can be illegal,

246
00:09:40,738 --> 00:09:43,199
and I need you to figure out
a way to make it questionable.

247
00:09:43,223 --> 00:09:44,890
And here I thought
you came in here

248
00:09:44,909 --> 00:09:47,059
to tell me how much fun
last night was.

249
00:09:47,077 --> 00:09:48,922
Oh, speaking of last night,

250
00:09:48,946 --> 00:09:51,063
you said you blamed yourself

251
00:09:51,081 --> 00:09:54,544
for helping Cahill
drop those cases.

252
00:09:54,568 --> 00:09:56,763
So here's your chance
to make up for it.

253
00:09:56,787 --> 00:09:57,903
Remind me never to have

254
00:09:57,922 --> 00:09:59,849
a moment of self-reflection
around you.

255
00:09:59,873 --> 00:10:02,385
I'm not using this
as ammunition.

256
00:10:02,409 --> 00:10:04,076
I am using it as motivation.

257
00:10:04,094 --> 00:10:06,940
So figure out a way
to set up the trust,

258
00:10:06,964 --> 00:10:08,080
and do it quickly,

259
00:10:08,098 --> 00:10:11,551
because we're running
out of time.

260
00:10:20,093 --> 00:10:22,428
You wanted to see me?

261
00:10:22,446 --> 00:10:23,446
Come here.

262
00:10:23,447 --> 00:10:26,149
I want to show you something.

263
00:10:32,105 --> 00:10:35,018
Lionsdale Electronics,
3 million shares,

264
00:10:35,042 --> 00:10:36,275
bought out by management.

265
00:10:36,293 --> 00:10:39,222
My first LBO.
I was right out of school.

266
00:10:39,246 --> 00:10:41,725
All I wanted was that first
tombstone because it meant...

267
00:10:41,749 --> 00:10:46,118
- Your first deal.
- Broke my cherry.

268
00:10:46,136 --> 00:10:47,136
Must have been nice.

269
00:10:47,137 --> 00:10:50,289
It was.

270
00:10:50,307 --> 00:10:52,485
But you know what the difference
between you and me is?

271
00:10:52,509 --> 00:10:53,603
I was just an analyst.

272
00:10:53,627 --> 00:10:54,821
I mean, sure,
I did all the work,

273
00:10:54,845 --> 00:10:55,989
but I didn't do any of the work.

274
00:10:56,013 --> 00:10:57,574
Know what I mean?

275
00:10:57,598 --> 00:10:59,042
- Jonathan.
- Don't be modest.

276
00:10:59,066 --> 00:11:00,443
I know I've been on your case,

277
00:11:00,467 --> 00:11:03,496
but the truth is,
you made this all happen.

278
00:11:03,520 --> 00:11:05,498
I haven't made
anything happen yet.

279
00:11:05,522 --> 00:11:07,473
No, you haven't.

280
00:11:07,491 --> 00:11:11,004
And there's a rule against
giving out tombstones too early.

281
00:11:11,028 --> 00:11:13,979
You're not supposed to jinx it.

282
00:11:13,998 --> 00:11:16,343
But there's no rule
against this.

283
00:11:16,367 --> 00:11:18,368
We'll fill it in later.

284
00:11:23,707 --> 00:11:25,068
Thank you, Jonathan.

285
00:11:25,092 --> 00:11:27,827
You're welcome.

286
00:11:27,845 --> 00:11:29,879
Now go bring this bad boy home.

287
00:11:50,036 --> 00:11:51,569
Rachel, they loved it.

288
00:11:51,587 --> 00:11:54,216
We are gonna go after Piedmont
in a week.

289
00:11:54,240 --> 00:11:55,601
We're gonna have
a lot of work to do.

290
00:11:55,625 --> 00:11:58,376
Give me a call when you get in.

291
00:12:07,770 --> 00:12:10,732
Harvey,
can I help you with something?

292
00:12:10,756 --> 00:12:11,956
Yes, you can help by telling me

293
00:12:11,974 --> 00:12:13,401
how much longer it's gonna take

294
00:12:13,425 --> 00:12:15,737
for you to find me a way
to bid on that stock.

295
00:12:15,761 --> 00:12:17,762
It's going to take
as long as it takes.

296
00:12:17,780 --> 00:12:19,708
Well, it better not be
more than a day,

297
00:12:19,732 --> 00:12:21,409
or I won't need it at all.

298
00:12:21,433 --> 00:12:24,213
It's so good to hear this
from the horse's mouth.

299
00:12:24,237 --> 00:12:25,547
What's that supposed to mean?

300
00:12:25,571 --> 00:12:27,683
It means the next time
you want me to break the law,

301
00:12:27,707 --> 00:12:29,417
at least have the balls
to ask me yourself.

302
00:12:29,441 --> 00:12:30,719
The balls?

303
00:12:30,743 --> 00:12:33,805
First off, Jessica insisted
on asking you herself,

304
00:12:33,829 --> 00:12:36,141
and I agreed with her,
because we're on the same page.

305
00:12:36,165 --> 00:12:37,926
And nobody's asking you
to break the law.

306
00:12:37,950 --> 00:12:39,311
We're telling you
to sidestep it.

307
00:12:39,335 --> 00:12:41,363
That's not the job
I signed on for.

308
00:12:41,387 --> 00:12:42,931
The job you signed on for

309
00:12:42,955 --> 00:12:44,455
is the job we tell you
you signed on for.

310
00:12:44,473 --> 00:12:46,291
Well, that's
a bullshit justification,

311
00:12:46,309 --> 00:12:47,319
and you know it.

312
00:12:47,343 --> 00:12:48,770
What I know is, there's a reason

313
00:12:48,794 --> 00:12:50,489
we make the kind of money we do.

314
00:12:50,513 --> 00:12:53,742
It's because we figure out a way
to get things like this done.

315
00:12:53,766 --> 00:12:57,519
So stop questioning my integrity
and start doing your job.

316
00:13:02,658 --> 00:13:03,818
Harvey, do you have a second?

317
00:13:03,826 --> 00:13:04,836
That's about all I have.

318
00:13:04,860 --> 00:13:06,144
All right, I was wondering if...

319
00:13:06,162 --> 00:13:07,389
if maybe I could possibly just...

320
00:13:07,413 --> 00:13:08,557
Time's up.

321
00:13:08,581 --> 00:13:10,315
Could I get a day or two off?

322
00:13:10,333 --> 00:13:11,459
A day or two?

323
00:13:11,483 --> 00:13:12,483
A day.

324
00:13:12,484 --> 00:13:13,985
I just need one day away.

325
00:13:14,003 --> 00:13:15,320
Are you sure
that's all you need?

326
00:13:15,338 --> 00:13:16,431
I'm sure.

327
00:13:16,455 --> 00:13:18,684
Would you also like me
to make your bed?

328
00:13:18,708 --> 00:13:20,018
What?

329
00:13:20,042 --> 00:13:21,970
Maybe I can triple your salary
while we're at it.

330
00:13:21,994 --> 00:13:23,328
No, that's not...

331
00:13:23,346 --> 00:13:26,074
No, really, what can I do
to make your life easier?

332
00:13:26,098 --> 00:13:27,409
That is not fair.

333
00:13:27,433 --> 00:13:29,500
I have been juggling work
and school for months now,

334
00:13:29,518 --> 00:13:30,979
and I-I haven't asked
for any special treatment.

335
00:13:31,003 --> 00:13:32,647
You're asking now.

336
00:13:32,671 --> 00:13:34,199
I'm not asking for time off

337
00:13:34,223 --> 00:13:35,483
to go to the Hamptons.

338
00:13:35,507 --> 00:13:37,286
This is law school
I'm talking about.

339
00:13:37,310 --> 00:13:38,453
You said a day away.

340
00:13:38,477 --> 00:13:39,821
You didn't say anything
about law school.

341
00:13:39,845 --> 00:13:40,885
Well, it's for law school.

342
00:13:40,896 --> 00:13:42,624
Well, this is your law school.

343
00:13:42,648 --> 00:13:44,826
This, right here.

344
00:13:44,850 --> 00:13:46,545
And by the way,
we're paying you for it.

345
00:13:46,569 --> 00:13:48,163
I know, and I'm grateful.

346
00:13:48,187 --> 00:13:50,215
If you're grateful,
then you'll stop complaining

347
00:13:50,239 --> 00:13:51,800
about how much work
you have to do,

348
00:13:51,824 --> 00:13:53,602
and you'll figure out
how to best manage your time,

349
00:13:53,626 --> 00:13:56,388
but as far as getting time off,
that's not gonna happen

350
00:13:56,412 --> 00:13:57,812
if you still plan on
working for me.

351
00:13:57,830 --> 00:13:59,641
Now, you still need
a day or two off?

352
00:13:59,665 --> 00:14:02,000
No, I can manage.

353
00:14:09,508 --> 00:14:11,953
Thou shalt have nothing
but the forfeiture

354
00:14:11,977 --> 00:14:14,545
to be so taken
at thy peril, Jew.

355
00:14:14,563 --> 00:14:16,524
Why, then, let the devil
give him good of it.

356
00:14:16,548 --> 00:14:20,329
I'll stay no longer question.

357
00:14:20,353 --> 00:14:21,663
Come on, let's go.
This be-eth awesome.

358
00:14:21,687 --> 00:14:22,914
Where's your script?

359
00:14:22,938 --> 00:14:24,499
I don't need a script.
I'm off book.

360
00:14:24,523 --> 00:14:26,251
How can you be off book?
You're not even in the play.

361
00:14:26,275 --> 00:14:28,503
Because I know
all of Willy's work by heart.

362
00:14:28,527 --> 00:14:31,729
- All 37 plays?
- Mm-hmm.

363
00:14:31,747 --> 00:14:33,041
Troilus and Cressida.

364
00:14:33,065 --> 00:14:36,378
For to be wise and love
exceeds man's might.

365
00:14:36,402 --> 00:14:37,596
Titus Andronicus.

366
00:14:37,620 --> 00:14:40,215
Vengeance is in my heart,
death in my hand.

367
00:14:40,239 --> 00:14:42,934
Blood and revenge
are hammering in my head.

368
00:14:42,958 --> 00:14:43,958
What... what's the matter?

369
00:14:43,959 --> 00:14:46,388
Are you kidding me?

370
00:14:46,412 --> 00:14:49,107
You have every word this man's
ever written memorized,

371
00:14:49,131 --> 00:14:50,325
and I'm on
in an hour and a half,

372
00:14:50,349 --> 00:14:51,749
and I'm gonna
make a fool of myself.

373
00:14:51,750 --> 00:14:53,195
Donna, forget
about my extraordinary gift

374
00:14:53,219 --> 00:14:54,496
and focus on yourself.

375
00:14:54,520 --> 00:14:56,114
We have done this whole play.

376
00:14:56,138 --> 00:14:58,066
You know your part.
It will be fine.

377
00:14:58,090 --> 00:15:01,036
- It's not gonna be fine.
- Donna.

378
00:15:01,060 --> 00:15:02,704
I haven't been on the stage
in years.

379
00:15:02,728 --> 00:15:04,072
So you're nervous.

380
00:15:04,096 --> 00:15:06,741
All great performers
get nervous.

381
00:15:06,765 --> 00:15:08,243
It brings out the genius.

382
00:15:08,267 --> 00:15:10,985
What if I'm not genius?
What if I'm not even good?

383
00:15:14,773 --> 00:15:17,469
I was pretty damn good, Louis.

384
00:15:17,493 --> 00:15:20,445
I was.

385
00:15:20,463 --> 00:15:22,113
But I knew the odds
of somebody making it

386
00:15:22,131 --> 00:15:26,428
were close to zero
no matter how good they were.

387
00:15:26,452 --> 00:15:28,647
My father lost our money
when I was 13,

388
00:15:28,671 --> 00:15:32,290
and I-I found out
what it was like to struggle,

389
00:15:32,308 --> 00:15:37,489
so instead of pursuing my dream,

390
00:15:37,513 --> 00:15:39,898
I chose this...

391
00:15:41,800 --> 00:15:43,044
And that let me pretend

392
00:15:43,068 --> 00:15:46,271
that maybe I was good enough
to make it.

393
00:15:49,475 --> 00:15:52,554
But what if I wasn't?

394
00:15:52,578 --> 00:15:53,755
Mm-mm, all right, look,

395
00:15:53,779 --> 00:15:55,123
I'm gonna tell you
something about myself

396
00:15:55,147 --> 00:15:58,149
that I never told anyone.

397
00:15:58,167 --> 00:16:00,729
I have stage fright.

398
00:16:00,753 --> 00:16:02,564
Got it when I was
in third grade.

399
00:16:02,588 --> 00:16:05,517
Let it get the best of me.

400
00:16:05,541 --> 00:16:08,470
I never got over it.

401
00:16:08,494 --> 00:16:11,930
And I cannot let you
make the same mistake.

402
00:16:12,965 --> 00:16:15,977
- But...
- Look at me.

403
00:16:16,001 --> 00:16:19,670
Donna Victoria Paulsen,

404
00:16:19,688 --> 00:16:22,751
you have never been
more beautiful

405
00:16:22,775 --> 00:16:25,987
and talented

406
00:16:26,011 --> 00:16:30,208
and perfect than you are
at this very moment.

407
00:16:30,232 --> 00:16:33,261
Your time is now.

408
00:16:33,285 --> 00:16:36,131
And you're gonna kill it.

409
00:16:36,155 --> 00:16:37,155
Thank you, Louis.

410
00:16:37,156 --> 00:16:40,168
No.

411
00:16:40,192 --> 00:16:43,305
Thank you.

412
00:16:43,329 --> 00:16:46,164
My middle name is Roberta.

413
00:16:47,866 --> 00:16:51,135
I'm so sorry for that.

414
00:16:55,374 --> 00:16:57,842
- Hey.
- Hey.

415
00:16:59,845 --> 00:17:01,045
Were you working late?

416
00:17:01,063 --> 00:17:03,625
You really have to ask?

417
00:17:03,649 --> 00:17:08,246
Thought maybe it would be nice
for us to lie down a little bit.

418
00:17:08,270 --> 00:17:12,133
Together.

419
00:17:12,157 --> 00:17:13,468
I would love that,

420
00:17:13,492 --> 00:17:16,861
but if I lie down,
I probably won't get back up.

421
00:17:23,118 --> 00:17:24,513
I know you don't want
to hear this,

422
00:17:24,537 --> 00:17:26,848
but I was thinking about it,

423
00:17:26,872 --> 00:17:30,575
and Harvey did kind of
give me special treatment.

424
00:17:30,593 --> 00:17:33,595
- Mike.
- He let me skip law school.

425
00:17:35,848 --> 00:17:38,726
Yeah.

426
00:17:38,750 --> 00:17:40,028
Hey.

427
00:17:40,052 --> 00:17:43,087
Maybe if you just find
the right time to ask, you know.

428
00:17:43,105 --> 00:17:47,141
I did, and he bit my head off.

429
00:17:48,811 --> 00:17:51,406
So please just let it go.

430
00:17:51,430 --> 00:17:53,908
Okay? Okay.

431
00:17:53,932 --> 00:17:56,678
Just wish all this Harvey
and Logan bullshit

432
00:17:56,702 --> 00:17:59,014
would be over.

433
00:17:59,038 --> 00:18:02,551
Yeah, me too.

434
00:18:02,575 --> 00:18:03,608
Maybe when it is,

435
00:18:03,626 --> 00:18:06,777
we can get out of town
for a weekend.

436
00:18:06,795 --> 00:18:09,297
I would love that.

437
00:18:24,916 --> 00:18:26,853
I'm worried Cahill, Harvey.

438
00:18:27,063 --> 00:18:28,774
I've checked
with everyone I know.

439
00:18:28,798 --> 00:18:29,941
He hasn't done a thing.

440
00:18:29,965 --> 00:18:31,877
Me too, which is exactly
why I'm worried.

441
00:18:31,901 --> 00:18:33,278
Jessica, I don't know
what to say.

442
00:18:33,302 --> 00:18:35,497
If I have to look over
my shoulder every 15 seconds,

443
00:18:35,521 --> 00:18:36,971
I might as well
give up right now.

444
00:18:36,989 --> 00:18:39,168
Okay, but it doesn't mean
you stop looking altogether.

445
00:18:39,192 --> 00:18:41,587
Hey, do you have a minute?

446
00:18:41,611 --> 00:18:42,755
Did you set up that trust?

447
00:18:42,779 --> 00:18:44,956
- No.
- In that case, we don't.

448
00:18:44,980 --> 00:18:46,124
I did something better.

449
00:18:46,148 --> 00:18:47,459
We're listening.

450
00:18:47,483 --> 00:18:49,651
One of the biggest red flags
at the S.E.C.

451
00:18:49,669 --> 00:18:52,431
is a stock purchase with money
kept in trust for clients.

452
00:18:52,455 --> 00:18:53,455
We've gone over this.

453
00:18:53,456 --> 00:18:55,490
Let him finish.

454
00:18:55,508 --> 00:18:57,102
On the other hand,

455
00:18:57,126 --> 00:18:59,661
there's nothing unusual
about a retainer.

456
00:18:59,679 --> 00:19:01,306
A retainer?

457
00:19:01,330 --> 00:19:02,474
From what I gather,

458
00:19:02,498 --> 00:19:04,610
this takeover is
a massive undertaking, right?

459
00:19:04,634 --> 00:19:06,361
Now, I don't know how you've
structured Logan's payments,

460
00:19:06,385 --> 00:19:09,337
but I think it's time he pay
this firm a hefty fee up front

461
00:19:09,355 --> 00:19:12,173
and something on the order
of $20 million.

462
00:19:12,191 --> 00:19:15,320
And we use $20 million of
our own money to buy that stock.

463
00:19:15,344 --> 00:19:16,755
There's nothing
that prohibits us

464
00:19:16,779 --> 00:19:18,624
from investing as a firm.

465
00:19:18,648 --> 00:19:20,325
And when the bulk
of our legal work is done,

466
00:19:20,349 --> 00:19:21,794
turns out
he has money coming back.

467
00:19:21,818 --> 00:19:23,962
We may just end up
giving him the shares

468
00:19:23,986 --> 00:19:25,631
instead of his unused retainer.

469
00:19:25,655 --> 00:19:26,855
Which we cannot plan

470
00:19:26,873 --> 00:19:28,690
or even discuss
with Logan Sanders in advance.

471
00:19:28,708 --> 00:19:30,168
And that makes it legal?

472
00:19:30,192 --> 00:19:32,938
No.

473
00:19:32,962 --> 00:19:35,107
It makes it questionable,

474
00:19:35,131 --> 00:19:36,942
because they still might
figure out what we did

475
00:19:36,966 --> 00:19:37,966
and make a case.

476
00:19:37,967 --> 00:19:39,228
We?

477
00:19:39,252 --> 00:19:41,647
You tell me, Harvey.

478
00:19:41,671 --> 00:19:43,682
Am I on the team now?

479
00:19:43,706 --> 00:19:44,900
Sounds like you're being

480
00:19:44,924 --> 00:19:46,852
a little bit of a dickhead
about this whole thing,

481
00:19:46,876 --> 00:19:50,979
so I'd say yes.

482
00:20:00,940 --> 00:20:03,302
Louis?

483
00:20:03,326 --> 00:20:04,369
Do you have a minute?

484
00:20:04,393 --> 00:20:05,704
Oh, no.

485
00:20:05,728 --> 00:20:07,061
It could not have been that bad.

486
00:20:07,079 --> 00:20:08,423
Oh, it wasn't.

487
00:20:08,447 --> 00:20:11,844
It was amazing.

488
00:20:11,868 --> 00:20:13,712
I mean,
it was like riding a bike.

489
00:20:13,736 --> 00:20:14,813
I got two standing Os,

490
00:20:14,837 --> 00:20:16,381
and I got you to thank for it.

491
00:20:16,405 --> 00:20:18,600
Well, that's great.

492
00:20:18,624 --> 00:20:19,741
What's wrong?

493
00:20:19,759 --> 00:20:21,103
Shylock got drunk
at the after-party,

494
00:20:21,127 --> 00:20:23,322
fell down a flight of stairs,
and broke his ankle,

495
00:20:23,346 --> 00:20:25,891
which means the show
won't go on.

496
00:20:25,915 --> 00:20:28,416
No, no, no, the show must go on.

497
00:20:28,434 --> 00:20:32,320
Well, the show can go on.

498
00:20:34,857 --> 00:20:36,902
- No.
- Louis.

499
00:20:36,926 --> 00:20:39,427
Come on, you're the only one
who can do it.

500
00:20:39,445 --> 00:20:42,958
No, I can't.

501
00:20:42,982 --> 00:20:45,511
I wanted to be a molar.

502
00:20:45,535 --> 00:20:47,796
But that teacher's pet,
Dorothy McHale, got the part,

503
00:20:47,820 --> 00:20:50,632
so I was forced to be plaque.

504
00:20:50,656 --> 00:20:53,302
Had to wear this ridiculous
flesh-colored unitard

505
00:20:53,326 --> 00:20:55,137
and drape myself
over my classmates,

506
00:20:55,161 --> 00:20:57,973
and every parent in the audience
laughed at me.

507
00:20:57,997 --> 00:20:59,224
Louis.

508
00:20:59,248 --> 00:21:00,392
And then the next year,
I got a bigger part.

509
00:21:00,416 --> 00:21:03,362
Walked right out onstage.

510
00:21:03,386 --> 00:21:06,865
Tommy Gallup screams out,
"plaque man!"

511
00:21:06,889 --> 00:21:09,868
Once again,
everyone laughs at me.

512
00:21:09,892 --> 00:21:14,479
So right then and there,
middle of the stage, I...

513
00:21:19,151 --> 00:21:22,948
I peed my pants.

514
00:21:22,972 --> 00:21:24,550
So I ran right off the stage,

515
00:21:24,574 --> 00:21:25,951
never went back,

516
00:21:25,975 --> 00:21:28,587
and I am not going back again.

517
00:21:28,611 --> 00:21:31,456
Louis.

518
00:21:31,480 --> 00:21:34,960
A part like this doesn't
come around very often.

519
00:21:34,984 --> 00:21:37,462
You gave me a gift,
and I killed it because of you.

520
00:21:37,486 --> 00:21:38,653
Donna, please.

521
00:21:38,671 --> 00:21:41,423
I'm not a lawyer, Louis.

522
00:21:42,875 --> 00:21:44,937
This is my chance to shine.

523
00:21:44,961 --> 00:21:49,881
But I'm about to lose
two more glorious nights.

524
00:21:51,851 --> 00:21:54,413
I've never asked anyone
for anything like this,

525
00:21:54,437 --> 00:21:57,199
but there's no other choice.

526
00:21:57,223 --> 00:21:59,808
Please do this for me.

527
00:22:03,696 --> 00:22:05,697
Please.

528
00:22:07,733 --> 00:22:09,183
You want me to sell
directly to you?

529
00:22:09,201 --> 00:22:10,201
I don't want you to.

530
00:22:10,202 --> 00:22:11,430
You're going to.

531
00:22:11,454 --> 00:22:12,881
Why would I do that?

532
00:22:12,905 --> 00:22:14,099
Because I'm the only one

533
00:22:14,123 --> 00:22:15,684
who's gonna buy your block
at a premium,

534
00:22:15,691 --> 00:22:17,386
instead of you flooding
the market with shares

535
00:22:17,410 --> 00:22:18,387
and ending up
getting a discount.

536
00:22:18,411 --> 00:22:20,305
That's funny.

537
00:22:20,329 --> 00:22:22,557
That's exactly what someone else
just told me an hour ago.

538
00:22:22,581 --> 00:22:23,642
What?

539
00:22:23,666 --> 00:22:25,110
And now I'll tell you
what I told him.

540
00:22:25,134 --> 00:22:26,511
I'll shut everyone else out,

541
00:22:26,535 --> 00:22:30,371
but you two are gonna
have to go head-to-head.

542
00:22:30,389 --> 00:22:32,618
You're talking
about a dark pool bidding war.

543
00:22:32,642 --> 00:22:33,735
That's no different

544
00:22:33,759 --> 00:22:35,070
than what you were
talking about.

545
00:22:35,094 --> 00:22:37,022
You just wanted to be
the only one bidding.

546
00:22:37,046 --> 00:22:39,157
Thanks for the scampi, Mr. Ross.

547
00:22:39,181 --> 00:22:40,859
It was delicious.

548
00:22:40,883 --> 00:22:43,051
I'll be in touch
with the details.

549
00:22:43,069 --> 00:22:46,081
Who's the other entity?

550
00:22:46,105 --> 00:22:48,366
If you can't figure that out
for yourself,

551
00:22:48,390 --> 00:22:49,471
I don't think you're likely

552
00:22:49,492 --> 00:22:52,777
to come out on top
of this whole thing.

553
00:23:07,877 --> 00:23:09,220
What the hell
do you think you're doing?

554
00:23:09,244 --> 00:23:10,522
I think I'm washing my hands,

555
00:23:10,546 --> 00:23:12,724
which I'd like to do
without you bothering me

556
00:23:12,748 --> 00:23:14,443
about whatever bullshit
you're here for.

557
00:23:14,467 --> 00:23:15,727
Bullshit?

558
00:23:15,751 --> 00:23:17,496
We'll see if the S.E.C.
thinks it's bullshit

559
00:23:17,520 --> 00:23:19,031
that you're
buying stock illegally.

560
00:23:19,055 --> 00:23:21,232
You're throwing some
pretty big accusations around

561
00:23:21,256 --> 00:23:22,284
for such a little guy.

562
00:23:22,308 --> 00:23:23,702
You think I didn't do
my homework?

563
00:23:23,726 --> 00:23:25,259
The registered bidder
traces back

564
00:23:25,277 --> 00:23:26,277
to a shell corporation

565
00:23:26,278 --> 00:23:28,340
we used six times last year.

566
00:23:28,364 --> 00:23:29,791
We're allowed to play
the stock market

567
00:23:29,815 --> 00:23:31,009
as much as the next fellow.

568
00:23:31,033 --> 00:23:32,744
You think
because you're using firm money,

569
00:23:32,768 --> 00:23:33,768
that makes it legal?

570
00:23:33,769 --> 00:23:35,180
Damn right I do,

571
00:23:35,204 --> 00:23:36,631
because we have no plan
to do anything

572
00:23:36,655 --> 00:23:38,633
other than keep those shares
ourselves.

573
00:23:38,657 --> 00:23:39,801
Now who's talking bullshit?

574
00:23:39,825 --> 00:23:41,419
What are you gonna do, Mike?

575
00:23:41,443 --> 00:23:42,921
You gonna run to the S.E.C.?

576
00:23:42,945 --> 00:23:45,090
You think I won't?

577
00:23:45,114 --> 00:23:46,758
These aren't your daddy's tapes,
Harvey.

578
00:23:46,782 --> 00:23:48,062
These are the rules of the game.

579
00:23:48,084 --> 00:23:50,195
Then let me dial their number
for you,

580
00:23:50,219 --> 00:23:51,646
because if you report us,

581
00:23:51,670 --> 00:23:53,315
they'll put a freeze
on this sale,

582
00:23:53,339 --> 00:23:55,400
and by the time we get it
all straightened out,

583
00:23:55,424 --> 00:23:57,069
my T.R.O. will be expired,

584
00:23:57,093 --> 00:23:58,153
and we'll be right back

585
00:23:58,177 --> 00:24:01,596
to where we're headed
this afternoon.

586
00:24:04,016 --> 00:24:05,494
You're a sore goddamn loser.

587
00:24:05,518 --> 00:24:08,413
I would be if I ever lost.

588
00:24:08,437 --> 00:24:11,106
See you at 6:00.

589
00:24:13,642 --> 00:24:14,953
Guess what piece of shit lawyer

590
00:24:14,977 --> 00:24:16,922
just got himself a seat
in the Wexler pool.

591
00:24:16,946 --> 00:24:18,146
Mike, what are you doing here?

592
00:24:18,147 --> 00:24:19,147
What do you mean?

593
00:24:19,148 --> 00:24:20,342
The sale's not until 6:00.

594
00:24:20,366 --> 00:24:21,676
Didn't you check your messages?

595
00:24:21,700 --> 00:24:22,700
No. Why?

596
00:24:22,701 --> 00:24:25,397
Columbia University called.

597
00:24:25,421 --> 00:24:28,673
Rachel was taken
to the hospital.

598
00:24:39,930 --> 00:24:42,131
- Rachel Zane.
- Sorry?

599
00:24:42,148 --> 00:24:43,159
You have a patient here,
Rachel Zane.

600
00:24:43,183 --> 00:24:44,183
What room is she in?

601
00:24:44,184 --> 00:24:46,111
Miss Zane is resting and can...

602
00:24:46,135 --> 00:24:47,413
What room is she in?

603
00:24:47,437 --> 00:24:50,305
As I was saying,
she can't have any visitors.

604
00:24:50,323 --> 00:24:51,383
Look at me.

605
00:24:51,407 --> 00:24:53,669
I'm gonna ask you one more time.
Mike.

606
00:24:53,693 --> 00:24:55,087
She's in 1024.

607
00:24:55,111 --> 00:24:56,144
You've seen her?

608
00:24:56,162 --> 00:24:57,790
- It's locked.
- I don't care.

609
00:24:57,814 --> 00:25:00,126
What are you gonna do?
You gonna break the door down?

610
00:25:00,150 --> 00:25:02,818
- Yeah, if I have to.
- I spoke to her doctors.

611
00:25:02,836 --> 00:25:05,014
They said she fainted at school.
She's fine.

612
00:25:05,038 --> 00:25:06,488
If she fainted, she's not fine.

613
00:25:06,506 --> 00:25:09,157
They said she's run down
and a little dehydrated

614
00:25:09,175 --> 00:25:10,492
but that she's okay.

615
00:25:10,510 --> 00:25:11,804
Okay, so then... then why won't
they let us see her?

616
00:25:11,828 --> 00:25:14,190
Because she's sleeping,
and she needs it.

617
00:25:14,214 --> 00:25:15,941
Mike, she's fine.

618
00:25:15,965 --> 00:25:16,965
She's gonna be fine.

619
00:25:16,966 --> 00:25:18,126
What are you even doing here?

620
00:25:18,134 --> 00:25:19,411
I'm one
of her emergency contacts.

621
00:25:19,435 --> 00:25:20,529
They called me.

622
00:25:20,553 --> 00:25:21,814
Yeah, I know, but...

623
00:25:21,838 --> 00:25:23,004
What's a heartless shithead
like me

624
00:25:23,022 --> 00:25:25,034
doing in a place like this?

625
00:25:25,058 --> 00:25:26,341
Yeah, something like that.

626
00:25:26,359 --> 00:25:27,787
I would have come for you

627
00:25:27,811 --> 00:25:31,280
if you ever worked hard enough
to pass out, but you never did.

628
00:25:33,817 --> 00:25:37,429
Look, there's a steakhouse
across the street.

629
00:25:37,453 --> 00:25:39,932
Why don't you and I
go get something to eat?

630
00:25:39,956 --> 00:25:41,690
What, you gonna break
the door down and wake her up?

631
00:25:41,708 --> 00:25:43,219
No, I'm gonna wait outside of it

632
00:25:43,243 --> 00:25:44,336
and be there when she does.

633
00:25:44,360 --> 00:25:45,360
Yeah, which won't happen

634
00:25:45,361 --> 00:25:46,605
for another eight hours,

635
00:25:46,629 --> 00:25:49,007
because they sedated her
to make sure she got some sleep.

636
00:25:49,031 --> 00:25:51,383
Come on, let's go get some food.

637
00:25:55,305 --> 00:25:57,316
Don't you need to be
at an auction?

638
00:25:57,340 --> 00:25:59,184
Right now, I don't want
to be at that sale

639
00:25:59,208 --> 00:26:00,486
any more than you do.

640
00:26:00,510 --> 00:26:02,321
You're saying you're willing
to postpone it?

641
00:26:02,345 --> 00:26:05,063
I'm saying I already did.
Come on.

642
00:26:10,069 --> 00:26:11,997
No, I'm telling you,
Dr. Lipschitz,

643
00:26:12,021 --> 00:26:14,366
this is like the whole
plaque incident all over again.

644
00:26:14,390 --> 00:26:18,393
Yes, I have told you
about the plaque incident,

645
00:26:18,411 --> 00:26:19,588
at least twice.

646
00:26:19,612 --> 00:26:21,897
I've... no, that...
you know, it doesn't...

647
00:26:21,915 --> 00:26:23,092
you know what, forget it.
That's not the point.

648
00:26:23,116 --> 00:26:24,593
The point is,
is that I'm supposed to be

649
00:26:24,617 --> 00:26:26,011
leaving for the theater
in ten minutes,

650
00:26:26,035 --> 00:26:27,596
and I am a complete wreck.

651
00:26:27,620 --> 00:26:28,681
I have the worst case
of cottonmouth

652
00:26:28,705 --> 00:26:31,717
in the history of...

653
00:26:31,741 --> 00:26:33,769
what? No, you can talk
with cotton mouth.

654
00:26:33,793 --> 00:26:35,771
That's frickin' lockjaw.

655
00:26:35,795 --> 00:26:36,912
You know something, Doc?

656
00:26:36,930 --> 00:26:38,357
Sometimes I just think
that I've wasted

657
00:26:38,381 --> 00:26:39,608
every single Monday, Wednesday,
and Friday

658
00:26:39,632 --> 00:26:42,217
for the last 14 years.

659
00:26:46,422 --> 00:26:47,702
You know, this is the first time

660
00:26:47,724 --> 00:26:49,401
we've ever had a steak dinner.

661
00:26:49,425 --> 00:26:51,069
I didn't know
you were keeping a tally.

662
00:26:51,093 --> 00:26:54,340
It's pretty easy to do
when the grand total is zero.

663
00:26:54,364 --> 00:26:57,098
I know.

664
00:26:57,116 --> 00:26:58,356
I said I wanted to take you out

665
00:26:58,368 --> 00:26:59,888
the night you told me
you were leaving.

666
00:26:59,903 --> 00:27:03,515
We never got around to it.

667
00:27:03,539 --> 00:27:06,408
I never got around to it.

668
00:27:09,045 --> 00:27:11,390
What's the real reason you
were at the hospital tonight?

669
00:27:11,414 --> 00:27:14,426
The truth?

670
00:27:14,450 --> 00:27:16,117
Rachel asked me
for some time off,

671
00:27:16,135 --> 00:27:17,897
and I all but spit in her face.

672
00:27:17,921 --> 00:27:19,765
So you felt guilty?

673
00:27:19,789 --> 00:27:21,367
Pretty much.

674
00:27:21,391 --> 00:27:23,124
Plus,
I knew you needed something

675
00:27:23,142 --> 00:27:24,570
to take your mind off her,

676
00:27:24,594 --> 00:27:28,991
but I can see this dinner
with me isn't working, so...

677
00:27:29,015 --> 00:27:30,993
Here.

678
00:27:31,017 --> 00:27:32,912
Holy shit.

679
00:27:32,936 --> 00:27:34,546
What is this?

680
00:27:34,570 --> 00:27:36,382
Louis is in a play.

681
00:27:36,406 --> 00:27:37,666
You wanted to cheer me up,

682
00:27:37,690 --> 00:27:39,291
and you didn't
start the night with this?

683
00:27:39,308 --> 00:27:40,419
Come on.

684
00:27:40,443 --> 00:27:42,004
I wanted to save something
for dessert.

685
00:27:42,028 --> 00:27:43,144
Oh, my God, that's got to be
a codpiece, right?

686
00:27:43,162 --> 00:27:44,673
What are you asking me for?

687
00:27:44,697 --> 00:27:47,017
I don't want to know if Louis
is packing that kind of heat.

688
00:27:47,033 --> 00:27:48,627
You think I do?

689
00:27:48,651 --> 00:27:49,762
You're the one
who went mudding with him.

690
00:27:49,786 --> 00:27:51,063
It was covered in mud.

691
00:27:51,087 --> 00:27:53,732
- How much mud?
- Stop.

692
00:27:53,756 --> 00:27:56,185
Why would I ask that?

693
00:27:56,209 --> 00:27:58,794
Oh, man.

694
00:28:00,680 --> 00:28:04,910
I shouldn't be laughing at him.

695
00:28:04,934 --> 00:28:09,221
He still hasn't forgiven me
for using Sheila against him.

696
00:28:10,807 --> 00:28:13,452
Mike, you did
what you had to do.

697
00:28:13,476 --> 00:28:14,987
You don't think
that was crossing a line?

698
00:28:15,011 --> 00:28:16,372
It was way over the line.

699
00:28:16,396 --> 00:28:18,457
But I got to tell you,
it was brilliant.

700
00:28:18,481 --> 00:28:21,616
It was harsh,
but it was brilliant.

701
00:28:24,988 --> 00:28:28,356
You know, Harvey,
I-I never told you.

702
00:28:28,374 --> 00:28:31,126
What you did with Gillis...

703
00:28:33,696 --> 00:28:36,308
I know you had to do it.

704
00:28:36,332 --> 00:28:39,801
Like I said before,
we do what we need to do.

705
00:28:44,373 --> 00:28:46,902
Louis, you're almost up.

706
00:28:46,926 --> 00:28:48,904
Oh, Christ, you're sweating
more than Nixon.

707
00:28:48,928 --> 00:28:50,322
I've gone through
four Elizabethan collars

708
00:28:50,346 --> 00:28:51,573
and a codpiece.

709
00:28:51,597 --> 00:28:52,574
Okay, just breathe.
You're gonna be fine.

710
00:28:52,598 --> 00:28:53,692
No, I can't do it.

711
00:28:53,716 --> 00:28:55,995
Louis, we are
in the middle of the play.

712
00:28:56,019 --> 00:28:57,913
You'll have to ad-lib.
Make something up.

713
00:28:57,937 --> 00:28:59,081
Say shylock went away.

714
00:28:59,105 --> 00:29:00,722
Say that he went to Israel.
Oh, my God.

715
00:29:00,740 --> 00:29:01,834
Wow!

716
00:29:01,858 --> 00:29:05,894
I don't even know what...
you know what?

717
00:29:05,912 --> 00:29:08,640
I never thought
you'd be so weak.

718
00:29:08,664 --> 00:29:09,898
Okay, why do you got to say
something hurtful right now?

719
00:29:09,916 --> 00:29:11,066
Oh, screw hurt!

720
00:29:11,084 --> 00:29:13,568
Turn that into rage.
Why would I do-

721
00:29:13,586 --> 00:29:16,515
You always turn hurt into
rage, you idiotic piece of shit.

722
00:29:16,539 --> 00:29:17,816
It is what you do.

723
00:29:17,840 --> 00:29:18,840
Okay, now I'm mad at you.

724
00:29:18,841 --> 00:29:20,075
Good!

725
00:29:20,093 --> 00:29:21,720
Now, imagine you're in court.
Court, how?

726
00:29:21,744 --> 00:29:22,911
It's too hard with the curtain.
Just do it, dipshit.

727
00:29:22,929 --> 00:29:24,156
Okay, fine,
I'm in court, God damn it.

728
00:29:24,180 --> 00:29:26,525
You happy now?
No, I'm not happy, you idiot.

729
00:29:26,549 --> 00:29:28,694
Now, you're in court,

730
00:29:28,718 --> 00:29:31,753
and you're enraged,
and you are fit to kill.

731
00:29:31,771 --> 00:29:34,566
Now, do you see
that audience out there?

732
00:29:34,590 --> 00:29:36,591
That's your jury.
They're a bunch of morons.

733
00:29:36,609 --> 00:29:37,836
Yeah, they're beneath you,
aren't they?

734
00:29:37,860 --> 00:29:38,954
- They're beneath everybody.
- What else?

735
00:29:38,978 --> 00:29:40,258
They're a bunch
of civil servants

736
00:29:40,262 --> 00:29:41,763
who can't keep up
with what I'm saying.

737
00:29:41,781 --> 00:29:43,292
You have absolute and total
contempt for them, don't you?

738
00:29:43,316 --> 00:29:45,878
I want to rip out their stupid
brains from their stupid heads.

739
00:29:45,902 --> 00:29:47,268
Exactly.

740
00:29:47,286 --> 00:29:50,105
Now, get out there
and make your case.

741
00:29:50,123 --> 00:29:51,363
Unless of course you're a pussy

742
00:29:51,374 --> 00:29:53,108
and you were meant to play
plaque your whole life.

743
00:29:53,126 --> 00:29:55,710
3,000 ducats.

744
00:29:59,615 --> 00:30:01,449
I'm gonna head back.

745
00:30:01,467 --> 00:30:05,253
Hey, tell Rachel she should
take the day off tomorrow.

746
00:30:07,140 --> 00:30:08,767
Thanks for this, Harvey.

747
00:30:08,791 --> 00:30:10,458
Excuse me.

748
00:30:10,476 --> 00:30:11,537
Which one of you is Franklin,

749
00:30:11,561 --> 00:30:13,939
and which one of you is Bash?

750
00:30:13,963 --> 00:30:15,964
Did you boys have a nice date?

751
00:30:15,982 --> 00:30:18,043
Couldn't be better.
He even paid.

752
00:30:18,067 --> 00:30:19,711
Oh, I guess he's flush with cash

753
00:30:19,735 --> 00:30:20,746
ever since he left you

754
00:30:20,770 --> 00:30:22,137
in order to do
investment banking.

755
00:30:22,155 --> 00:30:23,155
I'm sorry. Do I know you?

756
00:30:23,156 --> 00:30:25,140
No, but I know you. Mike Ross.

757
00:30:25,158 --> 00:30:26,474
Sean here is with the S.E.C.,

758
00:30:26,492 --> 00:30:28,504
and he's using his position
to harass my clients

759
00:30:28,528 --> 00:30:29,588
on behalf of Eric Woodall.

760
00:30:29,612 --> 00:30:30,839
Actually, not anymore, Harvey.

761
00:30:30,863 --> 00:30:35,227
I decided to take your advice
and focus on you.

762
00:30:35,251 --> 00:30:36,595
Are you following me?

763
00:30:36,619 --> 00:30:37,763
Oh, I've got guys who do that.

764
00:30:37,787 --> 00:30:39,231
Then you also better have
authorization

765
00:30:39,255 --> 00:30:40,799
from the Justice Department.

766
00:30:40,823 --> 00:30:42,267
Getting authorization was easy,

767
00:30:42,291 --> 00:30:43,435
because I told them you two

768
00:30:43,459 --> 00:30:45,604
are on opposite sides
of a takeover battle

769
00:30:45,628 --> 00:30:48,240
and that your girlfriend
is your associate.

770
00:30:48,264 --> 00:30:49,641
Are you trying to say
that we're colluding?

771
00:30:49,665 --> 00:30:50,665
Oh, you went right there,
didn't you?

772
00:30:50,683 --> 00:30:51,910
Because you led him there.

773
00:30:51,934 --> 00:30:53,278
Well, in the six hours
that I've been there,

774
00:30:53,302 --> 00:30:54,646
this is what I've learned.

775
00:30:54,670 --> 00:30:57,416
Your girlfriend, who I just
mentioned works for you,

776
00:30:57,440 --> 00:30:59,785
faints at law school
for five minutes.

777
00:30:59,809 --> 00:31:01,253
You guys meet at the hospital.

778
00:31:01,277 --> 00:31:02,598
Then you have dinner
for two hours

779
00:31:02,612 --> 00:31:04,623
where you cancel
a private stock sale

780
00:31:04,647 --> 00:31:07,376
that you both arranged,
and one hour ago,

781
00:31:07,400 --> 00:31:09,261
that stock mysteriously
gets bought

782
00:31:09,285 --> 00:31:11,686
by some shell corporation
set up last year.

783
00:31:11,704 --> 00:31:12,704
- Wait, what?
- Bullshit.

784
00:31:12,705 --> 00:31:13,832
Here's my favorite part,

785
00:31:13,856 --> 00:31:15,384
where you feign outrage
and you feign ignorance

786
00:31:15,408 --> 00:31:17,409
to help sell the whole story.

787
00:31:20,913 --> 00:31:24,332
Anyway, I just wanted
to give you a little heads-up.

788
00:31:26,752 --> 00:31:28,887
Smile for the cameras. Harvey.

789
00:31:33,643 --> 00:31:35,070
- You gave me your word.
- And I kept it.

790
00:31:35,094 --> 00:31:36,622
Oh, yeah,
then what about this stock?

791
00:31:36,646 --> 00:31:38,023
- Jessica must have done it.
- Bullshit.

792
00:31:38,047 --> 00:31:39,291
No, it's not bullshit.

793
00:31:39,315 --> 00:31:40,325
Yeah, and when were you
planning on telling me

794
00:31:40,349 --> 00:31:41,743
this guy was up your ass
for collusion?

795
00:31:41,767 --> 00:31:44,029
I didn't know about this
until five seconds ago.

796
00:31:44,053 --> 00:31:46,131
There are only so many things
I can buy, Harvey.

797
00:31:46,155 --> 00:31:48,667
Listen to me, we can deal
with this guy's bullshit later.

798
00:31:48,691 --> 00:31:51,336
Right now, let me deal
with the stock situation.

799
00:31:51,360 --> 00:31:53,088
I'll make it right.
You can't make it right.

800
00:31:53,112 --> 00:31:55,641
Mike, you used to trust me.

801
00:31:55,665 --> 00:31:58,833
I need you to trust me
right now.

802
00:32:16,010 --> 00:32:18,638
Rachel, wake up.

803
00:32:18,662 --> 00:32:21,381
Hey. Where were you so late?

804
00:32:24,101 --> 00:32:26,646
I was out, thinking.

805
00:32:26,670 --> 00:32:27,837
Thinking what?

806
00:32:27,855 --> 00:32:30,173
I don't want to be a fraud.

807
00:32:30,191 --> 00:32:32,152
What?

808
00:32:32,176 --> 00:32:34,154
I love you.

809
00:32:34,178 --> 00:32:36,623
I'm married to her,

810
00:32:36,647 --> 00:32:38,458
but I don't want
to do that anymore.

811
00:32:38,482 --> 00:32:40,127
I want to be married to you.

812
00:32:40,151 --> 00:32:41,962
Logan.

813
00:32:41,986 --> 00:32:44,798
Rachel...

814
00:32:44,822 --> 00:32:46,967
Will you marry me?

815
00:32:46,991 --> 00:32:48,524
I can't.

816
00:32:48,542 --> 00:32:51,221
Why not?

817
00:32:51,245 --> 00:32:53,724
Because you'll always be
a fraud.

818
00:32:53,748 --> 00:32:55,999
How can you say that to me?

819
00:32:58,385 --> 00:32:59,896
Hey.

820
00:32:59,920 --> 00:33:01,398
You okay?

821
00:33:01,422 --> 00:33:02,422
Hey.

822
00:33:02,423 --> 00:33:06,853
Come on, go back to sleep.

823
00:33:06,877 --> 00:33:09,512
I'll be here when you wake up.

824
00:33:16,720 --> 00:33:18,749
Who told you to buy that stock?

825
00:33:18,773 --> 00:33:20,333
Excuse me?

826
00:33:20,357 --> 00:33:21,701
Let me start again.

827
00:33:21,725 --> 00:33:22,836
Hello, Jessica.

828
00:33:22,860 --> 00:33:25,138
I just found out
we bought the Wexler block.

829
00:33:25,162 --> 00:33:27,007
Would you by any chance know
how that came to happen?

830
00:33:27,031 --> 00:33:28,875
It came to happen
when I found out

831
00:33:28,899 --> 00:33:31,511
the dark pool had been canceled
and I couldn't reach you.

832
00:33:31,535 --> 00:33:34,237
So you took it upon yourself
to make a preemptive bid.

833
00:33:34,255 --> 00:33:35,315
Of course I did.

834
00:33:35,339 --> 00:33:37,317
If I hadn't,
Forstman would have.

835
00:33:37,341 --> 00:33:39,102
So why are you here?

836
00:33:39,126 --> 00:33:42,411
I gave Mike my word
we'd postpone the sale.

837
00:33:42,429 --> 00:33:44,247
Well, I didn't give
Mike anything.

838
00:33:44,265 --> 00:33:45,609
Do you even want to know why?

839
00:33:45,633 --> 00:33:46,749
Not particularly.

840
00:33:46,767 --> 00:33:48,561
It was because Rachel
passed out at school

841
00:33:48,585 --> 00:33:49,896
and was in the hospital.

842
00:33:49,920 --> 00:33:51,198
Is she all right?

843
00:33:51,222 --> 00:33:52,222
Do you care?

844
00:33:52,223 --> 00:33:53,223
Don't you make me out

845
00:33:53,224 --> 00:33:54,545
to be the villain in this,
Harvey.

846
00:33:54,558 --> 00:33:57,871
I am sorry Rachel fainted,

847
00:33:57,895 --> 00:33:59,456
but our obligation
is to our client,

848
00:33:59,480 --> 00:34:02,175
and I'm not undoing that sale.

849
00:34:02,199 --> 00:34:03,376
We can't tonight anyway.

850
00:34:03,400 --> 00:34:04,767
Why not?

851
00:34:04,785 --> 00:34:06,435
Because Cahill
came out of nowhere.

852
00:34:06,453 --> 00:34:07,848
He's been having me followed.

853
00:34:07,872 --> 00:34:10,300
He thinks Mike and I
are colluding on Gillis,

854
00:34:10,324 --> 00:34:12,519
and if we undo that sale,
it'll just fuel the fire.

855
00:34:12,543 --> 00:34:14,587
I told you
I was still worried about him.

856
00:34:14,611 --> 00:34:15,806
What did you want me to do?

857
00:34:15,830 --> 00:34:18,141
Have myself tailed
to pick up a possible tail?

858
00:34:18,165 --> 00:34:21,617
What did you come in here
to tell me, Harvey?

859
00:34:21,635 --> 00:34:23,596
Now that Sean Cahill
is involved,

860
00:34:23,620 --> 00:34:26,233
we also can't ever transfer
those shares to Logan.

861
00:34:26,257 --> 00:34:29,152
Which conveniently helps
fix your deal with Mike Ross.

862
00:34:29,176 --> 00:34:30,436
- Jessica...
- You know what?

863
00:34:30,460 --> 00:34:31,905
Doesn't matter.
We don't need to transfer them.

864
00:34:31,929 --> 00:34:34,207
We'll just vote Logan's way
when the time comes.

865
00:34:34,231 --> 00:34:37,800
Jessica, I gave Mike my word.

866
00:34:37,818 --> 00:34:40,380
Harvey, I don't care
if you took a blood oath.

867
00:34:40,404 --> 00:34:44,668
Our duty is to our client,
not a handshake with Mike Ross.

868
00:34:44,692 --> 00:34:46,776
And this discussion is over.

869
00:34:54,668 --> 00:34:55,962
Checked you out.

870
00:34:55,986 --> 00:34:58,265
You're free to go
on your own recognizance.

871
00:34:58,289 --> 00:34:59,516
How much was bail?

872
00:34:59,540 --> 00:35:02,635
Oh, it's okay,
I took care of it.

873
00:35:02,659 --> 00:35:04,187
How are you feeling?

874
00:35:04,211 --> 00:35:05,605
You know,
I'm actually feeling...

875
00:35:05,629 --> 00:35:06,629
I'm feeling pretty good.

876
00:35:06,630 --> 00:35:07,910
In fact,
I think that I'm going...

877
00:35:07,932 --> 00:35:10,443
Rachel, no,
you can't do any work today.

878
00:35:10,467 --> 00:35:12,312
I'm just gonna
stop by the office

879
00:35:12,336 --> 00:35:15,448
and put away just three files,
send four emails.

880
00:35:15,472 --> 00:35:16,700
That's it.

881
00:35:16,724 --> 00:35:21,477
I have to do this
just for my own peace of mind.

882
00:35:24,615 --> 00:35:27,627
- No more.
- No more.

883
00:35:27,651 --> 00:35:30,714
I won't even tell anybody
that I'm there.

884
00:35:30,738 --> 00:35:33,689
I won't.

885
00:35:33,707 --> 00:35:35,187
Louis, can I talk to you
for a minute?

886
00:35:35,192 --> 00:35:36,303
Of course.

887
00:35:36,327 --> 00:35:39,379
First of all,
you were remarkable last night.

888
00:35:41,048 --> 00:35:42,865
- Who said?
- Everyone in the cast.

889
00:35:42,883 --> 00:35:44,177
The Flushing Chronicle?

890
00:35:44,201 --> 00:35:46,202
Um, you know, I don't
actually read the local...

891
00:35:46,220 --> 00:35:49,015
You should, because they said
I was a shock to the senses.

892
00:35:49,039 --> 00:35:50,183
I bought six copies
this morning.

893
00:35:50,207 --> 00:35:51,451
I'm gonna send five to Esther,

894
00:35:51,475 --> 00:35:53,403
because she thinks
she's such a great singer.

895
00:35:53,427 --> 00:35:54,427
Okay.

896
00:35:54,428 --> 00:35:55,878
Louis, what I came in here
to say...

897
00:35:55,896 --> 00:35:57,073
Donna, I'm retiring.

898
00:35:57,097 --> 00:36:00,526
You're what?

899
00:36:00,550 --> 00:36:02,862
You helped me get over a fear

900
00:36:02,886 --> 00:36:05,031
that I never thought
I'd get over.

901
00:36:05,055 --> 00:36:07,584
But I don't want to see
the audience as the jury.

902
00:36:07,608 --> 00:36:10,770
I don't want to have disdain
for them.

903
00:36:10,794 --> 00:36:14,741
I am the audience,

904
00:36:14,765 --> 00:36:17,811
and I want to love them.

905
00:36:17,835 --> 00:36:20,546
- Louis.
- Donna, I'm sorry.

906
00:36:20,570 --> 00:36:22,015
Because I know I'm taking away

907
00:36:22,039 --> 00:36:23,406
your last glorious night
from you,

908
00:36:23,424 --> 00:36:26,820
but I can't go on again.

909
00:36:26,844 --> 00:36:28,845
I, um...

910
00:36:31,215 --> 00:36:32,215
I can't do it.

911
00:36:32,216 --> 00:36:33,693
It's okay, Louis.

912
00:36:33,717 --> 00:36:34,828
It's okay.

913
00:36:34,852 --> 00:36:37,420
It turns out
that the other shylock

914
00:36:37,438 --> 00:36:40,589
only sprained his ankle.

915
00:36:40,607 --> 00:36:45,094
Looks like he's gonna be able
to go on tonight after all.

916
00:36:45,112 --> 00:36:47,763
Wait a minute.

917
00:36:47,781 --> 00:36:50,316
He never hurt his ankle at all,
did he?

918
00:36:54,238 --> 00:36:55,559
You know,
I just knew that you had

919
00:36:55,572 --> 00:37:00,053
a lot of things going on lately
with Harvey and Malone,

920
00:37:00,077 --> 00:37:02,856
and sometimes the best way
to deal with disappointment

921
00:37:02,880 --> 00:37:06,249
in one arena
is to accomplish something else.

922
00:37:07,968 --> 00:37:09,118
Thank you.

923
00:37:09,136 --> 00:37:12,955
You're welcome, Louis.

924
00:37:12,973 --> 00:37:17,343
Hey, remember when you said
that you're not a lawyer?

925
00:37:20,397 --> 00:37:22,482
You could be.

926
00:38:13,951 --> 00:38:16,262
Got Donna's message.
What's going on?

927
00:38:16,286 --> 00:38:19,549
How's Rachel?

928
00:38:19,573 --> 00:38:22,075
She's good. Resting.

929
00:38:23,660 --> 00:38:26,723
- Mike.
- God damn it, I knew it.

930
00:38:26,747 --> 00:38:28,108
I knew you wouldn't fix it.

931
00:38:28,132 --> 00:38:30,276
- I tried.
- You tried?

932
00:38:30,300 --> 00:38:31,561
You're a name partner.

933
00:38:31,585 --> 00:38:33,780
And she's the managing
partner, and you know it.

934
00:38:33,804 --> 00:38:34,781
That wouldn't have
made a difference

935
00:38:34,805 --> 00:38:36,015
if you were fighting for you.

936
00:38:36,039 --> 00:38:38,851
I fought Jessica for you
and won more than once,

937
00:38:38,875 --> 00:38:41,988
but this isn't
one of those times, Mike.

938
00:38:42,012 --> 00:38:43,523
Believe me,
this isn't what I wanted.

939
00:38:43,547 --> 00:38:47,100
My mistake was believing you
when you gave me your word.

940
00:38:49,403 --> 00:38:51,581
No.

941
00:38:51,605 --> 00:38:54,467
I made the mistake
by not believing in you

942
00:38:54,491 --> 00:38:58,538
the second you brought me
your takeover plan.

943
00:38:58,562 --> 00:39:03,476
Look, I don't have
a lot of regrets.

944
00:39:03,500 --> 00:39:04,733
It's just not who I am.

945
00:39:04,751 --> 00:39:09,149
But this is one of them.

946
00:39:09,173 --> 00:39:11,884
If I could go back
and change it, I would,

947
00:39:11,908 --> 00:39:15,595
but I can't.

948
00:39:17,431 --> 00:39:20,383
Is that supposed to stop me?

949
00:39:22,219 --> 00:39:25,165
No, I just wanted you
to know it.

950
00:39:25,189 --> 00:39:28,057
Do what you have to do.

951
00:39:48,278 --> 00:39:51,914
Mr. Ross,
what can I help you with?

952
00:39:53,550 --> 00:39:54,783
Actually, nothing.

953
00:39:54,801 --> 00:39:56,596
Nothing?

954
00:39:56,620 --> 00:39:57,647
What do you mean nothing?

955
00:39:57,671 --> 00:40:00,533
I mean I made a mistake.

956
00:40:00,557 --> 00:40:03,486
I'm gonna find another way
to win this thing.

957
00:40:03,510 --> 00:40:08,297
I'm grateful, but I'm not gonna
need your money anymore.

958
00:40:08,315 --> 00:40:12,652
You may not need my money,
but you've got it.

959
00:40:13,904 --> 00:40:16,282
What are you talking about?

960
00:40:16,306 --> 00:40:19,975
You think I didn't know
what you were up to?

961
00:40:19,993 --> 00:40:22,645
You tried not to fund the money,

962
00:40:22,663 --> 00:40:24,424
so you could leverage Specter
out of the deal

963
00:40:24,448 --> 00:40:26,025
and get out of our deal.

964
00:40:26,049 --> 00:40:27,483
- How...
- Did I know?

965
00:40:27,501 --> 00:40:31,820
I've done the same thing
a hundred times.

966
00:40:31,838 --> 00:40:33,266
I'm actually glad you did it,

967
00:40:33,290 --> 00:40:37,126
because now I know the kind
of person I'm in bed with.

968
00:40:39,162 --> 00:40:41,631
A sneaky little shit like me.

969
00:40:45,102 --> 00:40:47,614
Yeah, do you know the difference
between you and me?

970
00:40:47,638 --> 00:40:48,915
I'm not taking the money

971
00:40:48,939 --> 00:40:51,484
because I don't want
to screw over my partner.

972
00:40:51,508 --> 00:40:54,621
And if I were you,

973
00:40:54,645 --> 00:40:57,707
I wouldn't want
to screw him over either.

974
00:40:57,731 --> 00:40:59,492
That man has nothing
but wonderful things

975
00:40:59,516 --> 00:41:02,462
to say about you.

976
00:41:02,486 --> 00:41:04,997
You had him take the money,
didn't you?

977
00:41:05,021 --> 00:41:08,334
He couldn't believe
it hadn't happened already.

978
00:41:08,358 --> 00:41:12,861
He told me he's having a little
tombstone made up for you.

979
00:41:12,879 --> 00:41:16,776
Mike, we are partners on this,

980
00:41:16,800 --> 00:41:19,502
whether you like it or not.

981
00:41:37,404 --> 00:41:38,404
What are you doing here?

982
00:41:38,405 --> 00:41:40,556
I'm here to deliver these.

983
00:41:40,574 --> 00:41:41,574
Who are those for?

984
00:41:41,575 --> 00:41:45,588
Who do you think they're for?

985
00:41:45,612 --> 00:41:47,039
For you, for your dressing room.

986
00:41:47,063 --> 00:41:49,565
Let's go.

987
00:41:49,583 --> 00:41:50,876
You're coming?

988
00:41:50,900 --> 00:41:52,679
You think I'm gonna miss
your closing night?

989
00:41:52,703 --> 00:41:54,347
I didn't know
you were a Shakespeare fan.

990
00:41:54,371 --> 00:41:57,340
I'm a Donna fan.

991
00:41:58,792 --> 00:42:00,553
You know, Harvey,
you don't have to do this.

992
00:42:00,577 --> 00:42:01,821
I know you got a lot
going on with Mike.

993
00:42:01,845 --> 00:42:04,630
The only thing I got going on
tonight is you.

