Previously on Suits:
We're suing you and your
entire firm for fraud.
I'm looking at a document that
implicates you in a cover-up.
I savaged his reputation all
because you looked me in the eye
and told me that your hood
was rock solid.
You make it right
on your own or I will.
When were you planning
on telling me this?
Did you find what
you're not looking for?
No, did u find
what you're not looking for?
Nope.
That document never
came into this office.
Where the hell is Donna?
She's in the file room.
Hasn't found that document yet.
Anyone could have
seen it and missed it.
I need to know
that didn't happen,
or I need to know who to fire.
Never thought I'd see
the great Harvey Specter
break a sweat.
You want to race, Jeffrey?
I'm more than happy
to kick your ass.
Believe me, Harvey,
I didn't get up
at 5:00 a.m. for my health.
A guy like you
in Central Park at this hour?
That's not where
my mind went either.
Only guy I'm here
to solicit is you, buddy.
I'll assume you've heard
of Marco Mendoza.
Yeah, the 16-year-old
tennis phenom.
What about him?
I'm on the cusp
of signing that kid.
I want you
to be part of the team.
Just because
I know about tennis
doesn't mean I
give a shit about tennis.
Hey, the basketballs
in your office
didn't autograph
themselves, Harvey.
You owe me. Oh, please.
I've brought you just as
many clients as you brought me.
Five minutes with the kid.
That's all I'm asking.
You're an agent, Jeffrey.
It's never all you're asking.
There might be
one slight wrinkle.
So you want me to emancipate
him from his father?
That's a hell of a thing to do
just for a commission.
Just listen
to what he has to say.
Marco, tell him your story.
Look, I've been playing tennis
since before I could walk.
When I was six, I was
crushing kids in high school.
I don't play cards,
I don't drink.
What I do is win.
I like this kid.
So what does that have
to do with your father?
He won't let me go pro.
So it's all about the money.
No, I don't care
about the money.
You can keep the money.
Nine out of ten tournaments
are closed to amateurs.
If I don't go pro,
I can't play against the best.
And if I can't
play against the best,
I can't be the best.
That's a great speech,
but you're 16,
and what I'm not hearing is why
you can't wait two more years.
People hit their prime
at different ages, Mr. Specter.
Look at me.
I have a chance to be great,
and I have a chance now.
You know that paper doesn't...
put itself
in the machine, right?
What the hell
is wrong with you?
Me? You're the one that looks
like you're
burying a dead body.
It is 6:00 in the morning.
I come in here
to shred in peace,
and you walk in and you scare
the crap out of me.
I'm sorry... "Shred in peace"?
Do you have any idea
how dangerous this machine is?
Okay, I'm sorry.
If you want, I can help.
I'm actually here
to do some shredding myself.
You know what? Never mind.
You've ruined the whole thing.
Well, the good news is,
we don't have
a copy of that memo.
I'm sorry
to rain on your parade,
but the accusation here
isn't that you have it,
it's that you buried it,
so we should
probably move forward.
To what?
We need to put them
on the defensive.
- No, we don't.
- Harvey.
We need to get them
to drop the case.
- And how would we do that?
- How would I do it?
I would go to
the Randall family.
They got screwed
and they want justice,
but I'm not the guy
who screwed them,
so we need to
convince them that I...
Are you crazy?
You trashed this woman's
dead husband in open court.
Do you think she gives a shit
about whether or not
you buried that document?
If you go there, you're not
just poking the bear,
you're putting
a cattle prod up its ass.
Is that the same crack advice
you gave Brockton Cosmetics
and Drake Consulting
and Nappi LLC.?
'Cause none of those companies
exist anymore.
Congratulations, Harvey.
You found the three cases
that I've lost in 14 years.
And do you know what else
those cases have in common?
Nothing. Because I learn
from my mistakes.
Well, I'd prefer
to be represented by someone
who doesn't make any mistakes
in the first place.
Like you?
Because you've been accused
of burying evidence
not once, but twice.
Those accusations are bullshit.
And that is
what I'm here to prove.
Jessica, if I may?
I don't think Harvey's problem
is with Allison.
I think his problem is with me.
Daniel, we don't need
to air our laundry in here.
This is
a privileged conversation.
Jessica, I'm asking
you and Harvey to trust me.
So I'm going to
do the same for you.
I brought Allison in here
because I think she's the best.
Use her or don't.
But, if not, I suggest
you find someone just as good.
Harvey...
will you give
Allison and me a minute?
Let her down easy.
Allison, I am impressed by you.
But if I'm going
to give you this job,
I need to know
that I can trust you.
I'm a straight shooter,
Jessica.
Easy to say, harder to prove.
All right, how about this?
Um, you are an elegant woman,
but there's no
getting around it...
that dress does not
belong in this office.
I like you.
This may be something
that you don't like.
You won't be the one
dictating terms here. I will.
And regarding your laundry,
you have my word that Danny
won't be involved,
but you need to keep
that man on a leash.
- She said that to your face?
- Yep.
- You kick her ass out?
- Hired her on the spot.
The woman insults you,
all of a sudden
you're in bed with her?
Maybe I should tell you
how much I hate those shoes.
That's the joke
you're gonna make?
What? It's both respectful
and disrespectful
at the same time.
Harvey, I don't
want you to overlook
the point of the story.
It's Allison's case.
The firm is the client,
and you're...
- The dog on a leash?
- Stay out of her way.
I got the address.
Then I guess it's time
for this dog
to go chase some cars.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right
♪ all that time imagine this ♪
♪ The greenback boogie
That's good.
I am not seeing
what I'm seeing.
Mrs. Randall, please,
I know you hate me for
what I did to your husband.
"Hate" is not the word.
There is no word to describe
what I feel for you.
Now get your ass...
Jennifer, look where we are.
I don't mean to disrespect you
or dishonor
your husband's memory.
You've already done that.
I'm trying to make up
for it now.
Now that your back's
against the wall.
No, I started years ago.
This says
he's our anonymous donor.
- It's true.
- Of course. Guilty conscience.
No, I don't have
a guilty conscience,
'cause I wasn't the one
who hid that memo.
Look, I went after your husband
because I thought
that car was solid.
I didn't like doing it,
but it was my job.
Why'd you give us
the money then?
Because you were trying
to make something good
come from something bad,
like I am now.
- What do you want?
- I know what he wants.
We're not dropping our suit.
And the fact that you would
come here to tell me that
shows me just what kind
of self-serving trash you are.
You're right, I came here
to get you to drop your suit.
But instead of self-serving,
let's talk about me serving you.
You want payback
for what was done to you...
justice... and I can get it.
My husband died,
and you made me sit there
while you shit on him.
That's what was done to me.
Now you're gonna tell me
that wasn't you?
Yeah, I want justice,
but that little donation
doesn't cover it.
This isn't really helping
your street cred, Harold.
It's not mine, it's Louis'.
What's his name?
Bruno. He brought him in
because he hasn't been eating.
Whoa, wh... have you
mentioned to Louis
that you're allergic?
I tried to, but he said that...
Allergies
are a sign of weakness.
Right, and bringing your cat
to work is a sign of strength.
Yeah, you want to trade places?
Uh, nope.
No, I got a meeting
in the conference room.
That's right,
that little tennis fling.
Makes me sick.
Harvey's got no appreciation
for the game.
Man wouldn't know topspin
if it hit him in the ball sack.
But enjoy yourself. Get out.
Can you not smell that?
I'm stuffed up.
Uhhuh. How long has it been?
Two hours.
How often do
I tell you to do it?
I'll get the bag.
Hi.
What's wrong, Bruno?
You're my best friend.
- You all set?
- I'm ready to roll.
Good, 'cause I got
a bidding war starting
for Marco's endorsement.
Dad?
Marco, why don't
you take a seat?
What's he doing here?
He's here to meet with his son.
We're emancipating,
and you said you were in.
I did, which means
Marco's my client,
not you, so why don't you
go home, Jeffrey?
I'll call you when we're done.
Mr. Mendoza,
I want to be clear,
I'm not here
to exploit your son.
I'm here to protect him.
You're off to a good start.
You can ask
any one of my clients.
They'll tell you the same.
You represent Michael Jordan.
I do. In fact, I want
to tell you a story about him.
You want to tell me
a story about Michael Jordan
to convince me
my son should turn pro?
Let me tell you a story
about George Washington.
Maybe junior here
could become President.
I'm really more of
an Abe Lincoln fan myself.
You know, freed the slaves,
great beard.
- You finished?
- Yep.
Everybody knows M.J.
took two years off in his prime.
He regrets it to this day.
But he made
that decision himself,
and that's how
he lives with it.
All your son is asking is
for the chance to do the same.
I may not know Mr. Jordan,
but I do know
that he's divorced,
and I've heard the rumors
about his gambling problem.
He's a man apart.
Now, my son is not ready
to handle that kind of life.
You've prepared me for this
since I was three.
I taught you tennis
because it's a beautiful game.
You may not have set out
to raise a prodigy,
but the fact is, you did.
Do you have any children,
Mr. Specter?
No? Then I'm not interested
in your parenting advice.
I'm not giving
parenting advice.
I'm giving career advice.
You told me that
you didn't want to exploit him,
that you wanted
to protect him...
him, not his career.
Look, you don't get it.
They're the same to me.
All right, I'm committed
to both of them,
and I don't give a shit
if you like it or not.
Marco.
You say that word to me
in front of these parasites?
Yeah, I'll say
whatever I want to say.
Shut your mouth.
Now, you are not
going to turn pro,
and you are not going
to continue down this path,
and this conversation is over.
You just want to let him leave?
Look, I don't
care what he does, okay?
I want to file
for emancipation.
So you're telling me
you don't have it?
I don't, but I'm sure
it'll turn up.
You sure?
Your job was to keep track
of that one thing.
Nice work.
It's a birthday card for Norma.
She won't even tell us
how old she is.
Her birthday is today.
When do you think
it's going to turn up?
You know what, forget it.
What's the matter with you?
What's the matter with me
is that nobody ever has
what they're supposed to
in this goddamn office.
You know what?
I got bigger fish to fry.
Put the wheels in motion.
"The wheels"?
This isn't a merger, Harvey.
You're talking
about emancipation.
I'm talking about
filing for emancipation.
It's a tactic.
He cares about his son.
Nine times out of ten,
he backs down.
And what if he doesn't?
Then we'll be doing exactly
what the client wants us to do.
Oh, you mean
break up his family.
I mean help his family.
Wow, wonder
what kind of relationship
you had with your father.
Look, my father's
not up for discussion.
The only bone of contention
between them is this decision.
The sooner they resolve it,
the sooner they can move on.
The sooner you get paid.
I cut billion dollar deals
for breakfast.
I don't need this. I told you,
it's what the client wants.
It's what he thinks he wants.
Harvey, I was 11
when my dad died,
and our last conversation
was a fight.
If you gave me the choice
to be a pro anything
or to make up with him,
what do you think I'd choose?
If we don't do it, he'll find
someone else who will.
If you don't want him to do it,
change his goddamn mind.
Now go. Fine.
Here's your
goddamn birthday card.
I don't appreciate you
coming into my office saying
that no one at the firm has
what they're supposed to have,
and I don't know what
crawled up your ass today,
but I take care of my business.
I'm sorry, Rach. You're right.
This isn't about you.
This is about me.
Okay then.
I unplugged it.
And this time, I'm not
stopping you by accident.
I have no idea
what you're talking about...
Don't bullshit me, Donna.
That's the same file you had
in your hand this morning.
You ran out of here
like you saw a ghost,
you bit off Rachel's head,
talking about how people
never have the things
they're supposed to have,
and now you're
right back here again.
It's not Dalton Enterprises
you're holding.
That's the memo that Harvey's
been accused of burying.
You know, the fact that
you would even accuse me of that
makes me sick.
But if you still
don't believe me, fine.
See for yourself.
I don't know what to do.
Tell me what happened.
I found it in
the file room that day.
It has my date stamp
on it... mine.
We have to tell Harvey.
He'll know what to do.
No, he won't.
Donna, Harvey's been
operating under the assumption
that we never had
this memo, all right?
At some point, that assumption
is gonna bite him in the ass,
and the later it happens,
the bigger the bite.
Nobody is going to believe
that a file that important
just got lost.
They'll think that
I got rid of it,
and that Harvey
told me to do it.
This memo is part
of a legal proceeding.
Shredding it is a crime.
Like practicing law
without a license is a crime?
Unlike you,
I didn't do this on purpose,
and I am protecting Harvey
the best way that I know how.
Allison Holt is gonna
figure out what happened.
And when she does,
her priority's not going to be
protecting you or Harvey.
It's gonna be
protecting the firm.
You might be comfortable
putting Harvey in that position,
but I'm not.
So either you tell him,
or I will.
- The answer is yes.
- What?
You can have
Halloween off this year.
Every July, you sit there
staring at me
before coming in here with
that sheepish look on your face
to ask to...
I have to tell you something.
What? What is it?
What the hell
were you thinking?
You contacted the plaintiffs
without their lawyer present
or our lawyer present.
Exactly, I'm not our lawyer.
I had every legal right to.
You weren't supposed
to interfere.
Neither were you.
How did you even know?
She's not supposed
to tell you anything.
She was forced to tell me
when I got served
with this goddamn subpoena.
You didn't want
to put them on the defensive,
which is good,
because what you've just done
is put us on the defensive,
so now I have to spend
the next two weeks
prepping everyone from
Jessica to your secretary,
because Travis Tanner is gonna
depose them under oath.
Nobody here knows
a thing about that goddamn memo.
Let them waste
their time with it.
This is why you hire
outside counsel.
You can't see
how reckless that was,
even now, after
it's blown up in your face.
Fine, if you insist on
pre-deposing their depositions,
let's get it over with.
You can start with me.
I already have
your version of events.
Okay, you can start with Donna.
What's not to understand?
Most fathers in the same
situation would either
want to live vicariously
through their children's lives
or sponge off their backs,
but your father,
he's just trying to protect you.
Yeah, look, I know
what he thinks he's doing.
Marco, it's a year
and eight months.
Maybe, but you don't
know what it's like
to be better at something
than everyone.
A year and eight months
is 505 days.
12,120 hours
and 727,200 minutes.
Yeah, I know what it's like.
You can do math
when you're an old man.
I can only dominate
till I'm 30.
Maybe, but if you go through
with this now,
you're gonna drive a wedge
between the two of you
that'll last
the rest of your life.
It's already there
because of him.
I'm like the horse
in the stall.
He won't open the gate, and
if it stays shut much longer,
I'm gonna go crazy.
All right, you're the client.
I just have a couple
of questions for you
before we can file
with the courts, okay?
Okay, great.
Has your father ever
abused drugs or alcohol?
- No.
- Is he a gambling addict?
- No, nothing like that.
- Is your home without
electricity,
running water, food?
We don't live in a slum.
Emancipation requires proof
that your father
is an unfit parent.
We have to think about
how this plays in court.
And telling a judge
that he just wants you
to wait until you finish
high school before you make
millions of dollars
is not going to cut it.
Look, Marco...
what I saw in
that conference room
is not a father who was unfit.
I saw a father
who loves his son.
You saw something else
in there, too.
You saw how furious he gets
when he's defied.
What are you getting at?
I'm getting at what happens
when he feels that way
and nobody else is around.
There's no reason
to be concerned.
These are pro forma questions
I'm asking everyone.
Oh, I'm not concerned,
I'm bored,
so can we just...
Of course.
Do you think you can move
that other there?
It's my good side.
Well, my better side.
They're both good.
I'm just going to start. Um...
So, when documents
are received into the firm,
they then come to you.
Is that correct? Yes.
And how do they get
from the mail room to you?
Transporter beam.
Ms. Paulsen, I understand
that your time is valuable,
but I'm here to prepare you.
And to a jury,
sarcasm plays as obstructive.
Obviously, any further mention
of Star Trek
may just compound
the problem, okay?
Aye, cap'n.
It's Donna, right?
All right,
so where you from, Donna?
- Upstate.
- Like Utica?
No, Cortland, actually.
Cortland's kind of
in the middle, isn't it?
I'm sorry, what does this
have to do with...
I'm just trying
to get to know you,
break down the walls.
You may not know this about me,
but the truth is,
I'm actually single.
- Divorced?
- As a matter of fact, yes.
But anyway, I've been
going on all these dates,
and I found that
sometimes the best way
to get the conversation going
is just start asking
a bunch of questions.
For example, where do you
see yourself in five years?
Well, actually, that's...
'Cause where I see you
is in jail.
Do you think
I was born yesterday?
You know what Harvey did
with that memo,
and you're going
to tell me right now.
Harvey didn't do anything.
Oh, I see.
He didn't have to
because you did it for him.
That's not true.
Then tell me what is true.
Well, that's easy.
You don't give a shit
about me or Harvey.
This is a witch hunt,
and I'm not gonna sit in
this room for another minute.
I've worked with Harvey since
he was a rookie
in the mail room.
No way he buried that memo.
You didn't see Donna
in that room.
I'm not saying
she wouldn't do it if he asked.
I'm saying he wouldn't ask.
Wouldn't he?
Because she's not
the only person I talked to.
Now, a lot of people,
they don't like Harvey.
But even the ones that love him
say he likes to work
in the gray.
I'd like Harvey
to sign this affidavit
swearing that his office
never received the memo.
Why?
To put with
this motion to dismiss.
If you wanted to file
a motion to dismiss,
you would have
done that already.
You want me to sign that thing
to cover your ass.
Do I think it's likely
that this case
is gonna get dismissed?
No, but it's worth a shot,
and to your point,
I'm not just doing this
to cover my ass.
I'm doing it to cover your ass.
File the motion.
Harvey will sign
whatever I put in front of him.
I give you one simple task.
Bruno isn't eating,
so you give him milk.
- I did.
- This is half-and-half.
I thought he'd like it.
It's creamier.
Hey, you know what,
maybe next time
I'll just hand my cat over
to Michael Vick.
Is that a cat carrier
in your hand?
No.
Is there a cat in that thing?
It's called
a feline transportation unit.
Cat carrier.
Okay, they wouldn't call it
a cat carrier
when it costs $400.
- Do they call it a rip-off?
- Okay, you know what,
I don't have time for this.
Besides, I'm late as it is.
I have to ask.
What appointment?
- Dentist.
- With a cat?
- For the cat.
- You take him to a cat dentist?
I can't take him to my dentist.
Dr. Schneller wouldn't know
what to do with him.
- Dr. Richard Schneller?
- Good-bye, Harvey.
I don't want to hear it.
If it's bad news,
- You seem upset.
- Of course I'm upset.
I just found out
that Louis and I
share the same dentist.
Have you spoken to Donna yet?
No, and I'm pissed about it.
I need her to get me
a new dentist.
Well, we have a problem,
whether you want
to hear it or not.
What?
Marco needs to be emancipated
from his father.
But that's not a problem.
That's what we're doing.
No, I don't mean
to let him play.
I mean to keep him safe.
That is directly
from the hospital.
His dad did that to him.
We need to get him away
from his father.
I need to get him away.
I set the hearing,
and I'm going to win.
I'm hearing
a lot of "I" s in there.
- Harvey...
- This isn't housing court.
This is a kid's life.
I know that,
and the only reason
you know that
is because I gave a shit
about this kid's life
in the first place.
You think I didn't think
I was smarter
than the guy
I started working for?
I did, and I was,
and I waited my goddamn turn.
Harvey, I'm ready.
It's time to let me
out of the gate.
Allison's filing
a motion to dismiss.
She's swinging for the fences,
I'll give her that.
You know what, I'm gonna
swing for the fences too.
Mike's going to court.
- I am?
- What's the case?
Emancipation.
- From him?
- I wish.
He doesn't need
a court order for that.
- Our little baby's growing up.
- Okay.
Listen, I need you
to sign this affidavit
that we never received
that memo from Coastal Motors.
Oh, my God! Oh, I'm...
There are napkins over there.
I knew he wasn't a lawyer.
I didn't think he was an idiot.
I knew he was an idiot.
I didn't know he was spastic.
I'm sorry, guys.
When you get this cleaned up,
come see me.
I'll get you a fresh one.
- What the hell was that?
- What?
- You know what.
- It was an accident.
It was intentional.
You ambushed me
with a cup of coffee.
Think I haven't seen Ronin?
It was all I could think of.
Meaning?
Donna was supposed to tell you.
Tell me what?
You can't sign the affidavit.
You'll be committing perjury.
What the hell
were you thinking?
I didn't know how to tell you.
"Harvey, I found the memo."
Is that so goddamn hard?
You don't understand.
It had my name on it.
I stamped it in.
That implicates you.
Did you keep it
from me four years ago?
I don't even remember
seeing it four years ago.
Then I don't give a shit
what it implicates.
You don't keep it from me now.
I had never made
a mistake like that,
and I thought
that I needed to...
Look, keeping it from me
isn't a mistake.
It's a decision.
I wanted to protect you.
Lying to me doesn't protect me.
It betrays me. Betrays you?
If I had told you the truth...
You don't keep things from me!
You keep things from me
all the time!
That's because I'm your boss.
Well, maybe you shouldn't
be my boss anymore.
I did what I thought
I had to do for you,
and if you can't...
just fire me.
Let me explain
something to you.
That memo doesn't hurt me.
It helps me.
If I had buried it,
we wouldn't have it.
But you found it,
so that's a good thing.
What?
Wh-what'd you do?
Oh, what did you do?
Allison
had that freaking camera,
and I was...
she implied that we were...
What did you do?
It's gone.
You destroyed it?
I'm not going
to fire you, Donna.
I might kill you,
but I'm not gonna fire you.
What are you going to do?
What you should've done
from day one.
Let me get this straight.
Your own assistant
destroys evidence,
and you still want
to go to trial?
- Yes.
- No.
You need to cut a deal
right now.
You mean we need
to cut a deal, right,
because we're
all on the same side?
Harvey.
You think I didn't know
what you were up to
with that affidavit?
I was advising my client,
the firm.
You once told me
I was the firm.
She came to me and thought
that you were in on it.
I said no way.
She wanted you
to sign that thing.
I'm the leader of this firm.
I made a decision.
You were happy to do it.
Don't blame me for Donna.
I'm not, but I need to know
if you still believe me.
- I do.
- That's beside the point.
We have a decision to make.
There is no decision.
We need to cut a deal... today.
You know what,
that's the difference
between us, Allison.
You want to lose small.
I want to win big.
She's the one
who has to try the case.
Regardless of what Donna did,
I never saw the memo.
Are you gonna
sell a jury on that?
Maybe the same way you sold it
to the Randall family.
We have a window to settle this
before we have to disclose,
but it's closing,
and when it does,
we could offer them the moon.
They're not gonna take it.
What's the downside of asking?
We went through this
with the nurses.
It tells them we're weak.
We are weak.
Set it up.
And whatever you're thinking,
I don't want to hear it.
Mr. Mendoza, you've
asserted that, as a parent,
you have certain rights.
Do those include
the right to discipline Marco
as you see fit?
Every parent has that right.
The right to teach
your child a lesson.
- Yes.
- When he defies you.
If need be.
And if need be,
do you get angry?
Do you fly off the handle?
Do you become abusive?
No, I would never go that far.
Mr. Mendoza,
would you agree that,
along with those rights,
you have certain
responsibilities as a parent?
Of course.
The responsibility
to keep your son healthy?
Marco gets up every day
at 4:30 to train.
I think that one's covered.
The responsibility
to keep your son safe?
That's the first job
of every parent.
Hmm.
Let's talk about
May 18th of last year.
You took your son
to the hospital
where he was treated
for severe dehydration.
Rushed my son to keep him safe.
What I'm interested in
is how he got dehydrated
in the first place.
He was running laps.
Hadn't you had an argument
about going pro
the night before?
Yes.
And you wanted to teach him
a lesson, as was your right.
What?
He questioned your authority,
didn't he?
He's done it before, hasn't he?
And you don't like that,
do you?
- You are twisting this.
- You got angry,
you flew off the handle,
and you became abusive.
Objection, badgering.
Easy, Mr. Ross.
Marco has never called 911.
He's never reported me
to social services.
He's never complained
to anyone.
They never do.
You think I put my own son
in the hospital?
Oh, I've read this report.
I know you did.
And I know you will again.
You are a lying
little piece of shit.
- And there it is.
- Mr. Mendoza, that's enough.
No further questions.
Oh, what the hell?
You don't sneak up like that.
I wasn't sneaking up.
I was just getting coffee.
Yeah, well,
the paralegal needs coffee.
I guess the junior partner
needs to get out of her way.
You know what, Louis,
if you treated people here
just a tenth as nicely
as you treat your cat,
they might not feel about you
the way that you know they do.
I'm sorry.
Is everything okay?
No, I just have, like,
a condition with my tear ducts.
Oh, my God.
I just assumed
that he wasn't eating
because of his toothache...
but it turns out
his hygiene was perfect.
But of course it was, because
we flossed every day, so...
And then they did these tests.
And I told the vet,
"money is no object,"
but, uh...
it was too late.
Bruno was suffering...
Excuse me. No...
- hey.
- Hey.
- Is everything okay?
- Not exactly.
Okay, I'll come back
when you're finished.
I wasn't talking about you.
Not everything's about you,
you know.
Now, you see,
that's where you're wrong.
What's going on with Donna?
I don't know.
What do you mean?
I saw you watching us
the other day.
You know something.
Come on, Mike, how many secrets
are you gonna keep from me?
It's not mine. It's Donna's.
I'm not saying you need
to give me specifics.
I just need to know
that she's okay.
She screwed up,
and it's not small.
- What's gonna happen?
- Harvey's going to fix it.
How do you know?
You're gonna fix this
situation with Donna, right?
- Why should I tell you?
- What?
If I hadn't caught you,
when were you gonna tell me
that she had that memo?
I wasn't, 'cause
she promised me she would.
Well, what would have
happened if you hadn't been
in my office when Jessica
brought me that affidavit?
That would've been
between you and Donna.
And I would have
committed perjury.
You're right.
I should have told you,
or had Donna tell you then
and there, but I was thinking
the fact that she actually
found this thing helps us.
Yeah, it would've helped us.
She destroyed it.
- Whoa.
- Yeah.
Whoa.
Harvey, she was
backed into a corner.
She made a bad call.
Look, we can still...
Tell the truth?
How do you think
that's going to play in court?
Oh, my God. Um, I have to go.
You screwed up with Marco,
didn't you?
I'm on it.
And this thing with Donna,
just let it go.
I'm sure she said she was sorry.
She is sorry.
But she never said it.
Didn't expect to see you today.
I wanted to get you the offer
as soon as I could.
You could have called.
No, I couldn't.
Tanner's terms.
The firm pays
$5 million in damages,
as well as all legal fees.
What else?
Pearson Hardman
immediately and irrevocably
strips Harvey Specter
of his senior partnership
and reports him to
the New York Bar Association.
I know this isn't
what you want to hear,
but I would
take this deal and run.
What do you want now?
Sell me a vacuum cleaner?
Set of steak knives?
I don't want
to sell you anything.
I'm not here to do that.
I'm here to tell you
that I'm sorry.
I should have known
about that memo.
But I didn't do my job.
If I had, you and I
wouldn't be here right now.
But we are here right now
because of what you did
to my husband.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I never should have done it.
My mother marched, Mr. lawyer.
They set dogs on her.
I saw the scars.
She said it wasn't the dogs,
it was the men.
I say, put those dogs down.
So you think
we should take this deal?
I think we have to.
Just say it.
You want me
to cut Harvey loose.
You've never been afraid
to spill blood before.
You means yours.
I was actually referring
to when you and I
crossed the other names
off the letterhead.
That was for
the good of the firm.
Was it?
Evidence was destroyed,
Jessica.
- Not by Harvey.
- On his watch, therefore...
On mine.
If this were anyone else,
you'd be seeing it
the same way I do.
I'm not scapegoating him.
You care about Harvey.
I know that.
But I also know
that you care about
your position in this firm.
A law was broken.
Are you really going
to sit by and do nothing?
I've got to call you back.
Did you get it?
Got it right here,
fully executed emancipation.
You tell Marco yet?
No, I wanted you
to see it first.
Nice job.
This way I can call him
with the good news.
- Yeah, just one problem.
- What's that?
Marco lied.
- What?
- Yeah.
We got backed into a corner,
and he knew the truth
wouldn't play in court,
so he made up a story.
If it was a lie, Michael,
then why didn't Oscar say so?
Marco perjured himself.
You really think his father
was going to be the one
to point that out?
- That's a lot of conjecture.
- Yeah, it would be.
But I went to see Oscar.
Turns out he wasn't even there
when Marco ran those laps.
But you were.
Nuhuh, it's bullshit.
I saw the look
on your face in court.
You knew, and you did nothing.
You got me.
But it doesn't matter,
'cause we won.
No, we didn't.
'Cause I'm not filing papers
based on a lie.
Harvey is gonna make you
regret that.
Harvey's not gonna do shit.
This is my case,
and you are done.
♪
We need to talk.
It's subtle, but Daniel's
strong-arming me.
Not now.
My dad.
♪
I was wrong.
Am I in the right office?
I went to the plaintiffs again.
Why?
To tell them I was sorry.
Harvey, there is
a deal on the table.
Allison's right.
I shouldn't be the lawyer.
I don't even
make a good client.
Neither do I.
But I've got some hard news
I have to tell you.
Okay, let me guess,
you're here
to take me up on my offer
to trade offices. No.
But I did happen to find these.
Who still eats Twinkies?
Who doesn't still eat Twinkies?
What's up?
- I need a favor.
- Okay, what?
Is this from
your tennis client?
First one.
Not as big as Harvey's.
Really? You're gonna go there?
It's probably gonna be
worth a lot of money someday.
- Probably.
- I need it.
It's important.
What for?
Why don't we
just call that my secret?
Daniel,
will you come to
my office right now please?
Have a seat.
Couldn't we have done this
in my office?
Yes, we could have,
but I prefer to do it here...
in your old office.
What's this?
I want you to
let Allison Holt go.
- Why would I do that?
- Why you?
Because you brought her in
initially.
I am extending you
the courtesy of letting her go.
As for why at all,
I do care about
my position in this firm
and my position is that we win.
We win, Harvey wins,
and I win.
Allison Holt can't win,
because she doesn't
believe in Harvey.
I can, because I do.
- It's your decision.
- It is.
But don't try to pass it off
as a courtesy.
You're trying to humiliate me,
like you did by summoning me
into your office.
I summoned you because
I wanted you to understand
who you were
threatening earlier.
I wasn't threatening you.
I was pointing out facts. Yes.
The fact that,
if I'm not careful,
you'll try to take
this office back.
That's not going to happen.
And as for your point
about a law being broken,
you're right.
I'm not going to sit by
and do nothing.
Louis, can I come in?
I'm a little busy right now.
Where'd you get this?
I just know what
a huge tennis fan you are.
Rachel...
could you just close
the door on your way out?
Sure thing, Louis.
Harvey's not here.
He should be back soon.
I'm not here to see Harvey.
Oh.
He wanted to be the one to
have this conversation with you.
But it's my firm,
and I wanted you
to hear it from me.
Am I being fired?
Yes.
I appreciate everything
that you've done
for Harvey and for me,
but whatever
my personal feelings,
your actions
have left me no choice
but to terminate your employment
at Pearson Hardman
effective immediately.
♪
You said
he was going to fix it.
I thought he would.