Adrian?
Come on.
Zeus, I'm sorry.
I can't take you with me.
I'm sorry.
Shit. I'm not gonna leave you
with that thing on. Okay.
Come here. It's okay.
Good boy.
Come here.
There you go.
Fuck!
Emily, where are you?
Shit.
Cecilia,
what is going on?
Are you okay?
I'll explain later.
Just go, Emily.
Go!
Open the fucking door,
Cecilia! What is happening?
- Open the door!
- No!
Open the fucking door!
Open the door!
- Open the fucking door!
- I'm going! I'm going!
Cecilia! Get back here!
Jesus!
Get back here now! You
can't do this! Get back here!
Cee.
How long have you been up?
Few hours.
Can't sleep.
Cee, you know, if you close your eyes
and you lie down, that usually helps.
Um, don't think being tired gets
you out of our little deal, now.
I swore to your sister I'd get
you to step outside my house.
Hey, Cee.
He's not out there.
I promise.
I'm sorry, I'm just...
I'm not ready yet.
Hey, it's okay, Cee.
That's the furthest you've gone
since you've been here. Okay?
So as far as I'm concerned,
you just walked on the moon.
I can't work
with this damn thing.
It's all right.
I got it.
Do I know you?
Do I owe you money?
A lot.
A lot?
I told y'all about running
up on me in my house.
Hey. Cee, tell her
she can't take you back.
We're keeping you.
What are you doing here, Emily?
Well, it's nice
to see you too, sis.
I'm gonna go
see what Sydney's up to.
Just... Yeah.
Mmm.
This is not fair.
I asked you not to come over.
He knows where you live.
He will follow you.
Yes.
Well, I have some news...
There is no news
that justifies this.
Okay. I have a plan,
and I just...
I need you to go along with it.
And just not be in control
for one second.
I'm not trying
to control you, boo.
I'm desperately trying to tell you that
you don't need to cut me off anymore.
Because he's dead.
What?
Hey.
What did he do to you?
Can you talk to me?
It just doesn't make any sense.
He was... He was in complete
control of everything, you know?
Including me.
He controlled how I looked
and what I wore
and what I ate.
And then it was controlling
when I left the house
and what I said.
And eventually,
what I thought.
And if...
If he didn't like what he
assumed I was thinking...
He...
- He would...
- He'd what?
He would...
He would hit you?
Amongst other things.
He wanted to have a baby.
And I knew that if we did that,
that I would never be
able to get away from him,
so I took birth control
without him knowing it.
But, um, that can
only go on for so long,
so I called you.
Hey.
You're here with us now.
And you're safe.
He's gone.
I'm not telling you to aim low.
I'm just saying, explore
more than one option, okay?
Don't limit your choices to just
one school in the whole country.
But that one school is my
goal. Parsons is my goal.
Yeah, I told you
to have goals. Plural.
I think it's important
to have goals, James.
Hey.
Look at you,
getting out into the world.
Yo, by next year, you'll
make it across the street.
Mmm.
Mmm-mmm.
Uh, hey, Cee.
Something came for you.
No one knows I'm here.
So, who's it from?
Thank you both for coming in.
As the appointed attorney representing
my late brother's discretionary trust,
I'm required to enact
his final wishes.
And he stipulated
that I do this in person.
He wanted me to read
a prepared statement.
"Cecilia,"
"although our relationship
was far from perfect,"
"I at least thought
we had built up enough trust"
"that you would talk to me
rather than running away from..."
No. No!
Sorry, you're not allowed
to do that.
I'm required to read this.
She's not required to listen.
Email me a copy,
and we will read it.
You bet.
I'm just trying to do my job.
Your job is to explain the
money you mentioned on the phone.
I mentioned Cecilia, specifically,
is named in Adrian's trust.
That is why we're sitting here. Yes.
For the same reason so many women in
Adrian's life got close to him, his money.
If there was a chance of
physically being close to him,
we would not be here
for any amount of money.
You are physically close to him.
He's in that urn over there.
And as per his final wishes,
you're getting $5 million,
estate and income tax free.
Now, the money will be staggered
in installments of $100,000
each month for the next
four years or so.
Contingent, of course,
on the fine print.
You can't commit a crime,
etcetera.
Normally, I would have a
120-day contestability period,
but I'm gonna waive my
rights in that regard.
So,
as soon as I have your signature
and your banking information,
I can start releasing the funds.
Okay,
you can come in now.
Oh.
Hey. Wait. Where you at?
Okay.
Can we look now?
Yes, you can look.
Ta-da!
Oh.
Wow. Thanks, Cee.
Wow, that's nice.
Look at that.
A ladder?
Excuse you?
I know I didn't
hear you just say that.
I meant to say,
"Thank you." Uh-huh.
You're welcome.
Well, I knew you needed a new one,
and that one just... That has to go.
That's so nice of you, Cee.
Thank you so much.
That's very sweet of you.
Thank you.
I just... I wanted to thank you
for, you know, letting me stay here
and for taking such
good care of me, so...
And Sydney can also use ladders.
Don't think
I'm helping you paint.
I wouldn't even bother
to ask you.
No, not for, like, painting,
obviously, but just for a lot of things.
You climb them to get things.
Like... Like, stuff like that.
That's so strange.
God, I wish you had,
like... Oh, wait!
You could totally use the ladder...
Yeah. A ladder to climb up.
The ladder's cool.
This happened to just
pop up here by itself...
Convenient.
Wow.
What is it?
It has my name on it.
That's weird.
And it looks like your
handwriting. I don't...
You sure it's weird?
I just got a ladder, so I
don't know what...
Let's see.
A cool ladder is all.
It's a new bank
account, um, with your name on it.
And I'm gonna put $10,000 in it
every month for the rest of the year.
I called the account
"Parsons."
You're going to
fashion school, kid.
Hey, whoa, Cee...
That's... That's too much, Cee. Come on.
Are you sure you can do that?
Let me put it this way...
She can probably
go to grad school, too.
I'm going to Parsons.
You're going to Parsons.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Wait, no. We gotta...
We gotta celebrate.
And I don't want TV dinners,
microwave nothing. Oh!
It's like, I guess... We don't have
anything at all to celebrate with.
I don't know why you dancing.
You can't have none because
you're not 21. Yes, I can.
Come on. Just, like,
a little bit.
He said the other day
that I was mature for my age.
That's right.
He did.
A mature child.
I heard you say that.
I remember.
Hold up. This ain't fair.
Two against one.
I'm just an innocent man trying
to do right.
Are you scared?
This is abuse. I'm a cop.
You realize I'm a cop?
I got him.
Hey!
Oh, no.
I got him, Sydney!
I got him!
I'll protect you!
Morning.
You want some breakfast?
No. No, I gotta go.
You know, I'm a little
hungover, believe it or not.
Oh. Me too.
Champagne does that
to me every time.
We're getting old,
Cee. We old.
These winter mornings
are killing me.
All right, look, I'm out of here.
Um, I'll be back around 7:00.
Okay.
All right.
Oh. Uh, Cee?
Hmm?
You mind getting Sydney up?
She's actually pretty excited,
thanks to you. She, uh...
She might need a little help
staying focused.
You got it.
Syd, come on, girl.
You're gonna be late.
Shit!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
No, no, no.
Don't use water.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Oh.
Wow.
You did that.
Yeah.
You think we can salvage
it? No.
No?
No. Sorry.
James?
James! James!
Yeah. What
happened? What happened? What?
I saw something right there.
Right there.
There were footprints.
I saw it!
You saw footprints?
Yes, I saw... On the sheets!
I saw it, right there!
I saw them.
On the sheet?
I saw it.
There's someone in here.
There was someone in here.
Syd, put that stupid thing away.
You're the one
who bought it for me!
Who you gonna spray? Who?
James, I saw it.
I swear.
Hey, Cee.
Adrian will haunt you
if you let him.
Don't let him.
Now, you should try
and get some sleep.
You have an important
job interview tomorrow,
and I don't want
the memory of this...
That...
This person to ruin it.
Okay?
Okay. Sorry.
After Cal Poly, I worked
in Paris for six months.
That was the best time
of my life for sure.
Except for this next phase,
of course.
Take a seat.
So, any reason you worked
in Paris in particular?
Is that where all the
beautiful women in the world
have to go as a rule?
Well, I speak a little French,
and I've always
wanted to live there.
So after I graduated,
I went out there
on a totally student budget.
I slept in a broom closet,
literally.
I started this firm
in a supply closet, literally.
There you go.
We both know the value
of closet space. Yeah.
Let me see some of your work.
Yes, of course.
Um...
I don't, uh...
I know that I...
I know I put them in here, so I apologize.
I don't know what happened. Uh...
It's okay.
Uh, you can send it to us,
whenever you get a chance.
Okay.
So, uh, let me tell you
about us.
At Ruler, we approach
architecture on a human level.
First and...
Are you okay?
Um...
I'm sorry.
Uh, I'm just not feeling...
Would you like some water, or...
Cecilia?
Are you feeling okay?
Cecilia.
Okay, so, uh,
you probably shouldn't drive
or operate any heavy machinery
for the next few days.
But other than that,
you seem fine.
Either myself or my admitting
will follow up with you
with the results
of the blood test. Okay?
Can you just leave a number
with the nurse?
You guys can go home.
Okay.
You ready?
Yeah.
- Hello?
- Is Cecilia Kass there?
That's me.
Hi. Uh, this is
Doctor Lee at St. Vincent's.
So, we got the results
of your blood test back,
and it looks like the Diazepam was
the most likely cause of you fainting.
Um, sorry,
what Diazepam?
Well, your blood work showed
a very high amount of it.
That would definitely explain
what happened to you.
There's something else
I wanted to talk to you about,
but I'm not sure if we should
do it over the phone, so, um...
Tell him to stop.
Tell who to stop what?
Tell him to stop
what he's doing.
Do you know
what she's babbling about?
Nah, she hasn't explained
to me why we're here yet.
But being her very good friend,
I know it's a good reason.
So I'm gonna need you
to sit up and listen.
Show a little respect.
One night,
I was sitting,
and I was thinking about
how to leave Adrian.
I was planning the
whole thing in my mind.
And he was staring at me.
Studying me.
And without me
saying a single word...
He said that I could
never leave him.
That wherever I went,
he would find me.
That he would
walk right up to me
and I wouldn't
be able to see him.
But that he would
leave me a sign
so that I'd know he was there.
The night I left him,
I drugged him with that.
I lost the bottle that night.
And somehow, it found
its way back to me.
So, what exactly are you saying?
You lost the bottle,
you found the bottle.
He's not dead, Tom.
I have a pile of ashes in a box that
would disagree with you, Cecilia.
I don't know how he's done it.
He's figured it out, though.
He has figured out
a way to be invisible.
He is a world leader
in the field of optics.
I know that he could do this.
Something tells me you know
exactly what I'm talking about.
He's not dead.
I just can't see him.
Please tell him to stop.
Okay.
I agree with you,
Adrian was brilliant.
But it wasn't because of
anything he invented.
It was how he got
in people's heads.
That was his true genius,
knowing people's weaknesses.
You think about it.
He came up with the perfect way
to torture you, even in death.
Only thing more brilliant than inventing
something that makes you invisible
is not inventing it,
but making you think he did.
My brother controlled me long
before he met you, Cecilia.
I hated him.
You and I,
we got that in common.
I was relieved
when I heard that he was dead.
He's gone, Cecilia.
I saw his body.
Listen to me.
Don't let him win
by bringing him back to life.
Hey.
Emily, I need to talk to you.
Well, at least
now we have clarity.
Now I know
what you really think of me.
What?
Thanks so much
for carving out the time
to let me know how
"suffocating" I am to you.
What... What are you...
Not that I should
have to say this,
but I never expected
any of that money.
Emily, I don't... I don't
know what you're talking about.
The e-mail. The e-mail
you sent me this morning.
What e-mail? If that's
how you feel about me,
don't ask me to bail you
out of your
personal life anymore.
If you're too stupid
to know who the good guys are
and too weak
to get away from the bad ones,
don't sob to me for charity.
I'm out.
I didn't send you
the fucking e-mail.
I didn't.
Someone is doing this to me.
He's... He's doing this to me.
Who's...
Adrian?
Adrian sent me
the e-mail. Okay.
You need some medication.
Adrian is dead.
Em, please, no.
Cee?
It's okay, Syd.
You... You know
what I think we need?
Um...
I think we could kick Dad out
and have a little girls' night.
Eat some cake.
Yeah,
I do like cake.
Oh, my God.
Sydney, are you okay?
Why would you just...
Stop! Dad!
What? No.
No, Sydney, I didn't. No.
What? What happened?
She... She hit me.
What?
No, no, no.
James, I did not do that.
Sydney, I would never
hit you. I love you.
I would never do that, James. It
was him. He's here, I swear to you.
Enough. Enough!
Cee, enough.
Just stop it.
Are you okay?
I don't wanna stay here.
Sydney, I'm sorry.
I would never... Hey, hey.
Cee, right now, my priority is
getting my baby somewhere safe.
Do you understand?
Come on, baby.
It's okay.
No. James, please.
This is what he wants.
This is what he used to do
when we were together.
He wants you to think that I
did it. This is what he does.
He tries to isolate me and
he tries to get me alone...
Hey!
You need to calm down.
You are scaring my daughter.
If I were you, I would
go to your sister's place.
You don't need to be
here right now.
Come on, Sydney.
Sydney, I'm sorry. Sydney.
Where are you?
Come on!
Come on out.
Don't hit a little girl.
Hit me!
Okay.
So, why me, Adrian?
You could have
any woman you wanted.
That's the sad reality.
Right?
That's what money
and power buy you.
People.
So...
Why me?
I'm just a suburban girl
who stumbled into your life
one night at a party.
Can't you just forget
I ever existed?
There's nothing left
for you to take.
You've already taken it all.
This is Adrian Griffin.
Please leave a message, and
I'll get back to you when I can.
Cecilia?
Yes. Go.
Please, hurry.
Lock the doors. Lock
the doors! You okay?
Yes. Please.
Please, just go. Please.
Just... Please, hurry.
Please.
Stinson Beach?
That's a long way from here.
I... I just need
to get something.
Do you mind waiting for me?
I might be two minutes, I
might be 20. I don't know...
But you can bring me
back to the city after.
Sure, no problem.
Okay.
Zeus.
Hi. Hi.
12-14-17.
The day we met.
So romantic.
Please, meet me tonight,
if you can, in a public place.
Eight o'clock at Yulan.
And if you can't,
I understand,
but you have to tell me because
I have to call someone else,
because I don't think
I have much time left.
Thank you.
Hi.
Hey.
Hey, guys.
Welcome to Yulan.
My name is Taylor, and I will be
taking care of you this evening.
Do you know
how this place works?
I'm assuming you order
food, then you eat it. Hmm.
Pretty much. We just do things
a little bit differently.
It's all family style.
We've been here before.
It's all good.
Okay. Can I get you started
with some water?
We have still or sparkling.
Just the free kind.
Okay, tap it is.
Cool.
Thank you for being here.
I love you.
You're like a cop, Emily,
and you have
this brute-force strength
that is so, so comforting
when I'm in trouble
and it is really
intimidating when I'm not.
I mean, James actually
is a six-foot cop,
and he's, I think,
really intimidated by you.
As he should be.
I'd kick his ass.
I would.
You would.
I need that strength
in my life right now.
And I need you to believe
what I'm about to tell you.
Okay. What...
Thank you, Taylor.
All right, uh, do you guys need
more time with the drink menu?
Yes. Lots more time.
Okay,
no problem at all.
Emily...
I went to his house today.
You went to Adrian's house?
Yes.
I just walked right in.
I found something that can
prove what I'm experiencing.
That can prove
that Adrian is stalking me.
What is it?
It's some kind of suit
that Adrian has built.
And it has cameras,
and it somehow...
What?
No, please! No!
You can't do this.
You can't do this!
He killed her!
Please, I didn't do it!
I didn't do it!
No! No!
He killed her!
He did it!
- You have to listen to me!
- Just relax.
Please, no! Please.
No! No!
Listen to me!
No!
You motherfucker!
You killed her!
I see you!
He's here!
He's right here,
he's right here!
Please! You can't see him.
He's in the room!
You have to listen to me!
He's right there!
He's gonna hurt me.
Okay.
Please! No...
He's...
He's right there.
Okay?
You'll be all right.
Surprise.
Cecilia...
Can you confirm the person
in this video is you?
And can you confirm you recently
fainted during a job interview
due to a high amount of
Diazepam in your system?
I was drugged.
Uh-huh.
You also sent your sister
an email a few days ago
saying you wished
she was dead, didn't you?
I have something.
I have something
that'll prove he's alive.
I found it.
What do you have?
I can't tell you right now.
He's listening.
He's in the room, James.
You're saying that the person who killed
your sister is in the room right now,
but we can't see him.
Okay.
Yeah.
James...
Tell me you don't think
I did this.
Tell me you know that.
I may as well
have done it, though.
I brought Adrian into her life.
I did that.
I shouldn't have walked out
on you and left you alone.
I failed you.
Is this bed giving you
any problems, Cecilia?
No.
Is there anything in the room
that is distressing to you?
No.
Okay. Good.
I wanted to talk to you
about something.
We checked the blood test that you
had done at the hospital last week.
Do you remember
taking those blood tests?
Yes.
Okay.
Well, did you know
that you were pregnant?
No.
Didn't the doctor
who took the test tell you?
No, that can't be right.
That's...
That's not true.
The test shows us
that it was pretty recent.
We can't be sure
of exactly when,
but it must've been some time
in the last month.
Sweetie, is there anyone
we can call?
Family?
Any friends?
Okay.
It's upsetting to
see you in this condition.
Even though things ended badly for you
and Adrian, I still look at you as family.
Are you my lawyer now?
I'm the lawyer
for your source of income.
I represent my brother's trust.
The money from his trust
was payable to you
conditional upon you being subject
to criminal charges of any kind,
or being ruled to be
mentally incompetent.
Now, in light of
your current situation,
it's my duty to inform you that any
further payments are to be halted.
I know that you set up a bank account
for a friend of yours to go to college.
So, I take no pleasure
in relaying that.
I used to feel sorry for you.
The blood relative
of a narcissist sociopath.
Permanent punching bag.
Handcuffed to his wallet.
But now,
I can see you
for what you really are.
You're just the jellyfish
version of him.
Everything but the spine.
You can try to litigate it.
But that's going to be
an expensive option.
I can't see it working.
However...
if you sign this document and
forfeit your share of the trust,
it'll be a lot cleaner.
Or there's one option
where this all goes away.
Agree to have the baby
and go back to him.
You really think he didn't know you
were secretly using birth control?
'Course he did.
You should've known
he'd find out.
You knew him as well as I did.
He replaced them
with something else.
You only thought you were
taking birth control pills.
He was always going to find you,
no matter what he had to do.
He needs you because
you don't need him.
No one's ever left him before.
But he's punished you
enough now.
Now that he knows you're
the mother of his child.
It's time to stop playing games.
A new life with him
can be given to you
with one phone call.
A life just like
your old one with Adrian.
Cecilia, you don't really
have a choice right now.
Right now,
you're a murderer.
But I can change that.
Adrian killed my sister.
And you helped him.
I don't expect
you to make a decision right now.
I can come back in three days.
Be good to yourself until then.
We'll be watching.
Grab the
umbrella, grab your rain jacket,
grab your rain boots,
you're gonna need it.
You'll need them
for a couple of days.
This pattern we're in stays put.
We've got this atmospheric river
pointed right here at central California.
And that means cloudy and rainy
as we get through
the rest of the week.
This is a lot of moisture
coming in.
It's going to mean heavy rainfall
and flash-flooding concerns
right as we get through
the end of the week.
It's not until the weekend
that we get our next chance
of seeing some dry conditions.
In fact, the next glimpse of sunshine
doesn't come until Sunday afternoon,
when temperatures
hit the mid-60s.
But until then, it's gonna
be cool, it's gonna be damp...
Open your mouth.
Tongue up.
Tongue down.
Okay. Good night.
You won't get the baby.
And you won't get me.
There you are.
Fuck you!
Get back in bed, now.
Hey!
No! No!
Please, no! No!
No! Stop!
No, please! No!
No, stop!
He's right there!
Lay down.
He's right there.
He's right behind you.
Listen to me.
Who is?
He's right behind you.
I understand, Cecilia. Lay down.
Turn around! He's right there!
Listen to me!
He's right behind you!
Stay down.
No, no.
Bang.
Hey! Okay.
Get back! Get back!
She's over here!
You go left!
All right.
You think you're
learning how to beat me,
so I'm gonna
truly teach you something.
If you fight me,
I won't ever hurt you.
I'll find someone you love
and hurt them instead.
Copy. We're following.
Now you've only got yourself to blame
for that innocent young girl's death.
No, please!
Not Sydney.
Adrian, no.
Hold it!
Show me your hands!
Hey!
Cecilia, don't do
anything stupid.
I'm over here!
Hey,
stop her!
She's heading
towards the main exit!
What the...
What the fuck?
Hello? Hello?
Hey!
Harry, what's going on?
Harry?
What are you... Hey!
Hello?
Harry, are you okay?
He's fine.
He's fine, I promise.
What?
Who is this?
This is James Lanier.
James, it's me.
Cee?
How are you calling me?
It doesn't matter about that.
You have to listen to me.
No, it does matter.
Come on!
You can't be calling me.
James, listen to me!
Sydney's life is in danger.
Where are you right now?
I'm at work.
She's at the house.
You need to go to her
right now, James.
Do you hear me?
'Cause I'm afraid Adrian is
gonna do something to her.
Sydney.
Syd, you okay?
Sydney...
Stop!
No!
Dad!
Sydney, get down!
Don't cry.
Tom?
Is someone there?
Help!
Please. Help!
Stand clear!
Police!
Show me your hands.
Our tactical team
found Adrian this morning,
tied up in his basement.
Looks like he was a victim of
his brother just like you were.
No.
No, James.
That's not right.
Adrian did this to me.
He is not the victim here.
He was tied up in his basement.
If he faked his own death, he
could fake his own kidnapping.
We have Tom's body
laying in my living room,
wearing some sort of suit
that you shot to pieces.
If it did work,
it doesn't now.
But we have a whole bunch of corroborative
witnesses from the psychiatric hospital
when it comes to seeing
something strange.
Look, this is your best-case scenario
for getting your freedom back, okay?
No.
I...
I know Tom's body is in
your living room. Yeah.
Adrian did everything
before that though.
He set his own brother up.
I know how this works, Cee.
I know.
You don't understand.
No, you don't understand.
This is what he does.
He makes me feel
like I'm the crazy one.
This is...
This is what he does.
And he's doing it again.
Okay, okay.
But, listen.
I need you to
keep that to yourself
and let me do my job.
Okay?
Just let me help you.
Yeah, but as long as Adrian's
around, you can't help me.
Cecilia?
I'm so glad you called.
Well...
You look amazing.
I mean, you always...
You always look amazing.
I don't feel amazing.
It's all a lie.
Please, come on in.
It's cold.
Come on.
So, I... I wanted to
get us some simple takeout,
but of course I started obsessing
over what you'd be in the mood for.
Hence, we have the OCD buffet
of sushi, steak, and pasta.
Or you might not
be hungry at all.
Uh...
Which is so logical that it suddenly
makes this feast look moronic.
I'll have steak.
That's a good choice.
Uh...
My hand's shaking.
You know, you're the only
person in the world
who gets to see my hand shake.
It's 'cause I need you, Cecilia.
I know I didn't treat you the
way you should have been treated
when we were together.
But I've learned my lesson.
I would burn everything I own
just to prove that to you.
Okay.
If you want to be a part
of this child's life,
it has to start with honesty.
Of course.
Which means I need you to
admit everything that you did.
That it was you,
not your brother.
You.
Cecilia.
I loved my brother.
And I thought he loved me, too.
I know it didn't seem like it
to the outside world,
but Tom controlled me.
Just tell me the truth.
I need to know
that I'm not crazy.
Okay?
And we can't start this
with a lie.
But I'm not starting with a lie.
It wasn't me.
I swear it.
Why can't you just
tell me the truth?
I am.
Adrian, stop!
I need you to do this for me.
More than
that, do it for you, Adrian.
I'm giving you exactly
what you're asking for, Cecilia.
I am telling you the truth.
Oh, no, no, no.
I know that you feel like
you're going insane sometimes.
But I'm the only one
who can help you.
Remember?
Because I know you better
than anyone else in the world.
I mean...
That shouldn't come as a...
Surprise.
I should go clean myself up.
Of course.
No!
No, no!
What did you do?
911,
what is your emergency?
Please, you have to help me,
please.
I'm with somebody,
and I think he's...
He's tried to kill himself.
Hurry.
You have to help.
You have to hurry.
Please.
It's, uh,
3333 Celestial Drive.
Please.
Surprise.
Hey. Hey.
You okay?
I'm okay.
James, look at me.
He killed himself.
He cut his own throat.
There's security camera
video of it.
You never did want to get him
admitting anything on tape, did you?
Of course I did.
I just didn't know
he was that unstable.
You heard it, right?
James?
What'd it sound like to you?
It sounded a lot like
he killed himself.