(AIRPLANE APPROACHES)
(TIRES SCREECH)
(P.A. JINGLES)
MAN : (ON P.A.)
United Airlines announcing
the arrival of Flight
9435 from Beijing.
Customer service representative,
report to Gate C42.
(REPEATING ANNOUNCEMENT IN MANDARIN)
(ALL CHATTERING)
WOMAN : (ON P.A.) All visitors to the US
should line up at booths one through 15.
CUSTOMS OFFICIAL : Please have
your I-94 forms filled out.
- What's the purpose of your visit?
- What is the purpose of your visit?
What is the purpose of your visit?
Business or pleasure?
Just visiting. Shopping?
Euh, plaisir.
- Pleasure.
- Business.
How long will you be staying?
Could I see your return ticket?
- What's the purpose of your visit?
- Business or pleasure?
Enjoy your stay. Next.
WOMAN : (ON P.A.)
Please have your passports...
- Stand by. He's fishing.
- MAN : Copy that.
See this bunch of Mickey
Mouse sweatshirts?
That's the tour from China,
connecting to Orlando.
When was the last time
you saw Chinese tourists
on their way to Disney
World without any cameras?
Possible forged
documents on 10 and 11.
(SHOUTING)
Sir. Sir. Passport.
Thank you.
Welcome, Mr. Navorski.
Purpose of your visit?
(SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
Business or pleasure?
(BEEPS)
OFFICER : Have your declarations
forms ready, please.
Sir, I have an IBIS hit on six.
Mr. Navorski, please follow me.
WOMAN : (ON P.A.)...
from Montreal
must proceed to U.S.
Immigration for luggage.
All right, Mr. Navorski, we'd
like you to wait here, please.
Next, please.
(ELECTRIC RAZOR BUZZING)
THURMAN : What exactly are you doing
in the United States, Mr. Navorski?
Yellow taxicab, please.
Take me to Ramada Inn,
161 Lexington.
Staying at the Ramada Inn?
Keep the change.
Do you know anyone in New York?
Yes.
- Who?
- Yes.
- No, do you know anyone in New York?
- Who?
- Yes.
161 Lexington.
Okay, Mr. Navorski, I need to
see your return ticket, please.
No, your return ticket.
- Oh. Yes.
- Ah.
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
This is just a standard procedure.
I'm going to need the passport.
Oh. Oh, okay.
No, no. Mr. Navorski.
That. Passport.
That.
Mr. Navorski? Sorry
to keep you waiting.
I'm Frank Dixon, Director of Customs
and Border Protection here at JFK.
I help people with their
immigration problems.
We're looking for an
interpreter for you.
How are we doing on that?
Do we have an interpreter?
But I understand that you
speak a little English.
- Yes.
- You do?
I hope you don't mind if I eat while
we talk. I've a bit of bad news.
Your country has suspended
all traveling privileges
on passports issued
by your government.
And our State Department
has revoked the visa
that was going to allow
you to enter the U.S.
That's it in a nutshell, basically.
While you were in the air, there was
a military coup in your country.
Most of the dead were members
of the Presidential Guard.
They were attacked in the
middle of the night.
They got it all on GHN, I think.
There were few civilian casualties.
I'm sure your family's fine.
Mr. Navorski, your country
was annexed from the inside.
The Republic of Krakozhia
is under new leadership.
Krakozhia! Krakozhia.
- Krakozhia.
- Right. I don't think he gets it.
Let me... Look.
Imagine that these potato
chips are Krakozhia.
- Krakozhia. Yes. Okay.
- Krakozhia.
So the potato chips are Krakozhia.
- And this apple...
- Big Apple.
Big Apple represents the
Liberty Rebels. Okay?
No more Krakozhia. Okay?
New government.
Revolution. You understand?
All the flights in and out of
your country have been suspended.
The new government has sealed all
borders, so your visa's no longer valid.
So, currently, you are
a citizen of nowhere.
Now, we can't process
you new papers
until the U.S. recognizes your country's
new diplomatic reclassification.
You don't qualify for
asylum, refugee status,
temporary protective status,
humanitarian parole
or non-immigration work travel.
You don't qualify for any of these.
You are at this time simply...
- unacceptable.
- Unacceptable.
Big Apple tour includes
Brooklyn Bridge,
Empire State, Broadway show Cats.
I got more bad news
for you. Cats has closed.
Okay. Okay.
Now I go New York City. Thank you.
No, Mr. Navorski. I cannot allow you to
enter the United States at this time.
- Krakozhia.
- We can't allow you to go home either.
You don't really have a home.
Technically, it doesn't exist.
It's like a Twilight Zone.
Do you get that show over there?
"Talking Tina," "Nightmare at
30,000 Feet," "Zanti Misfits."
"Zanti Misfits" was
Outer Limits, sir.
Oh, really? It's not important.
Where do I buy the Nike shoes?
Okay, Mr. Navorski,
come here. Walk with me.
Here's my dilemma, Mr. Navorski.
You have no right to enter the U.S.
and I have no right to detain you.
You have fallen through
a crack in the system.
- I am crack.
- Yes. Until we get this sorted out,
I will allow you to enter the
International Transit Lounge.
I'm going to sign a release form that
is going to make you a free man.
- Free?
- Free.
Free to go anywhere you like
within the confines of the
International Transit Lounge.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Okay.
Uncle Sam will have this
sorted out by tomorrow,
and welcome to the
United States. Almost.
(LAUGHING)
- Thank you.
- Thanks, Judge.
Now, Mr. Navorski.
This is the International
Transit Lounge.
You are free to wait here.
These are food vouchers.
You can use them in the Food Court.
Your Krakozhian money
is no good here.
This is a 15-minute,
prepaid calling card.
You may call home, if you like.
This, in case we need to
contact you, is a pager.
You must keep this
with you at all times.
Here is an ID badge for you to get
into CBP. Beyond those doors...
Mr. Navorski. I'm going to
need you to look at me.
Beyond those doors
is American soil.
Mr. Dixon wants me to make it clear
that you are not to enter
through those doors.
You are not to leave this
building. America is closed.
America closed.
What I do?
There's only one thing you
can do here, Mr. Navorski.
Shop.
MAN : (ON P.A.) Ladies and gentlemen,
passengers of flight 854...
(BRASS BAND PLAYS ON TV)
WOMAN : (ON TV)...
the international community
tries to make inroads to
a peaceful resolution.
The populace has to wonder if they
will ever find political stability,
or find the leadership to secure
their place on the world stage.
And next this hour, looking
to buy a 90-foot yacht?
MAN : (ON TV) ...taken hostage.
We're also hearing that the
Vice President has been killed
along with four cabinet members,
13 injured soldiers and 20 civilians.
By dawn, rebel leaders had
surrounded the state houses.
In a symbolic gesture, the national
flag of Krakozhia was torn down
from the Presidential Palace
and the parliament building.
Please. Please.
Television.
(SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
WOMAN : (ON TV)
This just in.
Last night a military coup overthrew
the government of Krakozhia.
Bombing and gunfire were
heard through the night.
Although details are unclear,
we are told that President Vagobagin
and his aides have been taken hostage.
Bonjour, monsieur. You are
a Red Carpet Club member?
(SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
I need to see your boarding
pass and club card, sir.
I'm sorry, sir. This
is a private lounge.
The public lounge is downstairs.
WOMAN : (ON TV)
The tiniest nation in the region
has been shaken by
another uprising.
Krakozhia has been involved in civil
war throughout the late '80s and '90s
as it has tried to transition
from Communist rule.
- Watch it.
- Please.
Please, telephone? Telephone?
Please, please.
MAN : (OVER P.A.)
For security reasons,
please keep your luggage
with you at all times.
Unattended luggage will be
removed for inspection...
(SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
Oh, my God. Oh, my
God, you broke my bag!
I got this in Paris.
This is my favorite bag.
I can't believe you just broke my bag.
Mom, Dad. He broke my bag.
- Food document.
- Excuse me. Stop it.
Do you have an appointment?
I don't let anyone to look at my
trash without an appointment.
I have an opening next Tuesday.
Tuesday, Monday, Tuesday,
Wednesday, Tuesday.
It will be good time for you
to come back and get lost.
Okay, goodbye. Sorry.
Tuesday.
(STRANGERS IN THE NIGHT INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING)
(AIRPLANE DESCENDS)
(STRAINS)
(FIZZES)
(SIGHS)
(ENGINE SCREAMS)
Don't shoot.
SALCHAK : She sleeps 12, Frank.
Has a 120-volt generator,
wet bar, gas range.
She looks amazing.
She's my pot of gold at
the end of the rainbow.
She's a beautiful boat, and
I hope you get her soon.
- You've earned her.
- Thank you, Frank.
- You have.
- Actually, I bought her yesterday.
Oh, come on. Congratulations.
Frank, I'm nominating
you to take my place.
You will assume the duties
of acting Field Commissioner
until you get approval
from Washington.
Really? I don't know what to say.
- Jesus. Richard, is this real?
- Oh, it's real, Frank.
Don't pretend to be surprised.
You've been waiting for me to
retire or drop dead for years now.
No, I haven't been waiting
for you to retire.
(BOTH LAUGH)
That's all right, Frank.
My retirement will become official
the day you get sworn in.
- You've waited a long time for this.
- I have.
Just be careful about
the inspection process.
I will. I've been
here for 17 years...
We're talking about the Field
Commissioner position.
People are going to look to you for
leadership, to set an example.
What are you saying?
(CHUCKLES)
I'm saying the job
is yours to lose.
Ship the Colombians off to asylum
hearings, backgrounds on the Chinese
and call the parents of those
kids from Long Island.
Tell them it was a bad idea
to let them go to Jamaica.
Come on, let's go. South America
and Madrid are on the tarmac.
I want them out of
here in half an hour.
Mr. Thurman.
There's a man walking around
the terminal in a bathrobe.
I know, sir. You put him there.
TORRES : Next.
(SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
I need visa.
Where's your green form?
I can't do anything without it.
Go to the wall.
Next!
Sir.
The light green form.
(SINGING)
I love New York...
Light green.
Mr. Navorski, you cannot get
into New York without a visa.
You cannot get a visa
without a passport,
and you cannot get a new
passport without a country.
There's nothing we
can do for you here.
I give you light green.
I'm sorry, but you've
wasted an entire day.
At this time, you are simply...
- Unacceptable.
- Yes.
VIKTOR : Unacceptable.
(SNORING)
FRANK : Why is he still here?
You released him, sir.
You put him there.
Why doesn't he walk out the doors?
Why doesn't he try to escape?
- THURMAN : Sir, you told him to wait.
- I didn't think he'd actually do it.
I mean, he's in a crack. Who
the hell waits in a crack?
THURMAN :
No news from the State Department,
but we can deport
him in a few days.
Yeah, it could be a few days. It
could be a week, two weeks, a month.
Who knows what this guy is thinking,
what gulag he escaped from.
Everything he does
comes back to me.
- You want him back in the holding cell?
- No, I'll show him the door.
Hello.
- Do you have an appointment?
- Yes. 9:30.
Food document, trash. Tuesday.
Tuesday. I hate the Tuesday.
Excuse me.
(MAN SPEAKS GERMAN)
(SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
Airports are tricky
places, Mr. Navorski.
I'm about to tell you something.
Something you can never
repeat to anyone.
Do you understand? It's a secret.
- Secret?
- Yes, a secret.
At 12:00 today, the guards at those
doors will leave their posts
and their replacements are
going to be five minutes late.
Late five minutes.
Yes. Late five minutes. At 12:00.
Just today. Just this once.
No one is going to be
watching those doors.
- And no one will be watching you.
- So, America not closed.
No.
America, for five minutes, is open.
Have a nice life, Mr. Navorski.
United Airlines, final
boarding call...
Catch and release. It's simple.
Sometimes you land a small fish.
You unhook him and place
him back in the water.
You set him free so that somebody else
can have the pleasure of catching him.
All right, here we go.
Okay. Call them off.
Johnson, clear the doors.
All right. Go.
Get out of there.
All right, there's the door.
Here we go. Now where is he?
- There he is. Are you sure?
- No, that's not him.
There he is. Okay.
All right, Viktor. Here we go.
(WHISTLING)
What's so complicated?
Exit, Viktor.
Come on. In a few minutes, you'll
be somebody else's problem.
He wants to make sure
nobody's watching.
I told him nobody
would be watching.
Come on. All right, here we go.
- Call the Airport Police.
- He's on his way.
Excuse me.
(CAMERA WHIRS)
- You got it. There we go.
- BOTH : Ah!
He's got to get a running start,
I guess. Come on. Just leave.
Just leave. Leave. Leave.
What are you doing? Why is
he kneeling? Is he praying?
No. He's tying his shoelace.
Come on, leave. Get the cameras.
Where is he? Where is he?
- THURMAN : To the left of here.
- No. He was just at the door.
- THURMAN : Just go a little left.
- All right.
I wait.
What are you looking at?
Go back to work. Thank you.
(SHRIEKS)
Oh, God. Shit.
(SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
- This belong you? Please, please.
- Thank you.
Oh, shit.
See? Wet floor.
That you.
I'm so late.
Buenos Aires. I can't
remember the gate.
Gate 24.
- You sure?
- Yes.
Thanks.
Wait.
For you. Payless Shoes.
Second floor. Sensible heels.
- Hi, baby.
- Come here, you.
GUPTA : I think he's CIA.
The CIA put him here to spy on us.
You don't know what you're talking
about. He doesn't speak English.
If he could learn
to speak, this guy.
He can't speak English, how could he
have a meeting with a beautiful woman?
A flight attendant.
- Oh, so, she's CIA, too?
- No.
She look like a Russian. KGB.
She gave him heel of her shoes.
And he gave her a
piece of the paper.
- Was it microfilm?
- A coupon from Payless Shoes.
Must be some kind of the code.
You been spending too much time
inhaling them cleaning products.
I'm warning you guys.
You watch yourself.
This guy is here for a reason.
And I think that reason is us.
(MUSIC PLAYS)
Excuse me, buddy.
What's going on?
It's Navorski. He's
figured out the quarters.
(COINS JANGLE)
Good afternoon. Welcome to Burger
King. May I take your order?
Keep the change.
Excuse me.
Okay, go. Go.
Good boy. Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Welcome to Burger King.
May I take your...
(BRASS BAND PLAYS ON TV)
"Crisis. Krakozhia."
Now that heavy
fighting has subsided
and both sides have dug in
for the long winter ahead,
it's clear that the future of Krakozhia
may be in doubt for some time to come.
Meanwhile, the people of Krakozhia
suffer the consequences.
VIKTOR : "And food..."
REPORTER : Have caused food
and energy shortages.
"...In Krakozhia."
(SHOUTS IN BULGARIAN)
(SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
"The story of Broadway is the..."
"The cast"
"of comedy hit Friends,"
"which is set in New York."
(SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
Friends.
MAN : (ON P.A.)
Due to the heavy snowfall,
all flights have been canceled...
(ALL GROAN)
(VIKTOR SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
"Wayne Newton is 61 today."
"It's a miracle."
"Korean conjoined twins
separated today in Miami."
"Chances of survival 50-50."
50-50.
Next.
Let me ask you
something, Mr. Navorski.
Why do you wait here every day when
there's nothing I can do for you?
Your new visa will not arrive until
your country is recognized by the U.S.
You have two stamp.
One red, one green.
- So?
- I have chance to go New York, 50-50.
(CHUCKLES)
Yes. That's a beautiful way to look at
it, but America doesn't work that way.
As acting Field Commissioner, I've
created a new position here at JFK.
Transportation Liaison for
Passenger Assistance.
Sir, what will that person do?
(SHRIEKS)
Thank you. I'll take it from here.
I'm Transportation Liaison in
charge of Passenger Assistance.
No carts, no quarters.
No quarters, no food.
It'll be days before he goes through the
doors in violation of section 2.14.
Then he's somebody else's problem.
Why don't we tag him in
violation of section 2.14 now?
- Then ship him to detention.
- He has to break the law by leaving.
I won't lie, particularly to
get rid of somebody like him.
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING)
- MAX : Sorry, buddy.
- Honey!
Put it down. Put it down.
Put it down.
You try to take my mop.
You try to take my floor.
It's my job. Stay off my floor.
Stay away from my mop.
- Food.
- If you touch it again, I kill you.
(SHRIEKS)
Hey. I'm Enrique Cruz.
We need to talk.
- I want to make a deal with you.
- What deal?
I need information on
CBP Officer Torres.
You feed me information about
her, and I'll feed you.
- What do you want know?
- You see her every day.
I want to know what
makes her knees weak.
What makes her blood boil
and her body tingle.
She's a wild stallion, and
you'll help me break her.
I'm... I'm her man of mystery.
- Officer Torres is wild stallion?
- Her name is Dolores.
You help me to win her heart, and
you'll never go hungry again.
- I do this.
- Really? Promise?
- Yes.
- Okay. Thank you.
What mean, "wild stallion"?
(SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
Officer Torres. My friend
say you are stallion.
Mr. Navorski.
- A what?
- Stallion, like a horse.
Stand behind the yellow line.
- It's beautiful horse.
- Who said that?
- My friend drive the food.
- Mr. Navorski, behind the yellow line.
- I will help once it's your turn.
- I'll get light green.
- Light green form. Okay.
- I'll be back.
She say one thing.
- Very important.
- What? What did she tell you?
Something wrong with the salmon?
- Need gorchitsa.
- What?
Mustard. Mustard?
- Mustard?
- Yes. Please.
Thank you.
Officer Torres, you like the films?
- Movies?
- Not so much.
- The Rockettes?
- Can't afford it.
- What do you like?
- Conventions.
Conventions. What is?
- Conventions?
This is like secret place you go?
She go to these conventions
dressed as Yeoman Rand.
- Yeoman Rand.
- She's a Trekkie.
Favorite episode is
"Doomsday Machine."
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
Now, listen, Viktor. You gotta ask her
something that is very important.
Okay.
- I wait.
- Enjoy your visit.
Next.
- Officer Torres.
- M r. Navorski.
You have choose.
Man with money or man with love?
What is choose?
She had a boyfriend?
For how long? Two years?
What happened?
He chit.
- What?
- He chit.
Eat shit?
He chit. He chit. He chit.
- Repeat exactly what she said.
- He chit. She catch him. So...
- He cheats.
- Yes.
What we call krushkach.
We say krushkach.
One man, two womans.
So.
Crowded, you know. Eh!
Okay. He cheats.
- You say "cheats."
- He chit.
- No, "cheat."
- Enrique.
You, no chit.
- No cheat.
- No chit.
No. I won't cheat.
She's a nice girl. She
won't take your chitting.
Next.
VIKTOR : Officer Torres. Have
you been ever in the love?
Enough, Viktor. Who is it?
Who's telling you to
ask me these things?
It's a man of misery.
Misery?
- Mystery?
- No, no. Misery. Man of misery.
He's so sick. He's so in love.
But what did she say?
She did say, "next, next."
And now she say,
"Please. Please come."
- (PAGER BEEPS)
- That's... Wait.
(SHRIEKS)
- I coming now.
- No, wait. Viktor.
Viktor, just tell me more.
I coming. I coming.
Please, please.
(DOOR BEEPS AND CLUNKS)
VIKTOR : Beeper went off. Started
beeping. So, I grab. I come.
FRANK : We have an idea.
Would you like something to eat?
No. No food. I stuffed.
Thank you.
So, Mr. Navorski, I have
some very good news for you.
What?
I've figured out a way to get
you out of this airport.
How?
Well, we have laws here
that protect aliens
who have a credible fear of
returning to their own country.
If we can establish
this fear with you,
then the CBP will be forced to begin
Expedited Removal Procedures,
to bring you to an immigration judge and
let you plead your case for asylum.
Asylum.
Unfortunately, the courts are
so backed up with asylum cases
that the soonest you'd get before a
judge would be six months from now.
Yes, and we would have no choice
but to let you go for those six months.
It's the law. You'd be released.
You would be free to wait in New
York until your court date.
But, believe it or not, most people
never show up before the judge.
- So I go New York City?
- Uh-huh.
You can go to New
York City tonight.
But you only get to go if we
can establish a credible fear.
- Fear?
- Mmm-hmm. Fear.
- From what?
- That's the best part.
It doesn't matter what you're afraid of.
It's all the same to Uncle Sam.
So I'm going to ask
you one question.
If you give me the correct answer,
I can get you out of this airport tonight.
So, I answer one question.
Go to New York City. Tonight.
- Tonight.
- (LAUGHS) Okay.
- FRANK : Okay.
THURMAN : Okay.
Do you, at this time, have any fear
of returning to your own country?
No.
Okay. Let me try it again.
- Your country's at war.
- Yes. War.
There are men in the streets
with guns. Political persecution.
- Yes. It's terrible.
- Yeah, it's horrible.
And God only knows
what could happen.
Innocent people are
torn from their beds.
On Tuesdays. I hate Tuesdays.
So you're afraid.
- From what?
- Krakozhia.
- You're afraid of Krakozhia.
- Krakozhia?
No, I am not afraid from Krakozhia.
I'm a little afraid of this room.
I'm talking about bombs.
I'm talking about human dignity.
Human rights.
Viktor, please don't be afraid to
tell me you're afraid of Krakozhia.
Is home. I am not
afraid from my home.
So? I go to New York City now?
- No.
- No?
Okay.
- I'm afraid from ghosts.
- Thanks very much.
- I'm afraid from Dracula.
- Thanks a lot.
I'm afraid from Wolfmens,
afraid from sharks.
Thanks a lot.
(GROANS)
(GUPTA LAUGHS)
- Why you do this?
- Nobody read the sign in America.
This is the only fun I have.
AMELIA : A barbecue? That's why
I'm not going to see you?
Let me get this straight.
I change my schedule to meet you.
I take four back-to-back flights,
fly 27 hours straight
literally around the world,
and now you tell me you're going
to spend July 4th with your wife?
The woman hates fireworks.
Don't lie to me, okay?
I know for a fact you took
her to Rome last weekend.
Because you flew United, Max.
(SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
(SOBS)
You make a habit out of listening
to other people's conversations?
No, I try to call home.
So then...
- You know why men are such assholes?
- No.
Because they're all liars.
Wait.
Wet floor.
Please. Don't be hurt.
How can I not be? He's married.
One man. Two womens. Crowded.
You want to know what
the worst part is?
I never asked him to leave his wife.
I encouraged him to get counseling.
What kind of sick person am I?
I'm rooting for the home team.
(SOBS)
I just wish the sex
wasn't so amazing.
(LAUGHS)
- So amazing.
- Bye-bye.
You know, sometimes
in the mornings,
I just stare at him
over room service.
Watch him do the crossword puzzle.
I start to think that maybe,
maybe this could happen.
That we belong together.
This man has you.
Why he need puzzle?
This is my problem.
I always see men the way
I want to see them.
Do I know you from someplace?
Sensible heels. Payless
Shoes. Second floor.
(LAUGHS)
You headed for home?
No, no. I am...
I am delayed a long time.
I hate it when they delay
flights. What do you do?
Oh, I go from one building
to another building.
I have beeper.
Oh, contractors. You guys
travel as much as we do.
Ah.
Sorry about that.
Thank you very much.
What's "BH"?
In English,
Viktor Navorski.
- In English, Amelia Warren.
- Amelia Warren?
- Nice to meet you.
- You, too.
Nice to see you again.
You like Italian food?
I know, it's late and you've
probably got other plans,
but if you'd like to grab some dinner,
we can run right out and catch a cab.
I know a place that has
the greatest cannelloni.
No, I can't.
- You married?
- No.
- Girlfriend?
I can't go out with you.
God. I'm so sorry.
I am so sorry.
I must come off like a
complete nut job or something.
- No.
- I didn't want to eat alone.
Wet floor.
- VIKTOR : No, I...
- AMELIA : You don't have to explain.
Nadia.
In New York restaurant,
what cost is cantaloni?
I don't know. Maybe 15 bucks.
- Dollars?
- Twenty.
Two people, 40.
Two people, 40 dollars.
I help you?
I'm so sorry, sir. The position
has already been filled.
- Do you live nearby?
- Yes. Gate 67.
Because we are very particular about
punctual... Did you say Gate 67?
Gate 67.
(LAUGHS)
You got to be kidding.
You got to help me help you. I don't
see a Social Security number...
mailing address,
even a phone number.
Telephone? You need?
I get. I get. I get phone.
(STAMMERING)
I get phone.
451-1226.
All right. When's the
best time to reach you?
Now?
(PHONE RINGS)
- Hello?
- CLIFF : Hi, Mr. Navorski.
Yes, this is Viktor Navorski.
Who calls?
It's Cliff from the
Discovery Store.
Ah! Cliff. Hello.
- How's it going?
- Good.
- Is this a good time?
- Yes, I wait for your call all day.
Well, I got to tell you that
the position's been filled.
Yeah, so could you please
go sit someplace else?
- I go to bathroom now.
- CLIFF : That'd be good.
- All right.
- Thank you.
CLIFF : Okay.
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
(SHRIEKS)
Who is this?
- Who are you?
- WORKER : It's no one.
There's no one here for two weeks.
This isn't one of my guys.
(TURNS OFF MUSIC)
Look at this cornicing.
This is good work.
Must be Harry's crew.
You with Harry's crew?
Does Harry think he's
running this job?
- VIKTOR : I go now.
- Go where?
- Gate 67.
- 67?
We're ten months away from 67.
He's got to be Harry's. If he's
not mine, and he's not yours...
Harry's trying to make me look bad.
I've got to slow him down
before he gets to 67.
- What's your name?
- Viktor Navorski.
Pull him off Harry's
crew, put him on mine.
You start 6:30 Monday morning.
You give me job?
6:30, yes, boss.
(JAZZ PLAYS ON PERSONAL STEREO)
ENRIQUE : We have lobster
ravioli from Alitalia.
We have caviar from
Russian Aeroflot.
GUPTA : Okay. Just bring it.
- ENRIQUE : Hey, Viktor.
- Hello, all.
Look. The man without a country.
Come on in. Welcome.
- I see this.
- You did well.
Have a seat.
- Here?
- Here.
Come on, sit down.
- Who invited him?
- I did. We needed a fourth, right?
- I'm not going to play with him.
- Oh, Gupta, relax, would you?
- He isn't a spy.
- How do you know?
He could be recording everything
we say. A wire in his shirt.
A microphone up in his ass.
- I'm not going to lose my job.
- Fine.
- What if we x-rayed him?
- GUPTA : Yes.
ENRIQUE : Close your eyes.
- Okay. So you are clean.
- Good. Let's play cards.
I will have money. But Friday.
Don't worry about it.
We play for unclaimed items
from the Lost and Found.
You'll be amazed at what people
leave at airports. Come.
I have two nines and two nines.
Four nines.
- Careful, careful.
- Watch out.
Wait.
We have a question for you, Viktor.
Yeah, we're just curious.
What is in the can?
- What? This?
- Yeah, we saw the X-ray.
We know there's no nuts in there.
What is in there?
This is jazz.
- Jazz?
- Jazz, yes.
- Yes.
(ALL LAUGH)
You sure it's jazz in there?
It might be the blues.
- Or salsa.
- Maybe it's Stevie Wonder.
- No, no, is jazz.
- Okay, guys. Okay.
For tonight's grand
prize, we have...
Show them, Gupta.
I found this upstairs.
Virgin Air, first class lounge.
There you go.
And they belong to?
- Cher.
- Cher?
- As in Cher?
- Yeah. Cher.
I checked it out.
There were witnesses.
Those are Cher's panties.
- Ready?
- Hurry up.
So, will we share the panties?
- No, no, no.
- Not if I win.
- Come on.
- Wait a second.
WOMAN : (ON P.A.)...
flight number 801 to Narita
is now announcing final boarding...
VIKTOR : "You can't. That is mine."
"You can get so confused."
AMELIA : Viktor? Well, hi.
Please.
- How are you?
- Good.
I am so sorry about what happened
last time, asking you out like that.
I'm so used to guys trying to
grab my ass at 30,000 feet
that when I meet somebody that
doesn't, I don't know how to react.
- Let's just start over.
- Yes, okay.
- Are you coming or going?
- I don't know. Both.
- Tell me about it.
- Napoleon?
Yeah. I read a lot of history books.
They're long and cheap
and usually about men
killing each other.
Like 1,200 pages for $9.99.
You can't beat that.
- But Napoleon?
- Yeah. He's one of my favorites.
- You know what saved Napoleon's life?
- No.
- His ego.
- Ego?
Yes.
After he loses the
Battle of Waterloo,
Napoleon isolates himself on the
tiny island of Saint Helena.
No one knows exactly
what happens next,
but the version
I like goes like this.
He's very depressed and
decides to take his own life.
But Napoleon believes himself to
be of such superhuman strength
that he takes six times the amount
of poison needed to do the job.
His stomach is so full up with
poison that his body rejects it,
and he doesn't die.
See? Ego. Saved his life.
Maybe he need glasses.
- Glasses?
- Yes. To read words on bottle.
Poison.
It's funny you should say that.
Rumor has it that
Napoleon was farsighted.
- There you go.
- And there you go.
I think we're rewriting
history right here.
Why don't we talk
about it over lunch?
I can't believe it. I just
asked you out again.
I just did it again.
(AMELIA LAUGHS)
I'm so... Just stay away
from me, Viktor, okay?
I'm sick. I don't have the ability
to be alone for five seconds.
Okay.
- Okay, what?
- Okay.
Lunch with you.
- You'll have lunch with me?
- Yes.
You're not running
for a flight or...
I wait.
(PAGER BEEPS)
- It's me.
- You. Yes.
I'm sorry. I just got paged.
- You work?
- No.
Ah.
Three of you. Crowded.
Stay away from me, Viktor.
I'm... I have a serious problem.
I'm as bad as Napoleon.
I just keep ingesting these poisonous
men until I make myself sick.
You're not sick, Amelia. No.
No. You're farsighted.
- I have to go.
- I have to stay.
- Story of my life.
- Oh! Me, too.
THURMAN : Your CBP
inspection's in three days.
The FBI and Homeland Security
will tour the airport,
spend two hours observing these offices
before your interview process begins.
How much does Navorski make?
Sir?
How much does he make?
How much are they paying him?
They're paying him
cash under the table.
I know that. How much?
$19 an hour.
Unbelievable. Do you know
that's more than I make?
That's New York City construction.
One of my own men came
up to me the other day.
Asked me if I wanted
to join the big pool.
Look at him.
Place a bet on when Navorski's
going to leave this airport.
Have you heard about this?
I have January 3rd.
Bring him in.
Jake, he has no nationality.
Okay? No country.
He's a national security risk, according
to my interpretation of Section 2.12.
I want you to put him in a detention
center and run a clearance on him.
That's all I want.
Well, what about a federal prison?
Well, what about another airport?
Hello? Hello?
We're detaining so many people,
there's no room anywhere.
- Did you try the FBI?
- I tried everybody. Nobody'll take him.
You want me to bring him
back to the terminal?
No. From now on,
Navorski lives here.
The people who are
coming here today
will be observing
me, inspecting me.
But most of all they will be looking
at the way that this airport is run.
So let's show them why this is
the number one airport
in the United States.
We process about 600 planes a day,
with a processing time
of 37 minutes per plane,
about 60 seconds per passenger...
to be brought into the country.
We keep it as clean as possible.
- What do you import?
- Computer software.
That's a lot of walnuts.
Yeah. My mother-in-law
loves these things.
Every time I go to Brazil,
I bring her back a bag.
- Your mother-in-law?
- Yeah.
Mind if I try one?
How did you know those weren't
for his mother-in-law?
If he's married, where's his ring?
And if he's divorced, who still
talks to their mother-in-law?
(INSPECTORS CHUCKLING)
I'm sorry, but really. No offense
to mother-in-laws, but...
- Sir.
- Yeah.
Sir, we have a situation upstairs.
- It'll have to wait.
- No. This won't wait.
When the 9:12 from Toronto landed,
they found four prescriptions
without an MPL.
They tried to take the pills
away, and he went nuts.
There he is. We think
they're for his father.
Sir, sir, calm down.
Put your weapons down.
Everybody keep your weapons...
All right. We're here to help you.
We're here to help you, sir.
All right. Give me the knife.
- Where's he from?
- Russia.
The only interpreter
we got is in Newark.
- We have to get someone to talk to him.
- I have an idea, sir.
Viktor.
(SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
I need your help.
His name is Milodragovich.
He lives near you.
He may not speak your dialect,
but I need you to translate
and help me out.
- I help you? Why?
- I don't want anybody to get hurt.
This guy's very upset.
Just calm him down, and I'll
let you back in the terminal.
No. New York. No red stamp.
Green. I green.
- New York.
- Okay, yes.
- You say yes?
- Yes.
We have somebody here to talk to you.
Somebody to talk to you. Go ahead.
Stay out.
(SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
(SPEAKS RUSSIAN)
So?
Okay, tell him in order to export
medicines from this country,
he needs to have the proper form,
he needs to have a Medicinal
Purchase License.
Okay? You understand me, Viktor?
(SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
He say he bring the
medicine for his father.
This why he go to Canada.
Medicine for father.
It doesn't matter.
His plane landed in the U.S.
He needs to have the right form.
(SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
He did not know he
need this document.
No one say to him he
need document form.
I'm saying it to him.
He needs to have the form signed by the
hospital who is treating his father.
These medicines have to
stay in the United States.
They have to stay here.
(SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
- He's begging you.
- I know. I can see that he's begging.
I'm sorry, sir.
You'll have to take a flight in the
morning. The medicine stays here.
I'm sorry.
(SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
WOMAN : Send him down.
(MILODRAGOVICH SOBS)
Thank you, Viktor.
Good job. Let's go.
Oh, oh, oh, hey. Uh...
Goat.
- What?
- Goat. Medicine is for goat.
- Goat?
- Yes. Medicine is for goat. Goat.
(WHIMPERS)
- He said that?
- Yes.
He say...
We not understand.
I not understand "goat."
Why? What are you saying?
You misunderstood him?
- It's not for his dying father?
- No. No.
The... Krakozhia...
The name for "father"
sound like "goat."
I make mistake.
(CHUCKLES)
Why are you doing this, Viktor?
Medicine is for goat.
- No, it's not.
- Yes.
You read the blue immigration form.
- Blue?
- Yes. Blue.
- Blue. The blue form.
The one that says if it's an animal,
he doesn't need the license.
Then he can bring the drugs in. That's
good, Viktor. That's very good.
Why are you doing this? Huh?
You don't know him.
You don't know the rules.
Look at me.
I was going to help you.
Now I want you to
ask him... No, not you.
I want you to ask him.
I want to hear him say it.
I want to hear him say
who the medicine is for.
Please. Who the medicine is for.
(SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
Answer him, Mr. Milodragovich.
Who are the pills for?
Okay. The pills stay.
He goes. That's it.
Goat.
Please. For goat.
Medicine for goat.
Give him the pills.
Medicine...
(VIKTOR SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
He love that goat.
Do you think I need an excuse
to put you back in that cell
to keep you there for five years?
You go to war with me, and you go
to war with the United States.
Then you'll know why Krakozhians
wait in line for cheap toilet paper
while Uncle Sam wipes his
ass with Charmin two-ply.
GUPTA : There was a 20 man.
Immigration gun was drawn.
The Dixon was ready to fire.
To kill the little
man with the pills.
But then someone walks into the room
and stand in front of this little man.
"Put the guns away," the man say.
"Nobody will die today."
Who?
- Who was it that saved him?
- Yeah, tell us. Who was it?
Who was this man?
Navorski. Viktor
"The Goat" Navorski.
- It doesn't look good, Frank.
- I was just following the rules.
Sometimes you have to ignore the
rules and concentrate on the people.
The people, I know.
The people, compassion. That's
the foundation of this country.
You could learn something
from Navorski.
Cheer up. It's not over yet.
(SIGHS)
- Is that for me?
- Yes. Yes.
Is Virgin Isle sailfish.
For you.
For wall.
Fish for wall.
Why do you want to go to New York?
And what's in the can of peanuts?
Promise.
- A promise in the can?
- Yes. A promise.
Let me make you a promise, Viktor.
And this is a promise that comes
from a man who is stuck here.
A man who may be stuck here
for the next ten years.
From now on, you and
I are partners.
If I stay, you stay.
You will not set one
foot in New York City.
Not a single toe in the
United States of America.
Do you understand what
I am saying to you?
Yes.
You don't like fish.
Do you ever feel like you're
just living in an airport?
We don't have to do this, Viktor.
I can ship you out in a crate.
I can mail you anywhere in the U.S.
What about my food cart? He can
hide inside, and we'll drive out.
- No. I can't do this.
- You said you wanted us to help you.
- I do.
- What's her name?
Amelia Warren.
I thought we were looking for
a way out, not a way in.
Be careful. Those flight attendants
ain't like regular women.
Flying back and forth
between time zones
messes with their biological clock.
- They're always ready for sex.
- Okay, I found something.
I am leaving.
They will come for us.
Gupta, will you relax?
Just watch the door.
You go in jail. Not me.
MULROY : For... You know what? Forget it.
- Keep looking.
- Warren, right?
- Yes. Yes.
- Warren.
Amelia Jane Warren?
- VIKTOR : Jane?
- Yeah.
Way to go, Viktor. First class.
- When she come back?
- Three weeks.
Amelia, would you like
to get eat to bite?
Bite to eat? Cantaloni?
Bite to eat?
Eat to bite? Eat to bite.
Bite to eat. Bite to eat.
Bite to eat.
Gupta, you been ever married?
- What did you say?
- You been ever married?
I had a wife and two kids in India.
I left them there 23 years ago.
Why?
I had a small tobacco
shop in Madras.
Made just enough money to survive.
One day this policeman comes in
and tells me I owe him some tax.
I said okay. This is common.
So I pay him.
The next day, the same policeman come
and keep coming and keep coming.
And I am paying, and I'm paying him,
and I'm paying him, and I'm paying him.
And finally, on the fifth day, I take
a knife and I stab him in his chest.
- You killed policeman?
- No. I just missed his heart.
When they tried to arrest me,
I run away.
So you never go home?
If I go home, I go in the
jail for seven years.
What if United States
catch you? They deport you.
As long as I keep my floor
clean, keep my head down,
they have no reason to deport me.
They have no reason to
notice a man like me.
WOMAN : (ON P.A.) United Airlines
Flight 2703 from Rome, Italy,
is now arriving at Gate C43.
(CART BEEPS)
- Hey, wait.
- Sorry. I'm sorry.
No, no, no. It's wet.
- Hey.
- Watch where you're going.
Watch out.
(VIKTOR GRUNTS)
- Amelia.
- Viktor.
- Hello.
- Sorry. I'm sorry.
He nearly killed me.
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
I love the suit.
Hugo Boss.
On sale, $149.99.
That's a bargain.
- Napoleon?
- Yes, yes.
And Josephine.
Do you know what Napoleon gave
Josephine on their wedding day?
Amelia?
Would you like to have eat to bite?
Food. Tonight?
- You're asking me out for dinner?
- Yes.
Yeah. Sure.
- What time?
- Dinnertime.
- AMELIA : Where do you want to go?
- I know place.
- Do you have an appointment?
- Navorski.
This way, please.
Thank you.
I didn't know they
had a patio up here.
It's very nice.
Good night.
Please.
Sorry. So, tonight we have
cannellonis or chicken.
- Cannelloni, please.
- Cannelloni.
- Sorry.
- Thank you.
For you, sir?
- Same.
- That's a great, great choice.
I'll be back.
Let me see. Enjoy.
Did you know the croissant
was invented in Romania?
- Tell me.
- Okay.
It's 1742, and the Turks
invade Bucharest,
making a surprise attack
under the cover of night.
- But the town bakers...
- (PAGER BEEPS)
Sorry.
(CLATTERING)
So, the bakers?
- No, never mind. It's a dumb story.
- No, please.
I'm sorry, Viktor.
Nobody really cares where
the croissant was invented.
I'll bet the Romanians
themselves don't give a shit.
I care.
Is histories. Is truth.
- I'm 39 years old.
- No.
- Yeah.
- That's the truth.
- You are not.
I tell everybody I'm 33, and most of the
men I've dated think I'm 27, but no.
I'm 39.
So? I was 39 once.
I was 18 years old when I started
working for the airlines.
I've been doing this over 20 years.
And now there's no more pretending.
This is it.
It's why my address book is by city,
and my pager goes off during dinner.
(PAGER BEEPS)
You can switch off pager.
I wish I could.
I've been waiting for a
phone call for seven years.
I know it's coming, Viktor.
That's why I can't break it off.
That's why I live out of hotels and have
my little suitcase packed, ready to go,
just in case he wants to
meet me for the weekend.
Yeah.
I've been waiting my whole life.
- Just don't know what the hell for.
- (PAGER VIBRATES)
I'm so sorry.
VIKTOR : I live here.
- What?
- I live here, in terminal.
Gate 67.
- You live at the airport?
- Yes. Day and night.
This home, like you.
They tell me to wait.
So I wait.
All frequent fliers feel the
same way you do, Viktor.
Everybody's waiting. Everybody.
- For a flight, for a meeting...
- I don't wait for flight or meeting.
- Then what are you waiting for?
- (PAGER BEEPS)
Is okay. I understand.
I have an idea.
- Come here.
- What you do?
- You sure?
- More than anything, I'm sure of this.
Ready?
(BOTH LAUGH)
VIKTOR : So, when do you come back?
AMELIA : 13 days. How about you?
VIKTOR : I will be here.
AMELIA :
But what if your schedule changes?
Maybe we should
exchange phone numbers.
VIKTOR : No. I will be here.
You know what Napoleon give to
Josephine when he win Bavaria?
Tell me.
Come on. Tell me.
I will show you. 13 days from now.
(CAMERA WHIRS)
What's he doing?
I can't ask him. I'm supposed
to tell him what he's doing.
If I ask him, I look like an idiot.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
I'm sorry. Sorry. You
got to do this for me.
You'll get really fat with all
the food I'm going to give you.
But, please, do this for me. It will
be the last thing I ask you to do.
He waits for you to
answer at Sbarro.
- I have to work.
- He will wait.
(CHEERING)
(VIKTOR CHUCKLES)
- How was your flight?
- Good.
Thanks.
- Is something wrong?
- You'll have to come with us.
You're kidding. I come
through here twice a month.
Please follow me.
I'm supposed to be
meeting somebody.
FRANK : In my line of work,
there are three things that matter.
The person, the
document and the story.
Find the truth of one, and you
find the truth of all three.
I need your help finding the truth.
Do you know a man named
Viktor Navorski?
Yes.
Do you know why he's here
and where he's from?
No. We're just friends.
Have you noticed
that he hides a can
of dry roasted peanuts in his bag?
- So?
- What do you make of that?
(AMELIA CHUCKLES)
I'd make peanut butter, I guess.
We know that he's planning to go
to the Ramada Inn on Lexington.
- Has he told you why he's in New York?
- No.
- Has he told you where he lives?
- No. We just met at the airport.
All I know is that he's a building
contractor, living out of a suitcase.
That's it.
- He's a contractor?
- Yeah.
That's what he said?
Amelia. I'm just curious.
You are the kind of woman who
can get any guy she wants.
Why Viktor Navorski?
That's something a guy like
you could never understand.
I guess you missed your flight again.
Or maybe you have a bad travel agent.
Please. Sit.
It's okay, Viktor. All men lie.
- At least you're not very good at it.
- I did not lie.
You told me you were delayed. You
never said it was for nine months.
Maybe you see the man the
way you want see the man.
So, what am I seeing? Who are you?
- I...
- Unacceptable?
Yes. Yes.
You want to hear the funny part?
I broke up with him.
I was coming here to tell
you he's out of my life.
I'm free. I got tired of waiting.
At least we have that in common.
Amelia, you know what Napoleon give
to Josephine when he win Bavaria?
No.
I show you.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Please.
Sit. Please.
That was gift.
Napoleon to Josephine.
One thousand fountains.
You built this for me?
Please. Sit. Don't get wet.
(VIKTOR STRAINS)
VIKTOR : Come on.
Oh...
(SPEAKS BULGARIAN)
it no work.
It should shoot, big
water up to ceiling.
Just tell me the truth. Did you
escape from an institution?
Are you a criminal?
You're living here, Viktor.
You're living at Gate 67.
I just want to know why.
Here. I show you.
My father.
Viktor, please tell me your
father isn't in that peanut can.
This is jazz.
My father, Dimitar Asenov Navorski,
see this photograph in
Hungarian newspaper, 1958.
He say he look at
photograph for seven days.
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday...
Who are they?
Count Basie, Dizzy Gillespie,
Thelonious Monk, Sonny Rollins,
Art Blakey, Max Kaminsky.
57 of them all together.
After looking at photograph for
seven days, my father has idea.
He begin to write letters to club,
Lickety Split, Snookie's Sugar Bowl.
He ask the nuns to write
English. Hundreds letters.
And then he wait.
He wait month, week, year.
My father wait 40 year.
And they all sign names.
One by one.
They all write their name
and send it to my father.
All but not one.
Benny Golson.
Saxophone.
My father die before Benny Golson
write his name and send to my father.
So I make him promise.
I keep promise.
I promise I will go New York,
find Benny Golson,
have him write name to put in can.
And you've been living here so you
could do this for your father?
Maybe I think he do it for me.
You say you are waiting
for something.
And I say to you,
"Yes, yes. We all wait."
What are you waiting for?
You. I wait for you.
What?
The war is over.
The right wing military coup that
ousted President Vagobagin...
(ALL SING THE KRAKOZHIAN
NATIONAL ANTHEM IN BULGARIAN)
All right, everybody.
Let's raise your glasses.
Let's have a toast to my
friend, Viktor "The Goat."
- (BLEATS)
- (ALL BLEAT)
May he never lose
his country again.
Krakozhia.
Amelia. You here early.
Hello. Amelia, look.
Peace. Peace. The war. The war.
Please come. Come.
See, the war, the war
Krakozhia is over.
Peace. The war is over.
- You know my friend in Washington.
- Yes, yes.
He has a lot of connections. Here.
It's a pass, Viktor.
A one-day travel emergency
visa with your name on it.
- Wha... Visa?
- Yes.
- From your friend?
- Yeah.
Just go to New York, find that
last name and put it in the can.
- I go New York?
- Yes.
I go New York!
(ALL CHEER)
Amelia, you come with. You
come with me to New York.
Your friend do this for me?
Why he do this for me?
He did it for me.
I told you to stay away from me,
Viktor. But you didn't understand.
- I think you were confused.
- No, I confused about everything.
I not confused...
Not this. Not this.
I'm sorry. I'm running late.
Amelia. Why you go? Why you go?
You know what Napoleon gave
Josephine as a wedding present?
It was a gold locket.
And on the inside,
he made an inscription.
"Destiny."
Destiny.
WOMAN : (ON TV)...
rejoice in the streets
as well as in their local taverns.
The Krakozhian flag waved goodbye from
high atop the parliament buildings.
It is a clear sign of the power...
- Hey, baby.
- Hi.
I missed you.
Come on.
TORRES : Next.
Viktor.
Hello, Dolores. How I am today?
What do you have here?
Oh, no. It's not signed.
What?
This is a one-day
emergency travel visa.
To validate authenticity, it needs to
be signed by the supervising officer.
Dixon?
Yes.
Dixon.
The war in my country is over.
Yeah. I know. Congratulations.
It's strange, isn't it, Viktor?
When you wait so
long for one thing?
One tiny moment.
I had that moment today, too.
You see this badge?
This badge means that I was
made CBP Field Commissioner.
It means that my authority over the
security of this airport is absolute.
Your ticket and your passport.
It's time for you to go home.
Officer Waylin, please show
Mr. Navorski into the terminal
and make sure he does
not miss his flight.
Goodbye, Viktor, and good luck.
I think I want go New York City.
Don't make this difficult, Viktor.
I no more "unacceptable."
- I told you this is over.
- I go New York.
Are you sure you want to do that?
I go New York City now.
Part of my job is to get rid of
undesirables, and there are quite a few.
Like this guy, Joe Mulroy.
I think you know him.
He's been here for 20 years, but he's
been running an after-hour poker game.
Bringing in liquor and marijuana.
Poor guy's going to lose his pension.
And I think he has kids, too.
Yep.
And then there's this guy, Enrique Cruz.
I think you also know Enrique.
Enrique has been letting people
into the food preparation area.
That's a major security breach.
The poor guy,
I think he's a newlywed.
But I'm going to
have to let him go.
And then there's Gupta
Rajan. He's a janitor.
But he's wanted for assaulting a
police officer back in India in 1979.
I'll have to deport him.
I will go home.
- I'm sorry. What did you say?
- I will go home.
Leave them alone. I will go.
- Today.
- Yes.
If you don't get on that
plane, they're all gone.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
Okay. Good.
I don't believe you.
- Viktor, you don't have to do this.
- You can fight these guys.
- We'll help you.
- Viktor, come on. I owe you so much.
- Please let me help you.
- This is your friend talking.
We're all your friends.
We're your family now.
Gupta.
Goodbye.
You try to fool us.
You make us to think you would walk
out, that you will fight with them.
Why don't you fight?
- The war is over.
- Then go. Get lost.
Get lost. Go home and tell
them you never made it.
You come this close to America,
but you don't have the courage
to go from here to here.
You are a coward.
The plane is on time.
You are a coward!
You make me sick!
What's wrong with you,
man? Settle down.
Got people looking all around,
looking at me like I'm... (SIGHS)
Look at me.
Come on, look at me.
(SIGHS)
There's something you should know.
(WHISTLES)
WOMAN : (ON P.A.) Ladies and
gentlemen, United Airlines Flight 865
from Krakozhia has landed and
is now taxiing to the gate.
For those passengers holding tickets
for Flight 866 to Krakozhia,
we expect departure
to be on schedule.
Gupta.
(SIREN BLARING)
I am going home.
Get lost.
WOMAN : (ON P.A.)
Your attention, please.
Flight 866 to Krakozhia will be
delayed until further notice.
(GUNS COCK)
Do you have an appointment?
Somebody tell me what the
hell is going on down there.
We're right behind you.
Viktor's leaving.
- Monica, Viktor's leaving.
- I know. He's going home.
He's going for the front
door, out to the city.
What? Oh, my...
Viktor. Remember us.
From the Discovery Store,
I want to give you this.
It's good luck.
A digital camera for Cousin Katia.
I don't know where you're going,
but these will keep your feet warm.
- Everybody in position?
- THURMAN : We're here.
Secure the door.
(ALL TALK AT ONCE)
WAYLIN : Sorry, Viktor.
Take him, Judge.
Hold it, Viktor. Take it easy.
You see those doors?
Those are the entry
doors to New York City.
To the United States of
America. Turn around.
It's snowing in the city, and
you're going to need that.
Good luck.
Oh, no.
I'm going to miss you.
Try not to get stuck
wherever you're going.
Arrest him! Arrest him!
God damn it!
(CAR HORNS BEEPING)
Taxi.
Thank you.
Where you go?
161 Lexington. Please take Van Wyck
Expressway to Queensboro Bridge.
It's faster than BQE.
- Where you from?
- Krakozhia. Viktor Navorski.
I'm Goran. Albania.
- When do you come to New York?
- Thursday.
You want us to block the South exit
and have AP sweep every vehicle?
Sir?
5:30 from Tokyo just landed.
Got two planes on the tarmac.
Barcelona on approach.
The night is young, and 1,500
people are headed our way.
Everybody inside. Everybody inside.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
(CAR HORNS BLARING)
- Are you checking in, sir?
- No, no. I don't check in.
I want to go to this place, please.
The lobby lounge is
around the corner.
They have happy hour specials
and live music. Do you like jazz?
(BENNY GOLSON SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Let's do Killer Joe.
It worked all right last night.
- Yes?
- You are Benny Golson?
Yeah. Yes, I am.
Benny Golson, I am Viktor
Navorski. I am from Krakozhia.
My father, Dimitar Asenov Navorski,
was great, great fan of your music.
Oh, a jazz fan. Fantastic.
Would you sign your name, please?
Oh. Can I do it a little later?
We have to get started now.
- Just a minute.
- I will wait.
Okay.
(DISTANT SIREN WAILING)
Taxi. Taxi.
Where you want to go?
I am going home.