♪ Who do they call ♪
♪ When the chips are
startin' to fall ♪
♪ Just when the villains
are winning ♪
♪ The trouble's
beginning to brew ♪
[Explosion]
♪ The man called
Flintstone ♪
♪ That's who ♪
♪ Who's always there ♪
♪ There to rescue
some maiden fair ♪
♪ A man with instincts
unerring ♪
♪ Full of the old
daring-do ♪
♪ The man called
Flintstone ♪
♪ That's who ♪
♪ He thrives on a diet
of danger ♪
♪ And he's no stranger ♪
♪ To the unjust ♪
♪ As he is with romance ♪
♪ Who is the man ♪
♪ The man called
Flintstone ♪
[Rumbling]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
[Screeches]
Don't let him get away.
Don't worry.
I won't.
Ow!
Hee hee! Hee hee hee!
Hee hee! Hee hee--
[Angry muttering]
Detour! Watch out!
[Snores]
[Angry muttering]
We have parachute, too.
Good. Let's follow him.
That is our parachute?
Hee hee! Hee hee hee!
Hee hee! Hee hee!
Some parachute.
Oh, shut up, you!
[Angry muttering]
[Crash]
Ho ho!
We have him trapped!
Good.
Let's squish him.
ALI: Hurry, hurry!
He must not escape!
He won't.
We've got him now.
[Panting]
[Giggles]
[Chuckles]
[Both laughing]
That's the end
of Rock Slag.
Nice work, Bobo.
Thank you, Ali.
Ho ho! Ho ho!
[Chuckles]
They think they've
finished me off.
They don't know how tough
we secret agents are.
This is Secret Agent
Rock Slag
reporting
to Chief Boulder.
Come in, Chief.
This is Chief Boulder.
Anything wrong, Slag?
Plenty. Ali and Bobo,
2 of the Green Goose's
strong-arm boys,
got me cornered and
tried to do me in.
Are you OK, Slag?
Well, I think
I've twisted my tibia,
and cracked
my clavicle, Chief.
Stay there, Slag.
I'll get an ambulance
to you right away.
Right, Chief.
Cracked clavicle--
that's a bad break,
just as we were closing in
on the Green Goose
and his nefarious
SMIRK organization.
The whole world is
in peril as long as
the Green Goose is loose.
Operator, get me
the Bedrock Hospital.
Oh, Wilma!
We're gonna leave now.
WILMA: OK, Fred.
But please hurry.
We still have
a lot of packing to do.
Be back right after
we take Dino and Hoppy
to, uh, you know where.
I don't envy the boys.
Dino and Hoppy always
put up such a fuss
when they go to the vet's.
It's a shame we can't
take them with us.
I'm gonna miss Hoppy.
I'm gonna miss Dino, too.
But a camping vacation
is bad enough
without dragging
pets along.
How true.
Seems like there's a million
and one things to do
when you're going
on a trip, huh, Barney?
Yeah. We darn near forgot
to take Dino and Hoppy to--
Don't say it, Barn!
Oops, I almost
gave it away.
Watch it.
If those 2 knew
we were gonna
leave 'em
at the v-e-t-s,
for 2 weeks they'd
take to the woods.
Well, uh, how we gonna
get 'em in the office, Fred?
We'll sneak up
the back alley.
They've never been
taken inside that way before.
Hey, that's a good idea.
[Laughs]
Come on, Dino.
We gotta see a man
about something.
BARNEY: Uh, yeah,
you, too, Hoppy.
DINO: Yipe!
[Barking]
FRED: No!
No, Dino, no!
Hold it! Hold it!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
[Hoppy honking]
BARNEY:
Take it easy, Hoppy!
Take it easy,
calm down now!
Dino,
come back here!
Come--
Look out, Fred,
comin' through!
Oops!
Oh, boy.
Mr Flintstone!
Mr Rubble!
You're going
about it all wrong.
You have to use psychology.
Psychology? What do
you mean, Doc?
I'll show you.
Miss Soapstone,
send Zsa Zsa and Dolly
out here.
Yes, sir.
Who is Zsa Zsa?
And Dolly?
Zsa Zsa is
a girl hoparoo,
and Dolly is
a girl dinosaur.
Watch this.
[Honking]
[Barking]
[Honks]
[Barks]
[Honking and barking]
[Laughs] I gotta
hand it to you, Doc.
You sure know
your psychology.
Doesn't he, Barn?
Barney?
Woo, woo, woo,
woo, woo, woo!
FRED: Barney!
Uh, huh? What?
Oh, boy. Thanks, Fred.
That psychology stuff
was working on me, too.
[Both Laughing]
I hope the girls
have everything packed.
I'm anxious
to get started.
Me, too.
Hey, where you
going, Fred?
This is the way
to Rock Canyon Road.
Right, Barn.
We'll save 10 minutes
going home this way.
But Rock Canyon Road
is closed.
It's too dangerous!
Not for a good
driver like me.
Hold on, Barn,
here we are.
We ought to have
seat belts, Fred!
Oh, who needs 'em?
There, we're down.
How is that
for skilful driving?
Oh, my goodness, Fred!
Are you all right?
Oh--
Oh, my head!
Boy, that's some bump.
Ooh!
Hey, we'd better
get you to a doctor.
FRED: No, that's
not necessary.
Oh, I don't know, Fred.
It won't hurt to have
your head examined.
BARNEY: Here we are...
The Bedrock Hospital.
It'll only take a minute.
You wait here,
I'll go find a doctor.
Make it snappy,
will ya?
I feel OK now.
Uh, pardon me, Nurse.
My friend needs
to see a doctor.
You'll have to wait.
All the doctors are
busy with a patient
who fell off a roof
last night.
Fell off a roof?
Is he hurt?
I'll say.
They've been working
on him all night.
FIRST DOCTOR: Hold it.
You've got his head
on backwards.
SECOND DOCTOR:
Well, twist it around.
OK, that's enough.
Now, cut!
How are you doing,
Irving?
Be finished in a minute.
Nurse!
[Clanking]
There, we've finished.
The statue
looks just like new.
When the cement dries,
he can go back on the roof.
How about the man
who fell with him?
How's he doing?
Not bad. Dr Moonstone
is taking care of him.
Dr Moonstone,
I'm Chief Boulder,
head of this country's
Secret Service.
And your patient
is Rock Slag,
my best agent.
Thanks, Chief.
CHIEF: Doc, you must get Rock
back on his feet quickly.
He's the only agent
I have capable
of carrying out
a very important
and dangerous
mission.
Rock Slag survive fall.
He is still alive, Bobo.
Our work is
not done, Ali.
Mr Slag can
leave any time.
He just bruised
a few ribs.
So, now if you'll
excuse me,
I'll just look in
on my other patients.
Sure, Doc, sure.
And, uh, thanks.
That's great news.
What's this important
mission, Chief?
The biggest yet.
You're going
to eliminate the guy
that tried
to eliminate you.
ROCK: You mean
the Green Goose.
Yes!
Intelligence reports
he has a weapon
so powerful he could
destroy the world.
And probably will,
unless--
NURSE: Rock Slag!
Ooh! [Growls]
Mmm! [Giggles]
Unless
he is stopped.
So you see, Slag,
the safety of every man,
woman, and child
in every country
depends on you.
On me? Why me, Chief?
CHIEF: It has
to be you, Rock Slag.
Rock Slag!
Yum, yum, yum!
Mmm!
[Squeals and giggles]
There's your answer.
You have an uncontrollable
appeal to women.
Yes, I know.
But how can
that help us, Chief?
CHIEF: We're going to put
your gift to good use.
How, Chief?
Through Tanya,
the Green Goose's
number one lieutenant.
She's heard
about you, Rock.
And she wants
to meet you so badly,
she's made a deal
with us
to turn the Green Goose
over to you!
To me?
That's the deal.
You're going
to meet her in Paris.
When do I leave, Chief?
At once.
I'll call the office
and have them get
your plane ticket.
At last,
Rock Slag is alone!
Now we can finish
the job.
ALI: Hello, Rock Slag.
Ali! Bobo!
You're taking
a trip, Slag.
A one-way trip, huh?
Hee hee! Hee hee
hee! Hee hee!
This time we got him, Ali.
Rock Slag is
finished, Bobo!
Hee hee! Hee hee
hee! Hee hee!
Ho ho! Ho ho!
Hee hee! Hee hee!
With Rock back on the job,
the Green Goose's goose
is as good as cooked
right now.
Rock! What happened?
While you were gone
I had visitors, Chief.
Ali and Bobo?
Right. The goon twins.
CHIEF: Well,
that does it.
Tanya will never
go for you.
You're a mess!
That cooks
our Green Goose.
I'll try
to heal fast, Chief.
It won't be
fast enough, Rock.
At any moment,
the Green Goose may decide
to take over the world.
I'd better cancel
your trip to Paris.
Is this the patient?
Uh, yeah, Doc.
Fred Flintstone.
He fell on his head.
I'm OK now, Doc.
I feel fine.
Well, why don't we
check you over anyway?
Come with me,
Mr Flintstone.
OK, but I'm telling you,
it's a waste of time.
Hmm. Your pulse seems
to be normal.
Right on the button,
in fact.
Now cross your legs,
and we'll test
your reflexes.
Make it snappy,
will ya, Doc?
I'm on my vacation.
We're almost finished.
Reflex is normal.
[Mumbling]
You can leave now,
Mr Flintstone.
Right after I give you
a booster shot.
Best to play it safe,
you know.
Yeah, yeah,
yeah, all right.
Let's have the shot, Doc.
I wanna get out of here.
DOCTOR: You won't even
feel this, Mr Flintstone.
FRED: Yeow!
Watch it, Doc!
What are you
trying to do,
put me
in the hospital?
It's amazing!
That man is a dead ringer
for Rock Slag!
Look at the size
of this needle.
What do you think I am,
a brontosaurus?
Why, he could be
Rock's twin!
His twin!
I wonder if--
Why not?
It's worth a try.
Pardon me, sir.
Can I have a word
with you?
Who, me?
CHIEF: Yes.
Your country
needs you.
My country needsme?!
Now, let's see
if i got this straight.
The government will
send me and my family
to Paris to pick up
a Green Goose
because I look
like this guy?
Right, Mr Flintstone.
Your resemblance
to our regular messenger
is fantastic!
And as you can see,
he's in no condition
to make the trip.
FRED: Yeah,
I can see that.
This Green Goose
must be
a very valuable
bird.
Very valuable.
Our government wants
to put him in a cage.
I had planned a camping
trip this year,
but, uh, you did say
"all expenses paid"?
Every last penny.
In that case, I'll be
glad to help the government
get the Green Goose.
CHIEF: Good.
Now, raise
your right hand.
My right hand?
And repeat after me.
OK.
I will not reveal
my mission to anyone.
Not even my wife.
Not even my...
wife?!
Congratulations.
You are now an official
secret agent.
Gosh! [Laughs]
A spy-type guy.
[Music starts]
♪ He's gonna be a spy ♪
♪ A double zero guy ♪
♪ He's got
that certain air ♪
♪ Debonair ♪
♪ Full of the old
savoir-faire ♪
♪ He'll drive
a jazzy car ♪
♪ Like some big movie star ♪
♪ And catch
each lady's eye ♪
♪ A spy-type guy ♪
♪ Ah-ta-shay ♪
♪ He'll carry an attache ♪
♪ Don't ask
what's an attache ♪
♪ It fits
in the briefcase ♪
♪ All agents have 'em ♪
♪ If someone gets the drop ♪
♪ With one karate chop ♪
♪ He'll send
'em beddy-bye ♪
♪ 'Cause he's
the spy-type guy ♪
♪ He can shoot ♪
♪ A gun from
his handmade boot ♪
♪ His bulletproof,
tailored suit ♪
♪ Is really a whopper ♪
♪ It's a helicopper ♪
♪ He'll go
from place to place ♪
♪ And never leave a trace ♪
♪ He'll save
the human race ♪
♪ 'Cause he's spy-type ♪
♪ Sly-type ♪
♪ Spy-type ♪
♪ Guy ♪
[Music ends]
All right, Flintstone,
here are your plane tickets,
and some money.
You leave for Paris
in the morning.
Oh, boy!
And, rember,
your code name is
Rock Slag.
Gotcha. Rock Slag.
Rock Slag, Rock
Slag, Rock Slag.
Chief, are you
out of your mind?
Why that guy is no match
for the Green Goose
and his gang!
I know. But he's
our only chance.
Besides, I'll be there
to keep an eye on him.
You'd better,
or that Flintstone will be
in worse shape than I am!
It's a long shot,
but he just may
be able
to pull it off.
FRED: Hiya, Barney.
Fred! Gee, I thought
you'd never come out.
What did the doc
have to say?
I'm OK, but I got
to cancel
the camping trip.
Cancel the camping trip!
Oh! There he is!
Who? Who?
Rock Slag!
Rock Slag? Ooh!
You naughty boy!
Trying to leave
without good-bye!
[Kissing and giggling]
Wow!
What a hospital plan
they have here.
I don't get it!
Now, tell me, Fred.
How come you gotta
cancel our camping trip?
Because Wilma and I
are going to Paris.
Paris! Stop the car, Fred.
Stop the car!
What's the matter?
Look, you got a bump
on your head
and now you think
you're going to Paris, right?
FRED: Right.
But to go to Paris
you need A: money,
and B: plane tickets.
FRED: Here's "A."
Money.
And here's "B."
Plane tickets.
Gosh, Fred,
what's this all about?
I'll tell you
later, pal.
Right now, I want
to see Wilma's face
when she hears
the news.
That was Rock Slag, Bobo!
It can't be, Ali.
It was!
He is still alive!
Ooh, if we don't
get Slag,
the Green Goose
will get us!
Quick, after him!
Here he comes.
We must not fail
this time.
Boy, this is
a rough road!
You're not kidding.
When I give
the signal,
you push the rock.
BO: Right!
Push the rock.
Take it easy, Fred.
We don't want
another accident.
Whoops!
Hey, look.
The car is going
right through the tunnel.
ALI: Get ready,
get set...
Push!
Hee hee! Hee hee hee!
Hee hee! Hee hee!
Right on target.
That finishes
Rock Slag.
For keeps, this time.
Hee hee! Hee hee!
Ho ho! Ho ho!
You almost didn't make it
to Paris, huh, Fred?
Yeah.
That boulder would
have cancelled
my trip permanently.
I wonder what's taking
the boys so long?
They're waiting
for us
to finish packing,
what else?
Uh-oh!
The trailer's
got a flat.
WILMA: Just our luck.
Well, we'd better change it
and save some time.
OK, I'll get
the spare.
I'm always sticking
my neck out
for someone else.
One spare, coming up!
There, it's fixed.
Hiya, girls!
Sorry we're late.
WILMA: Fred!
How come
you're walking?
Where's the car?
Oh, never mind that.
Wait till you hear
the news!
What news?
A little change
in plans, my dear.
Mr and Mrs Flintstone
will be spending
their vacation
abroad this year
in Paris, France.
Paris?
France?
But--but--but how? What?
I mean, when did--
Tut-tut, sweetheart.
No questions, please.
Just take
my word for it.
Paris! I can
hardly believe it!
Oh, you wonderful
man! Mmm!
Ooh, I'm so happy
for you, Wilma.
I wish we could take
a trip like that.
Hey, that's a great idea!
Look, Barney,
we can get our money back
on all the camping stuff
we rented,
and buy plane tickets
for you and Betty
and Bamm Bamm.
Really, Fred?
Do you think there
would be enough?
FRED: Sure!
Maybe not enough
for first class,
or even second class.
But at least
we'd all be together.
What do you say, Barn?
I say put her there,
buddy boy!
You just talked me
into it.
Wilma, did you
hear that?
We're going
with you!
[Music starts]
♪ Here we are,
like we always are ♪
♪ When you're near
I'm never far ♪
♪ We're a matched
and perfect set ♪
♪ Never separated yet,
in fact ♪
FRED: ♪ We are
the indisputable ♪
BARNEY:
♪ spositively irrefutable ♪
TOGETHER: ♪ You might say
we're me-and-you-able ♪
♪ Team-mates,
Team-mates ♪
FRED: ♪ We may stay
or we may go ♪
BARNEY: ♪ Either way,
we always know ♪
♪ We will both
be on the scene ♪
♪ Nothing ever comes
between us 'cause ♪
♪ We are
the most reliable ♪
♪ Definitely
undeniable ♪
TOGETHER: ♪ It's like
we're you-and-I-able ♪
♪ Team-mates ♪
♪ Team-mates, we ♪
♪ When I broke my arm
last summer ♪
♪ You wore the cast ♪
♪ What else
could I do? ♪
♪ We're team-mates
through and through ♪
♪ Me and you ♪
TOGETHER: ♪ Team-mates,
team-mates, team-mates ♪
FRED: ♪ When I exercise ♪
♪ It's you who always starts
breathing fast ♪
BARNEY: ♪ How else
could it be? ♪
♪ We're suited to a "T,"
you and me ♪
TOGETHER: ♪ Team-mates,
team-mates, team-mates ♪
♪ Now that's the long
and short of it ♪
♪ The unabridged report
of it ♪
♪ The starboard
and the port of it ♪
♪ Team-mates ♪
♪ Team-mates, we ♪
FRED: [Laughs]
Put her there, Barn!
We're team-mates!
BARNEY: Yeah!
♪ Yeah, that's the long
and short of it ♪
♪ The unabridged
report of it ♪
♪ The starboard
and the port of it ♪
♪ Team-mates ♪
♪ Team-mates, we ♪
P.A. ANNOUNCER: Flight 70
for Paris now boarding
at gate 5.
All passengers
please check in.
Is this the flight
to Paris?
Yes, sir.
Here's our tickets.
One set First Class,
one set Last Class.
Fine. Put your luggage
on the scales, please.
With pleasure.
TICKET AGENT: 100 pounds.
That's quite a load.
Brak! You can
say that again.
You may board now, sir.
The helicopter will
take you to the flight deck.
Well, thank you.
First Class
passengers this way.
Come on, Wilma.
Hold it, bud!
Last class that way!
And don't walk
on the carpet!
Uh, uh, yes, sir.
Fred, why don't you
get some magazines?
Yeah, yeah. Good idea.
Book! Book!
And a colouring book
for Pebbles.
[Laughs]
All right.
I can hardly wait
to report
to the Green Goose
how we eliminated
Rock Slag.
Look!
Our reward
will be great.
Look! Look!
By the newsstand.
We'll live like kings.
We'll die like dogs.
Ooh! But how
could it be?
There's not
a scratch on him.
When the Green Goose
finds out we failed,
there'll be plenty
of scratches onus.
This time, I'll make sure.
You missed.
Hee hee! Hee hee hee!
Hee hee! Hee hee--
[Gulps, speaks
pseudo-Japanese]
Oh, how exciting.
I've never been
on a helicopter before.
Hold on to Daddy,
Pebbly-poo.
Hedicopter! Whee!
Eh hee hee hee.
She said "hedicopter."
Ha ha, hee hee hee.
Here's the flight deck.
I wonder how Barney's
making out.
Hurry, Barney,
or we'll miss the plane.
I'm hurryin',
I'm hurryin'!
Why is the flight deck
way up here, pilot?
Well, it's a big
aeroplane,
so we use jet propulsion
to get airborne.
Jet propulsion?
Yeah. You see,
the plane is attached
to that launching device
at the edge of the cliff.
When the pilot is ready,
he gives the signal,
the launching crew
releases the retaining rope,
and the plane takes off.
Oh, my, what will
they think of next?
Come on, Wilma.
Let's get aboard.
P.A. ANNOUNCER: Flight 70
for Paris now boarding
at Gate 5.
Fasten your
seat belts, please.
We are ready
to take off.
Got your seat belt
fastened, honey?
Uh-huh.
Ready for takeoff?
Roger.
Let 'er go!
I wish we were
already there, Fred.
I feel
a little nervous.
Oh, nonsense, honey.
There isn't a safer place
in the world than right here.
Let him have it.
All right.
Who's the wise guy?
Why don't you go see
how Betty and Barney
are doing?
Yeah. Yeah,
that's a good idea.
Uh, pardon me, Miss.
Where are the Last Class
passengers?
All the way back, sir.
Thank you, thank you.
Be back in a minute, dear.
All right, Fred.
Here he comes.
♪ Yup dum dum dum
da da da ♪
♪ Da da doo doo
doo doo doo ♪
Now's our chance.
Second Class?
Boy, they sure
pack them in tight.
Third Class.
Wow! A double-decker.
If it's this bad here,
Last Class must
really be something.
Barney! Betty!
Hello, Fred!
Hiya, neighbour!
You wanna take our
seats for a while?
Thanks, but we'll
be landing pretty soon.
OK. See you later!
I'm all finished,
Ali.
Just in time, Bobo.
Here he comes.
Oh. How could it be?
I sawed
the hole right here.
[Snoring]
Fred, look!
Huh? What is it?
We're over Paris.
Paris?! Let me see!
Let me see!
There's the Eiffel Rock
Tower!
Oh, what a beautiful
city!
Fasten your
seat belts, please.
We are about to land.
[Metallic squeak]
[Whistling]
♪ There is a happy sound ♪
♪ In my Paris ♪
♪ A sound
that's always here ♪
♪ For you and me ♪
♪ The little bicycles ♪
♪ With bells a-ringing ♪
♪ And tires singing along ♪
♪ Ah! The quiet murmur ♪
♪ Of the River Seine ♪
♪ And the children
singing a song ♪
♪ The funny taxi horns
that hurt your ears ♪
♪ They only try to say,
"We're glad you're here" ♪
♪ And each Parisian
you meet ♪
♪ Will greet you with,
"Welcome home,mon ami" ♪
♪ We are so happy
you could be with us ♪
♪ In Paris ♪
[Whistling]
♪ The little bicycles
with bells a-ringing ♪
♪ And tires singing along ♪
♪ Ah, the quiet murmur
of the River Seine ♪
♪ And the children
singing a song ♪
♪ The funny taxi horns ♪
♪ That hurt your ear ♪
♪ They only try to say ♪
♪ "We're glad you're here" ♪
♪ And each Parisian you meet
will greet you with ♪
♪ "Welcome home,mon ami" ♪
♪ We are so happy you could
be with us in Paris ♪
All right,
everybody. Smile.
BETTY:
How about you, Wilma?
Aren't you going to be
in the picture?
Oh, I will, as soon
as I focus the camera
and set the timer.
Hmm, 10 seconds
should be enough.
There!
All set!
She better hurry.
7, 6, 5,
4, 3, 2, 1!
She made it!
Oh, how I hate
these mob shots.
How's this?
Oh, that's swell!
Hey, it
turned out great.
Now let's take one
of you, Fred.
OK!
And no corny
poses, please.
How's this, Wilma?
BO: He's alone.
ALI: Now's
our chance.
ALI: All together...
Push!
There she goes.
And here
she comes.
[Both panting]
We safe now.
Right. Hee hee.
Hee hee. Hee hee hee.
[Rants
in pseudo-Japanese]
Be with you
in a minute, Fred.
I have to load
the camera.
Take your time, honey.
Oops!
I have to talk
to you, Flintstone.
Chief! What are you
doing here in Paris?
There's been
a change in plans.
The Green Goose
has flown to Rome.
You'll have to go
there immediately.
Rome? I've just
arrived in Paris.
How will I explain it
to Wilma?
You'll think
of something.
And how do I find
the Green Goose in Rome?
Triple X will help you.
Triple X? Who's he?
Our top foreign agent,
A master of disguise.
I'll show you.
[Whistles]
Ruff! Ruff! Ruff!
That's Triple X?
Mm-hmm.
Meet Rock Slag, Trip.
Pleased
to meet you, Slag.
Wow! That dog disguise
is terrific!
Yes, I've got
a million of them.
Watch.
[Transylvanian accent]
How do you do, Mr Slag?
Uhh! Uhh! Ooh!
Gee, that's a great
Frankenrock.
OK, Triple X,
you can go now.
See you
in Rome, Slag.
Ta ta.
Uh, ta ta, Triple X.
[Squawks]
Boy, he's good.
WILMA: Fred,
where are you?
I'm ready to take
your picture.
Hold it, Wilma!
Hold it!
How would you all
like some real,
genuine Italian food?
Hey, sounds like
an elegant idea, pal.
And I know an elegant
place to get it.
Where's that, Fred?
Italy. Where else?
ALL: Italy?!
Sure. We'll grab
a plane for Rome
and find a nice
restaurant.
But all the way
to Italy, just to get
an Italian dinner?
Hey, I guess we're lucky
he isn't in the mood
for Chinese food.
Ah heh heh heh heh
heh heh heh heh heh!
WILMA: Rome
by moonlight.
Ah, it's so beautiful,
isn't it, Fred?
Yeah. You know
something, Wilma?
If we were here
a long time ago,
I'd be down there
in that garden,
serenading you.
Really, Fred?
Uh-huh.
I'd be dressed
in one of those
Romeo outfits,
and I'd come leaping
over that garden wall...
Wilmalita!
Frederico!
♪ Pensate amore ♪
♪ Think love, think love ♪
♪ Think love ♪
♪ Oh,signora ♪
♪Signore ♪
♪ Pensate amore ♪
♪ Think love, think love ♪
♪ Think love ♪
♪ Don't think of tomorrow ♪
♪ Who thinks of tomorrow ♪
♪ With such a moon above? ♪
[Crash]
♪Signora, signore ♪
♪ Pensate amore ♪
♪ Think love, think love ♪
♪ Think love ♪
♪ Don't think of tomorrow ♪
♪ Who thinks of tomorrow? ♪
♪ Mmm, with such
a moon above ♪
♪Signora, signore ♪
♪ Pensate amore ♪
♪ Think love, think love ♪
♪ Think love ♪
Oh, Fred, you're
so romantic!
Oh, I hate to interrupt
you two love birds,
but your pizza's
getting cold.
Pizza? Oh, boy!
Come on, Wilma!
I might
as well face it.
Fred loves me,
all right,
but his big love
is food.
Hey, how about a nice bottle
of wine with our dinner?
Oh, waiter,uno botelo,uh,de vino, uh...pronto.
Ooh, you
speak Italian.
Heh heh heh.Si, si, fraulein.
Hows about-a dis-a
bottle, senor?
Yeah, sure,
that bottle'll be fine.
Did-a you read
the label,signore?
Uh, "Follow me, XXX."
Never heard
of that brand.
No, no. It says,
"Follow me.Triple X."
I want to talk to you.
Oh. Oh, oh, oh.
Yeah, yeah.
I--I'll be glad to.
Pardon me a minute.
I'll be right back.
Don't be long, dear.
Psst! Slag.
Is that you, Triple X?
Oh, you're great at that
disguise stuff. What's up?
The chief wants
to talk to you.
The chief? Here in Rome?
Where is he?
He's waiting
in the kitchen.
OK. I'll see
what he wants.
MAN: Hey, waiter!
How about some bread sticks?
OK, buddy.
Keep-a you shirt on!
Chief? You in here?
There's a girl
in this restaurant
asking for Rock Slag.
Hey, that's me.
Right, and she's going
to tell you
where to pick up
the Green Goose.
Great. How will
I know her?
You say, "50 flying
firefighters,"
and she'll answer,
"Bubala."
"Bubala," huh?
I'll go find her
right away, chief.
Pardon me, madame.
Ya?
Oh, Rock,
my little cabbage!
I'm so happy
to see you again.
Uh, 50 flighty
firefighters.
50 fiery fireflies.
Oh, Rock, where
have you been?
You're supposed
to answer Bubala.
Bubala.
You called me Bubala.
Oh, Rock! Oh ho!
Rock? Where are you?
Rock?
Mon cheri, Rock!
I heard you were here!
Ooh, I miss you
so, so much!
I, uh, uh--
By any chance
do you know
about the 50
flighty fireflies?
Oh, Rock!
Uh-oh.
Oh, my little cabbage.
Where are you?
Oh, excuse me.
FRED, ITALIAN ACCENT:
It's all right.
Shall we dance?
Dance, darling?
Doh, boy!
Where were you, Fred?
I was just
over the--uh-oh!
Rock! Baby,
where are you?
Yoo-hoo!
What are you doing
under the table, Fred?
I'm, uh, uh--
Just tying my shoe.
You're not wearing
any, Fred.
Uh, uh, yeah.
Hey, now why don't we all
go dancing or something?
I'm too tired, Fred.
I think Barney and I
will call it a night.
See you
in the morning, Wilma.
Good night, Betty.
Uh, night, you two.
I'm not tired, Fred.
I'd love to go dancing.
You just made yourself
a date, honey.
We'll find ourselves
a good night club
and a great band,
and whip it up.
Oh, it sounds like fun.
Shh! It's me.
How did you
make out, Flintstone?
You gave me a bum
steer, Chief.
Nobody called me
Bubala.
Hmm. There's another
girl in the garden.
She may be
the right one.
OK, I'll go talk to her,
but first I gotta
keep Wilma busy.
Will we be staying out
late, Fred?
Uh, yeah.
Why don't you put Pebbles
in with Betty and Barney,
and then while
you're doing that
I'll phone ahead
and reserve a table.
All right. I'll wait
for you upstairs.
I'll be with you
in 5 minutes, honey,
not a second longer.
3, please.
Yes-a, ma'am.
Take her up, George.
Whoa, Matilda.
Third floor!
Isn't that sweet?
Pebbles is so tired,
she doesn't even
know you moved her.
Thanks, Betty.
I'll pick Pebbles up
in the morning.
♪ I know a way ♪
♪ To make wishes
come true ♪
♪ Easy as climbin'
a tree ♪
♪ Just close your eyes ♪
♪ And open your heart ♪
♪ Slowly repeat
after me ♪
BOTH: ♪ Tickle, toddle ♪
♪ Nickel-y noddle ♪
♪ Tootle a bell
and a shoe ♪
♪ These are the magical
words I sing ♪
♪ When I want a wish
to come true ♪
♪ I wish
that I could ♪
♪ Fly higher
than high ♪
♪ Out where
tomorrow begins ♪
♪ I'd slide down
the moonbeams ♪
♪ That glimmer
and glow ♪
♪ And follow
the rainbows ♪
♪ To see
where they go ♪
BOTH: ♪ Tickle, toddle ♪
♪ Nickel-y noddle ♪
♪ Tootle a bell
and a shoe ♪
♪ These are the magical
words I say ♪
♪ When I want a wish
to come true ♪
♪ Tickle, toddle ♪
♪ Nickel-y noddle ♪
BAM BAM: ♪ I wish that there
was a circus in town ♪
♪ And I was the star
of the show ♪
♪ Taming the lions
is one thing I do ♪
♪ And right from their cage
I'd be waving at you ♪
BOTH: ♪ Tickle, toddle ♪
♪ Nickel-y noddle ♪
♪ Tootle a bell
and a shoe ♪
♪ These are the magical
words I say ♪
♪ And all of my wishes
come true ♪
♪ Tickle, toddle ♪
♪ Nickel-y noddle ♪
♪ Tootle a bell
and a shoe ♪
I wonder where
that girl is.
Yoo-hoo!
It's me!
Rockello!
Oh, darling!
Oh,mio amore!
Uh, wait, wait!
Fifty fittering fitter fi!
Fifty fighty flim foos!
Fl-fl-fl--
I give up. Anyway,
you know why I'm here.
Oh, yes, my darling,
I know.
My brother Mario,
he's-a come here
for the wedding.
How nice!
Whose wedding?
Ours!
Well, I hope
you'll be very happy.
Ours?!
Let's-a go.
Where?
To get
the licence.
Uh...oh...sure.
Eh...after you,
my dear.
Hee hee hee hee. Oh...
Oh, we'll-a be so happy,
Rockello!
Rockello?
Mario,
Rockello, he's-a gone!
Have you found him
yet, Mario?
Not yet,
little sister.
Aha!
Stop!
Stop! This-a way,
Roberta!
This is far enough,
driver.
Oui, monsieur.
Hey, taxi!
Taxi!
Let's see...
Paris to Rome...
That will be 1 million
francs, monsieur.
How much?
How about for free,
oui?
Hey, taxi!
Wait for me!
All right, cabbie.
Beat it.
Wait! Hold that cab!
Wait! [Panting]
G-gentlemen...
please h-help me
get outta here.
There's a couple
after me
who think
I'm somebody else.
It's Rock Slag!
Ha ha! He doesn't
recognize us.
Must have took
too many knocks on the head.
Sure, mister!
We help you.
Yeah, yeah.
We'll hide you...
permanently.
Hee hee! Hee hee hee!
Hee hee! Hee hee!
I sure appreciate this,
fellas.
ROBERTA:
Rockello!
Blast off, fellas,
quick!
Darling!
Don't-a worry.
We follow.
Here they come!
And they're gaing
on us!
Faster, Mario!
Faster!
We'll lose them
on the steps.
Hang on!
No good!
They're still coming!
I make a fast left
up the next alley.
Here's one.
Hey, fellas!
Wait!
Oh, boy! I can't
stop this thing!
Uh-oh!
A tour of Rome
would be great
but this is ridiculous!
Help!
Rockello!
Here she comes!
Oh, brother.
What a spot to be in.
Don't stop. He must
be on that train!
They're gone. Now to
get back to the hotel.
Oh, no!
"Rome, 50 miles"?
And I told Wilma
I'd be back in 5 minutes.
Oh, boy.
6.00 in the morning.
How will I ever
explain this to Wilma?
Hey, bud.
Who, me?
Yeah, You.
Wanna buy
some genuine
Italian leopard
skin ties?
No, thanks.
I have a tie.
Shaving lotion,
nail clippers,
hubcaps,
fountain pens,
a gold watch?
I don't need anything.
Then how about something
for the little lady,
like a genuine imitation
diamond necklace, maybe?
A diamond necklace?
Are you sure it's a real
genuine imitation
diamond necklace?
I guarantee it.
Wow!
How much?
Would you consider
a dollar and a quarter?
75 cents?
It's yours
for 2 bits, bud.
I don't know if this'll
square me with Wilma,
but it's worth a try.
She'll probably
throw a lamp at me
the minute I walk in,
but here goes.
Wilma! Look, surprise.
I spent all night
shopping...for...it...
Well, what do you know?
She's asleep.
[Riiing]
Fred?
Morning, Wilma.
1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2--
Wha--wh--whe--
What time is it, Fred?
7.00 in the morning,
dear.
7.00? Oh, no!
I slept all night!
Why didn't you
wake me?
Aw, you looked
so comfortable,
I didn't have the heart to,
sweetheart.
Oh, Fred, I ruined
your whole evening!
I feel terrible!
Perfectly all right, honey.
Think nothing of it.
Oh, you're
so wonderful.
I'll fix some breakfast
while you get dressed.
OK, sweetheart.
Boy, that was close.
This spy job
is too much for me.
I gotta find the Chief
and quit.
Look, Fred. There's a park
across the street.
Let's take the children
there after breakfast.
Good idea. I'll tell
Barney and Betty about it.
I'll be right back,
Wilma.
Now to find Triple X.
He can take me
to the Chief.
What luck!
Here he comes.
I was just lookin'
for you, Triple X.
I gotta see the Chief.
Very important.
Yeeow!
Triple X is such
a master of disguise,
he could be anyone.
Excuse me, sonny.
Even an old lady.
Triple X, right?
Fresh.
[Baby cries]
Hey, Trip!
Take me to the Chief,
will ya?
Well, he's not up here.
I'll take the elevator
down to the lobby.
Flintstone!
Chief!
How did you find
my secret headquarters?
Secret?
In an elevator?
Get in here, quick!
OK, OK.
I wanna talk to you,
Chief.
Hold it, Flintstone.
This room may be bugged.
Bugged?
Nothing there.
Chief, I'm quittin'
this job right now.
You can't quit.
Not before you pick up
the Green Goose.
Oh, anybody
can pick up a bird.
You don't need me
for that.
Quiet.
[Beep beep beep beep]
How about that?
They had my bed bugged!
All right, Flintstone.
I see I'm going to have
to level with you.
What do you mean?
I mean the Green Goose
is not a bird.
He's a master criminal
who plans to take over
the world!
Why don't you
arrest him?
No one knows who he is
or what he looks like.
But you can find out.
Me?! How?
Through a girl
named Tanya
who thinks
you're Rock Slag.
The minute she identifies
the Green Goose,
I'll grab him,
and your job is done.
How about it,
Flintstone?
Nothin' doin'!
Too dangerous!
I got a family
to think of--
Pebbles' future!
If we don't stop
the Green Goose,
Pebbles won't have
a future.
Sorry, Chief.
You'll have to get
somebody else.
Oh, look at those
children, Fred.
They're having the time
of their lives!
BARNEY: Ha ha ha!
Why not?
They got nothin'
to worry about.
Right, Fred?
Huh?
I said those kids got
nothin' to worry about.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I wonder...
♪ Someday ♪
♪ I'm gonna be
a great doctor ♪
♪ And cure every
deadly disease ♪
♪ You wait and see ♪
♪ I'm gonna help
other children ♪
♪ Like me ♪
♪ When I am grown up ♪
♪ You'll see ♪
♪ We know that some day ♪
♪ We will do great things ♪
♪ When we are grown up ♪
♪ You'll see ♪
♪ We know when
we're grown up ♪
♪ And not so small ♪
♪ We're gonna do
great things ♪
♪ You'll see ♪
♪ and show them all ♪
♪ Someday ♪
♪ I'm gonna be
a great farmer ♪
♪ And grow lots of
good things to eat ♪
♪ Won't that be neat? ♪
♪ No one will ever
go hungry again ♪
♪ Not when I'm grown up ♪
♪ Not then ♪
♪ We know that some day ♪
♪ We will do great things ♪
♪ When we are grown up ♪
♪ You'll see ♪
♪ We know when
we're grown up ♪
♪ And not so small ♪
♪ We're gonna do
great things ♪
♪ You'll see ♪
♪ and show them all ♪
♪ Some day ♪
♪ I'm gonna be
a great teacher ♪
♪ And teach everybody
to read ♪
♪ That's what we need ♪
♪ People who read
aren't so easy to fool ♪
♪ So I will teach them ♪
♪ In school ♪
♪ We know that some day ♪
♪ We will do great things ♪
♪ When we are grown up ♪
♪ You'll see ♪
♪ Someday ♪
♪ Some day ♪
♪ You'll see ♪
♪ Someday ♪
♪ I'm gonna be ♪
Isn't it wonderful
the way kids
get along together?
Yeah. We adults could take
a lesson from them.
What do we do now, Fred,
some sightseeing?
Fred? Do you hear me?
What?
Oh, uh, yeah, yeah.
Good idea.
You, uh...go ahead
and enjoy yourselves.
But aren't you coming
with us?
No. I got some
unfinished business
to take care of.
So long, honey.
See you later.
My, he's acting
strange.
I wonder what's
wrong?
I knew you'd change
your mind, Flintstone.
You're A-OK.
Are you sure this
is the right girl?
Absolutely.
You're having lunch
with her
at Papa Piccolo's
Pizza Palace.
Here we are, Flintstone.
Let's go inside.
There she is. Tanya.
The girl
who will lead us
to the Green Goose's
hideout.
Rrr! She's a doll.
Your job will be simpler
than we thought, Flintstone.
Rock Slag has recovered
and will be here within a hour.
All you have to do is keep
Tanya here until he arrives.
Think you can do it?
It'll be a cinch.
I'll order everything
on the menu.
Wait. I want you to wear
this recorder.
Recorder?
Yes. We wanna take down
everything Tanya says.
I'm glad I had
my beak sharpened.
Tanya may be
a real yacker.
This flower
is the microphone.
And remember,
keep her talking
until the real Rock Slag
takes over.
Gotcha, Chief.
BETTY:
Oh, how exciting!
The famous Papa Piccolo's
Pizza Palace.
Let's go in
and have some lunch.
Poor Fred. It's a shame
he isn't here.
Fifty flying
firefighters?
Mmm...
Bubala!
Ha ha ha.
Hello, Tanya.
Rock Slag.
At last we meet.
May I sit down?
Is that wise?
We should leave at once.
Oh, plenty of time.
Let's have
a little talk first
about, uh...
you know who.
Oh, the Green Goose.
He's a terrible man!
Do you know
he has a secret weapon
more powerful
than any?
A little louder, please,
and speak into
the flower.
How cute. I will
wear it in my hair.
No, no, no.
Allow me to get you
a fresh flower.
I'll be right back.
Toodle-oo!
Fred!
Wilma!
What are you
doing here?
And who are you
waving at?
Wa-wa-waving?
Who--who's waving?
Oh, that! Ha ha ha!
It's just a loose wrist.
I thought you had
some unfinished business
to take care of.
Well, I do.
That is, I finished.
I took a chance
you might be here,
so...ha ha...
here I am.
Oh, how nice!
Well, sit down,
Fred.
Yeah!
Join the party.
Huh? Oh, yeah. yeah.
Will you excuse me
a minute?
It's kinda drafty
in here.
I'll go close
the window.
Sorry. I couldn't
find a flower.
Oh, that's all right.
It's kinda drafty
in here.
I'll go close
the window. Excuse me.
What took you
so long, dear?
I was stuck.
I mean the window was stuck.
Well,
should we order?
Yeah. Good idea.
Uh-oh.
Excuse me!
Tanya, what are you
doing?
Getting my wrap.
We must leave!
Look, t-the orchestra's
gettin' ready to play.
Let's dance.
Well...maybe just
once.
[Slow song starts]
I'd sure like
to dance.
I wonder where Fred is.
Uh-oh.
What are you doing,
Rock?
In this business,
you can't be too careful.
[Upbeat song starts]
It's Fred!
I didn't know you
wanted to dance, honey.
Wilma!
Uh-oh!
Oh, you dance divinely,
darling.
So do you, dear.
Dear?
Darling?
Come on, Tiger.
Let's get out of here.
Tiger?
So that's it!
That's your
unfinished business.
L-l-look, Wilma,
I--I can explain
everything.
I wish you would.
I've been going crazy down there
trying to record it.
There's nothing
to explain.
It's all
very obvious!
Wilma, please,
won't ya listen?
I'm going home...Tiger!
Hey, Flintstone.
Rock Slag's cab
is arriving.
Go get Tanya.
You can switch with Slag
in the lobby. Hurry!
Taxi!
Allow me, madame.
Don't you get smart
with me, Fred Flintstone!
So we see you in your
true colours, you playboy!
How could you do that
to the mother of your child?
Consider our friendship
ended!
You playboy!
Rock! Oh, no,
not again.
You powder your nose,
Tanya.
I'll wait for ya
in the lobby.
All set, Chief.
Where's Rock?
Right there.
What happened?
He must have had
a relapse.
Look!
Rock Slag!
Quick, upstairs!
Looks like you're going
to have to carry the ball
a little longer, Flintstone.
Me? I gotta go home and
square myself with Wilma!
No time for that now!
I just got this message.
Listen.
"Green Goose
secret weapon
"is giant inter-rockinental
missile.
our anti-missile missile
is not operational yet."
So you see, it's up to us
to stop the Green Goose!
Us? What do you mean
us?
You go with Tanya
to the Green Goose's hideout.
I'll phone Triple X,
and we'll follow
right behind you.
Now just a minute.
That wasn't the deal--
I'm ready, Rock.
Let's go.
But--but--but--but---
Oh, boy.
Hello, operator?
Hello, hello?
Operator, are you there?
[Crash]
Hee hee! Hee hee!
Hee hee hee hee!
Right on target,
Bobo.
Thanks, Ali.
Now we get Rock Slag.
No time. First we must
take message to Green Goose.
Good idea, Ali.
Green Goose will be proud
of us. Bwa ha ha ha!
Here we are, Rock.
The Green Goose's
secret headquarters.
An abandoned
amusement park.
Pretty clever.
OK, Rock.
Now what?
Follow me.
Follow me, Chief,
wherever you are.
Why do you keep
looking behind you?
Oh, I just wanted
to make sure
we were being
followed.
I mean...we'renotbeing followed.
Heh heh heh. Eh...
The Green Goose
is in there.
I'll go in first
and get behind him.
Then when you come in,
I will drop this rope
over him.
Count to 5
before you break in.
OK.
1...2...
3...4...
5. Let's go, Chief!
We're movin' in!
All right, Goose!
You're cooked!
Ah...Mr Slag!
Nice of you to drop in.
Shall I tie him up?
That won't be necessary.
Ferocious
wouldn't like it
if Mr Slag
tried to leave.
Would you, Ferocious?
[Growls]
Hey, what is this?
What's goin' on, Tanya?
My dear Rock,
the Green Goose
needs some information.
So we set up
this little trap for you.
Surprised?
A double cross, huh?
Well, now I have
a surprise for you!
OK, Chief, come in!
Oh, uh,
there you are.
Barney!
Yeah, Barney.
I followed you here.
I'm not leaving until
I get some information!
Exactly what I was saying.
Hey, who are you,
buster?
And why are you
wearing this--
[Rrr]
Eh, ahem, look, Goose,
this guy is just
a friend of mine.
Why don't you
let him go?
Oh, come now, Mr Slag,
you know that's impossible!
Mr Slag?
Who's that?
That's me.
I'll explain later.
GOOSE: Slag?
I know your government
has been working on
an anti-missile missile.
I want to know
if they have completed it.
I don't know anything
about it.
GOOSE: I'd advise you
to cooperate.
I'd hate to resort
to using
unpleasant methods.
[Grrr]
Unpleasant methods?
What's going on?
This guy is
a master criminal
and I'm helping
the government capture him.
But don't worry.
Our agents will
bust in any minute.
You don't scare me,
Goose.
No?
What about your
chubby friend?
Uh-oh. I, uh...
I just rembered
I--I double parked outside.
I'll be right back.
Ferocious!
[Grrr]
[Grrr--grrr-grrr]
[Evil laughter]
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh!
GOOSE: Not yet, Ferocious.
I may need him.
Tanya!
Show them
the torture chamber!
[Creak]
These are some
of my toys,
but I want you to see
my latest one.
It's called
anerocktric chair.
We strap you in
and...
Quite effective,
isn't it?
Ab-bout my car.
I--I left my lights
on, too.
Can I turn 'em off?
Take it easy, Barn.
Help will be here
any second.
You'll get nothin'
out of me, Green Goose!
I knew it would be useless
to even try withyou, Slag,
but your chubby
little friend
is another story,
isn't he?
Heh heh heh.
Tanya, the rack!
FRED: Hey! Hey!
What are you doin'
to Barney?!
Perhaps when you see what
happens to your friend
you'll tell me what
I want to know.
Yeow!
You can't intimidate me
with these crude methods.
I'm intimi-nated!
Yeow!
Talk, Slag.
Never!
BARNEY: Yeow!
Talk!
No!
BARNEY: Yeow!
Don't worry, Barn.
All we gotta do is
stall him a little longer.
My lips are sealed, Goose!
BARNEY: Yeow!
Slag, you're
superhuman.
I've never met
anyone like you.
Zounds! How much pain
can a man stand?
All you can dish out
and more.
BARNEY: Yeow!
Don't worry, Barney.
I can take it.
You ain't takin' it.
I am!
You're gonna come outta this
abig man!
And a thin one, too!
[Knock, knock]
At last!
It's about time.
I was beginnin'
to think
you wouldn't
show up.
Chief?
If you're expecting
Chief Boulder, he's out--
out cold for the evening.
That's right.
And we found
this message on him.
Hmm...
"Green Goose
secret weapon
"is giant
inter-rockinental missile.
our anti-missile missile
is not operational yet."
Ha ha ha ha!
Good work, Ali.
Release the prisoner, Tanya.
I have the information
I need.
Lock those two up
and prepare to launch missile.
Nobody can stop me now!
Mwa ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha ha ha!
So that's the way
it was, Barney.
Just because I happen
to look like Rock Slag,
I got the plane tickets,
money, everything,
and I also got you
into this mess--
my best friend.
Well, uh,
could be worse, Fred.
At least Betty and Wilma
and the kids are OK.
Yeah. I wonder if we'll
ever see 'em again.
Hey, Slag!
Chowtime!
Hee hee! Hee hee!
Hee hee hee hee!
Oh, boy, food.
Oh, I'm starved.
[Slurp]
Fred: Barney!
Don't eat that stuff!
I couldn't
if I wanted to, Fred.
No spoon.
Looks like
the Green Goose
is tryin' to get rid
of us, Barney.
We've gotta get outta
here and find that missile.
Oh, I wonder
where it could be.
Enh heh heh
heh heh heh heh!
The Fun House.
I hope our guests are
enjoying their last moments.
This amusement park
is the perfect
launching spot.
Who would think
that the space ride
isreallya deadly missile?
No one.
Now, let's prepare
to launch.
Hey--hey, Fred,
you sure you know
what you're doin'?
This tower
is 100-feet high,
and you've got
an awful short tie.
Don't worry.
We'll make it.
Oh, e-easy, Fred.
Howya doin', Barn?
You think you can jump
the rest of the way?
Are you kiddin'?
Pull me up!
Uh-oh!
He-elp!
Faster, Barney!
Faster!
Hurry, Barney!
Hurry!
Oh, nice goin', Fred.
You nearly
got me killed.
What are you
complain' about?
That was my best tie
you ruined.
Oh, sorry, Fred.
Guess we never
will get outta here.
Hey, Barney, look.
What is it?
The guards--
They're asleep, and the key
is hangin' on the desk.
So what good
does that--
Shh! Quiet.
Oh, uh, sorry, Fred,
but, uh, how are we
gonna get the key?
[WHISPERING] That's what
we gotta figure out.
Hey, would you mind
speakin' a little louder?
I can't hear a word
you're saying.
Well, whaddya know?
The tape recorder.
How would you like to
do us a little favour?
What kind of
a little favour?
Oh, nothin' much.
You see that key?
What about it?
Just fly over there
and bring it back
to me.
Unh-uh.
I'm a recorder,
not a retriever.
But you've got to.
It's our only chance
to get outta here.
All right, All right,
simmer down.
I'll give it a try.
Shh! Turn around.
Whoops!
Oh, no!
Sorry, it slipped.
But don't worry.
I'll get it.
Just put me down and relax.
What's he gonna do,
Fred?
Beats me.
RECORDER:
Whoa! I'm hurt!
The old wing is shot.
Woe is me!
I can't fly anymore.
Never again to zoom
into the wild blue.
Isn't that
an awful thing
to happen
to poor little me?
[Grrr]
Get ready!
Here comes the pigeon!
[Grr]
Come on, bird!
Come on!
Open up!
Barney, I got it!
I got the key!
I just hope the union
never hears about this.
[Muffled yells]
Hold it, Barney.
That door might lead
to a trap.
You better
let me check first.
OK, Fred.
It's OK, Barn. Come on.
Barney, where are you?
Let me go! Let me go!
Take it easy, Rock.
It's only me,
Triple X.
Oh, boy, am I glad
to see you.
Where ya been?
What took you so long?
Where's the Chief?
One question
at a time, please.
Sorry.
Here. You dropped
your hat...
and your hanky.
Hey, that's funny,
Triple X.
The Green Goose was
wearin' a mask like this.
He was? What
a very clever disguise,
don't you think?
Now, may I have it back,
please?
You mean...
this is your mask?
Heh heh heh heh...
heh heh heh heh!
Yes, exactly.
Boo-hoo hoo hoo hoo!
Then you're--
you're the Green Goose.
And you're a dead duck.
Ali, Bobo, over here!
Oh, no, you don't!
Come back, you!
Never mind!
I'm going to
fire the missile.
Come on.
Hee hee! Hee hee hee!
Hee hee! Hee hee!
Ha ha ha!
BO: Oh, boy!
Big fireworks.
ALI: Whole world
go boom!
Hee hee! Hee hee hee!
Hee hee! Hee hee!
The missile.
I gotta stop 'em!
I wonder where Barney is.
Maybe he could--
He-elp!
[Grr]
Take it easy,
Ferocious.
Can't we sorta
talk this over?
[Grr--]
Fred, oh, boy,
am I glad to see you.
Ferocious wasn't gonna
wait till lunchtime.
Come on, Barney.
There's no time to lose.
[Green Goose cackles]
This is the big moment,
gentlemen.
First, I set
the directional control.
Then I set
the firing pin.
When the countdown
reaches zero,
The blade will snap back,
cut the rope,
and the missile
will take off.
Oh, Goose,
you are a genius.
Oh, you are so right.
In a matter of minutes,
the whole world
will know of my power,
and I alone shall rule
supreme.
[Buzz]
Ah ha ha ha ha ha!
We've got to find
that missile, Barney.
It's all up to us now.
Hey, Fred, look--
The Green Goose.
Hold on, Barney!
We're crashin' through.
Stop them, Bobo!
Right.
Ahh...Mr Slag,
We meet again.
But too late
for you to stop me!
Run, Barney! Run!
Head for the space ride,
Barney.
We can hide in there.
Oh! It's locked.
Uh, press
the button.
[Buzz]
Inside, quick.
Green Goose: Don't
open that door!
Our friends have
trapped themselves
in the missile.
Well, we no longer
need concern ourselves
with them.
Hey, didya hear that,
Fred?
Yeah, Barney.
We found the missile.
Well--well,
what can we do?
Nothin' to save ourselves,
but we can aim the missile
into space,
where it won't do any harm.
At least that's somethin'.
Oh, boy. Payload
in an interplanetary
projectile.
Oh! What a way
to go!
They say we all gotta go
sometime, Barn.
Too bad I'll
never get the chance
to give Wilma
this present.
Wow, Fred,
where'd you get that?
BARNEY: It must
be worth millions!
Huh?
Nah. No, it's
only worth, uh...
uh...
It's only worthone million.
Just think, Barney--
we'll be the richest guys
in space.
A million!
Slag! Heh heh heh!
I'll make a deal
with you.
I'll swap you
your lives
for that
necklace.
On your toes, Barn.
It's a deal.
[Buzz]
Hand it out.
Here you are!
[Crash]
[Thud]
Yii! Ali! Bobo!
Tanya! Help!
[Buzz]
Let--let me out!
No, no! Let me out!
Help!
Well, that's
what always happens
to guys who want
to take over the world.
Yeah. Heh heh heh!
They end up
out of it.
And with great pride,
we, the citizens
of Bedrock,
present you
with this medal.
[Cheering]
[Signal beeping]
ANNOUNCER: After a week
of parties, parades,
and speeches,
public hero Fred Flintstone
has slipped away
for a well-earned rest.
Only clue
as to his whereabouts
is a note saying
"Gone fishing."
Oh, it feels
so good to relax.
Yeah. It's been
one parade after another.
My Fred, a big hero.
Oh, I'm so proud of you.
Oh...hee hee!
Forget the hero stuff.
Forget everything
that happened in Eurock.
From now on, I am
just Fred Flintstone,
average citizen.
Besides, Barney deserves
as much credit as I do.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I deserve as much
credit as Fred.
Well, now, wait
a minute, Barn.
I was the one that--
Ha ha!
[Girls laugh]
Aw...ha ha ha!
Now, cut it out,
cut it out.
Hey, come on, Fred.
Last one
down to the lake
is a pickled
pterodactyl!
Hey...
yabba dabba do!
Here I am, pal!
Rockello!
Hey...eh,paesano!
Roberta! Mario!
Gangway!
After him, quick!
Wilma, help!
Rockello!
Hey,paesano,wait!
"Rockello? Paesano"?
What's going on?
I don't know,
but I have a feeling
that Fred
isn't going to forget
his trip to Eurock
in a hurry.
Help! Help!
Somebody,
do something!
Rockello,
come-a back!
Hey, come back here,peasan!
Help! Help!
Oh, we're gonna
get-a married!
MARIO: And-a go on
a nice-a honeymoon.
[Sobbing] Help!
Help!
Rockello!
Wilma!
♪ Who do they call ♪
♪ When the chips
are startin' to fall ♪
♪ Just when the villains
are wailin' ♪
♪ The troubles
beginnin' to brew? ♪
♪ The man called Flintstone ♪
♪ That's who ♪
♪ Who is the man ♪
♪ Who seems more
than merely a man ♪
♪ Who chases characters shady ♪
♪ While every lady melts? ♪
♪ The man called Flintstone ♪
♪ Who else? ♪
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org