[Music]
so
[Applause]
hmm
[Music]
hi this is angela please leave a message
at the beep
rise and shine sweetheart i know you're
listening
wake up wake up i'll just sing
until you pick up when i'm
calling you i'm up i'm awake
what time is it don't you own a clock
no and my rooster died no what a killer
i just called you to remind you about
your interview what interview
the one with chuck erin oh don't tell me
you forgot about your deadline
calm down calm down baxter i remember i
remember
where am i supposed to meet him you run
this far
every day 10 miles every day even when
i'm on location
you know every time i'm interviewed by
women they can't keep their hands off me
so try to control myself watch your step
got to stay on your toes how do you
respond to critics who say your movie's
glamorized war
ah they're full over the bed
like i was saying critics don't know
anything my pictures make millions of
dollars you want to know why
no yes because i represent the american
ideal
meat and potatoes monday night football
two cars in every garage
that's why i stay in shape people won't
buy me killing commies with a fat
[Music]
your political views made it difficult
for you to film in foreign countries
well yeah but well i can't help their
porn pointers
like we were shooting lost in combat
part six in the philippines
they got offended just because i
wouldn't eat that rice and fish craft
they served down there
so i have prime rib flowing in every day
around the tree huh
i send you out to talk to a popular
action star
and you massacre the guy i massacred him
listen to this aaron pushes u.s
supremacy to a point that makes john
wayne look like a liberal
just a casual observation oh really
well what about here where you refer to
him as a sexist
pig i call him as i see him
i wanted an interview not a barbecue
angela sweetheart hollywood beat is an
entertainment magazine
so just hold all the politics for the
editorial page
baxter you don't have an editorial page
precisely
[Music]
what happened to your face i cut myself
shaving
i find it becoming so when can i expect
the rewrite
look i can give it to one of the guys to
do you don't think you're gonna handle
it
when do you want it you're late
[Music]
[Applause]
what the hell do you think you're doing
oh i'm just doing some repairs in here
look what you did to my wall
yes i'm i'm real sorry about that you
know what you ought to do
you ought to talk to the manager
sure is a nice place you got here
y'all have a good day now here oh there
ain't no rest of the working class
boss
mr carrillo what is going on here
we were earthquake-proofing singularity
oh is that so
well some neanderthal just installed a
porthole in my living room
what what do you mean knock the hole in
my wall
don't you worry sir that will fix it oh
you bet you'll fix it
how long is all this gonna take oh that
should be done in one more week
what about all this noise it's okay they
go home at six
but i work at home during the day i am a
freelance writer company
i think i'd prefer the earthquake
hello aunt sarah this is angela
angela your niece who else would call
you aunt sarah
yes yes i know it's very noisy in here
that's why i'm calling you
do you still have that house up in
malibu the one that used to belong to
your half sister
can i uh use it for the next week or so
oh that's terrific you don't know how
much this means to me great i will drive
up first thing in the morning
thanks bye
[Applause]
oh great
[Music]
i've been waiting for so long
for
[Music]
i've been known to be cruel in my ways
you can make
[Music]
[Applause]
uh
[Music]
who are you what are you doing here i i
i was asleep
and and you woke me up okay so who are
you
my my name is b.j and i work for the
owner of this place
aunt sarah yeah that's the one aunt
sarah
hey you related to her i'm angela
angela reed i'm gonna be staying here
what happened to you know is you run
into a telephone pole
no a tree oh cool
my sentiments exactly
so tell me what do you do around here i
stop around every few days chase the
dust around
i'll make sure nobody ripped the place
off aunt sarah doesn't spend much time
here
are you kidding no way why
you mean you don't know what happened
here
oh wow well i know this place used to
belong to her half sister
half sister
the one and only billy blaine goddess of
the silver screen
excuse me for living she was a little
before your time wasn't she
i watched the late late show hey and
there was nobody else like her
she had the sexy voice and this awesome
bod
and this unbelievable set of cones
cones you know cones
but diddies bazookas yeah right and it
was in this very house that back in 1962
billy blaine at the height of her career
snuffed herself you mean she
bought the farm bit the big one she ate
a whole bottle of barbies and went for a
swim face down
and sarah never told me there was a
suicide here
why do you think she doesn't come around
here she can't even sell this place
ah right you're not trying to tell me
this place is haunted
i didn't say that
then what are you saying nothing
you want a pearl bj do i look like the
kind of guy who believes in ghosts
you look like you'd believe in the loch
ness monster
this monster i liked it this
okay okay it's just that
some people not me but
some people have seen and heard things
around here
what kind of things you know the usual
weird noises and things like that
and sometimes like right around dawn
people say that they've seen this
beautiful blonde running out of the
house
down the steps onto the beach
and she takes off her nightgown
and she disappears into the surf
hey whoa ho watch out there it's it's
nothing it's nothing
you're a little nervous aren't you oh me
oh no no it just
took me by surprise that's all but i
gotta get going
i'll stop back in a few days
but if you need me before then my
number's on the refrigerator
thanks okay oh yeah and one more thing
yeah watch out for the ghost
oh
[Music]
so
hello
[Music]
hello is anybody there
ah
[Music]
[Applause]
so
whoever's in there you better give
yourself up got a gun
i won't hesitate to shoot
i have had just about enough of you for
one night miss blaine
i am going for a walk
[Music]
[Applause]
people say that they've seen this
beautiful blonde
running out of the house down the steps
onto the beach and she takes off her
nightgown
and she disappears into the surface
[Music]
oh
take it easy i'm not gonna hurt you i'm
just walking my dog
see
i i'm sorry i yelled i'm tom farrell
see um why are you crawling around out
there
did you lose something no i was
following some footprints
footprints you mean these
no no those are mine these were
they were right there they led from the
steps at the back of my house out to the
water
and i was [ __ ]
[Music]
hi i'm angela reid nice to meet you
what are you doing not playing indian
scout
i'm a writer hey no kidding so am i
i work for the hair help oh it's a
really good paper
i think so i'm on vacation spending a
few weeks at the beach
how about you me no i'm i'm working
oh yeah which paper well actually it's a
magazine
hollywood beat oh but sounds like fun
yeah loads of laughs say
if you freeze some night maybe we could
go for a drink
maybe dinner yeah i don't know i'm kind
of busy oh come on
you can't ride around the clock what
about
okay maybe great
so how do i reach you
i'm right up there you must have some
electric bill
hey wait a minute isn't that the billy
blaine ghost house
what is it with everyone around here do
you all believe in the boogeyman
i didn't mean anything it just happens
to be a well-known landmark that's all
yeah that's what i love about this town
some freaked out starlet decides to kill
herself and everyone wants to build a
legend around i think it's disgusting
what did i say
nothing
careful you don't want to do that again
it's good meeting the neighbors isn't it
girl
ugh
[Music]
there
foreign
[Music]
so
wow
[Music]
hmm
i didn't mean to frit to fritten
to frighten you please help me
billy blaine
dj i want to talk to you bj that's it
bj oh man now look what i did i gave her
three nipples
hey maybe she looks better with three
what do you think i'd say you're
indulging in some wishful thinking
listen bj bj i have a
serious question to ask you and if such
a thing
is possible i really would like a
serious answer okay
okay shoot did you for
any reason go back to the beach house
last night
no you sure sure i'm sure i don't forget
things like that
then who wrote this
oh wow where did you get this
i found it on the table next to my
typewriter oh
wow
[Music]
boy when you said you were a fan you
weren't kidding hey ever since i saw in
the gilded goddess
i was hooked here it is the real thing
when i was a kid back east
i traded my entire baseball card
collection for this
see the same wow
i told you the place is haunted
[Applause]
[Music]
why start smoking now
i'm gonna break they say it's supposed
to calm you down you know it's very
oh so what so quit while you're ahead
what do you
wow is that my conscience talking to me
[Music]
all right all right who said that
who is it answer me no
[Music]
who is it come on you know who it is
no i don't yes you do no i don't of
course you do silly
it's me
[Music]
oh no no no no no no this is not
happening to me
i must be dreaming that's that's it i am
dreaming i'm dreaming
this isn't a dream yes it is no it isn't
[Music]
okay prove it all right i'll prove it
but you've got to promise me that you
won't get scared
okay okay i promise okay here goes
nothing hi
he promised you wouldn't get scared okay
so i lied
i'm not going to hurt you what do you
want
i've been trying to contact you didn't
you get my message last night
yes i did sometimes i get so lonely
i could scream please don't i don't
think i could handle that again
gosh no i wouldn't do that after all
i need your help how can i help you
my spirit is stuck here on earth until i
discover how i died
probable suicide just doesn't cut it
actually i was hoping they'd send
someone different you know
tall dark handsome
but since you're a relative and all i
guess you're it
is that supposed to be good news
someone's coming wait wait don't go
hi what's going on oh nothing nothing
why do you ask
no reason hey are you okay
you look like you've just seen a ghost
funny you should say that
mind if i come in
you sure i'm not interrupting anything
do you believe in life after death
uh i don't know
yeah yeah yeah i guess so then you think
it's
possible that a person's spirit could
come back and visit the living
well i don't know about that those
things don't happen every day
i beg your pardon what would you do if
the ghost of a famous movie star
appeared in front of you right now
well uh i'd ask about her life her
career
and then i'd get her phone number tom
i'm serious
it wouldn't make one hell of an article
though
yeah i hadn't thought of that yeah sure
imagine what it would be like to
interview a ghost
say the ghost of napoleon einstein or
hitler
well maybe not hitler but you get my
drift
i sure do but of course um
we can't talk to the dead
[Music]
no of course not it'd be nice if we
could but we
don't we can't listen it was so nice of
you to stop by we really should do this
again sometime uh
yeah hey hey you want to go for a drink
i'd love to i'm really busy right now
i i didn't mean now i meant later later
sure i'd loved this great guy
billy billy
that girl is nuts cute but nuts
[Music]
hello there you hello yourself
it's you course silly who'd you expect
it's good to see you it's good to see
you too angela
billy there was something i wanted to
talk to you about really
what well i can wait until you're
finished in here okay
boom oh lily don't sneak up on me like
that
i didn't sneak i faded in well
don't fade in behind me okay
sorry so uh
what did you want to talk to me about
you said you wanted me to help you free
your
spirit right right and the way to do
that
is to find out what happened to you that
night right
i'm gonna need some background billy i
would like to interview you for
hollywood beat
really what's hollywood beat
it's kind of a fan magazine oh they used
to write about me all the time
hey this isn't some kind of a joke is it
crossed my heart and hoped it
honest oh this is going to be just crazy
like the good old days when do we get
started
i was in this hotel on the riviera
locked out on the balcony with nothing
on but my goodwill
i climbed onto the balcony next door and
ran
into this simply creamy banker smack in
the middle of the wall street journal
boy was he ever surprised he never even
got to finish his paper
did you get all that
oh will you look at him
billy what is it with you and men i just
love them that's all
short ones tall ones thin ones fat ones
didn't you ever have any friends you
know female friends
not really you're my first one ever
auntie i don't know what i would have
done if you hadn't come along
life sure doesn't prepare you for being
dead
that almost sounded profound
so what about you who is that guy who is
here before
you mean tom he's just someone i met
so do you like him i don't know maybe
angie either you do or you don't so what
if i do
well you might show it a little just
because i like guy doesn't mean i have
to
throw myself at him who said anything
about throwing yourself at him
if you play it right i'll jump you
billy it's almost 1990.
women are different today
hey you want to go for a walk
billy how did you
you know what
i i know it wasn't suicide was it
hey i didn't mean to upset you i just
want to know
[Music]
i wish i could tell you well if you
don't want to talk about it believe me
i'll understand
no it's not that you see
i've tried and tried to remember what
happened that night
it just it just keeps coming at blank
you don't remember anything
everything before is crystal clear
then kaflui
good louie uh-huh
i'm dead and i don't even know how or
why
all i know is i'm stuck here and i can't
leave
really honey it's not so bad
that's easy for you to say hey you still
got your looks
everyone wonders what's gonna happen to
them after they're gone but
you you already know sure it's
not a picnic but at least it's better
than nothing
[Music]
billy billy
billy think you are i was wondering
where you'd gone
come on over here take a look at what
i've written so far
[Music]
billy billy come back
sorry excuse me
billy blaine in her own words
what happened to chuck aaron's story i
got a little sidetracked
wow that's completely irresponsible i
mean i'm putting this new issue to press
tonight
angela how could you do this to me just
put billy blaine in place of rambo jr
she's a lot more interesting believe me
she has been dead for more than 25 years
i know that i ran across an old diary of
hers in the house i'm staying at
an old diary you know this whole thing
is starting to sound like something out
of nancy drew
are you feeling all right does it sound
like it i'll be back in a minute
so what did you think of our story what
are you doing here i wanted to come
along
i haven't been anywhere since 1962. you
haven't
no every time i tried to leave the house
it felt like someone nailed my shoes to
the floor
but when i'm with you it's different i
just got in the car and
came along that's nice billy but you
can't stay somebody is gonna see you
oh no no one can see me unless i want
them to right now you're the only one
who can
oh well just keep it that way and don't
say anything either okay
okay angela
are you talking to yourself no
i was talking to my imaginary playmate
baxter say hello
oh nice to see you pal putting on a
little weight aren't you oh rude why i
never
so um what about the piece
angela sweetheart this blame name is old
news
she's history i am not
she's more than history she's a
hollywood legend
yes think about it baxter you could be
the first to publish her long-lost
autobiography which you just happened to
find after all
these years oh come on there's something
fishy about this whole thing
besides nobody is interested in reading
crap like that
[Music]
crap no
angela you can't let him treat you like
that
[Music]
baxter you can't treat me like that
what you can take hollywood beat and
stick it that's telling him
if you're not interested in the article
there are many other magazines who will
be
so put that in your pipe and smoke it
buster oh
come on you wouldn't do that to me try
me
yeah try it all right all right all
right sit down will you please
we can talk about this so
you'll do it as a series maybe all right
at double the normal rate hey you're
pretty sharp
that well i don't have money like that
no problem
all right all right all right okay well
you drive a hard bargain
there you go this should fit right in
the spot you save for the chuck aaron
peace
see you next issue
[Music]
oh my god i gotta teach you not to talk
that way about a lake
just get away get just get away please
look at this it becomes you
[Music]
really the new issue of hollywood beat
is here well let me see
whoa a cover story baxter
billy blaine in her own words by angela
reed with an
uncredited assist from me pretty good
for a ghost writer
yeah can i read it first please sure go
ahead
hello miss reed yes
i was told i could reach you there i
just finished your article in hollywood
beat
[Music]
what about it i'm very interested in
purchasing the diary of billy blaine
i'm sorry but it's not for sale who is
this
miss reed i'm sure you know perfectly
well who this is
i'm also sure that you know that i'd be
willing to pay handsomely for it
this is murray over at tinseltown isn't
it my offer is 25
000 for you to drop your story and hand
over the diary
hey look i don't know what magazine
you're with but in any case my answer is
no
well i'm sorry you don't want to
cooperate miss reed nevertheless i am
going to get that diary
it just would have been so much simpler
for you this way
[Music]
well looks like we're going to have to
do things the old-fashioned way
who is that on the phone i don't know
probably just a crank call
hey i've got an idea why don't we go out
to a club tonight do you mean it
sure the first installment's already out
the second one isn't due for a couple of
weeks
we owe ourselves a break ah that would
be just swell
i wonder what i should wear well what do
you think
[Music]
i think it would be great if we were
going to the academy awards
is it really too much or too little
depending on how you look at it
well i really don't know what's in
fashion these days oh don't worry about
it billy
besides no one can see you let's just go
out there and have a great time
i can't if i look yucky trust me you
don't look yucky
[Music]
she's talking to herself so what you
talk to yourself
oh i don't you should do it i do not
[Music]
hey she's taking off get the diary
i don't talk to myself just shut up all
right
[Music]
what am i gonna do about you
i've never seen anything like this
aren't you forgetting that you're a
ghost
a flying pinky dinky straight up make it
two make it two please
okay what's in those anyway
never mind
[Music]
it'll be seven dollars 11 bucks for two
drinks
holy cow welcome to the 80s huh
[Music]
nothing
there's mud in your eye
[Music]
come on angie don't hatch
you don't want it honey it's all yours
[Music]
hey what's the big idea do you want to
cause a panic in here
use a straw oh all right
[Music]
me
try not to drink so fast will you oh
don't be such a killer killjoy
i can hold my liquor better than anyone
hey miss reed oh no i didn't expect to
see you here what's going on
oh nothing i'm just hanging out here by
myself
yeah just call me a
two-fisted drinker cool
you mind if i sit down no i really would
be
i've been thinking about that letter you
got you know the one from billy blaine
i think she was trying to make contact
with you
oh yeah oh no doubt about it but
i got this idea you see what if you were
to hook up your typewriter to a ouija
board
then you you could ask her things and
the ouija board could type out the
answers
how would you hook the two together
i don't know i haven't figured that part
out yet
maybe uh if you uh
well if you hooked it up to a lightning
round and
and held the seance during the storm
that would never work it never rains in
california
so how do you like this place
would you just excuse me for a minute um
nice guns
[Music]
check this out already or what no you're
supposed to look in the closet okay i
didn't know it's a closet
i'm gonna open it and see
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
[Applause]
billy
[Music]
what's the matter wrong color no wrong
sex
ooh baby that [ __ ] turns me on
[Music]
who does she think she is
[Applause]
[Music]
who the hell is that
[Applause]
[Music]
looks like a friggin movie star
[Applause]
[Music]
check out the blonde in the dress
i'd sure like to go home with that uh me
too
excuse me do you see that girl over
there
[Music]
oh i sure do what about you do you see
her too
there's nothing wrong with my eyes
[Music]
is she a friend of yours
but she's not the one i think
[Applause]
this is not a strip joint get up there
and stop her before she shuts us down
[Music]
[Applause]
please don't take it off
yeah yeah
[Music]
what are you trying to prove out there
are you crazy
they loved me oh of course they loved
you they loved your
cones hurry up and get dressed
right let's get out of here just a
minute hey what's the big idea screwing
up our act
you call that an act look my friend here
has had a little too much to drink you
know how that is
let's just forget the whole thing no
you're not getting up that easy yeah
don't you push my greatness like that oh
yeah
why don't you stop me hey
hey watch where you're aiming you clumsy
off show you who's clumsy
[Music]
excuse me excuse me somebody may have
recognized you
silly no one in a million years you
think you're here
you're really playing i think your
millionaires are up
wait a minute
[Music]
oh jeez that was close oh i guess those
drinks went right to my head
yeah well it just goes to show you
ghosts and alcohol don't mix
now go make yourself invisible so you
don't get us in any more trouble okay
okay
i still see you of course you do
well how do i know no one else can ask
someone
excuse me can you see my friend over
[Music]
there
okay
angela this is a chariot i used to have
one just like it
it's very nice but we have to go home
now
billy what are you doing
would you get out of that car what if
the owner comes back
oh you like old cars huh
hi hi is this your car um
she's a beauty isn't she you don't see
many of them around
ask him to take us for a spin no
no i haven't seen any in such great
condition
yeah thanks so uh
what are you doing tonight oh nothing
much i'm just
out and about and about huh
hmm so how's your dog
i'm pretty good you want a bank no no i
meant your other dog oh perfect
she's fine she decided to stay home
tonight and do her nails
women oh i see here they are
hey you left your keys in the ignition
i did no i didn't i guess i did i could
have sworn i
damn lucky somebody didn't steal it
don't speak too soon
what the hell hey it starts great
doesn't it yeah yeah thanks but if and
how the heck
i'll drive i wanted to drive
are you coming or not yeah sure oh
i better just hop in the back here we go
[Music]
[Applause]
hey you nearly hit those guys i missed
him by a mile
i did i'd have to drive a lot more
carefully won't i
hey you go a little fast don't you
should slow down
i'm trying he's backstreet drivers
so where are we going anyway
[Music]
that's a good question looks like we're
headed towards santa barbara
we are yes we are perhaps i should turn
the car around and go back oh
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
i'm sorry i just lost control tom
you really take the wheel tom
do you think he has a concussion no he
probably just
fainted he was such a nervous passenger
but the way you drive him surprised he
didn't have a heart attack
hey see that must be some kind of a
college prank
let's get him huh come on wait a minute
let's get the coffee off
reverse first then follow it what the
hell did you get
i'm sorry i'm sorry okay
just take it nice and easy nice and easy
[Music]
i said easy he's not waking up
good what do you mean good i don't think
he'd be too
thrilled by what's behind us the light
the light
oh great just great let me
drive i got us into this nest
i'll get us out of it let's see what
this baby can really do
now that is what i call some seriously
reckless driving
you're gonna lock me up and throw away
the key
you have to catch us
[Music]
this first not my idea of fun
holy toledo these guys are fast
it calls for drastic measures steer for
me
[Music]
what the hell's going on up there i
don't know
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
what happened where are the cops
oh they had a little accident
bob yeah he mashed my donut
how's he doing still out like a light
i'll take
[Music]
[Applause]
billy what are we stopping here for this
looks like a makeout spot i'm not going
to give a mouth to mouth
what better way to wake a guy up billy
he's coming too i'll see you later don't
you dare
billy feel me the name's tom
where are we great
yes it is isn't it so the last thing i
remember
is you were driving
real fast
i was driving you home but you fell
asleep so i
so uh you decided to take me up here and
uh
take advantage of me no no that wasn't
the idea at all oh no
then what'd you have in mind like you
said it's a great view and
[Music]
this is so unexpected i know
especially after the way you treated me
the other day tom i am so sorry about
that i can explain everything
ah there's no need to yes there is
you seem like a nice guy and you really
should know the truth
no thanks it's her it's billy blaine
who is the ghost the one that's in my
house the one that's been driving your
car
what are you talking about okay i i know
this is hard to believe but
it's true i've seen her i've talked to
her i'm writing her biography
you're writing your biography well
actually she's writing it with me but
we're saying it came from an old diary
of hers because we don't want everyone
to know she's dead
actually everyone knows she's dead but
we don't want everyone to think she can
write
still you understand
what's wrong oh nothing nothing at all
ah tom you don't think i'm making this
up do you
i don't know what to think you're a very
pretty girl and a good kisser
but if you think you're seeing ghosts
you need something other than a
boyfriend but tom i swear
and if if you're making this up just to
break the mood it'd be a lot simpler
just to tell me you had a headache
[Music]
where are we going home yours
hey wait my car oh
i left it at the club
[Music]
billy i swear to god
angela i had nothing to do with this
who did this i don't know
maybe burglars
i'm too tired to worry about this now
i'll deal with the house my car
everything in the morning and as for you
you are in big trouble if we weren't
writing this story together i swear i
oh good night
[Music]
dear tom
please forgive the way i
acted last night
come over for a drink
round seven and
i'll make it up to you
love angela
i can't trust you guys to do the
simplest thing boss you pour the police
apart
yeah there was no sign of it anywhere
you gotta believe it all right all right
i believe you
maybe it is somewhere else yeah then how
are we gonna find it
i guess we'll just have to persuade her
won't we
hi hi these are for you
oh thanks come on in it's really sweet
in you
well i figured as long as you made the
first gesture well
what well when i got you note inviting
me over here tonight i thought it was
the least i could do what i didn't
billy tom tom farrell
yeah right yeah
can i get you something to drink sure
what would you like no
doesn't matter whatever you're having is
fine all i really want is you
i beg your pardon um will a
coke do uh yeah
yeah she wasn't already dead
fine turn down the lights and put on
some
soft music okay
[Music]
tom over here babe
why'd you turn off the lights well you
didn't tell me where the dimmer was
is the music okay sure
you know i have to admit i was pretty
surprised when you asked me over here
tonight
me too huh
that's me unpredictable
well i like that most of the women i
meet especially
writers are so boring then why don't you
just shut up and
kiss me all right i will
what's the matter no nothing nothing
wait right here i'll be right back i'm
just going to slip into something
more comfortable in the kitchen
ah kinky
billy billy you come here this instant
where do you get off meddling in my
affairs if i didn't meddle
you wouldn't have any affairs that is
none of your business
i was doing just fine without you not
from where i was watching
things haven't changed that much since
my day the way you were going you'll
wind up an old maid
ah great great just what i need
a sex education course from some out of
date bimbo
who are you calling out of date you you
put women's rights back in the dark ages
well we'll see how good you do without
my help miss 1980s cause this is the
last you'll see of me
[Music]
fine
hi i'm back
who were you talking to in there you're
not gonna go turn a schizo on me are you
me no no i was talking to my aunt sarah
you're in sarah you know how real tips
can be sometimes
can i get you something else to drink
no thanks
[Music]
now that's more like
you don't still think you're being
haunted by a billy blaine do you
uh
we're the only ones here
[Music]
[Applause]
hmm
hey it looks like our subject is uh
adjoined to the boudoir
to do a little horizontal entertainment
that means your guest is more than a
casual acquaintance
should i call the boss or what hey be my
[Music]
guest
good morning
you want me to make us some breakfast
okay what was that again
how come that's what i thought you said
[Applause]
[Music]
for somebody you mean by your dead
[Applause]
tom tom
hello we have your friend miss reed
the man you spent last night with i'm
willing to trade his life in the diary
you have
wait a minute who is this the time for
games is long past must read i'll give
you one hour to decide
and i wouldn't call the authorities if i
were you at the first sign of police
your friend
is a dead man
where is she where's who billy blaine
but she's not here oh then you don't
deny that she was here
just like you don't deny that i saw you
the other night with her at scream
yes yes it was her so where is she
back in ghostland how would i know look
i can't worry about her now tom has been
kidnapped
oh no
who's tom thank you angela think
they said they'd kill tom if i didn't
give him the diary so why don't you just
give him the diary
because i don't have it it doesn't even
exist billy was telling me her life
story i was writing it
we had to explain where it was coming
from so we made up the diary
whoever kidnapped tom must think that
billy had written something
incriminating about him
it's got to be someone she knows bj
you've got to help me call her back me
yeah she's she's kind of mad at me right
now and since you're such a big fan if
you called her maybe she'd come back
well all right but i i just feel really
kind of silly doing this
uh billy
billy blaine yo billy can i get an
autograph
certainly bj anything you want
really i'm so glad you're here i'm not
speaking to you
[Music]
so bj what would you like me to sign
billy i apologize for what i said last
night i really do but you've got to help
me tom has been kidnapped
oh no who's tom
by whom well that's what i don't know it
has to be someone from your past
someone who wouldn't want your memoirs
published
gosh that could be a hundred different
guys
and it has to be someone who wasn't
mentioned in the first article does that
help
i don't know were there any married men
no but there was this one guy i dated
secretly
i think he had mob connections so we
never met in public it was always here
or some secluded place good good
do you remember his name vinny
vinnie carbone vincent carbone the
politician
he's running for the senate no kidding
i always knew he was ambitious
wait a minute it couldn't be vinnie why
not
we were going to get married we were
going to announce it to the public and
everything
in fact he proposed to me the night i
drowned you never mentioned that before
i just remembered i wonder why
carbon why does that name sound familiar
why does that name sound so familiar you
probably heard it on the news
no no no no what's this it's from a 1962
paper it's uh billy blaine's uh a death
notice
it's a pretty ghoulish thing to carry
around isn't it i think it's sweet
now here it is right on the back here
carbon appointed to mayor's staff
vincent carbone attended ceremonies at
city hall accompanied by his wife
dorothy his wife what
you mean he was already married
jesus billy do you know what this means
yeah i sure do
means he was a no good two-timing bum it
was a lot worse than that
don't you see he couldn't marry you he
already had a wife
his political career was just starting
out
he didn't come here that night to
propose
he must have slipped an overdose of
barbiturates into your drink
and then he let the tide do the rest
holy [ __ ]
guess i never did have too much luck
with men
five husbands five divorces
then the last guy decides to kill me
before he even said
i do
lily honey i know this isn't easy for
you
but this guy murdered once to prevent a
scandal and he'll do it again
[Music]
even if i did have the diary to give to
him he'd never let tom or me go free
[Music]
please you've got to help us
what do you want me to do we've got to
shift the odds over to our side
count me in pj you mean it
sure thing let's nail this butthole
[Music]
she's clean right this way
billy billy are you still here
i'm right here oh good
listen i know how hard it's going to be
for you to control your temper when you
see him
please just try to remember tom's life
is at stake here don't you worry angie
well well miss reed nice to meet you
face to face
i'm sorry i can't say the same thing oh
come on now
you can't allow yourself to take these
things personally
may i pour you a drink no thank you no
well i hope you don't mind if i have one
to think i used to be in love with him
so miss reed i trust you brought the
diary with you no i didn't
why not because mr carbone once you have
it what's to stop you from killing us
both
[Laughter]
you must think i'm quite a desperate
character don't you
you have an affair with a movie star
then fake her suicide to protect your
career
now you're trying to prevent your past
from being dredged up before the
election
i'd say you're living slime
don't look misread please please don't
take these things
personally not quite right after all
this is strictly business isn't it
you know that's something billy would
never have understood oh spare me
i wanted to tell her i was married that
it would never work out between us but
the girl was crazy about me don't
flatter yourself
she demanded more and more of my time
she never got enough of me i think i'm
going to throw up
billy oh yes billy um you know i really
think i did her a favor when i slipped
to those pills
a girl never could have lived without me
why you dirty oh
what a nice plant you have here
miss reed how am i gonna get that diary
the exchange will be made tonight at a
place of my choice
i'll phone you later with the address in
the meantime why don't you round up say
500 000 in small bills and put it in a
briefcase
a half a million dollars or just a
little getaway fund
to keep us at a safe distance from your
constituents
ms reed you're pressing your luck a
little too far
you might not make it out of this house
if i don't a lot of people will be
reading billy blaine's memories of you
by tomorrow morning
can you afford that mr carbone that's an
awful lot of money to raise
under short notice i have every faith in
your ability to raise a dishonest dollar
catch i'll be in touch
[Music]
see you later
billy you didn't i sure did but he ain't
seen nothing yet
get in here okay now to implement phase
two
[Music]
check the place out boss the girl's
already inside she came along
you sure about that no please i swear
they're norm for miles
tony stay here make sure he stays
healthy for the moment
marco wait two minutes and come in
through the back
and give this girl a warm reception but
make sure i have the diary first
[Music]
ugh
what are you all dressed up for what do
you mean
oh this very funny where's the diary
where's tom he's outside and he's going
to stay there until i get what i came
for
no no that's not what we agreed on
you've got me my men have him
let's have it let me see the money first
[Music]
okay let's go where on a little tour
i hid the diary in one of the exhibits
one more minute
look i'll buy you pizza if you get off
the phone
huh
[Music]
this is all yours you know what i mean i
got a date with a lady
[Music]
how much further is this aren't you
enjoying this i thought you used to like
movie stars
yeah hey buddy can i bum a cigarette hey
get lost punk
oh come on man be a pal hey beat it
douchebag
hey that's no way to treat a fellow
human being
maybe the guy will be a little more
understanding on the other side
hey douchey get the hell away from there
[Music]
oops sorry i didn't know you were all
tied up all right that [ __ ]
when i get through with you you wish you
never were bored your mother uses
steroids
that's been not letting me wear my pants
guido hey
don't shoot don't shoot i'm b.j i'm tom
tom
i'm angela's friend yeah is this name
really guido
it's just a pet name where is angela
she's inside with that guy carbon
well they ain't alone one of his goons
just went inside there after them holy
[ __ ]
i better call the police look there's a
phone in the back seat i'm going inside
[Music]
hey
is this your idea of a joke
[Music]
you didn't think it would be that easy
did you vinny
huh i'm not over there i'm right here
what's the matter vinnie aren't you glad
to see me
this can't be you're supposed to be
you're dead that's right would you like
to join me
stay back can't hurt me vinny
not anymore you hurt me enough already
[Music]
you can run but you can't hide hey have
you seen it
no i guess you haven't
[Music]
look what's gone
frankly vinnie i don't give a damn
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
hmm
good evening vinnie
[Music]
i'm coming for you
no
[Music]
come back
cinderella
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
tom are you all right yeah yeah i'm okay
but let's get out of here before bam bam
comes too
come on
what happened in there where's corbon i
don't know i lost track of him
[Music]
you're dead meat pal hold it pal
up against the wall come on
um angela what's going on here
baxter's so glad you could make it you
better have a very good reason for
getting me out here in the middle of the
night
now what are all these other reporters
doing here sorry baxter but this was too
big to be an exclusive
what was to do
somebody please help me hey she's after
me hey buddy what's the problem
wait a minute aren't you vincent carbon
yes yes i am
spencer
you from home from her don't you see
it's billy blaine what's the matter
don't you go to the movies
they can't see me vinny only you can
they can't see you of course they can
see you you can see it can't you
she's standing right over there in a
low-cut evening
they can't protect you from me vinny not
if they can't see me
i can haunt you for the rest of your
days
oh no no please i'll do anything just
leave me alone please
i'll do anything maybe if you told them
exactly what happened that night
no i couldn't i couldn't do that my
career would be ruined
they throw me in jail maybe the gas
chamber i couldn't do that
well then i guess you and i will be
seeing a lot of each other
what are your plans for the next 20
years i win
i confess
you hear that everyone billy blade
didn't kill herself it was me back in
yeah i did i gave her an overdose and
let it drown
sorry come on
[Music]
angela this is sensational i mean it's
not every day that you see a candidate
crack up in front of the media
you said that he'd kidnap somebody yes
he did her baxter meet
tom farrell hi i'm the writer too
no kidding listen i wonder could i uh
interest you in uh writing a piece for
us i mean uh
say uh impressions of a kidnap victim uh
i don't know
no no no no i'll expect a story from you
as well but i just thought that you know
like we could
put them both together and uh make a
feature on it well whatever you're gonna
have to wait till we get back from our
vacation
what vacation where are you going i'll
send you a postcard
hey
i used to write in high school it's an
advice
i wonder what made carbon fall apart
like that i've never seen anything like
it
oh just forget about it let's talk about
this vacation
hmm sounds good to me aren't you two
forgetting something
billy i i thought you'd moved on
well now that i have a choice i figured
i'd hang around for a while
besides
the money i thought you might want it
for your vacation
half a million dollars goes a long way
even in the 80s
thanks billy you mean
there really is a ghost that's what i've
been trying to tell you
tom meet billy
there he goes again
[Music]
just put the other one over here please
you had enough waves yet b.j no way man
i never get enough
guys say hello to megan and tabitha
they're taking me to a luau tonight
catch you later man later bj
i guess that means we get the whole
evening to ourselves
um not quite
[Music]
memories
but without love they've been away
sweet dreams
[Music]
even though i know
sweet dreams
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
yesterday
we dreamed of your way