Good luck.
Hi. I have an appointment with...
...Emily Charlton?
- Andrea Sachs?
- Yes?
Great. Human Resources certainly has
an odd sense of humor. Follow me.
Okay. So I was Miranda's
second assistant...
...but her first recently got promoted,
and now I'm the first.
- You're replacing yourself.
- Well, I am trying.
Miranda sacked the last two girls
after a few weeks.
We need someone
who can survive here.
- Do you understand?
- Yeah, of course. Who's Miranda?
Oh, my God. I will pretend
you did not just ask me that.
She's the editor in chief of Runway.
Not to mention, a legend.
Work a year for her and you can get
a job at any magazine you want.
- A million girls would kill for this.
- It sounds like a great opportunity.
I'd love to be considered.
Andrea...
...Runway is a fashion magazine,
so an interest in fashion is crucial.
What makes you think
I'm not interested in fashion?
Oh, my God.
No, no, no!
What's wrong?
She's on her way. Tell everyone.
She's not supposed to be here until 9.
Her driver just text-messaged,
and her facialist ruptured a disk.
God, these people.
- Who 's that?
- That I can't even talk about.
All right, everyone. Gird your loins!
Did someone eat an onion bagel?
Sorry, Miranda.
Move it.
I don't understand why
it's so difficult to confirm appointments.
I'm so sorry. I actually did confirm...
Details of your incompetence
do not interest me.
Tell Simone I won't approve that girl
she sent me for the Brazilian layout.
I asked for clean, athletic, smiley.
She sent dirty, tired and paunchy.
R.S.V.P. "yes" to
the Michael Kors party.
I want the driver to drop me off at 9:30
and pick me up at 9:45 sharp.
Then call Natalie at Glorious Foods
and tell her "no" for the 40th time.
I don't want dacquoise. I want tortes
filled with rhubarb compote.
Call my ex and remind him the
parent-teacher conference is at Dalton.
Then call my husband,
ask him to meet me for dinner...
...at that place I went to
with Massimo.
Tell Richard I saw
the pictures he sent...
...for that feature
on female paratroopers...
...and they're all so unattractive.
Is it impossible to find a lovely...
...slender female paratrooper?
- No.
- Am I reaching for the stars?
Not really. Also...
...I need to see all the things that
Nigel has pulled...
...for Gwyneth's second cover try.
I wonder if she's lost any of
that weight yet. Who is that?
Nobody.
Well, Human Resources sent her up
about the new assistant job.
I was sort of
preinterviewing her for you.
But she's hopeless
and totally wrong for this...
Well, clearly, I have to
do that myself.
The last two you sent me
were completely inadequate...
...so send her in.
That's all.
Right.
- She wants to see you.
- She does?
Move.
This is foul. Don't let her see it.
- That's my...
- Go.
Who are you?
My name is Andy Sachs.
I recently graduated from
Northwestern University.
And what are you doing here?
Well, I think I could do a good job
as your assistant.
And...
I came to New York to be a journalist,
and sent letters out everywhere...
...and finally got a call
from Elias-Clarke...
...and met with Sherry
up at Human Resources and...
Basically, it's this or Auto Universe.
- So you don't read Runway?
- No.
- Before today, you'd never heard of me?
And you have no style
or sense of fashion.
Well...
I think that depends on
what you're...
No, no. That wasn't a question.
I was editor in chief of
The Daily Northwestern.
I also won a national competition for
college journalists with my series...
...on the janitors' union...
...which exposed the exploitation of...
- That's all.
Yeah, you know, okay.
You're right. I don't fit in here.
I am not skinny or glamorous and
I don't know that much about fashion...
...but I'm smart.
- I learn fast and work very hard.
- I've got the exclusive on...
...the Cavalli for Gwyneth.
The problem is, with that huge
feathered headdress she's wearing...
...she looks like she's working
the stage at the Golden Nugget.
Thank you for your time.
Who is that sad little person?
Are we doing a before-and-after piece
I don't know about?
Andrea.
Wait. You got a job
at a fashion magazine?
Well, what was it, a phone interview?
- Don't be a jerk.
- No, I'm just...
Miranda Priestly is famous
for being unpredictable.
Okay, Doug. How is it that
you know who she is and I didn't?
I'm actually a girl.
That would explain so much.
Look, seriously,
Miranda Priestly is a huge deal.
A million girls would kill for that job.
Yeah, great.
The thing is, I'm not one of them.
Well, look.
You gotta start somewhere, right?
I mean, look at this dump
Nate works in.
I mean, come on.
Paper napkins? Hello?
Yeah, and Lily, she works at
that gallery, doing... You know...
Oh, I'm sorry.
What exactly is it that you do, anyway?
Well, lucky for me,
I already have my dream job.
- You're a corporate research analyst.
- Research analyst.
- Oh, you're right. My job sucks.
- No.
- It sucks. I don't... It's boring.
- It's all right. Breathe.
- I'm trying.
- Take a drink.
- I will have a drink.
- I would like to propose a toast.
To jobs that pay the rent.
- To jobs that pay the rent.
- Yes. To jobs that pay the rent.
Oh, baby. You should see the way
these girls at Runway dress.
I don't have a thing to wear to work.
You'll be answering phones
and getting coffee.
You need a ball gown for that?
I think I might.
Well, I happen to think
you look great always.
I think you're full of it.
- Hey. Come on.
- Yeah.
Let's go. I can think of
something we can do...
...that doesn't require any clothing.
- Really?
- Hello?
- Andrea.
Miranda decided to kill
the autumn jacket story for September.
She's putting up
the Sedona shoot from October.
Come into the office this second.
- Pick up her coffee order on the way.
- Now?
Now, get a pen and write this down:
I want one no-foam, skimmed latte...
...with an extra shot and
three coffees with room for milk.
Searing hot. And I mean hot.
- Hello?
- Where are you?
I'm almost there. Yeah.
Shoot.
Is there some reason
that my coffee isn't here?
Has she died or something?
No. God...
Oh, about bloody time.
I hope you know this is a very difficult
job for which you are totally wrong.
If you mess up,
my head is on the chopping block.
Now, hang that up.
Don't just fling it anywhere.
- All right, where's the other layout?
- It's on its way.
This is the first part of the collection,
which we talked about...
Okay. First of all,
you and I answer the phones.
The phone must be answered
every single time it rings.
Calls roll to voice mail,
and she gets very upset.
If I'm not here... Andrea, Andrea.
- You are chained to that desk.
Well, what if I need to...?
What? No. One time,
an assistant left the desk...
...because she sliced her hand open
with a letter opener.
And Miranda missed Lagerfeld...
...just before he boarded
a 17-hour flight to Australia.
She now works at TV Guide.
Man the desk at all times, got it.
Miranda Priestly's office.
No, she's not available.
Who is...?
Yes, I will tell her you called.
Yet again.
Remember,
you and I have totally different jobs.
I mean, you get coffee
and you run errands.
I am in charge of her schedule...
...her appointments
and her expenses...
...and most importantly, I get to go with
her to Paris for Fashion Week in the fall.
I get to wear couture.
I go to all the shows and parties.
I meet all of the designers.
It's divine.
Okay, now, stay here.
I'm going to the Art Department
to give them the Book.
- The...?
- This is the Book.
Now, it is a mockup of
everything in the current issue.
We deliver it to Miranda's apartment
every night and she retu... Don't touch.
She returns it to us in the morning
with her notes.
Now, second assistant
is supposed to do this...
...but Miranda is very private and
she does not like strangers in her house.
So until she decides that
you're not a total psycho...
...I get the lovely task of
waiting around for the Book.
- Emily? What do I do if...?
- Deal with it.
Hello, Mrs. Priestly's office.
That's what I meant.
Miranda Priestly's office.
You know, she is in a meeting.
Could I please take a message?
Okay.
Can you please spell "Gabbana"?
Hello?
Guess not.
I guessed an eight and a half.
Wow, that's very nice of you.
But I don't think I need these.
Miranda hired me.
- She knows what I look like.
- Do you?
Emily.
Emily?
She means you.
- We just cut on the bias and so what...
- No, that's not what I asked you.
There you are, Emily. How many times
do I have to scream your name?
Actually, it's Andy.
My name is Andy.
Andrea, but everybody calls me Andy.
- I need 10 or 15 skirts from Calvin Klein.
- Okay. What kind of skirts do you...?
Please bore someone else
with your questions.
And make sure we have Pier 59
at 8 a.m. Tomorrow.
Remind Jocelyn I need to see those
satchels that Marc is doing in the pony.
And then tell Simone I'll take Jackie
if Maggie isn't available.
Did Demarchelier confirm?
- Did Demarcheli...?
- Demarchelier. Did he...
Get him on the phone.
Okay.
And, Emily...
Yes?
That's all.
It's the cavalier disregard for...
Do you have Demarchelier?
Demarchelier.
Leave it.
Do you have...? Oh.
I have Miranda Priestly calling.
I have Patrick!
She called me in there and then
she asked me about Pier 59.
And there was something
about Simone, Frankie, someone else.
And she needs skirts
from Calvin Klein.
And there was something
about a pony.
- Did she say which skirts?
- No.
- Did she say what kind?
- I tried to ask her.
You may never ask Miranda anything.
Right. I will deal with all of this,
and you will go to Calvin Klein.
- Me?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
Do you have some prior commitment?
Some hideous-skirt convention
you have to go to?
- Miranda?
- Are you there?
I'm about to walk in.
I'll call you as soon as I...
- Hello?
- While you're out...
...Miranda needs you to go to Hermès
to pick up 25 scarves we ordered for her.
Cassidy forgot her homework at Dalton.
Pick that up.
Miranda went out
to meet with Meisel.
She'll want more Starbucks
when she gets back.
- Hot Starbucks.
- Can you just repeat that first...? Hello?
Oh, my God.
What took you so long?
I have to pee.
- You haven't peed since I left?
- No.
Been manning the desk, haven't I?
I'm bursting.
Oh, hi.
- You do coat. Do the coat.
- Okay.
Be prepared. The run-through
is at 12:30, and people are panicking.
So the phone is going
to be ringing off the hook.
The run-through. Right.
Yes. Editors bring in options
for the shoot, and Miranda chooses.
She chooses every single thing
in every single issue.
It's a huge deal. I don't know
why you don't know that.
- Okay, are you ready?
- Oh, hi, hi.
Right, well, after the loo,
Serena and I are going to lunch.
- This is her, the new me.
- Hi.
- Told you.
- I thought you were kidding.
No, quite serious, yeah.
I get 20 minutes for lunch,
and you get 15.
- When I come back, you can go.
- Okay.
- What exactly is she wearing?
- Her grandmother's skirt.
Corn chowder.
That's an interesting choice.
You do know that cellulite is one of
the main ingredients in corn chowder?
None of the girls here eat anything?
Not since two became the new four
and zero became the new two.
Well, I'm a six.
Which is the new 14.
- Shoot.
- Oh, never mind.
I'm sure you have plenty more poly blend
where that came from.
Okay.
You think my clothes are hideous,
I get it.
But, you know, I'm not
going to be in fashion forever...
...so I don't see the point of changing
myself just because I have this job.
Yes, that's true.
That's what this multi-billion-dollar
industry is all about, anyway, isn't it?
Inner beauty.
Hello?
Right. Come on.
Miranda's pushed the run-through
up a half an hour.
She's always 15 minutes early.
- Which means...?
- You're already late.
- Come. Excuse me.
- Shoot!
- Mr. Ravitz.
- Nigel.
- Issue going well?
- Oh, yes. Our best September ever.
Great. Heard Miranda killed autumn
jackets and pulled up the Sedona shoot.
- What's that costing me?
- About 300,000.
Must have been some lousy jackets.
- Irv Ravitz.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
This is Andy Sachs,
Miranda's new assistant.
Oh, congratulations, young lady.
A million girls would kill for that job.
Bye-bye.
Chairman of Elias-Clarke. Irv Ravitz.
You know what they say:
Tiny man, huge ego.
No. And I've seen all this before.
Theyskens is trying to reinvent
the drop waist, so it's...
- Where are all the other dresses?
- We have some right here.
- Stand, watch and listen.
- I think it can be very interesting...
No.
No, I just...
It's just baffling to me.
Why is it so impossible
to put together a decent run-through?
You people have had
hours and hours to prepare.
It's just so confusing to me.
Where are the advertisers?
- We have some pieces from Banana...
- We need more, don't we? Oh.
This is...
- This might be... What do you think of...?
- Yeah. You know me.
Give me a full ballerina skirt
and a hint of saloon, and I'm onboard.
- But do you think it's too much like...?
- Like the Lacroix from July?
I thought that, but no,
not with the right accessories.
Where are the belts for this dress?
Why is no one ready?
Here. It's a tough call.
They're so different.
Something funny?
No. No, no, nothing's...
You know, it's just that both those belts
look exactly the same to me.
You know, I'm still
learning about this stuff and...
"This stuff"?
Oh, okay. I see. You think
this has nothing to do with you.
You go to your closet...
...and you select, I don't know,
that lumpy blue sweater, for instance...
...because you're trying to tell the world
you take yourself too seriously...
...to care about what you put on...
...but what you don't know is that
that sweater is not just blue.
It's not turquoise. It's not lapis.
It's actually cerulean.
And you're also blithely
unaware of the fact...
...that in 2002, Oscar de la Renta
did a collection of cerulean gowns...
...and then it was Yves Saint Laurent
who showed cerulean military jackets.
I think we need a jacket here.
Then cerulean quickly showed up in the
collections of eight different designers.
And then it filtered down through
the department stores...
...and then trickled on down
into some tragic Casual Corner...
...where you, no doubt,
fished it out of some clearance bin.
However, that blue represents
millions of dollars and countless jobs.
And it's sort of comical how you think
that you've made a choice...
...that exempts you
from the fashion industry...
...when, in fact, you're wearing
a sweater that was selected for you...
...by the people in this room...
...from a pile of "stuff."
And then I said, no,
I couldn't see the difference...
...between the two
absolutely identical belts.
You should've seen
the look she gave me.
I swear, I thought the flesh
was gonna melt off her face.
It's not funny.
She is not happy unless everyone around
her is panicked, nauseous or suicidal.
And the clackers just worship her.
- The who?
- They call them "clackers."
The sound that their stilettos make
in the marble lobby.
It's like:
And they all act like
they're curing cancer or something.
The amount of time and energy
that these people spend...
...on these insignificant, minute details.
And for what?
So that tomorrow they can spend
another $300,000...
...reshooting something
that was fine to begin with...
...to sell people things
they don't need. God!
- I'm not even hungry anymore.
- What?
- That is why those girls are so skinny.
- Oh, no, no, no. Give me that.
There's, like, $8 of Jarlsberg in there.
Know what?
I just have to stick it out for a year.
One year.
And then I can do
what I came to New York to do.
But I can't let Miranda get to me.
I won't.
Easy there, tiger.
- Oh, good morning, Miranda.
- Get me Isaac.
I don't see my breakfast here.
Where are my eggs?
Excuse me!
Pick up the Polaroids
from the lingerie shoot.
Have the brakes checked on my car.
Where is that piece of paper
I had in my hand yesterday morning?
Girls need new surfboards...
...or boogie boards
or something for spring break.
- Hello?
- The twins also need flip-flops.
Pick up my shoes from Blahnik...
...and then go get Patricia.
- Who's that?
Good girl! Good girl! Good girl!
Get me that little table that I like
at that store on Madison.
Get us a reservation for dinner tonight
at that place that got the good review.
- Notes delivered today.
Where is everyone?
Why is no one working?
- East Side.
Get me Demarchelier.
I have Miranda Priestly
calling for... Okay.
I have Patrick.
Thank God it's Friday, right?
At least Miranda will be in Miami, so we
don't have to be on call this weekend.
You know, my dad's coming in
from Ohio.
Yeah, we're gonna go out to dinner
and maybe see Chicago.
You doing anything fun this weekend?
Yes.
Yeah, Nate said it was great.
He actually... He applied here but they
wanted someone with more experience.
- Here.
- What's this?
I don't want you
to get behind on your rent.
- Dad? How did you...?
- It's...
I'm gonna kill Mom.
Thank you.
- It's really good to see you.
- You too, honey.
So do you wanna start grilling me now,
or should we wait till after dinner?
I thought I'd let you
at least enjoy the breadbasket first.
No, no, no, that's okay.
Go right ahead.
We're just a little worried, honey.
We get e-mails from you
at your office at 2 a.m.
Your pay is terrible.
You don't get to write anything.
Hey, that's not fair.
I wrote those e-mails.
I'm trying to understand why someone
who got accepted to Stanford Law...
...turns it down to be a journalist,
and now you're not even doing that.
Dad, you have to trust me.
Being Miranda's assistant
opens a lot of doors.
Emily is going to Paris with Miranda
in a few months...
...and she's gonna meet editors and
writers from every important magazine...
...and in a year, that could be me.
All right? Dad, I swear,
this is my break. This is my...
My chance. This is...
...my boss.
I'm sorry, Dad. I have to take this.
- Hello, Miranda?
- My flight has been cancelled.
There's some absurd weather problem.
I need to get home tonight.
The twins have a recital
tomorrow morning at school.
- What?
- At school.
- Absolutely. Let me see what I can do.
- Good.
Hi. I know this is totally last minute...
...but I was hoping that you could
maybe get a flight for my boss...
...from Miami to New York tonight?
- Yeah. Yeah, any kind of jet.
- Right here. Thank you.
- From Miami to New York.
- Thank you.
Yes, I need it tonight. I need it...
- I thought you were going out...
- No. It's over here, honey.
Hi, I'm trying to get a flight tonight,
for tonight, from Miami to New York.
Yes, I know there's a hurricane.
Nothing is flying out?
What do you mean, nothing?
It's for Miranda Priestly.
She's a client of yours.
She's flown with you before.
Yes, yes, hi.
I need a jet tonight
from Miami to New York.
- Yeah. Sorry, hold on.
- What?
Hello? Miranda, hi.
I'm trying to get a flight, but no one
is flying, because of the weather.
Please. It's just,
I don't know, drizzling.
Well, someone must be getting out.
Call Donatella. Get her jet.
Call everybody else that we know
that has a jet.
Call every... This is your respons...
This is your job.
Get me home.
Oh, my God.
She's going to murder me.
What does she want you to do,
have the National Guard airlift her?
Of course not. Could I do that?
Come on. Come on.
The girls' recital
was absolutely wonderful.
They played Rachmaninoff.
Everyone loved it.
Everyone except me,
because, sadly, I was not there.
- Miranda, I'm so sorry.
- Do you know why I hired you?
I always hire the same girl.
Stylish, slender, of course,
worships the magazine.
But so often, they turn out to be...
...I don't know, disappointing. And...
...stupid.
So you,
with that impressive résumé...
...and the big speech
about your so-called work ethic...
...I thought you would be different.
I said to myself, "Go ahead.
Take a chance.
Hire the smart fat girl."
I had hope.
My God, I live on it.
Anyway, you ended up
disappointing me more than...
More than any
of the other silly girls.
I really did everything I could think of.
That's all.
Excuse me, where do you
think you're going?
She hates me, Nigel.
And that's my problem because...
Oh, wait, no. It's not my problem.
I don't know what else I can do
because if I do something right...
...it's unacknowledged.
She doesn't even say thank you.
But if I do something wrong,
she is vicious.
So quit.
What?
- Quit.
- Qui...
I can get a girl to take
your job in five minutes.
One who really wants it.
But no, I don't wanna quit.
That's not fair.
But I... You know,
I'm just saying that...
...I would just like a little credit for
the fact that I'm killing myself trying.
Andy, be serious. You are not trying.
You are whining.
What do you want me
to say to you, huh?
Do you want me to say, "Poor you,
Miranda's picking on you...
...poor you, poor Andy"?
Wake up, six. She's just doing her job.
You are working at the place...
...that published some of
the greatest artists of the century:
Halston, Lagerfeld, de la Renta.
And what they did, what they created,
was greater than art.
Because you live your life in it.
Well, not you, obviously.
But some people.
You think this is just a magazine?
This is not just a magazine.
This is a shining beacon of hope for...
Oh, I don't know.
Let's say, a young boy growing up
in Rhode Island with six brothers...
...pretending to go to soccer when he
was going to sewing class...
...and reading Runway under the covers
at night with a flashlight.
You have no idea how many legends
have walked these halls, and worse...
...you don't care. Because this place...
...where so many people would die
to work, you only deign to work.
And you want to know why she
doesn't kiss you on the forehead...
...and give you a gold star on your
homework at the end of the day.
Wake up, sweetheart.
Okay, so I'm screwing it up.
I mean, I don't want to, I just wish
that I knew what I could do...
Nigel? Nigel, Nigel.
No.
I don't know what
you expect me to do.
There's nothing in this closet that'll
fit a size six, I can guarantee you.
These are all sample sizes,
two and four.
All right, we're doing this for you...
- And...
- A poncho?
You'll take what I give you
and you'll like it.
We're doing this Dolce for you.
And shoes...
Jimmy Choos.
Manolo Blahnik.
Nancy Gonzalez, love that.
Okay, Narciso Rodriguez.
This we love.
- It might fit. It might.
- What?
Okay, now Chanel. You're in
desperate need of Chanel.
Shall we? We have to get
to the Beauty Department...
...and God knows how long
that's going to take.
I mean, I have no idea
why Miranda hired her.
Me neither. We were
in the Beauty Department...
...and she held up the Shu Uemura
eyelash curler and said:
"What is this?"
I mean, I just knew from
the moment I saw her...
...she was going to be
a complete and utter disas...
Miranda Priestly's office.
No, actually, she's not available
but I'll leave word.
Okay, thanks. Bye.
How did...?
- Are you wearing the Ch...
- The Chanel boots?
Yeah, I am.
You look good.
What?
- She does.
- Oh, shut up, Serena.
- See you guys tomorrow.
- Good night, man. Take it easy.
Take care of that finger, huh?
So...
...what do you think?
I think we better get out of here
before my girlfriend sees me.
The gowns are fabulous, Ralph.
We're gonna use the burgundy...
...for the cover try...
So we spent a whole semester
on potatoes alone.
Take the fry and squeeze it.
See how firm that is?
Hey. Oh, I'm so sorry I'm late.
There was a crisis
in the Accessories Department.
- I needed to find a python headband.
- Python's hot right now.
I have exciting presents for all of you.
Are you ready?
- What is that?
- It's a Bang and Olufsen phone.
Charlie Rose sent it to Miranda
for her birthday.
I looked it up online.
It's eleven hundred dollars.
- What?
- Yep.
And I have some products.
Mason Pearson hairbrushes.
A little Clinique.
Oh, damn it, I love your job.
Oh, one more...
...little thing.
- Do you want it? You want... Oh.
- Gimme, gimme, gimme!
- I think she likes it.
- Oh, my God!
This is the new Marc Jacobs!
This is sold out everywhere.
- Where did you get this?
- Miranda didn't want it, so...
Oh, no, no, no. This bag is, like,
$ 1900. I cannot take this from you.
- Yeah, you can.
- Why do women need so many bags?
- Shut up.
- You have one, you put all your junk...
...in it, and that's it, you're done.
- Fashion is not about utility.
An accessory is merely
a piece of iconography...
...used to express individual identity.
- And it's pretty.
- That too.
It turns out that there is more
to Runway than just fancy purses.
Look. Here is an essay by Jay Mclnerney,
a piece by Joan Didion...
...even an interview with
Christiane Amanpour.
Someone's been
drinking the Kool-Aid.
What are you...?
- Nate.
- I got it.
- It's... Yep, the dragon lady.
- Let me talk to her.
- No. Okay, I need that. Lily, no, no, no!
- Tell her to get her own scrambled eggs.
It's gonna answer it! It's gonna
answer it! Gimme the phone! The phone.
Hi, Miranda.
Absolutely.
I'm leaving right now.
You know, you guys didn't
have to be such assholes.
Excuse me.
I'm looking for James Holt.
- That's him right there.
- Oh, oh, thanks.
No problem.
I put my stuff out there
and I pray they approve.
Excuse me. I'm Andy.
I'm picking up for Miranda Priestly.
Oh, yes. You must be
the new Emily.
- Oh, yeah.
- Nice to meet you.
Oh, let me see that bag.
Very, very nice.
Distressed, studded leather, pieced by
hand, finished with a metallic fringe.
Very nice, indeed.
Who made that fantastic thing?
You.
Duh. This way.
Here we go. It's a sketch
of Miranda's dress for the benefit.
Also the centerpiece of my spring
collection. Top-secret stuff.
- I'll guard it with my life.
- Please do.
Come on. You're working for Miranda,
you must be in need of hard liquor.
Excuse us, girls.
She'll have the punch.
It's deadly. Have fun.
He's right, you know.
The punch.
I drank it at his last party. I woke
up in Hoboken wearing nothing...
...but a poncho and a cowboy hat.
Well.
Wise.
- Hi.
- Christian Thompson.
Christian Thompson? You're kidding.
No, you're... You write for, like,
every magazine I love.
I reviewed your collection of essays
for my college newspaper.
Did you mention my good looks
and my killer charm?
- No, but...
- What do you do?
Oh, well... I wanna work for somewhere
like The New Yorker or Vanity Fair.
- I am a writer too.
- Is that right?
I should read your stuff. Send it over.
Yeah?
That would... Thank you.
That would be great.
Actually, right now, I'm working
as Miranda Priestly's assistant.
Oh, you're kidding.
Well, that's too bad. That's... Whoa.
You'll never survive Miranda.
- Excuse me?
- Well, you seem nice, smart.
You can't do that job.
Gotta go.
Okay. Well, it was very, very nice
to meet you, Miranda girl.
Emily?
Call James Holt's office. Tell them
I wanna move the preview up.
Today at 12:30. Tell everybody else.
Be ready to leave in half an hour.
But we're not expected
until Tuesday.
- Did she say why?
- Yes. She explained...
...every detail of her decision-making.
Then we brushed each other's hair...
...and gabbed about American Idol.
- I see your point.
- What's a preview, anyway?
- Good morning, Miranda.
Miranda insists on seeing the designer's
collections before they show them.
- Great to see you again.
- Hello.
- And she tells them what she thinks?
- In her way.
This season really began for me
with a meditation...
...on the intersection
between East and West.
There's a scale. One nod is good.
Two nods, very good.
There's only been one actual smile on
record, and that was Tom Ford in 2001.
An obi belt.
If she doesn 't like it,
she shakes her head.
This is the dress we have designed
specifically and exclusively for you.
Then, of course,
there's the pursing of the lips.
Which means...?
Catastrophe.
Just... Just go.
- I know.
- I just don't understand. I'm appalled.
- Appalled. I'll talk to him.
- You deal with it.
So because she pursed her lips,
he's gonna change his entire collection?
You still don't get it, do you?
Her opinion is the only one
that matters.
- Call my husband and confirm dinner...
- At Pastis? Done.
And I'll need a change of clothes.
Well, I've already messengered
your outfit over to the shoot.
Fine. And Andrea, I would like you
to deliver the Book to my home tonight.
Have Emily give you the key.
- Guard this with your life.
- Of course.
You know, if I can deliver the Book, that
means I must've done something right.
I'm not a psycho.
And, you know she called me Andrea?
I mean, she didn't call me Emily.
Isn't that great?
Yeah, whoopee.
Now, it's very important that you do
exactly what I'm about to tell you.
Oh, okay.
The Book is assembled by 10, 10:30...
...and you must wait around for it
until then.
You will be delivering Miranda's
dry-cleaning with the Book.
Now, the car will take you
straight to Miranda 's townhouse.
You let yourself in.
Andrea. You do not talk to anyone.
You do not look at anyone.
This is of the utmost importance. You
must be invisible. Do you understand?
You open the door
and you walk across the foyer.
You hang the dry-cleaning in the closet
across from the staircase.
And you leave the Book
on the table with the flowers.
- Shit.
- It's that door to the left.
Okay.
Thank you.
You can give the Book to us.
- Which...? Which table?
- It's okay. Come on up.
- No, I can't. I can't.
- What? It's okay. Come on.
- Yeah, come on. It's okay.
- Please stop talking.
Or you could bring the Book upstairs.
Emily does it all the time.
She does? Right. She does.
All the time.
Yeah? Okay.
What did you expect me to do,
walk out in the middle of a shoot?
I rushed out of an
investment committee meeting.
- And I sat there waiting.
- I told you cell phones...
...didn't work. No signals.
I knew everyone in the restaurant
was thinking:
"There he is, waiting for her again."
Okay, okay.
Okay, okay. It really wasn't
that big a deal. I promise.
The twins said hello,
I said hello back and then...
...I went up to give her the Book...
You went upstairs?
You went upstairs. My God.
Why didn't you just climb into bed
with her and ask for a bedtime story?
Okay. Okay.
I made a mistake. I know.
Andrea, you don't understand.
If you get fired, that might
jeopardize Paris. If that happens...
...I'll search every Blimpie's
in the tristate area for you.
Hold on. She's gonna fire me?
I don't know. She's not happy.
Andrea.
- Miranda, about last night, I'm...
- I need the Harry Potter book...
...for the twins.
Okay. Okay, I'll go down
to Barnes and Noble right now.
Did you fall down and smack
your little head on the pavement?
- Not that I can recall.
- We have all the published books.
The twins want to know
what happens next.
You want the unpublished manuscript?
We know everyone in publishing.
It shouldn't be a problem, should it?
And you can do anything, right?
Yes, Bobbsey?
I know, baby. Mommy's working
very hard to get it for you.
She doesn't get it. You know, I could
call fricking J. K. Rowling herself.
I'm not gonna get a copy
of that book.
My girls leave for their grandmother's
at 4 so the book better be here by 3.
- Of course.
- And I would like my steak here...
...in 15 minutes.
No problem.
Okay. I have four hours
to get the impossible manuscript.
Smith and Wollensky's
doesn't open until 11:30.
How am I gonna get the steak?
Okay. I will be back
in 15 minutes. Wish me luck.
No, shan't.
Yes, yes, yes, I've been on hold.
Well, it's for Miranda Priestly.
It's very important.
Yes, I know. I know it's impossible
to get, but, well, I was wondering...
...if you could make the impossible
possible, if that's at all possible?
Yes, I'm calling about
the Harry Potter manuscript.
No. Unpublished.
Not a chance? Could you tell her
that it's for Miranda Priestly?
Because I think it makes a difference.
Let me call you back.
Hi. You probably don't remember me.
We met at James Holt's party.
I'm Miranda Priestly's assistant.
The Harry Potter manuscript?
Oh, you're kidding.
Sorry to ask, but I am desperate.
Just tell her it can't be done.
You'll have to come up with a plan B.
This is Miranda Priestly
we're talking about.
There is no plan B.
There's only plan A.
Is she back? Am I fired?
You know, I rarely say this
to people who aren't me...
...but you have got to calm down.
Bloody hell.
Coat, bag.
What's that? Oh, I don't want that.
I'm having lunch with Irv. I'll be back
at 3. I'd like my Starbucks waiting.
And if you don't have
that Harry Potter book by then...
...don't even bother coming back.
Hello?
Quit? Are you sure?
I failed. She's gonna fire me anyway.
I might as well beat her to the punch.
Andy, good for you.
Congratulations. You're free.
- Yeah, well, listen, I'll call you later.
- Okay.
- Hello?
- I'm brilliant. No, really.
Monuments should be
erected in my honor.
- You didn't.
- Oh, yes.
Friend of a friend does the cover art,
and she happens to have the manuscript.
Oh, no, because that would mean
that I actually did something right.
It's just...
The thing is, Christian, I was just...
Look, you want this thing, you better
hurry. I'll meet you at the St. Regis.
Excuse me.
Welcome to the St. Regis.
May I assist you?
Yes, I'm meeting someone
at the King Cole Bar.
Right this way.
- You have one hour.
- Thank you.
One copy. What are my twins
gonna do with that? Share?
Oh, no, I made two copies.
And had them covered...
...reset and bound so they
wouldn't look like manuscripts.
This is an extra copy to have on file,
you know, just in case.
Well, where are these fabulous copies?
I don't see them anywhere.
They're with the twins. You know,
on the train on the way to Grandma 's.
Is there anything else
I can do for you?
That's all.
Okay.
- Hey.
- Hey, I went to Dean and DeLuca.
Man, they charge, like,
$5 a strawberry there. But I figure...
...since you quit your job...
...we should celebrate.
Listen, Nate...
Wait, you quit your job, but you're still
working on the twins' science project?
- Well, that's big of you.
- Okay, after we talked, I realized...
...it doesn't make sense throwing away
all those months of hard work.
I had a moment of weakness,
that's all.
Yeah, well, either that, or your job sucks
and your boss is a wacko.
All right.
Whatever. It's your job.
Nate.
Come on.
I'm still the same person I was.
I still want the same things. Okay?
I promise. Same Andy. Better clothes.
I liked the old clothes.
Really?
Well, what about these necklaces?
Do you like them?
No? And this dress? It's new.
Well, there is one other thing
that's new...
...that I thought you might like, but...
What about this?
You don't like it,
I should better do the twins'...
Is this number two look?
This is number two?
- Hi.
- Hi. All right, turn around for me, darling.
Oh, I get it. I get it. The piece
is called "Urban Jungle," right?
Yes. The modern woman
unleashes the animal within...
...to take on the big city.
Good. Go.
Sometimes I can't believe I talk about
this crap all day. Bobby, come here.
- Thanks.
- Make sure Miranda gets these...
...as soon as possible. And tell her that I
switched in the Dior for the Rocha.
Great, can't wait.
- Excuse me. Can we adjust the attitude?
- I'm sorry.
Don't make me feed you
to one of the models.
It's a busy day. And my personal life
is hanging by a thread, that's all.
Well, join the club. That happens when
you start doing well at work, darling.
Let me know when your whole life
goes up in smoke.
That means it's time for a promotion.
No. All right, February.
Back of the issue.
Did anybody speak
with Salma's people yet?
Yes. She'd rather do a summer cover,
because she has a movie...
No. Also I'm pulling the Toobin piece
on the Supreme Court women.
Woman. And I need to see a new draft
on that piece about shopping...
...for a plastic surgeon. It's dull.
And this layout for
the "Winter Wonderland" spread...
Not wonderful yet.
- Okay, I'll look at it.
- What about Testino?
- Where are we on that?
- Zac Posen's...
...doing some sculptural suits,
so I suggested...
...that Testino shoot them
at the Noguchi Garden.
Perfect.
Thank God somebody came to work
today. What about accessories for April?
One thought I had was enamel:
Bangles, pendants, earrings...
No, we did that two years ago.
What else?
They're showing a lot of florals
right now, so I was thinking I...
Florals? For spring? Groundbreaking.
We thought of shooting them in an
industrial space. The contrast between...
...the feminine florals, and the
rough-hewn background would create...
...this wonderful tension with...
- No.
Which would...
Does anybody else have
anything I can possibly use?
Antibacterial wipes, perhaps?
- How's the cold doing?
- Like death warmed up, actually.
God. It's the benefit tonight. I've been
looking forward to it for months.
I refuse to be sick. I'm wearing
Valentino, for crying out loud.
Right. Well, everybody will be
leaving soon to get ready...
...so I suggest you go drop Miranda's
Fendi bag off at the showroom...
...then I suppose you can go home.
Yeah? Oh, wow, that is great.
Perfect, actually. I need to get to
Magnolia Bakery before it closes.
It's Nate's birthday tonight. So we're
having a little party for him, and...
Yeah, I'm hearing this:
And I wanna hear this:
Bye.
I love my job,
I love my job, I love my job.
Hello?
Before the benefit tonight,
I need to make sure that you're both...
...fully prepped on the guest list.
But I thought that only the first
assistant went to the benefit.
Only when the first assistant
hasn't decided to become...
...an incubus of viral plague.
You'll come and help Emily.
That's all.
Right. These are all of the guests.
Miranda invites everyone. We have
to make sure that they all think...
...that she knows
exactly who they are.
And I've been studying for weeks.
- I have to learn all these by tonight?
- Now, don't be silly, Andrea. These too.
Better start without me.
I'll get there as soon as I can.
Andy, come on, it's his birth...
Okay, but hurry.
Believe me, I will.
This is the last thing I want to...
I love that. I'll call you
the second I'm leaving, okay?
- Will that fit me?
- Oh, yeah.
A little Crisco and some fishing line,
and we're in business.
Nothing really. This is...
I mean, really, this is...
...the social event
of the season, and...
Oh, my God. Andy, you look so chic.
Thanks, Em. You look so thin.
- Do I?
- Yeah.
It's for Paris. I'm on this new diet.
It's very effective.
I don't eat anything, and then
when I feel like I'm about to faint...
...I eat a cube of cheese.
- Well, it's definitely working.
I know. I'm just one stomach flu
away from my goal weight.
That's John Folger, the new artistic
director of the Chelsea Rep.
- John.
- Hey there.
- Thanks for coming.
- Thanks. It's always nice seeing you.
Stop fidgeting.
I'm sorry. I'm so late.
Just deal with it. You have to be here.
Emily. Come here.
Isn't that Jacqueline Follet
from French Runway?
Oh, my God, Miranda hates her.
She was supposed to arrive
after Miranda left.
- I didn't know.
- Yeah.
Miranda. Fabulous event, as always.
You've brought Jacqueline.
Wonderful. We're so happy that you
were able to come to our little gathering.
Of course.
I plan my whole year around this.
Well, we're so grateful that you do.
- Ciao.
- Have you gotten my note?
Yes, I did.
- We'll discuss it on Wednesday.
- Yes, I agree.
- No business tonight.
- Not tonight.
Enjoy.
- Em?
- Oh, great. Thanks.
Oh... Oh, my God.
I can't... I just can't remember
what his name is.
I saw his name this morning on the list.
It's... Oh, I know this.
It's something to do with...
Wait, he was part of the...
Oh, God, I know this. It's...
It's Ambassador Franklin.
And that's the woman
that he left his wife for, Rebecca.
Rebecca.
- Ambassador.
- Miranda, you look fabulous.
- You're very kind.
- Thank you.
Welcome back to civilization.
You must be so relieved.
- Look at you.
- Hello.
You're... You're a vision.
Thank God I saved your job.
Okay. You know, I figured out
a few things on my own too.
Turns out, I'm not as nice
as you thought.
I hope not.
Wow, if it weren't
for the stupid boyfriend...
...I'd have to whisk you away
right here and now.
Do you actually
say things like that to people?
Evidently.
Well, I gotta go.
Are you sure? Because my editor
for New York magazine is inside.
You know, I could introduce you two.
You sent over your stuff for me
to look at, I... Remember?
- Yeah.
- All right, I gotta admit...
...I only read a couple because
it was a very large packet you sent.
But what I did read wasn't half bad.
You know, I think...
I think you have a talent, Andy.
He should meet you.
Why don't you come in?
Just for one drink.
Okay. Yeah, I guess I could for one...
No, I can't.
I'm sorry, but I have to go.
All right.
Give my best to the boyfriend.
Roy, I'm sorry. Can you go any faster?
I'm sure Nate will understand.
Yeah.
Hey.
Happy birthday.
Nate, I'm so sorry.
I kept trying to leave,
but there was a lot going on...
...and you know
I didn't have a choice.
Don't worry about it.
I'm going to bed.
Can we at least talk about this?
You look really pretty.
Andrea?
Do you have the Book?
Paris is the most important week
of my entire year.
I need the best possible team
with me.
That no longer includes Emily.
Wait, you... You want me to...?
No. Miranda, I... Emily would die.
Her whole life is about Paris.
She hasn't eaten in weeks, I...
I can't do that, Miranda, I can't.
If you don't go, I'll assume
you're not serious about your future.
At Runway or any other publication.
The decision's yours.
- But...
- That's all.
- Hey, Andy.
- Hey.
You coming to bed anytime soon?
Yeah, five minutes, okay?
Andrea, don't forget to tell Emily.
Do it now.
Don't pick up.
Don't pick up. Don't pick up.
- Don't pick...
- Hi.
- Emily.
- Hi, hi. Sorry I'm late.
It's just, Miranda wanted
some scarves from Hermès.
She did tell me yesterday.
I forgot, like an idiot.
- So I freaked out, of course.
- Emily... Emily, I need to talk to you.
I called Martine at home
and she opened the shop early...
I'm sorry. She opened the shop early
for me, so I got them, which is great.
Yeah, okay, Emily,
when you come in...
...there's something
I have to talk to you about.
- I hope it's not another Miranda problem.
- Not exactly.
Well, good, because I've got
so much to deal with before I go.
I swear to God, I mean...
Oh, my God!
Emily?
I don't care if she was gonna fire you
or beat you with a red-hot poker...
...you should have said no.
Emily, I didn't have a choice.
You know how she is.
Please, that is a pathetic excuse.
Thanks.
Do you know what really just gets me
about this whole thing?
Is that, you know,
you're the one who said...
...that you don't really care
about this stuff.
You don't really care about fashion,
you just wanna be a journalist.
Oh, what a pile of bollocks!
I know you're mad,
I don't blame you.
Face it, Andy, you sold your soul the day
you put on that pair of Jimmy Choos.
I saw it. And do you know what really
just kills me about this whole thing?
Is the clothes that you're gonna get,
I mean, you don't deserve them.
You eat carbs, for chrissake!
God!
It's so unfair.
- Emily...
- Just go.
- Emily, I...
- I said, go.
You are going to Paris
for the couture shows?
That's the coolest fashion event
of the year.
- Who are you gonna see, Galliano?
- Yeah.
- And Lagerfeld?
- Yep.
- And Nicolas Ghesquière.
- Ye... Okay, now you're scaring me.
- Hey.
This show is amazing.
I am so proud of you.
Thank you.
Start with the photos in the back,
work your way forward.
The way I designed it.
Brilliant. You will love it.
- Of course.
- And you...
...I have somebody
I want you to meet.
Art and sex. Lead the way.
- See you later.
- Okay.
Hey.
Hey, Miranda girl.
Hi.
I was just thinking about you.
Oh, come on.
- It's true.
- No.
I'm profiling Gaultier for Interview.
And making my Paris plans...
...I found myself wondering
if you were gonna be there.
Well, actually, I am going.
Great.
I'm staying at a fantastic little hotel
in the seventh.
Right across the street from a falafel
restaurant that will change your life.
I'm sorry, I'll be too busy working.
You'll have to find
someone else's life to change.
Well, that's just it.
I'm beginning to wonder if I can.
Lily.
Lily, he's just a guy
I know from work.
- Yeah, that looked like work.
- You're making a big deal out of...
You know, the Andy I know
is madly in love with Nate...
...is always five minutes early...
...and thinks, I don't know,
Club Monaco is couture.
For the last 16 years,
I've known everything about that Andy.
But this person?
This glamazon
who skulks around in corners...
...with some random,
hot fashion guy?
I don't get her.
- Lily.
- Have fun in Paris.
You're going to Paris?
Yeah, it just happened.
I thought Paris was a big deal
for Emily or...
Great. Now you're gonna
give me a hard time too?
Hey, Andy.
Andy!
- Andy, what the hell is wrong with you?
- I didn't have a choice.
- Miranda asked me. I couldn't say no.
- I know.
Your answer for everything:
"I didn't have a choice."
Like this job was forced on you,
like you don't make decisions.
You're mad because I work late and
I missed your birthday party. I'm sorry.
- Oh, come on, what am I, 4?
- You... You hate Runway. And Miranda.
And you think fashion is stupid.
You've made that clear.
Andy, I make
port-wine reductions all day.
I'm not exactly in the Peace Corps.
You know, I wouldn't care
if you were out pole-dancing all night...
...as long as you did it
with a little integrity.
You used to say this was just a job.
You used to make fun
of the Runway girls.
What happened?
Now you've become one of them.
- That's absurd.
- Hey, that's okay, that's fine.
Just own up to it.
And then we can stop pretending like
we have anything in common anymore.
- You don't mean that, you...
- No, I do.
Well, maybe this trip
is coming at a good time.
Maybe we should take a break.
Nate?
I'm sorry. Just one second.
You know, in case
you were wondering...
...the person whose calls
you always take...
...that's the relationship you're in.
I hope you two
are very happy together.
Hello, Miranda.
Miranda.
How are you? So glad to see you.
Thank you for coming.
- Do you like the collection?
- Absolutely.
This is very important.
Very, very important.
This is my new Emily.
Hello. How do you do?
- I'm good.
- Nice to meet you.
- A pleasure.
- You love the show?
- Miranda. This way, please.
- This way.
Miranda. Nigel.
Fashion's great gatekeepers.
Miranda, what is Runway's position on
French fashion versus American fashion?
I've been thinking.
You still owe me for Harry Potter.
- Oh, do I?
- Of course you do.
Are you working tonight?
- No, actually, Miranda has a dinner.
- Great, you're free.
Oh, but there is the problem
of le boyfriend.
Wait, don't tell me,
the boyfriend non plus?
Oh, you're so full of it.
You're not desolé at all.
Not even a little.
What time should I pick you up?
I'll call you.
Christian, photo!
Oh, there you are.
We need to go over the seating chart.
- For the luncheon.
- Okay. Yeah, sure.
I have it right here.
By all means, move at a glacial pace.
You know how that thrills me.
Okay. So...
...first of all, we need to move
Snoop Dogg to my table.
But your table's full.
Stephen isn't coming.
Oh, Stephen is...
So I don't need to fetch Stephen
from the airport tomorrow?
Well, if you speak to him
and he decides to rethink the divorce...
...then yes, fetch away.
You're very fetching, so go fetch.
And then, when we get back to
New York, we need to contact Leslie...
...and see what she can do
to minimize the press on all this.
Another divorce.
Splashed across "Page Six."
I can just imagine
what they're gonna write about me:
"The Dragon Lady. Career-obsessed.
Snow Queen drives away
another Mr. Priestly."
Rupert Murdoch should cut me a check
for all the papers I sell for him.
Anyway, I don't...
I don't really care
what anybody writes about me.
But my... My girls, I just...
It's just so unfair to the girls.
And it's just...
...another disappointment.
Another letdown.
Another father. Figure.
Gone.
Anyway, the point is...
The point is...
The point is, we really need to figure out
where to place Donatella...
...because she's barely
speaking to anyone.
I'm so sorry, Miranda.
If you want me
to cancel your evening, I can.
Don't be ridiculous.
Why would we do that?
Is there anything else I can do?
Your job.
That's all.
Hi. I need Miranda's itinerary
for tomorrow.
- Okay. Come in.
- All right.
Who put that together for you?
Oh, this isn't...
It's just something I threw on.
Turn around. Let me see. Turn.
- It's really just... No, it's... No.
- Yeah? Yeah? Okay, good.
Gorgeous. Really.
I think that my work here is done.
We're going to celebrate.
I'm going to get some champagne.
Okay. What are we toasting?
We're toasting, my dear,
to the dream job.
The one that a million girls wanted.
Which I got months ago.
I'm not talking about you.
- James Holt.
- Yeah.
Massimo Corteleoni is investing
in James' company and talking it global.
Bags, shoes, fragrances, the works.
And James needs a partner.
And that partner would be me.
- Does Miranda...?
- No, Miranda knows...
...because she put me up for it.
Oh, God, no. Can you imagine?
But... But... But you're leaving.
- I can't imagine Runway without you.
- I know.
I'm so excited, though!
For the first time in 18 years...
...I'll call the shots in my own life.
Oh, my God!
I'm going to be able to come to Paris
and actually see Paris.
Well, congratulations.
Nigel, you deserve it.
You bet your size-six ass.
- Four.
- Really?
- Cheers.
- Cheers to you.
- To us.
- Let me see that.
Okay, I just wanna say that, yes...
...there are things Miranda does
that I don't agree with...
Come on, you hate her.
Just admit it to me.
- No.
- She's a notorious sadist.
And not... Not in a good way.
Okay, she's tough.
But if Miranda were a man...
...no one would notice anything about
her except how great she is at her job.
I'm sorry, I can't... I can't believe this.
- You're defending her?
- Yeah.
The wide-eyed girl,
peddling her earnest newspaper stories?
You, my friend,
are crossing over to the dark side.
I resent that.
- You shouldn't. It's sexy.
- Sexy?
- Really?
- Really.
So do you...? Do you know
where we're going? Because...
- Yeah.
...I'm lost.
Don't worry. I know this city
like the back of my hand.
It's my favorite place
in the whole world.
You know, Gertrude Stein once said:
"America is my country,
and Paris is my hometown."
It's true.
What do you do?
Do you just write stuff like that down...
...and then file it away
to use on us girls?
I'm Christian Thompson.
That's my way.
That's your way. Right.
I work freelance.
I have a lot of free time on my hands.
You know, I never understood...
...why everyone
was so crazy about Paris.
But it is so beautiful.
I can't. I'm sorry, I can't, I...
You know, Nate and I just split up
a couple of days ago, and I can't...
I've had too much wine
and my hearing... Vision...
Judgment's impaired.
No, I barely know you.
I'm in a strange city.
I am out of excuses.
Thank God.
Yes.
Oh, hi. What the hell is this?
What does it look like? It's a mockup.
Yeah. Of...?
Of what American Runway
will look like...
...when Jacqueline Follet
is the new editor in chief.
They're replacing Miranda?
Yeah. And she's bringing me in
to run all the editorial content.
You're really surprised?
Jacqueline's a lot younger than Miranda.
She has a fresher take on things.
Not to mention that American Runway
is one of the most expensive books...
...in the business.
Jacqueline does the same thing
for a lot less money.
And Irv's a businessman, you know.
Miranda will be devastated.
Her whole life is about Runway.
- He can't do that to her.
- It's done.
Irv's gonna tell Miranda
after the party for James.
And she has no idea?
She's a big girl. She'll be fine.
I have to go.
Andy. Andy, it's done.
Baby, it's done.
I'm not your baby.
- Oh, thank God. You're there.
- Excuse me?
I need to talk to you right away.
It's about Jacqueline Follet. She's...
Damn. Shit, shit, shit.
- Yes?
- Oh, hello.
Mr. Ravitz, I'm so sorry to bother you,
but I was wondering...
Have you completely lost your mind?
I need to talk to you.
- Do not disturb me again.
- But... It's just... Miranda!
Miranda?
Miranda. Wait, I need to talk to you.
Irv is making Jacqueline Follet
the editor in chief of Runway.
Christian told me
he's gonna work for her.
Irv is gonna tell you today. I thought
if I told you, you could fix it.
- Do I smell freesias?
- What?
No. I specifically told them...
If I see freesias anywhere...
...I will be very disappointed.
For 72 years, Runway
has been more than a magazine.
It has been a beacon
of elegance and grace.
Miranda Priestly is the finest
possible guardian of that beacon.
Setting a standard
that inspires people across the globe.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you Miranda Priestly.
Thank you, my dear friend.
Thank you very much
for coming today...
...to help celebrate
our dear friend, James Holt.
But before I talk to you about James
and his many accomplishments...
...I would like first
to share some news with you.
As many of you know,
recently Massimo Corteleoni...
...has agreed to finance
the expansion of the James Holt label.
Transforming the work
of this visionary artist...
...into a global brand,
which is really an exciting enterprise.
Runway and James Holt
share many things in common.
Chief among them,
a commitment to excellence.
And so it should come as no surprise...
...that when the time came
for James to choose the new president...
...of James Holt International...
...he chose from within
the Runway family.
And it's my great happiness today
to announce to you all...
...that that person is my friend...
...and long-time esteemed colleague,
Jacqueline Follet.
And now to the main event:
Our celebration of James Holt.
We at Runway are very proud
to have been among the first to...
When the time is right
she'll pay me back.
You sure about that?
No.
But I hope for the best.
I have to.
You thought I didn't know.
I've known what was happening
for quite some time.
It just took me a little while to find
a suitable alternative for Jacqueline.
And that James Holt job
was just so absurdly overpaid...
...that of course she jumped at it.
So I just had to tell Irv
that Jacqueline was unavailable.
Truth is, there is no one
that can do what I do.
Including her.
Any of the other choices
would have found that job impossible...
...and the magazine
would have suffered.
Especially because of the list.
The list of designers, photographers,
editors, writers, models...
...all of whom were found by me,
nurtured by me...
...and have promised me
they will follow me...
...whenever and if ever
I chose to leave Runway.
So he reconsidered.
But I was very, very impressed
by how intently you tried to warn me.
I never thought I would say this,
Andrea, but I really...
I see a great deal of myself in you.
You can see beyond what people want,
and what they need...
...and you can choose for yourself.
I don't think I'm like that.
I...
I couldn't do what you did to Nigel.
I couldn't do something like that.
You already did.
To Emily.
That's not what I...
No, that was different.
I didn't have a choice.
Oh, no, you chose.
You chose to get ahead.
You want this life,
those choices are necessary.
But what if this isn't what I want?
I mean, what if I don't wanna live
the way you live?
Oh, don't be ridiculous, Andrea.
Everybody wants this.
Everybody wants to be us.
I have to be at work in 20 minutes.
What's up?
Well, I just...
I wanted to say
that you were right about everything.
That...
...I turned my back on my friends
and my family...
...and on everything
I believed in and...
- And for what?
- For shoes.
And shirts.
And jackets and belts and...
Nate...
...I'm sorry.
I...
I flew up to Boston
while you were gone.
Interviewed at the Oak Room.
And?
And you're looking at
their new sous-chef.
- I'm moving up there in a couple weeks.
- Oh, that's great. Congratulations.
Don't know what I'm gonna do without
late-night grilled cheeses, but...
I'm pretty sure
they have bread in Boston.
May even have Jarlsberg.
We might be able
to figure something out.
You think?
Yeah.
So, what about you?
I mean, what are you gonna do now?
I actually...
I have a job interview today.
Oh, yeah?
That's what you're wearing?
Shut up. I like this.
Andy. Greg Hill.
- Hello.
- Come on.
These clips are excellent.
This janitors' union thing,
that's exactly what we do here.
My only question is: Runway?
You were there for less than a year.
What the hell kind of a blip is that?
Learned a lot.
In the end, though,
I kind of screwed it up.
I called over there for a reference,
left word with some snooty girl...
...next thing you know, I got a fax
from Miranda Priestly herself...
...saying of all the assistants
she's ever had...
...you were by far
her biggest disappointment.
And if I don't hire you, I am an idiot.
You must have done something right.
Miranda Priestly's office.
Hey, Emily, it's Andy.
Don 't hang up.
I have a favor to ask you.
- You have a favor to ask of me?
- Yeah.
Thing is,
I have all these clothes from Paris...
...and I don't have any place
to wear them...
...so I was wondering
if you could take them off my hands.
Well, I don't know.
It's a huge imposition,
and I'll have to get them taken in.
I mean, they'll drown me.
But I suppose I could help you out.
I'll have Roy pick them up this afternoon.
Thanks, Em, I appreciate it.
Good luck.
You have some very large shoes to fill.
Hope you know that.
I don't understand
why it's so challenging...
...to get my car when I ask for it.
Go.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH]