[Inaudible]
[Gargling]
[Man] You're live in two minutes,Your Royal Highness.
Sir?
Thank you.
Let the microphone do the work, sir.
I'm sure you'll be splendid.Just take your time.
[Warming Up Voice Softly]
Time to go.
[BBC News Reader]Good afternoon.
"This is the BBC National Programand Empire Service...
...taking you to Wembley Stadiumfor the closing ceremony...
...Of the Empire Exhibition.
...Where His Royal Highness,the Duke of York,...
...will read a message from his father;His Majesty King George V."
"Fifty eight British coloniesand dominions have taken part,...
making this the largest exhibitionstaged anywhere in the world."
Remember, sir, three flashes,then steady red means you're live.
[BBC News Reader]"Using the new invention of radio,...
...the opening ceremony was the first timeHis Majesty the King...
...addressed his subjects on the wireless."
"At the close of the first season,
...the heir to the throne,His Royal Highness, the Prince of Wales,...
...made his first broadcast, and today,...
...his younger brother,His Royal Highness, the Duke of York,...
...will give his inaugural broadcastto the nation and the world."
[Horse Whinnies]
[Voice Echoing]I have received...
...from His Majesty the...
[Stammering]
...the...
...the King...
[Continues Stuttering]
[Sir Blandine Bentham] Inhale deep into your lungs,Your Royal Highness.
Relaxes your larynx, does it not?
Cigarette smoking calms the nerves,and gives you confidence.
[Chuckling] Now, if Your Royal Highnesswould be so kind as to open your hand.
It's Sterilized. Now..
One, two,
three, four,
five, six...
...seven. Now, if I may take theliberty, insert them into your mouth?
Excuse me, Doctor.What is the purpose of this?
It's the classic approach.It cured Demosthenes.
That was in Ancient Greece...uhHas it worked since?
[Chuckling] Now, if you would beso kind as to read.
"A wealth of words."
[Mumbling]
Fight against those marbles,Your Royal Highness.
Enunciate.
[Voice Muffled]
A little more concentration,Your Royal Highness.
[Choking]
I nearly swallowed the bloody things!
Thank you so much, Doctor.It's been most, um...
- ...interesting.- Your Royal Highness.
[Stuttering] Insert marbles.He can insert his own bloody marbles.
Tick, tock. Tick, tock.
You know you can'tkeep doing this, Bertie.
- I know.- Mmm.
Promise me...
Promise me no more.
[Elevator Door Closing]
Ah!
Hello?
- Is anyone there?- [Man] I'm just in the loo.
[Toilet Flushes]
Ah, Mrs. Johnson, there you are.
I'm sorry, I don't have a receptionist.I like to keep things simple.
"Poor and contentis rich and rich enough."
- I'm sorry?- Shakespeare. How are you?
- How do you do?- Oh, chuffing along.
Um, now, this is slightly awkward,but I'm afraid you're late.
- Yes. I'm afraid I am.- Where's Mr. Johnson?
Ah... He doesn't know I'm here.
Well, that's not a very promising start.
No. No, look,my husband has seen everyone...
...To no avail.I'm awfully afraid he's given up hope.
- He hasn't seen me.- You’re awfully sure of yourself.
Well, I'm sure of anyonewho wants to be cured.
Of course he wants to be cured.My husband is, um...
- Well, he's required to speak publicly.- Perhaps he should change jobs?
- He can't.- Indentured servitude?
Something of that nature, yes.
Well, we need to have your hubby pop by.
Uh... Tuesday would be good.
He can give me his personal details,I'll make a frank appraisal...
- ...and then we'll take it from there.- Doctor, forgive me.
Uh, I don't have a "hubby."We don't "pop."
And nor do we ever talk aboutour private lives.
No, you must come to us.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Johnson,my game, my turf, my rules.
Mmm.
You'll have to talk this overwith your husband,
and then you can speak to meon the telephone.
Thank you very much for dropping by...Good afternoon.
And what if my husbandwere the Duke of York?
- The Duke of York?- Yes... The Duke of York.
I thought the appointmentwas for Johnson. Forgive me, Your...
- Royal Highness.- ...Royal Highness.
Yes, Johnson was used during the GreatWar, when the Navy didn't want the enemy
- ...to know he was aboard.- Am I...considered the enemy?
You will be, if you remain un-obliging.
You'll appreciate the needfor absolute discretion.
Of course.
How did you find me,Your Royal Highness?
The President of The SocietyFor Speech Therapists.
Eileen McCleod?[Laughs] She's a sport.
Dr McCleod warned me your antipodeanmethods were...
...both "unorthodox" and "controversial."
I warned her thoseare not my favorite words.
I can cure your husband.But for my method to work,...
...I need trust and total equality, herein the safety of my consultation room.
No exceptions.
Oh, well then... In that case...
When can you start?
[Indistinct Chattering]
- She's still sounding a bit rough, mate.- You make me drive too slowly, Dad!
- Did you pick Mum up from bridge?- Yeah, I've hardly been out of the car.
I had a special visitor this afternoon.
- [Boy] May I please leave the table?- How special's special?
No, you must stay, bored stupid, listeningto your parents' inane conversation.
- Thanks, Dad...- And Mum.
- And Mum.- Me, too.
- You meeting Jean?- No. Someone else.
- Doctor? Doctor?- Hmm?
Go and help your brotherwith the washing up.
- I'm fine.- [Woman] Who is it, Lionel?
Why bring it upif you can't talk about it?
Myrtle, it's just a womanlooking to help her husband.
Oh, and I had a call... for an audition.
- One of my favorites.- Aren't they all?
It Could be a lot of fun.
[Door Shuts]I'm sure you'll be splendid.
In the amateur scene,they're a highly regarded group.
From Putney.
[Woman] No, that's all girls.Tomorrow, chapter four, "The Flight."
[Girl] Mama,I long to know where they fly to.
- I can't wait!- Oh, to fly away.
Weren't they lucky?
Now Papa, tell a story.
Can't I be a penguin instead?[Girls Giggling]
Well, no, I want a penguin story.
Very quickly.[Clears Throat]
Once there were...[Stuttering] two princesses.
Princess Elizabethand Princess Margaret,
whose papa was a penguin.
This was because he'd beenturned into one by a wicked witch.
This was very inconvenient for himbecause he loved...
...to hold his princesses in his arms.
But you can't if you're a penguinbecause you...
- ...you have wings like herrings.- Herrings don't have wings.
Penguins have wings which are...are shaped like herrings.
And what made matters worse is thatshe... she sent him to the South Pole,
which is an awfully long walk back if...
...if you can't fly.
So when he reached the water, he...
...he dived in, through the depths,
so fast that he was inSouthampton Waters by lunchtime.
And from there,he took the 2:30 to Weybridge,
changed at Clapham Junction, asked a...
...a passing mallard the wayto Buckingham Palace,
swam up The Thames,out through the plughole
and gave the cook, Mamaand Mrs. Whittaker quite a shock.
Now, when the girlsheard all the commotion,
they ran to the kitchen,where they gave him a...
...a good scrub, a mackerel and a kiss.
And as they kissed him...
...guess what he turned into?
- A handsome prince.- A short-tailed albatross.
- [Disappointed] Oh.- With wings so big,
that he could wrap them both aroundhis two girls together.
Now, girls. Time for bed. Come on.
- And take those horses to the stable.- Quickly, now.
- You have exactly a minute.- Good night.
Feed them, brush them and to bed.
- Will Mrs. Simpson be there?- My brother's insisting.
- Is he serious?- About her coming to dinner?
No. About her.
- A married woman? He can't be.- She can.
By the way, I think I've foundsomeone rather interesting.
On Harley Street. A doctor.
Out of the question.
I'm not having this conversation again.Mat... Matter's settled.
Mmm. His approachseems rather different.
[Indistinct Whispering]
Now?
Now.
Now is the winter of our discontent,
made glorious summerby this sun of York.
And all the cloudsthat lour'd upon our house
In the deep bosom of the ocean buried.
Now are our brows boundwith... victorious... wreaths;
Thank you.
- Lovely diction, Mr...?- Logue. Lionel Logue.
Well, Mr. Logue,
I'm not hearing the criesof a deformed creature
yearning to be king.
Nor did I realize Richard IIIwas King of the Colonies.
I do know all the lines.I've played the role before.
- Sydney?- Perth.
Major theater town, is it?
- Enthusiastic.- Ah.
I was well reviewed.
Yes.
Well, Lionel,I think our dramatic society
is looking for someone slightly younger.
And a... little more regal.
- There you are.- Thank you.
- Oh.- Mmm.
No, you have to shut that one first.
Close that one first. That's it.
Where did you find this... physician?
Classifieds. Next to a"French model, Shepherd's Market."
No, he comes highly recommended.
Charges substantial feesto help the poor.
Oh, dear. Perhaps he's a Bolshevik.
Ah, there's no receptionist.Likes to keep things simple.
Uh... The Johnsons.
You can go in now, Mr. Johnson.
Lionel says wait hereif you wish, Mrs. Johnson.
Or, it being a...
[Stuttering]... pleasant day...
P...perhaps take a stroll.
Was that all right, Lionel?
Marvelous, Willie.
You can stay here and wait for your mum.
Mrs. Johnson.
Mr. Johnson. Do come in.
Would you like a sweetie?
He's a good lad, Willie.
He could hardly make a sound, you know,when he first came to me.
My boys make those.They're good, aren't they?
Please, make yourself comfortable.
I was told not to sit too close.
Well I believe when speaking with a prince,
One waits for the princeto choose the topic.
[Stuttering]
Waiting for me to...
...commence a conversation,one can wait rather a long wait.
Ah, yes, well...
Do you know any jokes?
- Timing isn't my strong suit.- [Chuckles] Cup of tea?
- No. No, thank you.- I think I'll have one.
[Lionel Humming]
Aren't you going to start treating me,Dr. Logue?
Only if you're interestedin being treated.
Please, call me Lionel.
No, I... prefer Doctor.
I prefer Lionel.
- What will I call you?- Your Royal Highness.
Then... it's "sir" after that.
It's a little bit formal for here.I prefer names.
Prince Albert Frederick Arthur...
...George?
How about Bertie?
- Only my family uses that.- Perfect.
In here, it's better if we're equals.
If... if we were equals,I wouldn't be here.
I'd be... at home with my wife,
and no one would give a damn.
Please, don't do that.
I'm sorry?
I believe sucking smoke into your lungs,well, it will kill you.
My physicians say it relaxes the...
- ...the throat.- They're idiots.
- They've all been knighted.- Makes it official, then.
My castle, my rules.
Thank you.
What was your earliest memory?
- What on earth do you mean?- Your first recollection.
I'm not...
...here to discuss personal matters.
- Well, why are you here, then?- Because I bloody well stammer!
- You have a bit of a temper.- One of my many faults.
- When did the defect start?- I've always been this way.
- I doubt that.- Don't...
- ...tell me, it's my stammer.- It's my field.
I can assure you, no infantstarts to speak with a stammer.
When did yours start?
- Four or five.- That's typical.
So I've been told.
I... I can't remember not doing it.
I can believe that.Do you hesitate when you think?
- Don't be ridiculous.- How about when you talk to yourself?
Everyone natters to themselvesoccasionally, Bertie.
Stop... Stop calling me that.
I'm not going to call you anything else.
Then we shan't speak.[Water Boiling]
[Blows Out Flame]
Are you charging for this, Doctor?
A fortune.
[Lionel Whistling]
I'll just let that brew.
So... when you talk to yourself,do you stammer?
No... of course not.
Well, that proves that your impedimentisn't a permanent part of you.
What do you think was the cause?
I don't... don't know.
I... I don't... I don't care.
I... I stammer.
No one can fix it.
I'll bet you that you can readflawlessly, right here, right now.
And if I win the bet,I get to ask you more questions.
- And if I win?- You don't have to answer them.
One usually... wagers money.
A bob each to keep it sweet?
- Let's see your shilling.- I don't... carry money.
I had a funny feeling you mightn't.
I'll stake you, and you canpay me back next time.
- If there is a next time.- I haven't agreed to take you on yet.
So please stand, uh,and take a look at that.
From there.
I... I can't read this.
Well, then you owe mea shilling for not trying.
[Stutters]
To be...
...or not to be, that...
- Can't read it.- Uh-uh-uh! I haven't finished yet.
I'm going to record your voice and thenplay it back to you on the same machine.
This is brilliant.It's the latest thing from America.
It's a Silvertone.
Pop these on.
There's a bob in this, mate.You could go home rich.
[  Classical Music Playing  ]
- You're playing music!- I know.
So how can I hear what I'm saying?
Well, surely a prince's brainknows what its mouth's doing?
You're not... well acquaintedwith royal princes, are you?
[  Music Plays Loudly  ]
[Voice Muffled]
Hopeless.
Hopeless!
You were sublime.
Would I lie to a prince of the realmto win 12 pennies?
I've no idea...
...what an Australianmight do for that sort of money.
Let me play it back to you.
No.
All right, then, well,I get to ask you the questions.
Thank you, Doctor. I don't...
...feel this is for me.
Thank you for your time.
Goodbye.
Sir?
The recording is free.Please keep it as a souvenir.
No.
Oh, well.
[Whispering]Bugger.
[George V] For the present, the workto which we are all equally bound,
is to arrive at a reasoned tranquilitywithin our borders,
...to regain prosperityat this time of depression
without self-seeking,and to carry with us
those whom the burden of the past years
has disheartened or overborne.
To all, to each,I wish a happy Christmas.
God bless you.
[Man]And off air.
Easy when you know how.
[Man #2]Sir?
Have a go yourself.
- [Man] Congratulations, sir.- [George V] Ah, Mr. Wood.
Splendid fellow.Chap who taught me everything I know.
- Let the microphone do the work.- Sir.
- Thank you.- Gentlemen.
Sit up. Straight back.
Face boldly up to the bloody thingand stare it square in the eye,
as would any decent Englishman.Show who's in command.
Papa, I d...don't... thu...thu...think I c... c... can read this.
This devilish device will changeeverything if you don't.
In the past, all a king had to dowas look respectable in uniform
and not fall off his horse.
Now, we must invade people's homesand ingratiate ourselves with them.
This family's been reduced to thoselowest, basest of all creatures.
We've become actors.
We're not a family, we're a firm.
Yet at any moment,some of us may be out of work.
Your darling brother and future king,
the only wife he appears interested inis invariably the wife of another.
- He's broken off with Lady Furness.- And taken up with Mrs. Simpson.
A woman with two husbands living.I told him straight.
No divorced personcan ever be received at court.
He said it made him sublimely happy.[Scoffs]
I imagine that wasbecause she was sleeping with him.
"I give you my word,"this is what he said.
"I give you my word,we've never had immoral relations."
Stared square intohis father's face and lied.
When I'm dead,that boy will ruin himself,
this family and this nationwithin 12 months.
Who will pick up the pieces, hmm?Herr Hitler intimidating half of Europe.
Marshal Stalin the other half.
Who will stand between us,
the jackbootsand the proletarian abyss?
You?
[Sighs]Well?
With your older brothershirking his duties,
you're going to have to doa lot more of this.
Have a go yourself.
Through the...[Stuttering]
...wireless...- Get it out, boy.
...one of the...
... m... marvels of m...
"Modern." Just take your time.Form your words carefully.
...science...
...I am enabled, this ...
Relax.
Just try it!
...this Christmas Day...
...to speak to all my...
Do it!
[  Ambrose and His Orchestra -Who's Been Polishing the Sun?  ]
Lying... bastard.
[Needle Scratches On Record]
- [Bertie] You're playing music.- [Lionel] I know.
[Bertie] So how can I...hear what I'm saying?
[Lionel] Well, surely a prince's brainknows what its mouth's doing.
[Bertie] You're not... well acquaintedwith royal princes, are you?
"To be or not be,that is the question.
Whether tis nobler in the mind to suffer
the slings and arrowsof outrageous fortune,
or to take armsagainst a sea of troubles,
and by opposing end them?
To die, to sleep no more,
and by a sleep to say the end
is the heartacheand the thousand natural shocks
the flesh is heir to.Tis a consummation hopeless."
Hopeless!
Strictly business. No...
- ...personal nonsense.- Yes, I thought I'd made that clear...
- ...in our interview.- Have you got the shilling you owe me?
- No, I haven't.- Didn't think so.
Besides, you... you tricked me.
Physical exercisesand tricks are important,
but what you're asking will only dealwith the surface of the problem.
Is that sufficient? Uh, no.
As far as I see it, my husband hasmechanical difficulties with his speech.
- I...- Maybe just deal with that.
I...
- I'm willing to work hard, Dr. Logue.- Lionel.
[Stammering] Are you...Are you willing to do your part?
All right. You want mechanics?
We need to relax your jaw muscles,strengthen your tongue,
by repeating tongue twisters.For example, "I'm a thistle-sifter.
I have a sieve of sifted thistlesand a sieve of unsifted thistles.
- Because I am a thistle-sifter."- Fine.
And you do have a flabby tummy,so we'll need to spend some time
strengthening your diaphragm.Simple mechanics.
- That's all we ask.- All that's about a shilling's worth.
Forget about the blessed shilling!
Perhaps, upon occasions...
...you might be requested to assist...
...in coping with...
...with some minor event.Would that be agreeable?
Of course.
Yes, and that would be the full extentof your services.
- Shall I see you next week?- I shall see you every day.
[Both Vocalizing]Ahahahahhahahahahahahahahahahahah.
Feel the looseness of the jaw.
[Vocalizing Continues]
Good. Little bounces. Bounces.
Shoulders loose, shoulders loose.
Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful.Now, loose.
[Lionel] Take a nice deep breath.Expand the chest.
Put your hands onto your ribs.
Deeper. Good.
- How do you feel?- Full of hot air.
Isn't that whatpublic speaking's all about?
My wife and I are gladto visit this important...
[Lionel] Take a good deep breath,and up comes Your Royal Highness.
And slowly exhale,and down comes Your Royal Highness.
- You all right, Bertie?- [Groaning] Yes.
It's actually quite good fun.
Mmm... Mother.
[Lionel]Shorten the humming each time.
Mother. Mmm...
...manufacturing district...- [Lionel] Another deep breath.
- And Jack and Jill.- [Bertie] Jack and Jill.
- [Lionel] Went up the hill.- Went up the hill.
Now, just sway.
Perfect.
...will not permit us to...- [Lionel] Loosen the shoulders.
[Bertie] Ding dong bell,pussy's in the well.
Who put her in? Little Tommy Tin.
You have a short memory, Bertie.Come on.
- A cow, a cow...- A king.
A... a king...
[All Vocalizing]
Anyone who can shout vowels at an openwindow can learn to deliver a speech.
- Fourteen, 15!- [Lionel] Good. Deep breath, and...
It is...
- [Lionel] Let the words flow.- No, it doesn't bloody work.
[Lionel] Come on, one more time, Bertie.You can do it.
A sieve of thisted siphles.
Gah! Mah! Bah!
[Vocalizing]
[Lionel]Father.
- [Bertie] Father.- [Lionel] Father.
- [Lionel] Aim for the a-t-h.- Father.
- [Lionel] Father.- Father.
Father. Father.
[Airplane Approaching]
- Hello, Bertie.- Hello, David.
- Nice of you to come out.- Not at all.
You been waiting long?
Christ, bloody freezing.
Where have you been?
- I've been busy.- So have I.
- Elizabeth has pneumonia.- Oh, I'm sorry.
- She'll recover.- Father won't.
I'll drive.
Old bugger's doing this on purpose.
- Dying?- Departing prematurely.
To... To complicate matters with Wallis.
For heaven's sake, David.You know how long he's been ill.
Wallis explained. She's terribly cleverabout these things.
[Lord Wigram] Whereas my letters patentunder the Great Seal
bearing date of Westminsterthe 11th day of June 1912,
His Majesty King George the Fifthdid constitute order
and declare that thereshould be a Guardian...
- What's going on here?- ...custos regne...
I cannot follow you.I'm confused and I don't understand...
It's the Orderof the Council of State, sir.
So that we may act on your behalf...
...much clearer to me, I'm afraid...
- Well, I'm so confused that...- Approved.
Thank you.
- [Man] Let me help you, sir.- Ah, yes...
- Thank you, sir.- Thank you.
- Feeling a little better, sir?- No, I'm not feeling any better.
I feel dreadful. Ah...
Been, uh, ice skating? Ice skating?
No. No, George.
[Clocks Ticking]
[David] Yes. Yes, all right, of course.
I know, darling.A talk, even a lovely long talk
is a poor substitutefor holding tight and making drowsy.
Nor making our own drowsies either,as we've had to do too often lately.
- [Bertie] David. Dinner.- I'm on with Wallis.
It's Bertie.
No. No, it's not important.
[Groans]I don't want to.
No. Telephone me later?
All right, goodbye.[Hangs Up Phone]
- Wallis misses me terribly.- Mama says you're late for dinner.
She forgets Papa's bloody clocksare all half an hour fast.
How's the King?I... I hope he's not in pain.
No, no, sir.His Majesty's quieter now.
Thank you.
David, if your father were here,tardiness would not be tolerated.
None of this unpleasantnesswould be tolerated.
You know, sir, I appreciatethat you are different from your father,
both in outlook and... temperament.
I want you to know that wheneverthe King questioned your conduct,
I tried, in your interest,
to present itin the most favorable light.
Mmm. I can always trust youto have my best interests at heart.
[Whispering Indistinctly]
I fear our vigil will not beof long duration. Please continue.
Let us commend our brother Georgeto the mercy of God,
Our Maker and Redeemer.
Long live the King.
I hope I will make goodas he has made good.
[Sobbing]
- What on earth was that?- Poor Wallis.
Now, I'm trapped.
[Man On Radio] And in these last 25crowded, troubled, glorious years,
if there is one thingthat King George has taught,
it is the art of the leader whois also a brother to his followers.
As long as he lived, he wasthe guiding star of a great nation.
- Dad?- Mmm-hmm?
- [Man] When he died...- Time for a Shake, Dad?
[Radio]... the little childrencried in the streets.
- You sure?- Go on.
Put your thinking caps on.
- I bet it's the Scottish play.- No, it's Othello. It's always Othello.
[Lionel Groaning Theatrically]
Art thou afeard?
- Be not afeard.- Caliban.
Oh, for heaven's sake.That was a lucky guess.
Don't listen to egghead. Go on, Dad.
The isle is full of noises,sounds and sweet airs
that give delight, and hurt not.
Sometimes a thousand twanglinginstruments will hum about mine ears,
and sometimes voices, that,if then I had waked after long sleep,
will make me sleep again. All right,clever clogs, so what comes next?
And then, in dreaming,methought the clouds would...
- The clouds methought.- The clouds methought would open,
and show riches ready to drop upon me,
that when I waked,I cried to dream again.
That's such a sad thought.[Knock On Door]
My next patient must be a bit early.You better go, lads, I'm sorry.
Won't be a moment, Clifford.
Bertie?
They told me not to expect you.
I'm sorry about your father.
- I don't wish to intrude.- Not at all. Please, come in. Come in.
I've been practicing. An hour a day.
In spite of everything.
What's going on there?
Oh, I was... Sorry.
Mucking around with my kids.
Do you feel like working today?
- A Curtis bi-plane.- I'll put on some hot milk.
Logue. Logue.
I'd kill for something stronger.
[Lionel] I wasn't therefor my father's death.
- Still makes me sad.- [Bertie] I can imagine so.
- What did your father do?- He was a brewer.
At least there was free beer.
Here's to the memory of your father.
I was informed, after the fact,
that my father's...
My father's last words were...
..."Bertie has more guts than therest of his brothers put together."
He couldn’t say that to my face.
My brother.
What about him?
[Straining To Speak][Lionel] Try singing it.
- I'm sorry.- What songs do you know?
- Songs?- Yeah, songs.
- "Swanee River."- I love that song.
- It happens to be my favorite.- Sing me the chorus.
No. Certainly not.
You know...I always wanted to build models.
But... Father wouldn't allow it.
He... collected stamps,so we had to collect stamps.
You can finish that off if you sing.
"My brother DavidDum, dum, dum, dum..."
- I'm not going to sit here warbling.- You can with me.
- Because you're peculiar.- I take that as a compliment.
Well...
Rules are rules.
I'm not... crooning "Swanee River".
"Camptown Races", then."My brother David said to me...
...Doo-dah, doo-dah"
- Continuous sound will give you flow.- No.
Does it feel strangenow that David's on the throne?
To tell the truth, it was a relief.
Knowing I...
...wouldn't be... King.
But unless he produces an heir,you're next in line.
And your daughter, Elizabeth,would then succeed you.
"You're barking upthe wrong tree now, Doctor, Doctor"
"Lionel"
See? You didn't stammer.
Of course I didn't stammer,I was singing.
Well, as a little reward, you getto put some glue on these struts.
- Your boy... won't mind?- No, not at all.
David and I were... very close.
Young bucks, you know.
Did you chase the same girls?
David was always very helpfulin... arranging introductions.
We shared the...
...expert ministrations
Of Paulette in the Palace.
Not at the same time, of course.
- Did David ever tease you?- Oh, yes, they all did.
"Buh-buh-buh-Bertie."
Father encouraged it.
Said, "Get it out, boy!"Said it would make me stop.
He said, "I was afraid of my father
and my children are...damn well gonna be afraid of me!"
Are you naturally right-handed?
Left.
I was... punished,and now I use the right.
Yes, that's very common with stammerers.
- Any other corrections?- Knock knees.
[Stammering]Metal splints were made.
Worn... worn day and night.
- Must have been painful.- Bloody agony.
Straight legs now.
Who were you closest to in your family?
Nannies.
Not my first nanny. She...
She loved David. Hated me.
When we were...
...presented to my parentsfor the daily viewing,
she would... she'd pinch me
so that I'd cry and be handed backto her immediately.
And then she would...
[Struggling To Speak][Lionel] Sing it.
# Then she wouldn't feed me #
# Far, far away #
Took my parents...three years to notice.
As you... as you can imagine,caused some stomach problems.
Still.
What about your brother, Johnnie?
Were you close to him?
Johnnie... sweet boy.
Had...
...epilepsy.
And he was... different.
He died at... 13.
Hidden from view.
I'm... I'm told it's not... catching.
Do you want a top-up?
Please.
[Bertie]You know...
...Lionel, you're...
...you're the firstordinary Englishman...
- Australian.- ...I've ever really spoken to.
When I'm... driven through the streets
and I see the, you know,the common man staring at me, I...
...I'm struck by how littleI know of his life
and how little he knows of mine.
- Thank you.- What are friends for?
I wouldn't know.
[Bertie]I sifted seven...
...thick-stalked thistlesthrough a strong, thick sieve.
- I sifted seven thick-stalked...- That's enough now, darling.
Listen, I have to keep doing this,it's awful. I sifted seven...
- Oh, no.- ...thick-stalked...
One-hundred-year-old sprucesremoved to improve the view?
Who does she think she is?
Nonetheless, we must tryto be pleasant towards Mrs. Simpson.
- She calls me "The Fat Scottish Cook."- You're not fat.
I'm getting plump.
Well, you seldom cook.
[Chuckles]
- I sifted seven...- Shut up.
...thick sieves...[Muffled] I sifted seven...
[Laughing]
[  Up-Tempo Music Playing  ]Three, two, one and...
[Man] Their Royal Highnessesthe Duke and Duchess of York.
Oh, how lovely to see you both.
Welcome to our little country shack.
I came at the invitation of the King.
Your Majesty.
- You all right?- Sorry we're late.
Very nice to see you... Mrs. Simpson.
Very nice.
Hello, David. Making some...
...changes to the garden, I see.
Yes, I'm not quite finished yet.
Don't tell me I behaved badly,Mr. Churchill.
On the contrary, Your Royal Highness.
Etiquette decrees that royaltyshould be greeted by the official host,
in this case, the King. Not a commoner.
Thank you.
- What is her hold on him?- I've no idea.
Apparently, she has certain skills
acquired in an establishmentin Shanghai.
David.
Just be a sec, darling.Would you excuse me?
- David, I've been trying to see you.- I've been terribly busy.
- Doing what?- Kinging.
Really? Kinging is a...
...a precarious business these days.Where's the Russian tsar?
- Where's cousin Wilhelm?- [Sighs] You're being dreary.
Is kinging laying off 80... staffand buying more pearls for Wallis,
while people are marching across Europesinging The Red Flag?
- Herr Hitler will sort them out.- Who will sort out Herr Hitler?
Where's the bloody 23?
And you put that womanin our mother's suite!
- Mama's not still in the bed, is she?- That's not funny.
Here it is. Wallis likes the very best.
I don't care what womanyou carry on with at night,
as long as you... show upfor duty in the morning.
Wallis is not just some womanI'm carrying on with.
We intend to marry.
- Excuse me?- She's filing a petition for divorce.
Good God.
Can't you just give hera nice house and a title?
- I'm not having her as my mistress.- The Church doesn't recognize divorce,
- and you are the... head of the Church.- Haven't I any rights?
- Many privileges.- Not the same thing.
Your beloved common manmay marry for love. Why not me?
If you were... a common man,
On what basis could you...possibly claim to be King?
Sounds like you'vestudied our wretched Constitution.
- Sounds like you haven't.- That's what this is about.
Brushing up.Hence, the elocution lessons.
- That's the scoop around town.- I'm trying to...
Yearning for a larger audience,are we, B-B-Bertie?
Don't...
[Struggles To Speak]What's that?
I'm sorry, I...
Younger brother trying to pusholder brother off the throne.
P-P-Positively mediaeval.
[Pops Cork]Wallis.
Ah. Where have you been all this time?
- Who have you been talking to?- Never you mind.
[Sighs] What a very complicatedlittle King you are.
I try to be.[Wallis Chuckles]
All that work... down the drain.
My own brother.
I couldn't say a single wordto him in reply.
Why do you stammer so much morewith David than you ever do with me?
Because you're bloody wellpaid to listen.
- Bertie, I'm not a geisha girl.- Stop trying to be so bloody clever.
What is it about Davidthat stops you speaking?
What is it about you that bloodywell makes you want to go on about him
- the whole bloody time?- Vulgar but fluent.
- You don't stammer when you swear.- Bugger off!
- Is that the best you can do?- Well, bloody...
...bugger to you, you beastly bastard.
Oh, a public school prigcould do better than that.
Shit.
Shit, shit, shit.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit!
Yes, defecation flowstrippingly from the tongue.
- Because I'm angry!- Do you know the "f" word?
- [Stammering] Fornication?- Oh, Bertie.
Fuck. Fuck!
Fuck, fuck, fuckin' fuck!Fuck, fuck and bugger!
Bugger, bugger, buggedy, fuck!
- Fuck, ass!- Yes!
- Balls, balls, fuckety shit.- You see? Not a hesitation.
Willy, shit and fuck! And tits.
- Dad, what's going on?- [Lionel] Sorry.
Just finish your homework.
Well, that's a side of youwe don't get to see all that often.
No.
No, we're not supposed to, really.Not publicly.
- Let's get some air.- No, I don't think that's a good idea.
[Lionel] What's the matter?Why are you so upset?
Logue, you have no idea.
My... my brother
is infatuated with a...
...woman who's been married twice.
She's asking for a divorce,and he's determined to marry her.
- Jesus.- Mrs. Wallis Simpson...
- ...of Baltimore.- That's not right.
- Queen Wallis of Baltimore.- Unthinkable.
- Can he do it?- Absolutely not.
But he's going to anyway.All hell's broken loose.
- Can't they just carry on privately?- If only they would.
Where does this leave you?
I know my place. I...
I... I will do anything...
...in my power to keepmy brother on the throne.
Is it that serious?
- Your place may well be on the throne.- I am not an alternative to my brother.
- You can outshine David.- Don't take liberties!
- That's bordering on treason.- I'm just saying you could be King.
- You could do it.- That is treason.
I'm trying to get you to realizeyou needn't be governed by fear.
I've had enough of this.
- What are you so afraid of?- Your poisonous words!
Why did you come to me?You're not some middle-class banker
who wants elocution lessonsso you can chitchat...
Don't attempt to instruct meon my duties!
I am the son of a... King.
And the brother of... of a King.
You're the disappointing sonof a brewer.
A jumped-up jackeroo from the outback.
You're a nobody.These sessions are over.
[Man #1]Through here, sir.
[Man #2] It's not because she's anAmerican. That is the least of it.
It's because she's a soonto be twice divorced American.
And the King,as head of the Church of England,
cannot marry a divorced woman.
And, sir, I apologizefor the nature of this.
According to Scotland Yard,
the King has not alwayspossessed exclusive rights
to Mrs. Simpson's...favors and affections...
...sharing them with amarried used car salesman,
a certain Mr. Guy Trundle.
[Coughs]
In addition, it is alsorumored Hitler's ambassador,
Count von Ribbentrop,sends her 17 carnations every day.
Should His Majesty continue to ignorethe advice of his government,
he must abdicate.
Otherwise, his governmenthas no choice but to resign.
Prime Minister,you'd leave a country without a...
...a government?
Does the King do what he wants?
Or does he do whatthe people expect him to do?
[Man On Radio] As crowds in DowningStreet watch ministers come and go,
there is raised an age-old problem:Can a king separate his personal life
- from his public duty...- What's the matter, love?
I'm just having trouble with a patient.
[Myrtle]That isn't like you.
- Why?- He's scared.
He's afraid of his own shadow.
Isn't that why they come to you?
This fellow couldreally be somebody great.
He's fighting me.
Perhaps he doesn't want to be great.
Perhaps that's what you want.
I might have overstepped the mark.
Apologize. Do you both good.
[Footsteps Approaching]
I'm very sorry, Mr. Logue,the Duke is busy.
I'm happy to wait.Or I could come back later.
As I said, the Duke is terribly busy.
[Door Opens]
Thank you.
Parliament will not supportthe marriage.
But there are other reasons for concern.
He was careless with state papers.He lacked commitment and resolve,
and there are those who areworried about where he will stand
when war comes with Germany.
- We're not coming to that?- Indeed we are, sir.
Prime Minister Baldwin may deny this,but Hitler's intent is crystal clear.
War with Germany will come.
And we will need a Kingwhom we can all stand behind, united.
I fear my...
...brother is not of sound mind...
...at this time.
Have you thoughtwhat you will call yourself? Hmm?
[Struggles To Speak]
Certainly not Albert, sir.Too Germanic. [Chuckles]
[Stammering]
What about George?After your father?
George the Sixthhas a rather nice continuity to it.
Don't you think?
David. Thank God.
[Door Shuts]You look exhausted.
How are you bearing up?
Bertie, the decision's been made. I...
I'm going.
- I can't accept that...- I'm afraid there's no other way.
I must marry her.
My mind's made up. I'm... sorry.
That's a terrible thing to hear.
Nobody wants that.
I, least of all.
[David On Radio]At long last,
I am able to say a few words of my own.
I have never wantedto withhold anything,
but until now it has not beenconstitutionally possible
for me to speak.
A few hours ago,I discharged my last duty
as King and Emperor,
and now that I have been succeededby my brother,
the Duke of York,
my first words must beto declare my allegiance to him.
This I do with all my heart.
You all know the reasons which haveimpelled me to renounce the throne,
but you must believe me when I tell you
that I have found it impossibleto carry the heavy burden
Of responsibilityand to discharge my duties as King,
as I would wish to do
without the help and supportof the woman I love.
[Continuing On Radio]And I want you to know,
this decision has beenmade less difficult to me
by the sure knowledge that my brother,
with his long trainingin the public affairs of this country,
and with his fine qualities,
will be able to take my place forthwith
without interruption or injury
to the life and progress of the Empire.
[Bell Chimes]
[Doors Shut]
I meet you today...
...in...
...in circumstances which are...
[Struggling To Speak]
- [Elizabeth] I'm sure you'll love it.- [Margaret] There you go.
Thank you, darling.Saddles. Margaret.
- There's Montezuma.- Oh, here's one.
- Mama, here's a horse and saddle.- Thank you. Oops.
- Don't worry, Sally. We'll get you...- Mama?
- Yes?- Will we have space for our horses...
- ...in our new home?- Course we will, darling.
We'll have a palace of rooms.
[Whispers]Curtsey.
Your Majesty.
How was it?
[Bertie] I was trying to...familiarize myself
with... what a state paper looks like.
It's a...
...dispatch from Mr. Baldwin,which I don't understand a word of.
David's finances.
[Chuckles]Christmas... broadcast.
- Think that would be a mistake.- No, don't worry about that.
Oh.
Plans for the Coronation.
[Voice Breaking] Think that would bean even bigger mistake.
- [Crying] I'm not a King.- Oh, shush.
I'm a Naval officer. That's all I know.
I'm not a King. I'm not a King.
- I'm sorry.- No.
- I'm sorry.- No, don't be silly. Please.
[Sniffling]
Oh, my dear.
My dear, dear man.
- I'm sorry.- You know,
I refused your firsttwo marriage proposals,
not because I didn't love you,
but because I couldn't bearthe idea of a Royal life.
Couldn't bear the idea of a lifeof tours, public duty, of...
Well, a life that no longerwas really to be my own.
But then I thought, he stammersso beautifully, they'll leave us alone.
[Sniffles]
[Indistinct Chattering]
[Knocking On Door]
Waiting for a King to apologize,one can wait rather a long wait.
I'm afraid we're slightly late.
This is home.
Myrtle's at bridge.I made sure the boys were out.
It's lovely. Absolutely lovely.
- Oh! May I sit down?- Yes, of course.
- Would you like some tea, ma'am?- Yes, I'll help myself.
Now, off you go.Or must I knock your heads together?
Here's your shilling.
I...
I understand...
...what you were trying to say, Logue.
I went about it the wrong way.
I'm sorry.
So, here I am.
Is the nation ready for two...minutes of radio silence?
Every stammerer always fearsgoing back to square one.
I don't let that happen.
If I fail in my duty,
David could come back.I've seen the placards.
"God save our... King."
They don't mean me.
Every monarch in history
has succeeded someone who's dead
Or just about to be.
My predecessor is not only alive,but very much so.
It's a bloody mess.
Couldn't even give thema Christmas speech.
- Like your dad used to do?- Precisely.
He's not here anymore.
Yes, he is.He's on that shilling I gave you.
[Chuckles]Easy enough to give away.
You don't have to carry himaround in your pocket.
Or your brother.
You don't need to be afraidof the things you were afraid of
when you were five.
[Sighs]
You're very much your own man, Bertie.
Am I?
- Your face is next, mate.- [Myrtle] Lionel, dear!
Myrtle.
- [Bertie] Is this your wife?- [Lionel] Yes.
Bertie. Come here.
- Are you all right, Logue?- Yes.
- [Bertie] Shouldn't we go through?- [Lionel] Trust me, it's important.
- [Bertie] What is it?- Oh!
- You're...- It's "Your Majesty" the first time.
After that, it's "Ma'am." As in "ham."
Not "malm" as in "palm."
I haven't told her about us.
Sit down, relax.
I'm told your husbandcalls my husband Bertie.
And my husband callsyour husband Lionel.
I trust you won't call me Liz.
Your Majesty, you maycall me Mrs. Logue, ma'am.
Very nice to meet you, Mrs. Logue.
- Logue, we can't stay here all day.- Yes, we can.
- Logue!- I need to wait for the right moment.
- Logue, you're being a coward.- You're damn right.
Get out there, man.
Hello, Myrtle, darling.
You're early.
I believe you two have met,but I don't think you know...
...king George the Sixth.- It's very nice to meet you.
Will Their Majestiesbe staying to dinner?
We'd love to, such a treat,but alas a...
...previous engagement. What a pity.
- Archbishop.- Welcome, Your Majesty.
What a glorious transformation, sir.
I hope you'll forgive usif we continue our preparations?
Now, allow me to guide youthrough the ceremony.
We begin, of course,at the West door into the nave.
I see all your pronouncementsare to be broadcast, Archbishop.
Ah, yes. Wireless.
It is, indeed, a Pandora's box,
and I'm afraid I've also hadto permit the newsreel cameras.
The product of whichI shall personally edit.
Without momentary hesitations.
This is Dr. Logue of Harley Street.
He's... my speech therapist.
- Your Grace.- Had I known that Your Majesty
was seeking assistance, I shouldhave made my own recommendation.
Dr. Logue will...
...will be attending the Coronation.
Of course I'll speak to the Dean,but it will be extremely difficult.
I should like the...
...doctor to be seated in the...
...King's Box.
[Archbishop] But members of your familywill be seated there, sir.
That is why it is suitable.
And now, if you don't mind, Your Grace,we need the premises.
My dear fellow,this is Westminster Abbey.
The Church must prepare His Majesty.
My preparations are equallyas important.
With complete privacy,if you don't mind.
Those are my wishes, Your Grace.
I will place the Abbeyat Your Majesty's disposal,
this evening. Your Majesty.
[Indistinct Murmuring]
I can't believe I'm walkingon Chaucer and Handel and Dickens.
Everything all right?Let's get cracking.
I'm not here to rehearse, Dr. Logue.
Call me Lionel.
True, you... never...
...called yourself Doctor. I did that...
...for you.
No training.
No diploma, no...
...qualifications.
Just... a great deal of nerve.
The Star Chamber inquisition, is it?
You asked for trust.
And... total equality.
Bertie, I heard you at Wembley.I was there.
My son Laurie said, "Dad, do you thinkyou could help that poor man?"
- What, as a failed actor?- It's true.
I'm not a doctor.And yes, I acted, a bit.
Well, I recited in pubs.I taught elocution in schools.
When the Great War came,
all our soldiers were returningto Australia from the front,
a lot of them shell-shocked,unable to speak.
Somebody said, Lionel,"You're very good at this speech stuff.
Do you think you could possiblyhelp these poor buggers?"
I did muscle therapy,exercises, relaxation,
but I knew I had to go deeper.
Those poor young blokeshad cried out in fear.
No one was listening to them.
My job was to give them faithin their own voice,
and let them know thata friend was listening.
That must ringa few bells with you, Bertie.
You give a very nobleaccount of yourself.
- Make inquiries. It's all true.- Inquiries have been made.
You have no idea who I havebreathing down my neck.
I vouched for you, and you have no...
- ...credentials.- But lots of success.
I can't show you a certificate.There was no training then.
Everything I know,I know from experience.
And that war was some experience.
My plaque says,"L. Logue, Speech Defects."
Not "Doctor."There are no letters after my name.
- Lock me in the Tower.- I would if I could.
- On what charge?- Fraud.
With war looming, you've saddledthis nation with a voiceless...
...King. You've destroyedthe happiness of my family,
all for the sake of ensnaringa star... patient you couldn't...
...possibly hope to assist.
It'll be like mad...
...King George the Third.
I'll be... Mad King...
...George the Stammerer...
...who let his people downso badly in their hour of need.
What are you doing? Get up!You can't sit there! Get up!
- Why not? It's a chair.- No, it... That is not a chair!
That is... That...
- That is Saint Edward's chair.- People have carved their names on it.
That chair is the seaton which every King...
- It's held in place by a large rock.- That is the Stone of Scone!
- You are trivializing everything.- I don't care how many royal assholes
- ...have sat on this chair.- Listen to me! Listen to me!
- Listen to you? By what right?- By Divine Right, if you must.
- I am your King!- No, you're not.
You told me so yourself.You said you didn't want it.
Why should I waste my timelistening to you?
Because I have a right to be heard!I have a voice!
Yes, you do.
You have such perseverance, Bertie.You're the bravest man I know.
You'll make a bloody good King.
- What on earth is going on, sir?- It's quite all right, Archbishop.
Mr. Logue, you must know that
I've found a replacement Englishspecialist with impeccable credentials.
Hence, your serviceswill no longer be required.
- I'm sorry?- Your Majesty's function
is to consult and be advised.Now, you didn't consult,
- ...but you have just been advised.- And now I advise you.
In this personal matter,I will make my own decision.
My concern is for the headon which I must place the crown.
I appreciate that, Archbishop.
But it's my head.
Your humble servant.
Thank you, Bertie.
Shall we rehearse? Come on.Up on your perch.
Now, when you and Elizabethenter through the West door,
you will be greeted by the hymn"I was glad when they said unto me."
Actually, you won't be that glad becausethey do sing it for a very long time.
Then your friend, the Archbishop,will ponce up the stairs towards you,
and say, "Sir, is Your Majestywilling to take the oath?"
- "I am willing."- Well, of course you are.
I'm gonna see what this sounds likein the cheap seats,
so even your old nanny can hear.
"Will you govern your peoples,Great Britain, Ireland, Canada,
Australia and New Zealand,
according to their lands and customs?"
- "I SOLEMNLY PROMISE TO DO SO!"- Louder.
- I can't hear you up the back.- "I solemnly promise to do so."
Very good. "And will you, to your power,
cause Law and Justice, in Mercy to beexecuted in all your judgments?"
"I will. [Louder] "I WILL!"
Then there's a very long bitabout upholding the faith. It goes on,
rubbish, rubbish, rubbish,to which you finally say...
"The things which I have...here before promised,
I will perform and keep.So help me God."
And that's all you say.Four short responses.
Kiss the book, sign the oath,and you're King.
Easy.
[Man On Film Speaks Indistinctly]
You nearly crowned him backwards,Archbishop.
Someone had removed the threadmarking the back of the crown, sir.
Try not to lose the thread, Archbishop.
[Chuckles]Archbishop, we're missing Papa.
- [All] God save the King.- Very good.
Very good, Archbishop.
Well, I hope Your Majestiesare thrilled with the result.
- You can switch that machine off.- No, wait. Keep going.
- Nazism has held its great convention.- Do take a seat, Archbishop.
Masses of uniformed men,stupefying to the eye,
and incredible to the imaginationhave stood in spellbound audience...
...of the Fuhrer.[Speaking German]
- Papao Papa, what's he saying?- [Bertie] Hmm?
I don't know, but he seemsto be saying it rather well.
Sir... I have asked to see you today
in order to tender my resignationas Prime Minister.
I'm so sorry to hear that,Mr. Baldwin.
Neville Chamberlain willtake my place as Prime Minister.
It's a matter of principle.I was mistaken.
I have found it impossible to believe
that there is any man in the world
so lacking in moral feeling as Hitler,
that the world may be hurledfor a second time
into the abyss of destructive war.
Churchill was right all along.
This was always Hitler's intention.
I'm only very sorry to leave youat this great time of crisis.
I'm very much afraid, sir,that your greatest test is yet to come.
[Chamberlain On Radio]I am speaking to you...
...from the Cabinet roomat 10 Downing Street.
This morning,the British ambassador in Berlin
handed the German governmenta final note
stating that unlesswe heard from them by 11:00,
that they were prepared at onceto withdraw their troops from Poland,
...a state of war would exist between us.[Door Shuts]
I have to tell you now thatno such undertaking has been received,
and that, consequently, this countryis at war with Germany.
At last, sir, here is your speech.
You are on air at six.
I have timed itto just under nine minutes.
The wording is fully approved.
The Prime Ministerwill be joining you for the broadcast,
which will go out liveacross the nation, the Empire
- ...and to our armed forces.- Get Logue here immediately.
- [Laurie] There's the barrage balloons.- [Lionel] Yes.
- They got them up there quickly.- Yeah.
[Air-Raid Siren Wails][Indistinct Shouting]
- Shall we pull over and find a shelter?- No, no. Go straight there.
We'll be all right.
- Yes, sir?- Lionel Logue.
Major Hartley is expecting me.This is my son, Laurie.
- Thank you, Laurie.- Good luck, Dad.
- The King's speech.- Thank you, sir.
We have about 40 minutesto the broadcast.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
[Bertie]There may be dark days ahead...
...and...- Try again.
There may be dark days ahead, and...
Turn the hesitations into pauses and sayto yourself, "God save the King."
I say that continuously,but apparently no one's listening.
Long pauses are good.They add solemnity to great occasions.
Then I'm the solemnest kingwho ever lived.
You know, if I'm a king,where's my power?
Can I... can I form a government?
Can I... can I... levy a tax?
Declare a... a war? No.
And yet I'm the seat of all authority.Why? Because...
...the nation believesthat when I... I speak,
I speak for them. But I can't speak.
Let's take it all again from the top."In this grave hour."
[Clears Throat]
In this grave hour...Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Perhaps the most fatefulin our history... Bugger, shit, shit.
I send to every household of my...
You see, "P" is always difficult,even when I'm singing.
Bounce on to it. "A peoples."
A people. A people.
Household of my peoples,both at home
- ...and overseas.- Beautiful.
This message...  Doo-dah
Spoken with the same depth of feeling,Doo-dah day,
...for each one of you,as if I were able to...
Shit, fuck, bugger! ...cross yourthreshold and speak to you...
In your head now. "I have a rightto be bloody well heard."
Bloody well heard,bloody well heard myself!
Now, waltz. Move.Get continuous movement.
"For the second timein the lives of most of us...
- "We are at..."- [Lionel] "We are," take a pause.
- Lionel, I can't do this.- Bertie, you can do it.
- Have a look at the last paragraph.- Bertie. It's time.
[Indistinct Chattering]There he is.
[Dog Barks]
- Archbishop.- Your Majesty.
A great moment, Sir.
- Prime Minister.- Your Majesty.
Nice to see you... again so soon.
Good of you to be here.I'm sure you have had...
- ...a rather busy day.- I hope we have no more interruptions...
- ...from those damn sirens, sir.- Or the wretched dogs.
Congrat... Congratulations.
- First Lord of the Admiralty.- Your Majesty.
The long... walk.
Good luck, sir.
I, too, dread this apparatus.
Had a speech impediment myself,you know.
- I didn't.- Family secret. Tongue-tied.
An operation was consideredto be too dangerous.
I eventually made an asset of it.
[Chuckles]
- Thank you, Mr. Churchill.- Sir.
Darling.
- How long, Logue?- Just under three minutes.
- Mr. Wood.- Good luck, Your Majesty.
[Elizabeth]Mr. Wood.
- You've redecorated, Logue.- I made it cozy.
- Some fresh air.- There you are, darling.
I'm a thistle-sifter.
I've a sieve of sifted thistlesand a sieve of unsifted thistles.
A sieve of sifted thistlesand a sieve of unsifted thistles.
- [Clears Throat] Because I'm...- Bertie. Darling.
Make sure it's not switched on.
Remember, the red lightwill blink four times,
then I've asked them to turn it off.
'Cause we don't want that evil eyestaring at you all the way through.
[Man]One minute, sir.
I'm sure you'll be splendid.
Forty seconds, sir.
[Bertie]Logue.
However this turns out...
...I don't know how to thank you...for what you've done.
Knighthood?
[Man]Twenty seconds.
Forget everything else,and just say it to me.
Say it to me as a friend.
[Coughs]
[Muted]
In this grave...
...hour...
...perhaps the most fatefulin our history...
...I send...
...to every household of my...
...a- peoples...
...both at home...
...and overseas...
...this message...
...spoken with the samedepth of feeling...
...for each one of you...
...as if I were ableto cross your threshold
and speak to you... myself.
For the second timein the lives of most of us...
...we are... at...
[Mouthing]Fuck, fuck, fuck!
...at war.
[Mouthing]Very good.
Over and over again...
...we have tried to find...
...a peaceful way outof the differences...
...between ourselves...
...and those...
...who are now our... enemies.
But it has been... in vain.
We have been forced into a conflict,
for we are calledto meet the challenge of a principle,
which, if it were to prevail,
would be fatal to any civilized order
in the world.
Such a principle,
stripped of all disguise,
is surely the mere...
...primitive doctrine that might...
...is right.
For the sake of allthat we ourselves hold dear,
it is unthinkable
that we should refuse to meet...
...the challenge.
It is to this high purpose
that I now call
my people at home,
and my peoples across the seas,
who will make our cause their own.
I ask them to stand calm
and firm and united
in this time of trial.
The task will be hard.
There may be dark days ahead,
and war can no longer be confined
to the battlefield.
But we can only do the right
as we see the right,
and reverently commit
Our cause to God.
If one and all we keep
resolutely faithful to it,
then, with God's help,
we shall... prevail.
[Long Sigh][Indistinct Murmuring]
It was very good, Bertie.
[Exhales]
You still stammered on the "W."
Well, I had to throw in a few,so they knew it was me.
Congratulations, Your Majesty.A true broadcaster.
[Applause]Thank you, Mr. Wood.
- Congratulations, Your Majesty.- Sir.
- Congratulations, Your Majesty.- Thank you.
Ready.
- Good?- Perfect, sir.
Your first wartime speech.
Congratulations.
I expect I shall have to...do a great deal more.
Thank you, Logue.
Well done.
My friend.
Thank you...
...Your Majesty.
[Doors Open]
I knew you'd be good.
Thank you... Lionel.
Onwards.
- [Man #1] Congratulations, sir.- [Man #2] Well done, sir.
Couldn't havesaid it better myself, sir.
Your Majesty, I am speechless.
- Congratulations, sir.- Gentlemen.
- So how was Papa, Elizabeth?- Halting at first,
- But you got much better, Papa.- Well, bless you.
- And how about you, Margaret?- You were just splendid, Papa.
Of course I was.
Are we all ready?
[Elizabeth] Come on, girls.
[Crowd Cheering]