I'd never given much thought
to how I would die.
But dying in the place
of someone I love...
seems like a good way to go.
So I can't bring myself to...
regret the decision
to leave home.
I would miss Phoenix.
I'd miss the heat.
I would miss my
loving, erratic,
harebrained mother.
Okay.
Renee, come on.
- And her new husband.
Guys, come on.
I love you both.
We got a plane to catch.
But they want to
go on the road,
so I'm gonna spend
some time with my dad,
and this will be a good thing.
I think.
When the thorn
bush turns white
That's when I'll come home
I am going out to
see what I can sow
And I don't know where I'll go
And I don't know what I'll see
In the state of Washington,
under a near constant cover
of clouds and rain,
there's a small
town named Forks.
Population, 3, 120 people.
This is where I'm moving.
My dad's Charlie.
He's the chief of police.
Curse the powers that be
Cause all I want is...
Your hair's longer.
I cut it since the
last time I saw you.
Guess it grew out again.
I used to spend two weeks here
almost every summer,
but it's been years.
I've cleared some shelves off
in the bathroom.
Right. One bathroom.
It's a pretty good work lamp.
The sales lady picked
out the bed stuff.
You like purple, right?
Purple's cool.
Thanks.
Okay.
One of the best
things about Charlie,
he doesn't hover.
Heard you guys coming
all the way down the road.
Good to see you.
Bella, you remember
Billy Black.
Yeah.
Wow, you're looking good.
- Well, I'm still dancing.
I'm glad you're finally here.
Charlie here hasn't
shut up about it...
since you told him
you were coming.
All right, keep exaggerating.
I'll roll you into the mud.
After I ram you in the ankles.
You want to go?
- Yeah.
Bring it.
Hi, I'm Jacob.
- Hey.
We used to make mud pies
when we were little.
Right. No, I remember.
Are they always like this?
It's getting worse
with old age.
Good.
So, what do you think?
Of what?
Your homecoming present.
- This?
Just bought it off Billy here.
- Yep.
I totally rebuilt
the engine for you.
Come on.
Oh, my gosh.
This is perfect.
Are you joking me?
Sorry.
I told you she'd love it.
I'm down with the kids.
Oh, yeah, dude.
You're the bomb.
Okay.
Listen, you gotta double-pump
the clutch when you shift,
but besides that,
you should be good.
That's this one?
- Yeah. Yeah, right there.
All right.
Do you want a ride to
school or something?
I go to school on
the reservation.
Right, right.
- Yeah.
That's too bad.
It would've been nice
to know one person.
My first day at a new school.
It's March, middle
of the semester.
Great.
Nice ride.
- Thanks.
Good one.
You're Isabella
Swan, the new girl.
Hi, I'm Eric, the eyes
and ears of this place.
Anything you need, tour guide,
lunch date,
shoulder to cry on?
I'm really kind of the more
suffer-in-silence type.
Good headline
for your feature.
I'm on the paper,
and you're news,
baby, front page.
No, I'm not.
You...
Please don't have
any sort of...
Chillax. No feature.
Okay, thanks.
- Cool?
All right. Okay. Yeah.
Get it. Get it. Get it.
To you.
Whoa.
I'm sorry.
I told them not
to let me play.
No way. No, no, no.
That's... That's... Don't...
You're Isabella, right?
Just Bella.
Yeah. Hey, I'm Mike Newton.
Nice to meet you.
- Yeah, yeah.
She's got a great spike, huh?
- Yeah, it's...
I'm Jessica, by the way.
Hey, you're from
Arizona, right?
Yeah.
Aren't people from Arizona...
supposed to be,
like, really tan?
Yeah.
Maybe that's why
they kicked me out.
You're good.
That's so funny.
Back in, Jess.
- Down here.
Like a masterpiece, you know,
we'll have, like,
this crazy pyramid
fall from the sky,
and then you guys can...
- It's my pleasure, Madame.
You guys can give each
other high fives.
Burrito, my friend?
Hey, Mikey. You met
my home girl, Bella?
Hey.
Your home girl?
Yeah.
- Yeah?
That's...
- My girl.
Sorry I had to mess
up your game, Mike.
Tyler.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
It's like first
grade all over again.
You're the shiny new toy.
Smile.
Okay.
- Sorry.
I needed a candid
for the feature.
The feature's dead, Angela.
Don't bring it up again.
It's okay, I just...
I got your back, baby.
Guess we'll just run
another editorial...
on teen drinking.
You know,
you can always go
for eating disorders.
Speedo padding on
the swim team.
Actually, that's a good one.
Kirk. Right? That's
exactly what I thought.
Yeah.
We're talking Olympic-size.
There's no way.
He's so skinny.
It doesn't make sense.
Totally.
- Yeah.
Who are they?
The Cullens.
They're Dr. and Mrs.
Cullen's foster kids.
They moved down
here from Alaska,
like, a few years ago.
They kind of keep
to themselves.
Yeah, 'cause they're
all together.
Like, together, together.
The blonde girl,
that's Rosalie,
and the big dark-haired
guy, Emmett,
they're, like, a thing.
I'm not even sure
that's legal.
Jess, they're not
actually related.
Yeah, but they live
together. It's weird.
And, okay, the little
dark-haired girl's Alice.
She's really weird,
and she's with Jasper,
the blond one...
who looks like he's in pain.
Dr. Cullen's like this
foster dad/matchmaker.
Maybe he'll adopt me.
Who's he?
That's Edward Cullen.
He's totally
gorgeous, obviously,
but apparently nobody here's
good enough for him.
Like I care, you know?
So, yeah.
Seriously, like,
don't waste your time.
I wasn't planning on it.
Mr. Molina.
- Hey, Mike.
Oh, yes. Miss Swan.
Hi. Can I have the
pass? Thank you.
Welcome to the class.
Here. Here's your stuff, okay?
And I got a seat
for you right here,
so come over.
The last one.
Just follow along
till you catch up.
All right, guys, today
we are gonna be...
observing the
behavior of planaria,
aka flatworms.
So what we're gonna do...
...regenerate.
Zombie worms.
No cell phones. Guys,
let's get to it.
Gentle, gentle, certain areas.
Please just don't cut here.
We don't cut here.
You won't believe this.
Let's try to focus...
while we check those
out, huh, guys?
There must be something open.
Physics? Biochem?
- No, every class is full.
Just a minute, dear.
I'm afraid you'll have
to stay in biology.
Fine. Just... I'll just
have to endure it.
I just can't get over
how grown up you are.
And so gorgeous.
Hey, Bella.
You remember me?
I played Santa one year.
Yeah, Waylon, she hasn't had...
a Christmas here
since she was four.
I bet I made an impression,
though, didn't I?
You always do.
- Butt-crack Santa?
Hey, kids love those
little bottles, though.
All right,
let the girl eat her
garden burger, Waylon.
As soon as you're done,
I will bring you
your favorite.
Berry cobbler, remember?
Your dad still has
it. Every Thursday.
Thank you. That'd be great.
Here.
Thanks.
Hey, baby. So, listen,
if spring training goes well,
we could be moving to Florida.
Please insert $1.25...
for an additional
three minutes.
Mom, where's your cell?
Okay, don't laugh.
I didn't lose my power
cord. It ran away.
Screaming. I literally
repel technology now.
I miss you.
- Oh, baby, I miss you, too.
But tell me more
about your school.
Now, what are the kids like?
Are there any cute guys?
Are they being nice to you?
Well,
they're all very welcoming.
Tell me all about it.
It doesn't even matter.
Yes, it does, honey.
I have homework to do.
I'll talk to you later.
Okay. I love you.
Love you, too.
I planned to confront him...
and demand to know
what his problem was.
But he never showed.
Bella.
And the next day,
another no-show.
More days passed.
Things were getting
a little strange.
You all right?
- Yeah, I'm good.
Ice doesn't really help
the uncoordinated.
Yeah. That's why I had...
some new tires
put on the truck.
Old ones were
getting pretty bald.
Well, probably be
late for dinner.
I gotta head down
to Mason County.
Security guard at
the Grisham Mill...
got killed by some
kind of animal.
An animal?
You're not in Phoenix
anymore, Bells.
Anyway, I figured
I'd lend a hand.
Be careful.
- Always am.
And thanks for the tires.
- Yeah.
Prom Committee is
a chick thing,
but I gotta cover it
for the paper anyway,
and they need a guy
to help choose the music,
so I need your play list.
Hey, listen, I was wondering,
did you have a date to...
What's up, Arizona? Huh?
How you liking the rain, girl?
Better get used to it, girl.
Yeah, Mike, hey,
you're real cute, man.
Oh, I know...
- That was really awesome.
Why you shooting down my game?
Let a playa play.
Yeah, okay.
What you playing at, T-Ball?
Hello.
I'm sorry, I didn't
get a chance...
to introduce myself last week.
I'm Edward Cullen.
You're Bella?
Yes.
Onion root tip cells,
that's what's on your
slides right now.
Okay? So, separate
and label them...
into the phases of mitosis,
and the first partners
that get it right...
are gonna win
the Golden Onion.
All right, good.
Ladies first.
You were gone.
Yeah.
I was out of town
for a couple of days.
Personal reasons.
Prophase.
Do you mind if I look?
It's prophase.
Like I said.
So are you enjoying the rain?
What?
You're asking me
about the weather?
Yeah, I...
I guess I am.
Well, I don't really
like the rain.
Any cold, wet thing,
I don't really...
What?
- Nothing.
It's anaphase.
You mind if I check?
- Sure.
Anaphase.
Like I said.
If you hate the cold
and the rain so much,
why'd you move to
the wettest place...
in the continental US?
It's complicated.
I'm sure I can keep up.
My mom remarried, and...
So you don't like
the guy, or...
No, that's not...
Phil's really nice.
It's metaphase. You
want to check it?
I believe you.
Why didn't you move
with your mother and Phil?
Well, Phil's a minor
league baseball player,
and he travels a lot,
and my mom stayed
home with me,
but I knew it
made her unhappy,
so I figured I'd stay
with my dad for a while.
And now you're unhappy.
No.
- I'm sorry, I'm just...
I'm just trying to
figure you out.
You're very difficult
for me to read.
Hey, did you get contacts?
No.
Your eyes were black
the last time I saw you,
and now they're,
like, golden brown.
Yeah, I know, it's the...
It's the fluorescents.
Bella.
- Bella.
Dial 911.
I already called.
They're gonna send
somebody over soon.
Bella, I'm so
sorry. I panicked.
Bella, I've got 911
on the phone now.
Bella. You okay?
You and I are gonna
talk. You all right?
I'm fine, Dad. Calm down.
I'm sorry, Bella.
I tried to stop.
I know. It's okay.
No. It sure as
hell is not okay.
Dad, it wasn't his fault.
You could've been killed.
You understand that?
Yes. But I wasn't, so...
You can kiss your
license goodbye.
I heard the chief's
daughter was here.
Dr. Cullen.
Charlie.
I've got this one, Jackie.
Isabella.
Bella.
Well, Bella, looks like
you took quite a spill.
How do you feel?
Good.
Look here.
You might experience some...
post-traumatic stress
or disorientation,
but your vitals look good.
No signs of any head trauma.
I think you'll be just fine.
I'm so sorry, Bella.
I'm really...
You know,
it would've been a
whole lot worse...
if Edward wasn't there.
He knocked me out of the way.
Edward? Your boy?
Yeah, it was amazing.
I mean, he got to me so fast.
He was nowhere near me.
Sounds like you
were very lucky.
Charlie.
I gotta go sign
some paperwork.
You should...
You should probably
call your mom.
Did you tell her?
She's probably just...
freaking out.
fifteen kids that saw
what happened.
What was I supposed
to do, then?
Let her die?
This isn't just about you.
It's about all of us.
I think we should
take this in my office.
Can I talk to
you for a minute?
Rosalie.
What?
How did you get
over to me so fast?
I was standing right
next to you, Bella.
No. You were next to your car,
across the lot.
No, I wasn't.
Yes, you were.
Bella, you're...
You hit your head.
I think you're confused.
I know what I saw.
And what exactly was that?
You...
You stopped the van.
You pushed it away
with your hand.
Well, nobody's gonna
believe you, so...
I wasn't gonna tell anybody.
I just need to know the truth.
Can't you just thank
me and get over it?
Thank you.
You're not gonna let
this go, are you?
No.
Well, then I hope you
enjoy disappointment.
And that was the first night
I dreamt of Edward Cullen.
I need everybody's
permission slips, okay?
Sammy, please collect them.
- Yeah.
Guys, let's go.
Come on, get in. In. Let's go.
Look at you, huh?
You're alive.
I know, yeah. False
alarm, I guess.
Yeah.
Now, I wanted to ask you,
you know, if, you know,
it's like a month away, but...
Do you wanna go
to prom with me?
So, what do you think?
About what?
- Do you want to go?
To prom?
With me?
I...
Prom.
Dancing.
Not such a good idea for me.
I have something
that weekend anyway.
I'm going to Jacksonville
that weekend.
You can't go another weekend?
Non-refundable ticket.
You should ask Jessica.
I know she wants
to go with you.
All right. All right.
Yo, yo, yo. Hey,
guys, come on.
We gotta go. We gotta go.
Green is what? Good.
Let's go. Guys, come on.
Other bus, other
bus. Let's go.
Egg shells, carrot tops.
Compost is cool.
Now, stuff that
in there, Eric.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
- Very good, very good.
Now, I am gonna make
a steaming cup...
of compost tea.
Okay.
- Give me that.
Yeah. This is recycling
in its most basic form, guys.
Don't drink it. It's
for the plants.
What's in Jacksonville?
How did you know about that?
You didn't answer my question.
You don't answer
any of mine, so...
I mean, you don't
even say hi to me.
Hi.
Are you gonna tell me
how you stopped the van?
Yeah. I had an
adrenaline rush.
It's very common.
You can Google it.
Floridians.
That's what's in Jacksonville.
Can you at least
watch where you walk?
Look, I'm sorry I'm
being rude all the time.
I just think it's
the best way.
Bella. Guess who just
asked me to prom.
Who?
Yeah, I actually
totally thought...
that Mike was gonna ask you.
It's not gonna be
weird, though, right?
No. Zero weirdness.
You guys are great together.
- I know, right?
Tyler...
- Gross.
Bella, look. It's a worm.
It's a worm.
Bella, we shouldn't
be friends.
You really should've figured
that out a little earlier.
I mean, why didn't you just
let the van crush me...
and save yourself
all this regret?
What, you think I
regret saving you?
I can see that you do.
I just... I don't know why.
You don't know anything.
Hi.
Are you gonna be
riding with us?
No, our bus is full.
Your mom called. Again.
Well, that's your fault.
You shouldn't have told her...
about the 'almost'
accident. You finished?
Yeah.
Yeah, I suppose you're right.
She always did
know how to worry.
She seems different.
She seems happy.
Phil sounds like
an all right guy.
Yeah, he is.
All right.
No, you need the mitts.
You need them.
No, why do you keep
arguing with me?
You just need them.
You're gonna get frostbite.
- I don't even know.
Yeah. Hey.
La Push, baby. You in?
Should I know what that means?
La Push Beach down
at the Quileute Rez.
We're all going tomorrow.
Yeah, there's a big
swell coming in.
And I don't just
surf the Internet.
Eric, you stood up once,
and it was a foam board.
But there's whale
watching, too.
Come with us.
La Push, baby. It's La Push.
Okay, I'll go if you
stop saying that, okay?
Seriously, dude.
It's creepy, man.
What? That's what it's called.
- So...
Edible art?
Bella.
Thanks.
You know, your mood swings...
are kind of giving
me whiplash.
I only said it'd be better
if we weren't friends,
not that I didn't wanna be.
What does that mean?
It means if you were smart,
you'd stay away from me.
Okay, well, let's say
for argument's sake...
that I'm not smart.
Would you tell me the truth?
- No, probably not.
I'd rather hear your theories.
I have considered...
radioactive spiders
and Kryptonite.
That's all superhero
stuff, right?
What if I'm not the hero?
What if I'm the bad guy?
You're not.
I can see what you're
trying to put off,
but I can see that it's just
to keep people away from you.
It's a mask.
Why don't we just hang out?
Everybody's going
to the beach.
Come.
I mean, have fun.
Which beach?
- La Push.
I don't know.
I just...
Is there something
wrong with that beach?
It's just a little crowded.
Hey, it's freezing.
- I'm paddling out, Coates.
I don't know if it's
worth it anymore.
We drove all the way out here.
I'm at least paddling out.
- Yeah.
She's right.
- You guys are babies.
So, I keep thinking
that Eric's...
gonna ask me to the prom,
and then he just doesn't.
You should ask him.
Take control.
You're a strong,
independent woman.
I am?
- Yes.
Hey, will you do me up?
- Yeah.
Bella.
- Hi, Jacob.
Guys, this is Jacob.
- Hey, guys. How you doing?
Hi.
- Hi.
What are you,
like, stalking me?
You're on my rez, remember?
Are you surfing?
Definitely not.
- Thanks.
You guys should
keep Bella company.
Her date bailed.
What date?
She invited Edward.
To be polite, that's it.
I think it's nice
she invited him.
Nobody ever does.
Yeah, 'cause Cullen's a freak.
You got that right.
You guys know him?
The Cullens don't come here.
What did your
friends mean about,
you know, 'The Cullens
don't come here?'
You caught that, huh?
I'm not really supposed
to say anything about it.
Hey, I can keep a secret.
Really, it's just like
an old scary story.
Well, I want to know.
Okay, did you know Quileutes...
are supposedly
descended from wolves?
What? Like, wolves?
Yeah.
- Like, real wolves?
Well, that's the
legend of our tribe.
Okay.
So what's the story
about the Cullens?
Well, they're
supposedly descended...
from this, like, enemy clan.
My great grandfather,
the chief,
found them hunting
on our land.
But they claimed to be
something different,
so we made a treaty with them.
If they promised to stay
off Quileute lands,
then we wouldn't expose...
what they really were
to the palefaces.
I thought they
just moved here.
Or just moved back.
Right.
It touched my hand.
A snake. Stop.
Well, what are they really?
It's just a story, Bella.
Come on, let's go.
A snake. A snake.
My mama said I didn't know
how to make a kitty meow
Hello?
Gerald?
Hello.
Nice jacket.
Who are you?
It's always the same
inane questions.
'Who are you?'
'What do you want?'
'Why are you doing this?'
James, let's not
play with our food.
He's not here.
Whenever the weather's nice,
the Cullens disappear.
What, do they just ditch?
No, Dr. and Mrs. Cullen
yank them out...
for, like, hiking and
camping and stuff.
I tried that out
on my parents.
Not even close.
Guys, I'm going to
the prom with Eric.
I just asked him.
I took control.
I told you that would happen.
Are you sure you have
to go out of town?
Oh, yeah, it's a
little family thing.
Okay, we should go shopping
in Port Angeles...
before all the good
dresses get cleaned out.
Port Angeles? You
mind if I come?
Yeah, I need your opinion.
I like this one.
- That's cool.
But, like, I don't know about
the one-shoulder thing.
I like this one.
- Yeah, I like the beading,
and you wouldn't need jewelry.
Jess, what do you
think? Lavender?
Is that good? Is
that my color?
I like it.
I liked that dusty
rose one, too.
Okay, I like this one.
It makes my boobs look good.
Hey.
- Right?
Nice.
Oh, God.
- That is uncomfortable.
That's disgusting.
Bella, what do you think?
Yes?
That looks great.
You said that about, like,
the last five dresses, though.
I thought they were
all pretty good.
You're not really
into this, are you?
I actually really just want
to go to this bookstore.
I'll meet you guys
at the restaurant?
Are you sure?
Yeah, yeah. I'll
see you in a minute.
Okay.
- Okay.
She's right, though.
This looks awesome.
There you go.
Have a good night.
- Thank you.
Saw you in the dress store.
- Hey, where you running to?
There she is.
What's up?
- It's my girl.
How you guys doing?
- Look who we just found.
What's up, girl? Hey...
Where you going?
Where are you going?
- Come get a drink with us.
Yeah, you should
hang out with us.
Come on.
It's fun.
What's the problem?
- She doesn't like that, man.
You're pretty.
- Don't touch me.
Cute.
Really, no. Seriously,
you should.
Don't touch me.
Get in the car.
That was a very
dangerous maneuver.
I should go back there
and rip those guys' heads off.
No, you shouldn't.
You don't know the vile,
repulsive things...
they were thinking.
And you do?
It's not hard to guess.
Can you talk about
something else?
Distract me so I
won't turn around.
You should put
your seatbelt on.
I thought the salad
was pretty good.
Hey, you guys, I'm
sorry. I just...
Where were you? We
left you messages.
Yeah, we waited,
but we were, like,
starving, so we...
I'm sorry I kept
Bella from dinner.
We just sort of ran
into each other...
and got talking.
Yeah.
- No.
No, we totally understand.
I mean, that happens, right?
Yeah, we were...
We were, yeah, we were
just leaving. So...
Let's get this...
Bella, if you wanna...
I think I should make sure
Bella gets something to eat.
If you'd like.
I'll drive you home myself.
That's so thoughtful.
It's really thoughtful. Yeah.
Yeah. I should eat something.
Yeah.
Okay, so we'll
see you tomorrow.
Okay, yeah.
See ya.
- Okay.
All right, one
mushroom ravioli.
Thanks.
- Yeah, no problem.
So are you sure
there isn't anything
I can get for you?
No. No, thank you.
Let me know.
You're really not gonna eat?
No, I'm on a special diet.
You gotta give
me some answers.
Yes, no.
To get to the other side.
1.77245...
I don't want to know
what the square root of pi is.
You knew that?
How did you know where I was?
I didn't.
All right.
- What?
Don't leave. I...
Did you follow me?
I...
I feel very protective of you.
So you followed me.
I was trying to
keep a distance...
unless you needed my help,
and then I heard what
those low-lifes...
were thinking.
Wait.
You say you heard what
they were thinking?
So what, you...
You read minds?
I can read every
mind in this room.
Apart from yours.
There's money, sex,
money,
sex,
cat.
And then you, nothing.
It's very frustrating.
Is there something
wrong with me?
See, I tell you
I can read minds,
and you think there's
something wrong with you.
What is it?
I don't have the strength
to stay away from you anymore.
Then don't.
Okay, I think I'm
warm enough now.
Your hand is so cold.
Whoa.
What is going on?
My dad's still here.
Can you pull in?
That's my father's
car on the end.
What is he doing here?
Carlisle, what's going on?
Waylon Forge was
found in a boat...
out near his place.
I just examined the body.
- He died?
How?
- Animal attack.
Was it the same one that...
got that security
guard down in Mason?
Most likely.
Well, it's getting
closer to town, then.
Bella, you should go inside.
Waylon was your
father's friend.
Okay.
I'll see you later.
Hey.
- Hey.
Dad, I'm really sorry.
I've known him
going on 30 years.
Don't worry, we're
gonna find this thing.
Meantime.
I want you to carry
this with you.
I don't know if you...
It'll give your old
man some peace of mind.
Okay.
Let's go home.
Cold One.
You're impossibly
fast and strong.
Your skin is pale
white and ice-cold.
Your eyes change color.
And sometimes you speak...
like you're from
a different time.
You never eat or
drink anything.
You don't go out
in the sunlight.
How old are you?
Seventeen.
How long have you been 17?
A while.
I know what you are.
Say it.
Out loud.
Vampire.
Are you afraid?
No.
Then ask me the most
basic question.
What do we eat?
You won't hurt me.
Where are we going?
Up the mountain.
Out of the cloud bank.
You need to see what
I look like in the sunlight.
This is why we don't show
ourselves in sunlight.
People would know
we're different.
This is what I am.
It's like diamonds.
You're beautiful.
Beautiful?
This is the skin of
a killer, Bella.
I'm a killer.
I don't believe that.
That's because you
believe the lie.
It's camouflage.
I'm the world's most
dangerous predator.
Everything about
me invites you in,
my voice, my face,
even my smell.
As if I would
need any of that.
As if you could outrun me.
As if you could fight me off.
I'm designed to kill.
I don't care.
I've killed people before.
It does not matter.
I wanted to kill you.
I've never wanted
a human's blood...
so much in my life.
I trust you.
Don't.
I'm here. I trust you.
My family,
we're different from
others of our kind.
We only hunt animals.
We've learned to
control our thirst.
But it's you, your scent,
it's like a drug to me.
You're like...
my own personal
brand of heroin.
Why did you hate me
so much when we met?
I did.
Only for making me
want you so badly.
I still don't know if
I can control myself.
I know you can.
I can't read your mind.
You have to tell me
what you're thinking.
Now I'm afraid.
Good.
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm only afraid of losing you.
I feel like you're
gonna disappear.
You don't know how long
I've waited for you.
So the lion fell in
love with the lamb.
What a stupid lamb.
What a sick, masochistic lion.
About three things
I was absolutely positive.
First.
Edward was a vampire.
Second,
there was a part of him,
and I didn't know...
how dominant that
part might be,
that thirsted for my blood.
And third.
I was unconditionally
and irrevocably...
in love with him.
Monte Carlo?
That's our prom theme?
Gambling, tuxedos,
and Bond, James Bond.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
You know, everybody's staring.
Not that guy. No,
he just looked.
I'm breaking all the
rules now anyway.
Since I'm going to hell.
So, does a person
have to be dying...
to become like you?
No, that's just Carlisle.
He'd never do this to someone
who had another choice.
So, how long have
you been like this?
Since 1918.
That's when Carlisle found me
dying of Spanish influenza.
What was it like?
The venom was excruciating.
But what Carlisle
did was much harder.
Not many of us have the
restraint to do that.
But didn't he just
have to bite?
Not exactly.
When we taste...
human blood, a sort
of frenzy begins,
and it's almost
impossible to stop.
But Carlisle did.
First with me
and then with his wife, Esme.
So is Carlisle the real reason
that you don't kill people?
No, he's not the only reason.
I don't want to be a monster.
My family,
we think of ourselves
as vegetarians, right,
'cause we only survive
on the blood of animals.
But it's...
It's like a human
only living on tofu.
It keeps you strong,
but you're never
fully satisfied.
It wouldn't be like
drinking your blood,
for instance.
Was it other vampires
that killed Waylon?
Yeah.
There are others out there,
and we run into them
from time to time.
Can the rest of your family...
read people's
minds like you can?
No. That's just me.
But Alice can see the future.
I bet she saw me coming.
Alice's visions
are subjective.
I mean, the future
can always change.
Could you act human?
I mean, I've got neighbors.
I'm gonna take you to
my place tomorrow.
Thanks.
Wait, like, with your family?
- Yeah.
What if they don't like me?
So, you're worried not because...
you'll be in a house
full of vampires,
but because you think
they won't approve of you?
I'm glad I amuse you.
What is it?
Complication.
I'll pick you up tomorrow.
Hey. Come to visit your truck?
Looks good. Got that dent out.
Yeah.
Actually, we came to
visit your flat-screen.
First Mariners game
of the season.
Plus Jacob here keeps
bugging me about...
seeing you again.
Great, Dad. Thanks.
Just keeping it real, son.
Vitamin R.
Well done, Chief.
Harry Clearwater's
homemade fish fry.
Good man.
Any luck with
that Waylon case?
Well, I don't think
it was an animal...
that killed him.
Never thought it was.
So spread the word
out at the rez, huh?
Keep the kids
out of the woods.
Will do.
Don't want no one else
getting hurt, do we?
Whoa.
This is incredible.
It's so light and
open, you know?
What did you expect,
coffins and
dungeons and moats?
No, not the moats.
Not the moats.
This is the one place
we don't have to hide.
I told them not to do this.
You add a little
bit of olive oil...
to a non-stick saut pan,
and you want to cook...
with the olive oil
in medium-high heat.
What I do, I cut
this in strips,
and then we gonna cut this...
Is she even Italian?
- Her name is Bella.
I'm sure she'll love
it, no matter what.
Get a whiff of that.
Here comes the human.
Bella, we're making
Italiano for you.
Bella, this is Esme.
My mother for all
intents and purposes.
You've given us an excuse...
to use the kitchen
for the first time.
I hope you're hungry.
Yeah, absolutely.
- She already ate.
Perfect.
Yeah, it's just because
I know that you
guys don't eat...
Of course. It's very
considerate of you.
Just ignore Rosalie. I do.
- Yeah.
Let's just keep pretending...
like this isn't
dangerous for all of us.
I would never tell
anybody anything.
She knows that.
Yeah, well, the problem is,
you two have gone
public now, so...
Emmett.
No, she should know.
The entire family...
will be implicated
if this ends badly.
Badly, as in...
I would become the meal.
Hi, Bella.
I'm Alice.
Hi.
- Hi.
You do smell good.
Alice, what are you...
It's okay.
Bella and I are gonna
be great friends.
Sorry,
Jasper's our
newest vegetarian.
It's a little
difficult for him.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
It's okay, Jasper.
You won't hurt her.
All right, I'm gonna take you...
on a tour of the
rest of the house.
Okay.
- Well, I'll see you soon.
Cute.
- I know.
I think that went well.
Clean this up. Now.
Was that as weird for
you as it was for me?
I don't know.
Graduation caps?
Yeah. It's a private joke.
We matriculate a lot.
That's kind of miserable.
I mean, repeating high school
over and over.
True, but the younger
we start out...
in a new place,
the longer we can stay there.
Come on.
Yeah, this is my room.
No bed?
No, I don't...
I don't sleep.
Ever?
- No, not at all.
Okay.
Boy, you have so much music.
What are you listening to?
It's Debussy.
I don't know...
- Yeah.
Claire De Lune is great.
What?
- I can't dance.
Well, I could always make you.
I'm not scared of you.
Well, you really
shouldn't have said that.
You better hold on
tight, spider monkey.
Do you trust me?
In theory.
Then close your eyes.
What?
This isn't real.
This kind of stuff
just doesn't exist.
It does in my world.
Hold up.
It's human.
Arizona. Yo, what's happening?
So you and Cullen, huh?
That's... I don't like it.
I mean, I don't know,
he just looks at you
like you're something to eat.
Here's your veggie
plate, Stephenie.
Hey, sorry I'm late.
Biology project.
I ordered you the
spinach salad.
I hope that's okay.
You should order one
for yourself next time.
Cut back on the steak.
Hey, I'm as
healthy as a horse.
Say, Chief, boys want to know,
did you find anything
down by Queets River today?
Yeah, we found a bare
human footprint,
but it looks like
whoever that is,
is headed east,
so Kitsap County
sheriff is gonna take...
over from here.
Okay.
- Okay?
I just hope they
catch him fast.
Looks like your friends
are flagging you.
It's okay if you
wanna go join them.
I'm just gonna turn
in early anyway.
Me, too.
Bella, it's Friday
night. Go out.
Looks like the Newton boy's
got a big smile for you.
Yeah, he's a good buddy.
What about any of these
other yahoos in town?
Anybody interest you?
Dad, we gonna talk about boys?
Yeah, I guess not.
I just feel like I leave
you alone too much.
You should be around people.
I don't really
mind being alone.
I guess I'm kind of like
my dad in that way.
So, how's all the
baseball stuff going?
Phil's working so hard.
You know, spring training.
We're looking for
a house to rent...
in case things become
more permanent.
You'd like Jacksonville, baby.
Yeah?
I'm really liking Forks.
What?
Forks is growing on me.
Could a guy have anything
to do with that?
Well, yeah.
I knew it. Tell me everything.
What is he? Jock? Indie?
I bet he's smart. Is he smart?
Mom, can I talk to you later?
Come on, we gotta talk boys.
Are you being safe?
How did you get in here?
The window.
Do you do that a lot?
Well, just the past
couple of months.
I like watching you sleep.
It's kind of
fascinating to me.
I always want to
try one thing.
Just stay very still.
Don't move.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
I'm stronger than I thought.
Yeah. I wish I
could say the same.
I can't ever lose
control with you.
Hey, don't go.
Hey, got you another one.
- Thanks.
I have a date with
Edward Cullen.
He's a little old
for you, isn't he?
No.
He's a junior. I'm a junior.
I thought you
liked the Cullens.
I thought you didn't like
any of the boys in town.
Edward doesn't live in town.
Technically.
He's right outside.
He is?
Yeah, he wanted to
meet you, officially.
All right. Bring him in.
Could you be nice?
He's important.
Chief Swan.
I want to formally
introduce myself.
I'm Edward Cullen.
Hi, Edward.
Bella won't be out
too late tonight.
She's just gonna play baseball
with my family.
Baseball?
Yes, sir, that's the plan.
Bella's gonna play baseball.
Well, good luck with that.
I'll take good care
of her. I promise.
Hey.
Still got that pepper spray?
Yeah, Dad.
And since when do
vampires like baseball?
Well, it's the
American pastime,
and there's a
thunderstorm coming.
It's the only
time we can play.
You'll see why.
Hey.
Glad you're here.
We need an umpire.
She thinks we cheat.
I know you cheat.
Call them as you
see them, Bella.
Okay.
It's time.
Okay, now I see why
you need the thunder.
That's gotta be a
home run, right?
Edward's very fast.
Ooh, baby,
don't you know I suffer?
Ooh, baby, I'm a fool for you
Come home, Rosalie.
You're out.
- Out.
Babe, come on.
It's just a game.
You set my soul alight
Nice kitty.
Ooh
You set my soul alight
What are you doing?
Super massive black hole
My monkey man.
Stop.
They were leaving.
Then they heard us.
Let's go.
- It's too late.
Get your hair down.
Like that'll help.
I can smell her from
across the field.
I shouldn't have
brought you here.
I'm so sorry.
What? What are you...
Just be quiet and
stand behind me.
I believe this belongs to you.
Thank you.
I am Laurent.
And this is Victoria...
and James.
I'm Carlisle. This
is my family.
Hello.
I'm afraid your
hunting activities...
have caused something
of a mess for us.
Our apologies.
We didn't realize
the territory...
had been claimed.
Yes, well, we maintain
a permanent residence nearby.
Really?
Well, we won't be
a problem anymore.
We were just passing through.
The humans were tracking us,
but we led them east.
You should be safe.
Excellent.
So,
could you use
three more players?
Come on. Just one game.
Sure. Why not?
A few of us were leaving.
You could take their place.
We'll bat first.
I'm the one with the
wicked curveball.
Well, I think we
can handle that.
We shall see.
You brought a snack.
A human?
The girl is with us.
I think it best if you leave.
I can see the game is over.
We'll go now.
James.
Get Bella out of here.
Go.
Okay, I've got it. I've
got it. I'm all right.
What, now he's
coming after me?
Listen to me.
James is a tracker.
The hunt is his obsession.
I read his mind.
My reaction on the
field set him off.
I just made this his
most exciting game ever.
He's never gonna stop.
- What should we do?
We have to kill him.
Rip him apart and
burn the pieces.
Where we going?
- Away from Forks.
We'll get a ferry
to Vancouver.
I have to go home. Now.
You have to take me home.
- You can't go home.
He's just gonna trace
your scent there.
It's the first place
he's gonna look.
But my dad is there. We...
- It doesn't matter.
Yes, it does.
He could get killed
because of us.
Just let me get you
out of here first,
all right?
It's my dad. We
have to go back.
We'll figure a way...
to lead the tracker
away somehow.
I don't know. But we
have to do something.
Edward, I said leave me alone.
Bella, don't do this, please.
It's over. Get out.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Bella? What's going on?
I just gotta get out of
here. I'm leaving now.
Hey.
Bella?
What am I gonna say to him?
I can't hurt him.
Bella, what's going on?
- You just have to.
I'll be down at the truck.
Did he hurt you?
No.
Break up with
you or something?
No, I broke up with him.
I thought you liked him.
Yeah, that's why
I have to leave.
I don't want this.
I have to go home.
Home? Your...
Your mom's not
even in Phoenix.
She'll come home.
I'll call her from the road.
You're not gonna
drive home right now.
You can sleep on it.
If you still feel like
going in the morning.
I'll take you to the airport.
- No. I want to drive.
It'll give me more
time to think.
I mean, if I get really tired,
I'll pull into a
motel. I promise.
Look, Bella, I know I'm not
that much fun to be around,
but I can change that.
We can do more stuff together.
Like what?
Like watch baseball
on the flat-screen?
Eat at the diner every night?
Steak and cobbler?
Dad, that's you.
That's not me.
Bella, come on, I just...
I just got you back.
Yeah, and, you know, if
I don't get out now,
then I'm just gonna be
stuck here like Mom.
Your father's
gonna forgive you.
Why don't you let me drive?
He won't.
You should've seen his face.
I told him the same thing
that my mom told him...
when she was leaving him.
It's the only way
he'd let you go.
Just don't worry
about him now.
He's safe. The
tracker's following us.
Oh, God.
- It's just Emmett.
Alice is in the car behind us.
Wait.
He came to warn
us about James.
This isn't my fight,
and I've grown
tired of his games,
but he's got
unparalleled senses,
absolutely lethal.
I've never seen
anything like him...
in my 300 years.
And the woman, Victoria,
don't underestimate her.
I've had to fight
our kind before.
They're not easy to kill.
- But not impossible.
We'll tear them apart
and burn the pieces.
I don't relish the thought
of killing another creature,
even a sadistic
one like James.
What if he kills
one of us first?
I'm gonna run Bella south.
Can you lead the
tracker away from here?
No, Edward.
James knows you would
never leave Bella.
He'll follow you.
- I'll go with Bella.
Jasper and I will
drive her south.
I'll keep her safe, Edward.
Can you keep your
thoughts to yourself?
Yes.
Rosalie, Esme,
could you put these on...
so the tracker will
pick up Bella's scent?
Why? What is she to me?
Rosalie, Bella is with Edward.
She's part of this family now,
and we protect our family.
Oh, God. If anything...
What if...
If anything happens,
I swear to God...
Nothing's gonna happen.
There's seven of us,
and there's two of them,
and when everything's done,
I'm gonna come
back and get you.
Yeah.
Bella, you are my life now.
Hey, Mom. It's me again.
You must have let
your phone die...
or something.
I'm not in Forks, but
everything's okay,
and I'll explain it later.
Rosalie, mark the tree.
That's good.
What is it? What do you see?
He's figured it out.
The tracker, he just
changed course.
Where will it take him, Alice?
- Mirrors.
A room full of mirrors.
Edward said the visions
weren't always certain.
She sees the course people
are on while they're on it.
If they change their minds,
the vision changes.
Okay, so the course that
the tracker's on now...
is gonna lead him
to a ballet studio?
You've been here?
- I took lessons as a kid.
The school I went to
had an arch just like that.
Was your school
here in Phoenix?
Yeah.
Edward, are you okay?
- We've lost the tracker.
The woman's still in the area.
Rosalie and Esme
are going back...
to Forks to protect
your father.
I'm coming to get you.
Then you and I...
are gonna go somewhere alone.
And the others
will keep hunting.
I'll do whatever it takes
to make you safe again.
Hey, Mom, I'm glad
you got my message.
What are you doing home?
Bella? Bella? Bella,
where are you?
Calm down, everything's fine.
- Bella? Bella?
I'll explain everything later.
Mom, are you there?
Forks High School
doesn't protect...
its students'
privacy very well.
It was just too easy
for Victoria...
to find your previous address.
It's a nice house
you have here.
I was prepared
to wait for you,
but then Mom came home
after she received...
a very worried call
from your dad,
and it all worked
out quite well.
Wait, wait...
Don't touch her. Don't...
You can still save her.
- Don't.
But you're gonna
have to get away...
from your friends.
Can you handle that?
- Where should I meet you?
How about your
old ballet studio?
And I'll know if you
bring anyone along.
Poor Mommy would...
pay the price
for that mistake.
I'd never given much thought
to how I would die.
But dying in the place
of someone I love...
seems like a good way to go.
I can't bring myself to
regret the decisions...
that brought me
face-to-face with death.
They also brought
me to Edward.
Bella? Bella? Bella,
where are you?
Mom?
- Bella?
- There you are.
What are you doing in here?
Everyone makes fun of me.
Come on, you're a
wonderful dancer.
Mom, I suck.
You do not suck.
That's my favorite part.
You were a stubborn
child, weren't you?
She's not even here.
- No.
Sorry.
You know, but you really
made it too easy.
So to make things
more entertaining.
I'm gonna make a little film
of our time together.
I borrowed this
from your house.
I hope you don't mind.
Good.
And...
action.
That'll break Edward's
little heart.
You have...
Edward has nothing
to do with this.
But he does.
His rage will make for
more interesting sport...
than his feeble
attempt to protect you.
And let's continue.
Beautiful. Very
visually dynamic.
I chose my stage well.
It's too bad he didn't have
the strength to turn you.
Instead, he kept you
this fragile little human.
It's cruel, really.
Tell Edward how much it hurts.
Tell him to avenge
you. Tell him.
No, Edward, don't.
- Tell him. Tell him.
You're alone...
'cause you're faster
than the others.
But not stronger.
I'm strong enough to kill you.
I'm sorry.
Bella, Bella, it's okay.
Son. Enough.
Remember who you are.
Bella, you're okay.
Bella needs you.
It's okay.
Oh, God.
Carlisle? Her blood.
Your brothers will
take care of him.
I got him.
Carlisle.
- Start the fire.
Get the floorboards.
Alice.
- Alice, go.
Her femoral artery's
been severed.
She's losing too much blood.
No, no, my head is burning.
It's the venom.
You have to make a choice.
You could let the
change happen.
No.
It's gonna happen,
Edward. I've seen it.
It doesn't have
to be that way.
She's still hemorrhaging.
Alice, make me a
tourniquet. Your belt.
Carlisle, what's
my other option?
Tie it above my hands.
Carlisle.
Go.
We could try to
suck the venom out.
You know I won't
be able to stop.
Then find the will to stop.
But choose.
She only has minutes left.
I'm gonna make it
go away, Bella.
I'm gonna make it go away.
Edward, stop.
Her blood is clean.
You're killing her.
Edward.
Stop.
Find the will.
Death is peaceful, easy.
Life is harder.
Bella?
Baby?
Bella.
Mom?
- Hey.
Where is he?
Where's...
Where's Edward?
He's asleep.
He never leaves.
And your dad, he's
down at the cafeteria.
What happened?
Well, when you fell,
you broke your leg,
and you lost a lot of blood.
You don't remember
any of this, do you?
Edward came down
with his dad...
to try to convince you
to come back to Forks.
So you went over
to their hotel,
then you tripped,
and you fell down two
flights of stairs.
Went through a window.
Yeah, that sounds like me.
Oh, honey, I'm so sorry.
It's Phil.
He's so worried about you.
You're texting.
Finally, yeah.
I told him to stay
down in Florida.
Honey, you are gonna
love Jacksonville.
It's sunny every day,
and we found the
cutest little house,
and you've got
your own bathroom.
Mom, I still want
to live in Forks.
What?
I want to live in Forks.
Well, okay, but
we'll talk about it.
Do you mind getting Dad?
I have to talk to
him. Apologize.
Okay, baby. I'll go get him.
And I'll go get a nurse, okay?
- Okay.
So what happened?
Where's James?
We took care of it.
And the woman,
Victoria, she ran off.
I'm alive because of you.
No, you're in here
because of me.
The worst part of it was that
I thought I wasn't
gonna be able to stop.
You did stop.
Bella, you gotta go
to Jacksonville...
so I can't hurt you anymore.
What?
Are you... No.
No.
I don't even know
what you're... How...
What are you talking about?
You want me to go
away? I can't...
No, I can't... I can't
just leave you...
I know.
We can't be apart.
You can't leave me.
I'm here.
Okay, just don't...
You just can't say stuff
like that to me. Ever.
Where else am I gonna go?
Alice lent me the dress.
The cast is...
You're perfect.
I'll take care of
her, Chief Swan.
I've heard that before.
All right, Bells.
I put a new can of pepper
spray in your bag.
Dad.
And...
Well, you look beautiful.
Thanks.
See you.
Hey. I'll be right back.
Bella.
- Jacob.
Hey.
Nice.
- You, too.
Are you crashing the
prom or something?
Did you come with a date?
No.
My dad paid me to
come talk to you.
Twenty bucks.
Let's hear it.
Just don't get mad, okay?
He wants you to break up
with your boyfriend.
It's just, he said, quote,
'We'll be watching you. '
Okay, well, tell
him, 'Thanks. '
Okay.
And to pay up.
- Okay. Let me help you.
Jacob.
I'll take it from here.
Guess I'll see
you around, Bella.
All right.
I leave you alone
for two minutes,
and the wolves descend.
I can't believe you're
making me do this.
Just smile.
Tonight. Lightning Strikes.
Don't go stay tonight.
Wow. You are really
trying to kill me.
The prom is an important
rite of passage.
I didn't want you
to miss anything.
Oh.
Everyday we're
going all the way
Everyday, everyday, everyday
we're going all the way
Tonight. Lightning Strikes.
Bella, hey.
Do you want to go?
- Yeah.
All right, slowing it down.
Shall we?
You're serious?
Why not.
Wide on my plastic toys
Then when the cops
closed the fair
I cut my long baby hair
Stole me a dog-eared map
See, you're dancing.
At prom.
Have I found you
Flightless bird
Jealous
Weeping
Edward, why did you save me?
If you just let
the venom spread.
I could be like you by now.
You don't know what
you're saying.
You don't want this.
- I want you.
Always.
I'm not gonna end
your life for you.
I'm dying already.
Every second, I get closer.
Older.
That's the way it's
supposed to be.
Alice said that she
saw me like you.
I heard her.
- Her visions change.
Yeah, based on what
people decide.
I've decided.
So that's what
you dream about.
Becoming a monster.
I dream about being
with you forever.
Forever?
And you're ready right now?
Yes.
Bleeding or lost you
American mouth
Big pill
Is it not enough...
just to have a long
and happy life with me?
Yeah.
For now.
No one will surrender tonight,
but I won't give in.
I know what I want.
Have I found you
Flightless bird
Grounded
Bleeding or lost you
American mouth...
How come I end up
where I started
where I went wrong
Won't take my eyes
off the ball again
You reel me out then
you cut the string
How come I end up
where I started
where I went wrong
Won't take my eyes
off the ball again
First you reel me out
and then you cut the string
You used to be all right
What happened?
Did the cat get your tongue
Did your string come undone
One by one
It comes to us all
It's as soft as your pillow...
I dreamed I was missing
You were so scared
But no one would listen...
'Cause no one else cared
After my dreaming
I woke with this fear
What am I leaving
When I'm done here?
So if you're asking me
I want you to know
When my time comes
Forget the wrong
that I've done
Help me leave behind some
Reasons to be missed
Don't resent me
And when you're feeling empty
Keep me in your memory
Leave out all the rest
Forgetting all the hurt inside
You've learned to hide so well
Pretending someone
else can come
And save me from myself
I can't be who you are
When my time comes
Forget the wrong
that I've done
Help me leave behind some
Reasons to be missed
Don't resent me
And when you're feeling empty
Keep me in your memory
Leave out all the rest
Forgetting all the hurt inside
You've learned to hide so well
Pretending someone
else can come
And save me from myself
I can't be who you are
I can't be who you are...
How can I decide what's right
When you're
clouding up my mind
I can't win your losing fight
All the time
How can I ever own what's mine
When you're always
taking sides
But you won't take
away my pride
No, not this time
How did we get here?
When I used to
know you so well
But how did we get here?
I think I know
The truth is hiding
in your eyes
And its hanging on your tongue
Just boiling in my blood
But you think that I can't see
What kind of man that you are
If you're a man at all
Well, I will figure
this one out on my own
I'm screaming I love you so
My thoughts you can't decode
How did we get here?
When I used to
know you so well
Yeah But how did we get here?
Well, I think I know how
Do you see what we've done
We're gonna make such
fools of ourselves
How did we get here?
When I used to
know you so well
Yeah, yeah, yeah
How did we get here?
When I used to
know you so well
I think I know
There is something
I see in you
It might kill me
I want it to be true