Oh.
- Oh, yeah.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- You all right?
- Yeah, I'm... I'm okay.
Hey.
Hi.
Can I get you somethin'?
A coffee would be great.
So, um...
about last night.
What?
Did something happen I should be aware of?
Oh, you're funny.
I would really like
to take you out to dinner.
Think of it as a meal between friends.
Come on, we eat together all the time.
Yeah, but this would be different.
All right, no pressure.
All right, no expectations.
I, uh...
I just don't know that I'm ready.
You've got about ten hours.
I think you'll be fine.
Stop.
- Okay.
- Yes?
- Let's do it?
- Yeah. Okay.
Okay.
Oh, gosh.
I almost forgot.
I... I have to pick up Doc's breakfast.
Well, Ricky can walk it over.
Yeah, I know,
but, uh, he asked me to do it.
So tired of him treating me
like his intern-slash-assistant.
Yeah, I get it.
Just give him some time.
It's just that my trial period
is almost up.
Thanks.
Look, I know in his heart
he wants you to stay.
Yeah.
Well, I'm gonna talk to him.
I should get going.
- Bye.
Pick you up at six?
Yeah.
Stop scratching.
I can't stand it.
Well, just remember that feeling
next time you try to sneak away
from your field trip, okay?
- Okay.
- Yeah. No, no, no.
Here.
That, and get that prescription filled,
all right?
Take care, Benny.
Delores.
Ben.
I need the keys to your truck.
Oh, good morning to you, sunshine.
I don't have time for formalities.
- Keys.
- Well, what's wrong with your car?
- You tried to fix it.
- Oh.
How on earth did you graduate
medical school?
You know, the other day
you said I was brilliant.
Not with cars. Keys.
Where you goin'?
That's not your business.
Oh, my truck, my business.
I have errands.
Errands.
In Clear River.
Uh... Just stay out of Jack's life.
It's too late for that.
I've treated Jack like family
since he moved to Virgin River,
and I'll be damned if I'm gonna
stand by and watch him get hurt.
Can't you just leave anything alone?
Trust me. He'll be grateful I intervened.
Either that or he'll be resentful
you meddled.
No, I... I will not be a party to this. No.
Fine. I'll just, uh... wait here
until you come to your senses.
Sick people touch those.
I'm not afraid of germs,
and I'm not afraid of you.
Everything okay?
Ask Doc.
You know what?
Since I'm here,
I think I'll just tidy up your office.
- You always loved that.
- Okay, okay. Okay.
- Thank you.
- Hm.
That woman is tenacious
with a capital T.
That's a nice way of putting it.
I wasn't bein' nice.
Thanks.
- There somethin' on your mind?
- Yes, actually, there is.
Well, go on. Go on. I'm listenin'.
I would like to talk about my future here.
Oh, right.
Oh, and by the way, before I forget,
we're almost out of coffee.
It's not the end of the world.
Just make some more.
Okay.
Let me ask you something.
Do you want me to stay here?
Because in order for me to stay,
I need to believe
that the work that I'm doing matters.
- Coffee is important.
- I'm not your assistant.
I am the doctor.
I know, and I respect that.
- Good.
- But respect needs to run both ways
for us to continue to work together.
Give me a hand with the setup?
Hey, go easy on that thing.
Grease and dirt's the only thing
holdin' it together.
Okay, why don't you
put the steel wool down,
and step away from the grill?
All right, talk to me.
Uh, it's, uh... it's Paige.
- Is she okay?
- Yeah.
No.
No, man. You know, I, uh...
think she may be lying to me.
- What are you talking about?
- I found an old ID of hers,
except it had a different name.
Okay.
Yeah.
I think her... her real name...
may be Michelle Logan.
Well, people change their names
for all sorts of reasons.
Doesn't necessarily make her a liar.
Look, I know you like her.
Why don't you just ask her
what's goin' on?
Well, what if she won't tell me, hm?
Well, you can cross that bridge.
- Ricky, help me set up, will ya?
- Yeah, sure.
Where's Brady?
Probably late again.
Do you need some help?
I need him to close tonight.
Okay. You goin' somewhere?
- Yeah, out.
- With Mel?
Maybe.
- What, like on a date?
- No, just dinner.
But I thought she was married.
Well, she... was, and now she's not.
Oh. So, uh, where you takin' her?
I was thinkin' about Eureka.
There's this little place on the pier.
Oh, Arthur's. It's really romantic.
You know that place?
I Googled it.
Wh... why would you do that?
Emily.
Emily Walker is why.
I... I sit behind her in biology.
Ah?
And you like her, huh?
Yeah. I... I think she's amazing.
I... I thought maybe if I took her out
or something...
Okay.
So, what's the move?
Oh, I... I don't have any moves.
Well, try askin' her out.
You've got a fifty/fifty chance
she'll say yes.
Yeah, the same chance she'll say no.
Be an optimist.
- She's way out of my league.
- Says who?
The last guy she dated,
he was the captain of the football team.
- What's that got to do with it?
- I don't know if you noticed,
- but I'm not the captain of anything.
- So? Take a chance, all right?
You won't get anything in life
by playing it safe,
whether that's Emily or anything else.
Sometimes you gotta stick your neck out.
You're smart, kind, respectful.
She'll be lucky to have you.
There you go.
Thank you so much for coming in.
I'm glad you like it.
Charmaine.
- Hi.
Just started snowing.
Yeah, that happens here sometimes.
What are you doing in Clear River, Hope?
Uh, I came to see you.
Are you gonna get rid of the gray?
Oh, I think some lowlights
would just really brighten your face up.
My face is bright enough. Here.
I... I...
I don't understand.
Did Jack tell you to give this back to me?
- Not exactly.
- Then why do you still have it?
Because I think you need to talk to Jack
about the contents of this letter
in person.
You read it?
The envelope wasn't sealed.
It was in a box with a lid on it.
It's... it's addressed to Jack.
Okay, look. Let's not bicker
about whose fault this is.
The point is I read it,
and you need to talk to him.
I can't. That's why I wrote the letter.
So, wait until you can
and then go talk to him.
No.
I'm... I'm moving on.
I... I don't want to have
some big dramatic conversation,
just shake everything up, I just...
I I just wanted him to know how I felt.
Are you trying to hurt him?
Because that's how he's going to feel
when he reads this.
He's gonna think you don't care
about how this might affect him.
It's all in the letter.
I know Jack.
He's going to want to talk to you.
I... I've waited long enough. I...
I should have left him a long time ago.
I have a... a client.
Could you just please respect my wishes
and just give Jack the letter?
Please.
For the record,
I think you're making a mistake.
Well. It's a good thing
it's not your decision to make.
Doc!
Jeb, Pauline. What's goin' on?
Oh, Annabelle.
Annabelle, here.
Sit down, right here, sweetie.
How long has she been like this?
I don't know exactly, uh...
About an hour, maybe.
She's having trouble breathing.
Those inhaler things you gave her,
they aren't workin'.
Annabelle has a... a touch of asthma.
Why don't we get you in the exam room?
We'll take a listen to those lungs
and see why they're havin'
to work so hard, okay, sweetie?
It's gonna be okay.
Just come right in here.
Are you... are you okay?
Oh... just a bit of a headache.
Bit of a headache.
How long have you had it?
Uh... I get 'em all the time.
I'm a logger.
Okay. Can you take a seat for me?
Just a second.
Yeah. Okay, all right.
Look, help my girl, okay? I'll be fine.
Doc is in with her. I just wanna
take a look at you real fast, okay?
It's gonna be quick and painless,
I promise.
Have your headaches
been getting worse recently?
Give or take.
This is gonna be really tight
on your arm, okay?
- Okay...
- Okay.
There we go. Good.
I have to listen to your lungs.
Okay.
Yeah.
Okay. I'll be right back.
Mel, can I talk to you for a minute?
Yeah.
- Just stay right here.
- Wh...
- I'll be right back. Okay?
- What's wrong?
Yeah, it's not her asthma.
- Allergies?
- No, she has none.
And my gut feeling
is this is not an allergic reaction.
Well, Jeb has diminished breath sounds
on both sides,
and his oxygen sats are around 80.
- That can't be a coincidence.
- No.
What about Pauline?
She looked distressed, too,
but I was... I was focusing on Annabelle.
Besides the breathing issues,
Annabelle is nauseous,
sweaty, slow heart rate.
- She's bradycarding.
- I'm guessing it's some kind of poisoning.
- Agreed.
- Okay. We won't know how to treat them
until we know what it is
we're dealing with.
You go in with them.
I'll get the charcoal.
- Okay.
- Okay. And... and, oh, start an IV.
Annabelle's BP is down.
- I don't want her fluids getting low.
- Okay.
- Lactated Ringer's?
- Exactly.
- Where's Doc?
- He'll be right back.
- Hi, Annabelle.
- Hi.
Hi. My name is Mel.
I'm just gonna pop an IV
in your hand, okay?
- Okay.
- It's not gonna hurt.
- Uh-huh.
- I'm very good at this. Okay?
Pauline, did, uh,
Annabelle go to school today?
Uh, no, we kept her home.
She wasn't feeling well.
We've all been under the weather lately.
You're not feeling well either?
What are your symptoms?
Oh, just tired, uh,
nauseous, bad headache.
I thought it might be the stomach flu.
Jeb's got it, too.
We don't think it's the stomach flu.
No. We think you've all been exposed
to some kind of toxin.
Now, Pauline, I need you to focus.
- Hold that.
- Okay.
And have you been
preparing any new dishes?
Uh, done your grocery shopping
anywhere new?
- Drink that. Try and keep it down.
- Is there anything
that Annabelle
could have gotten into?
I keep the shed locked.
That's where I keep anything
that's dangerous.
What about cleaning products,
or gardening?
We keep all that in the shed, too.
She needs to get to a hospital.
Who do I call?
It'll take EMT services hours to get here.
- She doesn't have hours.
- I know.
That's why we're gonna
take her ourselves.
Okay, we gotta go now.
Okay, Jeb.
Your truck has a back seat, right?
- Uh, yeah.
- Good. Okay.
Mel, I'm driving.
You'll hold Annabelle's IV in the back.
- Bring my bag.
- Got it.
Here we go.
Jack?
All right.
Ricky, will you take their lunch order?
- I need to talk to you in private.
- I can't talk right now.
- Jack.
- Brady hasn't even shown up.
- Ricky can handle things.
- No, he can't.
Fine.
I'll... come back before the dinner rush.
Well, I won't be here.
Okay. Whoa, whoa. What's going on?
- All right.
- What?
Can you be discreet?
I can't believe I just asked you that.
How about a 24-hour gag order?
Fine.
- I'm taking Mel out to dinner.
- Damn it.
That's not exactly the reaction
I expected.
- This can't wait.
- Just let me get this order in.
I'll meet you in ten minutes.
- In your office.
- Okay.
Okay.
Hey, guys.
Oh, all of you?
Hey, Ricky. Give us a hand here?
She's bradying down.
- Is she hypoxic?
- Yes.
- BVM?
- It's in the bag.
Annabelle. Annabelle!
Okay. I need you to keep this
over her nose and mouth.
- What are you doing?
- I'm helping her to breathe.
Hey, be careful!
- Sorry, sorry.
- Please help her. Please help my baby.
How long until we get to the hospital?
Gardening. Uh...
Doc.
- Gardening. Gardening.
- No.They kept the supplies in the shed.
No, not that kind of gardening.
Jeb, did you ever get hooked up
to the town water supply?
Been saving up for the contractor.
So, where are you gettin' your water from?
Still using the well on our property.
Which borders state park land.
Which is right down the road from where
our friend Calvin has his grow operation.
I saw pesticides in the supply tent.
I think... I think that's leeching
into their groundwater.
- Do you have atropine?
- Yeah, bag. Right side.
That'll counteract the poison.
- Help her, please.
- Yeah. Okay. It's okay.
Hang in there, baby.
Annabelle, please.
- Hospital's ahead.
- Come on. We're almost there.
- Come on, Annabelle.
- Okay, we're comin' in.
Where are my wheelchairs?
I need two wheelchairs.
Clear the trauma rooms.
Hit that oxygen hard.
We're gonna need an atropine drip.
- Here they are.
- Hi.
Okay, Doc, what do we have?
We've got a 12-year-old female
suffering from organophosphate poisoning.
No known allergies.
History of asthma. Mel?
She's tachycardic.
We've helped with ventilation
and given her two amps of atropine
on the way.
You're gonna be okay.
Okay, we've got it from here.
Okay, folks. Let's move.
These are her parents.
We suspect that they have been exposed
to the same poison.
- I want to go with Annabelle.
- Right.
- Okay, she's gonna be okay.
- Yeah.
- Go with her now. Take them there.
- It's okay.
Okay.
Oh!
God.
- I hope we got her here in time.
- Yeah.
I think...
I think we did.
Uh... All right, just...
I don't have much time.
Just tell me what you need.
What's this?
It's from Charmaine.
She asked me to give it to you.
Well, why would she write me a letter?
I think she's afraid
if she talks to you in person
she'll end up wanting you back.
Come on.
She's the one that broke up with me.
She knows
you aren't in love with her.
Well, I... I can't make myself
feel something I don't.
Exactly. And you shouldn't.
Which is something I want you to remember
when you read her letter.
- Just... Can you give us a minute?
- Uh...
- Um...
- Yeah.
Jack, you need to read that.
Okay, yeah. I will.
That party of six,
the order's all messed up.
- All right. I'll be right there.
- Promise?
- Uh, I said I would.
- All right, then.
- Uh, Brady, come here.
- What's up?
I... I need you to close tonight.
- Can't Preacher do it?
- What?
Fine.
And you're late.
Yeah. Uh...
I know. I'm... sorry about that.
That happens again, we'll have a problem.
Understand?
Yes, sir.
You know, we should really warn
the people in that area
that their groundwater
may be contaminated.
Yeah. Yeah.
And I need to pay a visit to Calvin.
That sounds dangerous.
Well, you know, Calvin appreciates
the...
you know,
the importance of keeping the peace.
I don't know why you help him.
Oh, I don't help him.
You're always going up to the camps.
Yeah, but it's not for Calvin.
He's a son of a bitch.
His workers deserve decent healthcare.
Well, that's very noble of you.
Nothing noble about...
caring about people.
More people should do it.
Hm.
Not for nothin'...
you were great back there.
Thank you.
That LA hospital must have hated
to lose you.
Yeah. Well, I needed a change of scenery.
So, does that mean you're stayin'?
Um, are you asking?
Well, I would be open to...
extending your trial period.
No. There's no more trial period.
Aah.
I'm not changing the stationery.
I can live with that.
I need a coffee.
- Jeez.
- Yeah.
Can I get you a cup?
I would love a latte.
Good Lord, even your drink is difficult.
You said he was gonna be okay.
You told us.
Hey, Doc?
- Did you say something?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry,
I just realized what time it is.
I have to... I have to get back.
I don't have time to get coffee.
- Oh. Of course. Of course.
- Sorry.
Oh, you got company.
Yeah. Um...
Uh... Don't worry. Unlike Hope,
I believe the less I know,
the happier I'll be.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Uh-huh.
- I'll see ya tomorrow.
Hey.
Whose truck is that?
It's Jeb's.
Is everything okay?
Um...
I should just tell you on the way. It's...
I still have to get ready, and you know.
- Yeah. Take your time.
- Okay. You look nice.
Thank you.
Wow.
I thought we'd, um...
head over to Eureka,
away from any prying eyes.
Oh. You thought of everything,
didn't you?
No pressure.
Right.
Just like I promised.
Okay.
Just dinner.
Right.
I can't believe we're only two hours
from Virgin River.
It's a whole other world here, huh?
Yeah.
It's really a beautiful night.
Well, wait till you taste the food.
They, uh...
have a Michelin star.
Ooh, impressive.
Well, that was the plan.
Damn it, Brady. What the hell?
Take it out of my pay.
No. You know what?
The toilet in the men's room is backed up.
Sounds nasty. Better get on that.
- Brady.
- Come on, man. How's that my job?
- Get Ricky to do it.
- So what, you think that's beneath you?
Yeah. As a matter of fact, I do.
Well, from where I'm standin',
that is exactly where you belong.
No.
Brady, I wasn't askin'.
You know, I'm sick of you bossing me
around, thinking you're better than me.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- You had it out for me the minute I came.
- That's because you...
you are unreliable,
you are insubordinate,
and I wasn't convinced
that you had changed.
And it seems like I'm right.
I'm not interested in cleaning up other
people's crap for the rest of my life.
That might be enough for you,
but it isn't for me.
At least I never got a man killed.
Leave that alone.
I lost two ribs and a kidney
because of you.
Lonergan is dead because of you.
And Jack...
Ah, don't even know.
I don't even know why I bother.
You didn't care then,
you... you don't care now.
You are nothing...
but a damned liability.
Okay, uh...
I've been meaning to ask you this.
- Hm?
- I noticed that your bedside reading
- is Kierkegaard.
- Oh...
- That surprised you?
- No.
No, it didn't surprise me. Um...
I took a few philosophy courses
in college, and I really liked him.
- Yeah.
- What did you like about him?
He's, um... a rebel philosopher.
You know, it wasn't just that he disagreed
with what everyone was saying,
but he thought they were ridiculous
because they were so sure of themselves.
And I loved how he thought trying
to predict how life was gonna play out
was impossible 'cause you can
never really account for free will, right?
Not everyone's free will.
Right.
But what about fate?
Well, isn't fate ultimately
just a collection of everybody's choices?
No, I... I have to disagree.
Okay.
We're here right now,
experiencing this moment,
and that wasn't inevitable.
I chose to be here.
I like it
when you put it like that.
Well, I think...
I chose to move to Virgin River.
- Right?
- But I think it was fate
that I saw Hope's ad,
and so it was both of those things
that led me to be in this moment with you.
But was it fate or coincidence
that you saw the ad?
Maybe it was serendipity.
- I like that.
- Mm-hm.
Well, whatever it was, I'm...
I'm grateful that you did, um...
I'm glad that we're here.
I really like talking with you.
I really like talking to you, too.
While I would love
to spend the rest of the evening
debating the finer points
of free will and fate...
- I think our waitress wants to go home.
- Oh.
Ah.
Well, we should go for a walk.
Thank you.
Preacher.
It's, uh... it's late.
What are you doing here?
Hey, uh... I know.
I know. I'm... I'm sorry, but I...
I just really need to speak to you.
Ah, can't it wait until morning?
It's just I gotta...
I gotta get somethin' off my chest.
Uh, Christopher's asleep,
so how about I come by the bar tomorrow?
- Okay?
- Hey...
I know your real name's Michelle.
And I know that you're scared.
And the things that I... I've read...
I know that you would never,
ever hurt Christopher.
I want to help you.
I just... I just need you to trust me.
I will come by the bar tomorrow,
and we can talk then.
Okay?
Okay.
This is so cool.
I'm glad you like it here.
I love it. It's awesome.
There's so many boats.
Well, you ought to see it
in the summertime.
You've got your commercial fishing boats.
You have... fishing charters.
Daysailers.
Powerboats.
Over here, you have all the live-aboards.
Is that "Taps"?
Yeah. Lots of vets live around here.
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
You know, Jack,
if you ever wanna talk about it,
I'm here.
Yeah.
Thank you. I'm, uh...
I'd rather focus on what's in front of me.
♪ Hello, can you hear me? ♪
♪ The dark is gettin' close ♪
Hey, look who it is.
And who the hell are you?
Your fairy godmother.
You're from Virgin River, right?
Jack's little helper?
I got this. Here.
Leave that bottle behind. Thanks.
That's a lot of money.
Nah, it's nothin'.
Mm.
So...
what do you do?
Well, I don't work in a bar.
Hell, I hardly work at all.
♪ Catch me if you can ♪
I had a really nice time.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Eureka's a beautiful town.
Yeah, there's a lot of other places
I'd love to show you around here.
Sometime.
♪ I will go ♪
- ♪ if you ask me ♪
- Okay. Um...
- Well, good night.
- ♪ I will stay ♪
Good night, Mel.
♪ If you dare ♪
♪ If I go, I'm goin' on fred ♪
♪ Let my anger take me there ♪
You okay?
- ♪ The shingles ♪
- Yeah. I just, uh...
- ♪ Man, they're shakin' ♪
- I just need to take things slowly.
- It's okay.
- ♪ The back door's ♪
♪ Burnin' through ♪
♪ This old house, she's quite the keeper ♪
♪ Quite the keeper of you ♪
- Oh, now you're killing me.
- Ohh...
You're gonna be just fine.
Good night.
- ♪ I will go ♪
- Will I see you tomorrow?
Um...
♪ If you ask me to ♪
- I make great pancakes.
- ♪ I wil stay ♪
- I bet you do.
- ♪ If you dare ♪
Okay.
♪ If I go, I'm goin' crazy ♪
See you in the morning, then.
- ♪ Let my darlin' take me there ♪
- Okay.
♪ If I go, I'm goin' crazy ♪
♪ Let my darlin' take me there ♪
I can't believe it.
You might consider surrogacy.
I'll be right back.
- Do you wanna look for a surrogate?
- ♪ Take my hand and see ♪
I think we need a break, Mel.
- ♪ Where we can go ♪
- What?
It's all we do. It's all we talk about.
This thing, it's consumed
the entire marriage, and we...
Now you want to start the process
of vetting a total stranger
to carry our baby?
- It's...
- Wait. It doesn't have to be a stranger.
- Mel.
- I could ask Joey.
- You can't ask Joey.
- I could ask her.
No, I don't want you to do that.
Sweetheart,
our lives are hard enough as it is,
and I can't handle...
worrying about someone who isn't you.
- I thought you wanted to have a family.
- I did. I do.
- ♪ 'Cause I need your counsel ♪
- Please, Mark.
♪ Give me strength ♪
Please, I... Please, honey.
♪ So I can be ♪
♪ How long for the perfect time? ♪
♪ If not now, then when? ♪
♪ Oh, how long? ♪
♪ No, don't be silent ♪
♪ We can be true again ♪
♪ No need to wait ♪
♪ Wait for now ♪
♪ Our walls come down ♪
♪ Reveal to me ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ No need to wait, no ♪
♪ For me to see ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Now is the time ♪
♪ Reveal to me ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ If not now, when? ♪
♪ For me to see ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ If not now, when? ♪
♪ For me to see ♪