♪ I woke up and wished that I was dead ♪
♪ With an aching in my head ♪
♪ I lay motionless in bed ♪
♪ The night is here ♪
♪ And the day is gone ♪
♪ And the world spins madly on ♪
♪ I thought of you ♪
♪ And where you'd gone ♪
♪ And the world spins madly on ♪
♪ And the world ♪
- ♪ Spins madly on ♪
- Oh, great.
Oh.
Well, that looks like a nasty bump.
- How do you feel?
- Not great.
I'm not surprised.
Word to the wise.
That particular patient
always requires restraints.
Right. There wasn't a chart.
It's your first day, huh?
- Yeah.
- Always get the chart.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
Don't wanna walk into a situation
totally blind.
- You'll wind up...
- Knocked on my ass?
Yeah.
Mm.
Have a good day.
- Oh!
- You need to get out of the car.
- What?
- You need to get out of the car, ma'am.
- Your vehicle is stuck in the ditch.
- What?
Oh, it's unbelievable.
Well, you're lucky you didn't smash
this ridiculous little car into a tree.
Thank you for stopping.
I'll just call AAA.
Uh... Look around.
You're in a heavily wooded area.
There's no cell reception here.
Damn it.
I'll call Bert once we get into town.
If he's not too busy,
maybe you'll get your car back this week.
Are you comin' or not?
Um... Could you drop me
at the McCrea cabin?
It's in Virgin River.
I've got the address here.
Anyone who lives within 50 miles of here
knows the McCrea cabin.
Oh. Well, from the photo, it's beautiful.
Um...
Here.
Folks around here,
we don't pay each other to be neighborly.
Just somethin' we do.
Right. I'm sorry.
Thank you.
And here we are.
Oh, no.
That's a beaut, huh?
Oh!
Someone pulled a fast one on you.
Never book your vacation online,
they'll scam you every time.
No, I... I'm not on vacation.
I'm here for a job.
I'm the new nurse.
I'm... I'm actually a nurse practitioner
and midwife.
I'm gonna be working with Dr. Mullins.
I heard he's handling the practice alone,
and it's getting to be too much for him.
Oh, is... is that what you heard, huh?
- Okay.
- Yeah. I think he's in his 70s
and still working full time.
Oh, it's a wonder he's still above ground.
So, old Doc hired ya, huh?
Well, Hope McCrea did the actual hiring.
Aah.
I'm so sorry. I don't know your name.
I'm Melinda Monroe. People call me Mel.
I'm Vernon.
People call me Doc Mullins.
And for the record, missy,
I'm 72.
Oh. Oh, what is that?
Oh!
- Hello?
Hi.
Melinda!
I'm Hope McCrea.
As the mayor of Virgin River,
I'd like to officially welcome you
to our little slice of heaven.
Hi, Hope. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I just...
I'm a little confused.
Um...
This is what you sent me.
The... "This farmhouse-chic cabin...
nestled in the woods
of Northern California
is designed to enjoy
all the trappings of country life?"
Like... "Farmhouse-chic" is not
an accurate description of this property.
I admit, I... I haven't gotten around
to taking a more current photo.
Okay, well, the job I accepted
included housing for a year.
- And I obviously can't stay here.
- Um...
I'll have it cleaned.
Was that... Did you just put a bird's...
Is that a bird's nest from the oven?
You did come a bit early.
No, I didn't. I'm three days late.
Well, no need to get all twisted up.
- Well...
- I can wake up the Fitches.
Jo Ellen and Nick
rent out their extra rooms.
Of course, the husband's a bit handsy.
He pretends it's an accident,
but it isn't.
Um... Anyway, you look like
you can take care of yourself.
Uh...
Oh, well, at least the fridge is stocked
with gourmet foods and beverages.
I was going to take care of that earlier,
but we... we had a ribbon cutting ceremony
over at the firehouse.
Got ourselves a new hose.
- When did you eat last?
- Why?
Hungry equals cranky.
And between us gals,
you don't wear cranky well.
- Hm.
- Head to Jack's. By the time you get back,
I'll have the hot water running
and fresh towels and blankets.
- Who's Jack? I...
- Jack's Bar.
Only place to eat in town after five.
You can walk.
Out the door and to the left.
Okay, but we're not done
talking about this.
Of course we aren't.
Bye.
♪...love ♪
♪ You're bringin' trouble ♪
♪ You keep me hangin' ♪
I think it's great.
- I know!
- ♪ I'm givin' love ♪
♪ You're bringin' trouble ♪
♪ You keep me hangin' ♪
♪ On your line ♪
♪ I get the feelin' ♪
♪ It's gettin' heavy ♪
♪ The situation ♪
- Ricky.
- Yeah?
More glasses, please.
Uh, sure, boss.
So, what are we havin'?
Whiskey? Soda? Wine?
You look like a wine person.
You need a minute?
Uh, no. Uh, any chance of getting a cosmo?
Nope. Not unless you brought
your own Cointreau.
I did not.
Uh... So, mixed drinks are not...
Not our thing.
But I have all the boys,
Johnnie, Jack, and Jim.
All the regular stuff and beer.
Just no frills.
All right,
make it a Jim straight up.
Okay.
I commend you on your choice.
Huh.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hm.
♪ The feelin' is quite deceivin' ♪
Well, I didn't know city girls
could shoot whiskey.
What makes you think I'm a city girl?
Come on. Cosmo?
Manicure? Cartier?
Wow. You should be a detective.
No. My days of tracking bad guys are over.
- What?
- Sorry.
We don't get a lot of visitors.
Certainly not as beautiful as you.
I'm sorry. Does that line really work?
Oh, you'd be surprised.
Well, you're lucky
we're not in Los Angeles,
because Angelinos can smell BS
a mile away.
Oh, really? That's one of the reasons
why I love living here so much.
People aren't so jaded.
I'm Jack Sheridan.
Mel Monroe.
So, is this your bar?
Well, it will be
in about 60 more payments.
So, Miss Mel Monroe from LA,
what brings you to our tiny little hamlet?
- Work.
- Yeah?
Where you staying?
Uh, the McCrea cabin.
Oof. What'd you do to deserve that?
Yeah, I should have come up
and vetted the place first.
Oh, come on.
I think spontaneity's
an admirable quality.
Oh, no. You... you can't credit me
with being spontaneous.
No, it once took me six months
to buy a crêpe pan.
- Six months.
Yeah, I usually check everything
three times, and then I check it again.
Used to drive my...
- So, how long you here for?
- Um...
A year.
I'm working with Dr. Mullins.
I'm a nurse.
Oh, that should be an experience.
Yeah. I imagine
it's gonna resemble the cabin.
- Uncomfortable.
- Exactly.
I think you might be right.
So, you know Dr. Mullins?
Oh, everybody knows everybody around here.
- Small town.
- Right.
And it's Doc.
He does not like formalities.
Oh, well, he does not like me.
I basically called him old.
But in my defense,
I didn't know it was him I was talking to
when I said it.
- He is old.
- I know, right?
Thank you.
Preacher, Mel.
- Mel, Preacher.
- Hi.
Yeah, he's a man of few words,
but he's a good friend,
- and he's a great cook.
- Mm.
Um...
This is amazing. What is this?
Squirrel.
Mm...
- That was too easy.
- That's not funny.
You're dining
on squash and lentils.
You know what?
I actually have had squirrel,
and if it's done right, it's pretty tasty.
Okay, well,
I'm gonna take your word on that.
Oh, no, no, no.
If I have any more,
I won't be able to find the cabin.
Which might not be a bad thing, so...
it's fine.
It's my car. God bless you, Bert.
I can't sleep in that.
You certainly can't drive.
Oh, no, no, no.
No. I mean, leaving town's
just not even an option.
Would you like to know why?
I will tell you.
Because... I sold my house...
and most of my belongings.
And then I quit my job.
And I moved to this town that I've never
heard of just so I could live in there.
- Yep.
- So...
I hate it when Joey's right.
You know?
Husband?
Sister.
- Yeah.
- Well...
if I had a spare room, I'd offer, but...
Oh, no, no, no.
That's sweet, but it's... it's fine.
I'll just, you know, it'll be one night.
It'll be like camping. Right?
Yeah, sure.
Oh...
Mm-hm.
Oh.
It's not that bad, right?
Well...
Perspective is most often
the key to happiness.
So, what you're saying
is that acclimation is possible.
Oh, yeah.
Just try not to insult any more residents.
Thank you, Jack.
Thank you for the... the help,
and the kind words, and food.
But mostly, thank you for the whiskey.
Any time, Mel.
Hey, Mark, do you know which box
the towels are in?
No...
but I found a set of sheets.
- Oh.
- Mm.
What are you doing with this?
I'm drying my hands.
Uh-uh.
This is personally autographed
by Bob Seger
and the entire Silver Bullet Band.
Handed down to me by my father,
who was at Cobo Hall in Detroit
on the night of the live recording
of their very first album.
Now, one beautiful day
in the not-too-distant future,
I'm gonna hand this on to our son,
Mark Junior.
- Mm.
- And he to his son, Mark Junior Junior.
And so on and so forth.
Mm.
What if we have a girl?
Hmm.
Oh!
Oh, Mark, stop!
Come on!
I hate this place.
God. Ugh!
It's too early for lectures.
Hey, I didn't say a thing.
Yeah, you didn't have to.
So?
The pretty lady make it home last night?
She had a ring on.
Yeah, I wasn't sure you noticed.
I did.
That gun's not loaded, right?
Okay. Uh, first, I just wanted
to say thank you
for stopping and helping me last night.
And second, I would like to apologize
for what I said.
The part where you called me old
or the part where you said
I can't handle my practice?
In my defense, I was told
by Mrs. McCrea that you were elderly
and nearing retirement.
It took me 30 years
to build this practice from scratch.
No help.
No nurse. I don't need ya.
Well, I signed a contract.
Hah. Not with me, you didn't.
I don't even recall interviewing you,
but maybe that's...
that's just my dementia actin' up.
Well, I was hired to do a job,
and I'm here to do that job.
You know, in this county,
trespassers can be shot...
on sight.
Uh, I'm not trespassing.
Do you work here? No.
Are you a patient here? No.
Did I invite you in? No.
If it looks like a duck
and quacks like a duck,
that is a duck.
Okay. What are you gonna do, shoot me?
Oh-ho-ho.
Well, it's finally happened.
- You've lost your damn mind.
- Ow.
You threatened her with a gun?
I simply educated her
- on some of our local laws.
- You are a stubborn goat.
I think you mean stubborn old goat.
You're old. I'm old. It's not a secret.
- I told you I would find somebody myself.
- Maybe I should just go...
- Go!
- Stay!
I gave you an entire year.
This is not your business.
- This town depends on both of us.
- And who put you in charge?
The town did when they elected me mayor.
- You ran unopposed.
- The point is, I won.
You are the only one
who thinks I need any help.
- The only one.
- Bull.
Everyone thinks you need help.
They're just too scared to tell you.
Vernon, we both know
you can't be in two places at once.
Even for you, that was low.
I thought you were dead.
Hey, I'm sorry, sis. I...
Yeah, I was about to call out
the National Guard.
Well, they probably wouldn't
be able to find this place, anyway.
What's wrong?
Nothing. I'm fi... I'm fine.
I'm worried about you.
Just tell me what's goin' on.
Um, nothing.
Nothing, nothing. I'm... fine.
I just...
It's just this doctor that I'm working for
doesn't want me here.
And this cabin I'm in, it's just...
it's just awful.
And I...
I just feel really alone right now.
Mel, you are not alone.
Okay? Come back here.
You can stay with us
for as long as you want.
Mel, stop trying to punish yourself
for what happened.
Nobody blames you.
Just come home.
Honey, all you changed by moving
was your address.
I'm sorry, Joe.
I'm gonna call you tomorrow, okay?
- I love you.
- No.
Hey.
I've got goat, beef,
venison, rabbit, and buffalo.
Uh... Any fish?
You know, you should try the salad
with the shaved brussels sprouts and kale.
- Kale?
- Yeah.
All of Preacher's vegetables
are farm-to-table,
and the farm is about
50 feet from the table.
Okay, great.
Well, I'll have that salad, please.
- Thanks for the assist.
- I'm Paige Lassiter.
I run the bakery truck.
- Hi. I'm Mel...
- Monroe. Yeah, the new nurse.
In small towns, the internet is slow,
but the gossip is fast.
Right.
Is that a Celine bag?
Um...
Yes, it is.
I'm probably the only person in
Virgin River with a subscription to Vogue.
So, this...
Um... Anyway, you should stop by
for a muffin or something.
- Oh?
- Yeah. Us girls should stick together.
Absolutely.
- Okay. It's nice to meet you.
- You too.
Look...
- you are a brilliant doctor...
- Huh.
But when you're finally ready
to hang up your stethoscope,
you'll be leaving behind
a gaping hole in this community.
I don't even know her.
She ranked top of her class at UC Irvine,
did her practical at County USC,
then she spent five years
working emergency at Cedars-Sinai.
Her references are good as gold.
Then what the heck's she doin' here?
I guess she... wanted a change.
Even if you're too stubborn to admit it,
we both know you need help.
Give her a chance.
You got nothing to lose.
Thirty days.
But... if she can't cut it,
I've got your word this is the last time
you stick your nose in my business.
Ooh. Good choice.
This is so delicious.
Well, you sound surprised.
Oh, no, it's totally normal to have
a gourmet kale and brussels sprout salad
at a bar in the middle of nowhere
surrounded by animal heads.
You want something to drink?
I would kill for a latte.
Sorry. Nearest Starbucks, 80 miles away.
- Really?
- Mm-hm.
You know there's a Starbucks
in Kuala Lumpur?
Um, Nurses Beyond Borders.
Oh.
A humanitarian.
There's so many things
to learn about you, huh?
Hm. Yeah, well, according to Doc,
I'm an ageist.
Well, good thing
I'm still relatively young and attractive.
You know,
looks have nothing to do with it.
You're the only restaurant in town.
Oh, yeah, you keep telling yourself that.
What I keep telling myself
is that I'm crazy
for not packing up and going home.
Good news.
Doc's not gonna throw you a parade,
but he agreed to try you out.
You start immediately.
Hope, you've already hired me.
Well, here's the thing.
I'm paying your salary,
but it is his practice, so...
Why didn't you just tell me that?
Honey, then you wouldn't have come,
would you?
Like my father said to my mother
at the altar,
"You're already here,
so let's make the best of it."
Hmm.
Well, I'm not staying
in that shack another night.
I gotta side with Mel on that one.
You stay out of this.
Do I need to remind you that we have a...
Oh, oh, I'm fully aware
that we have a contract.
Okay? I'm also aware that
suitable housing was part of the deal,
so technically, you're in breach.
Which means the contract is null and void.
I can leave whenever I want.
Can you afford to have her leave?
No.
Well, why don't you get her a room
at the Fitches'?
I'll fix up the cabin.
Ricky could help me.
I'm not made of money.
Hope,
please don't poor-mouth to me.
You and I both know you couldn't spend
half of what you have if you tried.
You're offering an awful lot of yourself
to help a complete stranger.
Oh, Hope,
I thought you knew me better than that.
Jack, I've known you a long time.
If Mel was short for Melvin,
we wouldn't be having this conversation.
I believe Hope has some good news for you.
I'll put you up at the Fitches' while
I figure out what to do with the cabin.
The place with the handsy husband?
Did I say that?
You know, I can fight my own battles.
Never turn down help
when deep in a foxhole.
How about a show
of Virgin River hospitality?
Why don't I take you on a tour tomorrow?
Okay, tell you what.
I'm gonna be at the river at seven a.m.
If you want to join me,
I'll be there.
Uh...
Hey. Uh, so, should I just pull up a chart
and grab a patient?
- No.
- No?
No. Until I can confirm
that you are competent, no patients.
Well, how can you confirm my competency
if I can't see any patients?
Chitchat is over.
I've got a waitin' room full of people.
- Welcome.
- Hi.
Oh, I am sorry that my husband
isn't here to greet you as well.
- Oh...
- He's doing a supply run in Grace Valley.
We only have one room left, and, uh...
I'm nervous that you won't like it.
Hope told me that you're very picky.
Yeah.
- Come take a look.
- Okay.
- After you.
- Thank you.
Boy, you picked the wrong place to rob.
Get your hands up.
Now turn around. Slowly.
Oh-ho-ho!
Come on.
Hey, man.
Brady!
Bro, what are you doing in here, man?
I was leaving you a note.
Wanted to let you know I was okay.
How the hell did you get in here?
Come on.
I know where you keep the spare key.
Listen, I... I've got plans this morning.
But why don't you go get something to eat,
and then go up to my room,
grab some sleep,
and then clean yourself up, okay?
All right.
Long time.
Welcome back.
Thanks, man.
Yeah.
Hey!
Hey.
Are you coming up, or am I coming down?
- You're comin' down here.
- Okay.
Oh, I see you got a coffee.
Yeah. Paige's bakery truck.
You could have mentioned it.
- I believe in self-discovery.
- Ah.
- And practicality.
- Ah!
Yeah.
- No, thank you.
- No, no, no. I insist.
Where are we going?
I cleared your morning with Doc.
You cleared my morning.
Well, there's no cell reception out here,
so I figured you wouldn't want to give Doc
any more ammunition by being late, so...
- Wow.
- But let me help you.
No, no.
I don't need your assistance, okay?
Okay. I'm sorry I called Doc for you.
It won't happen again.
Now, you wanna put your hand
on my shoulder?
Okay, now step.
Oh...
And... other one.
Step.
Okay.
- All right. We can leave this here.
- Wait.
No. No, no, no.
My whole life is in that bag.
Oh, look, no one's gonna take it.
- Hm?
- Because no one's here.
- Trust me?
- Hm.
Aah.
Mm. Hey, thank you.
- Uh... How much further?
- We're almost there.
Wow.
It's not even the best part.
Eagles.
Here.
This is their favorite spot.
Mine too.
They're incredible. Huh.
Yeah.
So, what's next?
Nothin'.
Here.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah.
Aah.
I think I can actually
hear my heart beating.
"In peace, nothing so becomes a man..."
Or woman...
- "...as modest stillness."
- Shakespeare?
- Mm.
- You an English major?
Hm?
No, I never went to college.
But in my 20s,
I loved to read while drinkin',
so it kind of all evens out.
Uh...
- Is that hunters?
- Yeah, could be.
Could be somethin' else.
There's a lot of illegal pot fields
outside of Virgin River.
But it's legal now.
Yeah. It doesn't stop the illegal growers
from doin' business.
Cross them, and things can turn dangerous.
I used to work in the, uh...
ER Level One Trauma Center,
so I've seen my fair share
of what dangerous can do.
ER, huh?
Sounds like an intense job.
Yeah, you could say that.
But I'm sure owning a bar
has its challenges.
Piece of cake,
compared to my time in the service.
Marine.
Joined up right out of high school.
Spent 20-plus years,
mostly in the Middle East.
Preacher was with me.
And Brady. You haven't met him yet.
Wow.
Do you miss it?
Yes and no.
I had, um...
People who... depended on me.
And Virgin River, well, it's, uh...
it's a utopia, compared to a war zone.
- Oh, here.
- Oh...
Come on...
- Aah.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
Thanks for this morning.
It was my pleasure.
Well, I'll see you around.
Yeah, you will.
- See ya.
- Bye.
Hello?
Doc?
Is Doc here?
Hi, there. No, no, he's not in right now.
He'll be back soon.
I'll wait.
Uh... I'm the new nurse practitioner.
Maybe I can help you.
Uh... Oh, I'll wait for Doc.
Ooh...
- Um... When are you due?
- Ooh...
Any day now.
It's okay.
Okay. I think I should take a look at you.
I don't know when the doctor'll be back.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Okay. Can you stand?
Uh... Yeah.
- Yeah.
- It's okay. Just take a breath.
- Ready? One, two, three. Up.
- Okay.
There you go.
It's okay. You're gonna be just fine.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Yeah.
- What's your name?
- Polly.
- Polly Fishburn.
My name's Mel.
And I'm gonna take
really good care of you, okay?
Okay.
You're gonna be just fine now.
Can you get up on this table?
- Yeah.
- Got it?
You got it. You got it.
Yeah...
I've gone through
last night's receipts twice.
- Mm-hm?
- The cash box is light.
Oh, y... you know what?
I advanced Ricky a week to prep
the McCrea cabin for some maintenance. I...
I thought I logged that.
Must have forgotten.
Oh, look who's back in town...
Brady.
So, how long before you disappear again?
I told him he could stay
as long as he wants.
Mm.
I'm gonna head to Clear River.
Run some errands. Catch you in a bit.
Yeah.
Uh, I left...
a lot of kids behind who I couldn't help.
I can help Brady, okay?
I'm not turning my back on him.
Well, then, you may wanna
change the locks on the office door.
Or you may be "advancing Ricky"
a whole lot more than a week's pay.
What is goin' on?
- I'm with a patient.
- No, I...
I'm almost done. I'll be right out.
Is everything okay?
You're doing fine.
Your baby is doing fine, okay?
You're just having... some Braxton Hicks.
- Oh.
- False labor pains.
They don't feel false though, do they?
- No.
Uh... Why don't you just
lay here and rest,
and I'll go call your husband
to come pick you up, okay?
Okay.
Thanks, Mel.
You're very welcome.
- Who said you could give her an exam?
- I was just doing my job.
This is my practice.
My name is on that door.
You do not work with a patient
unless you have my permission.
Polly was having Braxton Hicks.
I had to examine her to make sure
that she wasn't in premature labor.
Did you know there's protein in her urine?
Don't lecture me about my patient.
Well, it's not in her chart.
- I don't put everything in the chart.
- Uh-huh.
- Okay, well, where do you put it?
- Right here.
And if you're not here to tell me
what's not in the chart?
My dear, I'm not just old, I'm old-school.
And in my day,
a nurse would never, never question
the methods of a supervising physician.
A nurse would know her place.
Well, I hope you'll join me
in the 21st century.
And your point is?
This time it was false labor,
but what about the next Polly or whoever?
Wh... Do you want me to just stand by
and watch someone bleed out
if you're not here?
You should have called me.
I had things under control.
These patients, they are like my family.
And I cannot trust you with them
unless I know for sure
you're not gonna hurt someone.
So, if I can't do what I was hired
to do, what is it that you want me to do?
Well, straighten up the office.
File things.
Uh... Keep the coffee pot full.
I like mine black and fresh.
Hello, Polly.
He's refusing to let me do my job.
- Give it time.
- No, no, no, no, no.
This is not about time.
Okay, good medicine is about teamwork,
and he doesn't want me on his team.
He'll come around.
He is rude, he is demeaning,
and he's a big-time chauvinist.
The man's got his quirks,
I'll give you that.
It's obvious that he needs somebody,
but it's not gonna work like this, okay?
It needs to be his idea,
or he's never gonna accept it.
My grandfather was just like him.
So, you understand.
Yeah, and he's never gonna change.
Look, Hope, the bottom line is
that this is not what I signed up for.
Join the club, sweetheart.
Life rarely gives us what we want.
Okay...
I didn't join a club, okay? I took a job.
I'm sorry, I have to give you notice.
I'll give you time to find someone,
but you need to start looking now.
♪ I took my love and I took it down ♪
♪ I climbed a mountain
And I turned around ♪
She's so beautiful.
- ♪ And I saw my reflection ♪
- So, where's Bill?
- ♪ In the snow-covered hills ♪
- Work.
Auntie Mel.
- ♪ Till the landslide brought me down ♪
- You make beautiful babies.
So, when are you two gonna make me
an aunt?
♪ Oh, mirror in the sky ♪
- ♪ What is love? ♪
- We're working on it.
- ♪ Can the child ♪
- Work harder.
♪ Within my heart ♪
- ♪ Rise above? ♪
- Okay.
- You know I rarely agree with your sister.
- ♪ Can I sail ♪
- Mm-hm.
- ♪ Through the changing ♪
- ♪ Ocean tides?
- She's right.
- ♪ Can I handle the seasons ♪
- I have to run. Sorry.
♪ Of my life? ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Well, I've been 'fraid of changin' ♪
♪ 'Cause I've built my life around you ♪
♪ But time makes you bolder ♪
♪ Children get older ♪
♪ And I'm getting older, too ♪
♪ So take this love and take it down ♪
♪ Yeah, and if you climb a mountain ♪
♪ And you turn around ♪
♪ And if you see my reflection ♪
♪ In the snow-covered hills ♪
♪ Well, the landslide brought me down ♪
♪ And if you see my reflection ♪
♪ In the snow-covered hills ♪
♪ Well, maybe ♪
Hey, Mel.
Jack?
- ♪ Well, maybe ♪
- You better take a look at this.
- Jesus.
I'm pretty sure that's not Jesus.
♪ The landslide will bring you down ♪