Two IVs in place in antecubital fossae.
- Any known allergies?
- Um...
When was the last time he ate?
- I... I don't know.
- Blood type?
- Um... It was...
- Height? Weight?
Uh, he's, uh...
- Relation?
- He's my husband!
He's my husband! Mark!
No! No!
- Hi.
- I thought I heard something.
- Is everything all right?
- Yeah. I just, um...
I stubbed my toe.
Um, the... the light's not working.
There's a power outage across town.
It happens every time
we get a big storm rolling through.
Great. Um, do you know
when it's gonna come back on?
It's impossible to say.
It depends on how damaged
the power lines are.
You okay?
I'm just not... I'm not a fan of storms.
Oh. Well, I am sorry to say
we get them quite often this time of year.
Whenever there's a power outage,
the whole town congregates at Jack's Bar.
We'll be heading over in a little while.
Do you wanna walk with us?
Oh. No, no, I'll just stay here.
Honey, you'll freeze.
It's fine. I'll just...
I'll... I'll put some layers on.
I love this house,
but without heat, it gets cold. Fast.
It's... it's okay. I'll be fine.
Really.
Okay.
But if you change your mind,
you know where to find us.
Thank you.
Okay.
Hey, Doc.
Hey, Jack.
Good to have you back.
Yeah.
So, the steelheads bitin'?
Oh, I practically had to kick 'em
out of the boat.
How many'd you bring back?
Well, I reeled in quite a few beauties,
but you know me,
I'm a catch and release man.
We both know the only thing you caught
was a chill.
Some people just don't understand.
It's the thrill of the chase,
not the size of the trophy.
Oh.
I keep telling you to weight your flies,
but you never listen.
Dead drift is the only way
to catch 'em in the winter,
but no, you keep trying
to get 'em to chase up high.
Says the woman who couldn't tie a nymph
if her life depended on it.
Lucky for me, it doesn't.
Are you gonna discard anytime soon?
I did, five minutes ago.
How about more play and less yappin'?
What are you lookin' at?
Connie and her gaggle of gossip queens.
They couldn't stitch their way
out of a paper bag.
Someone sounds a little bitter.
That's ridiculous.
Muriel St. Claire. Who's she think
she's fooling with that name?
A lot of actors change their names.
So do criminals, Vernon. So do criminals.
What'd that woman ever do to you?
Move here.
Ah.
Gin.
Oh... Oh.
Oh.
Hi.
I saw the forecast in Virgin River.
It looks really bad.
Yeah. The, uh, power's out
and it's freezing.
How are you and Bill doing?
I'm in San Francisco for the weekend.
We're managing.
How are you gonna stay warm
if the power's out?
Um... Ev... everybody's at Jack's Bar.
I guess he's got a... a generator.
Well, why aren't you there?
Mel?
It's raining and I don't wanna drive.
You could walk there.
Mel, if you hang up,
I'm just gonna call you back.
I told Jack about Mark.
I wish I hadn't said anything.
No, it's good that you told him.
Mel?
I'm just not...
ready to get close to anyone.
No one is saying that you have to.
I like him.
He seems like someone you can trust.
Yeah.
Oh, I just wish I could take it all back.
No.
Saying it out loud,
it just... makes it feel more real.
I can't believe it's been almost a year
and I'm still this messed up.
Telling Jack means you're starting
to come to terms with losing Mark.
You have to take it one step at a time.
Can I call you back?
Sure.
Hey, I love you.
Ditto.
Hey.
Thought caffeine was a no-no.
This is decaf.
- No, it's not.
- Really? Tastes like decaf.
Hey, Jack.
Hey, Muriel.
What can I get you?
Do you have an older brother?
Uh, only sisters.
I guess it's gonna have to be a hot tea.
Milk and sugar, right?
You know what I like.
Oh. Hope.
How you feeling?
Poor thing,
I heard about the heart attack.
Did you now?
Yeah. I was gonna come see you, actually,
in the hospital,
but then I booked this big commercial
in Los Angeles.
- Yes, I heard.
- Did you?
You told everyone at canasta.
Oh.
Oh! Well, I'm just so glad
that you bounced back so quickly.
I mean, at your age, you just never know.
Right?
Ahem.
You are such a doll.
And those dimples, right? Oh.
I can't stand that woman.
Really?
You hide it so well.
I'm very sorry.
♪ I wish I had the why ♪
♪ Why the dark comes out some days ♪
♪ Why it takes your peace away ♪
♪ And it breaks you down inside ♪
♪ When your peace like a river ♪
♪ Runs dry like a desert land ♪
♪ I've seen the darkness fall
And rise up ♪
♪ From the sand ♪
♪ I wish I had the why ♪
♪ I know that I will love again ♪
- ♪ Falling in it never ends ♪
- My umbrella broke.
♪ Oh, oh, feelin' fine ♪
- Hey.
- You're soaked. What happened?
- Ugh...
I was gonna ride out the storm
at Jo Ellen's.
Why would you do that?
I didn't wanna get caught in the rain.
Well, you could have driven.
Yes, I could have done that.
Well, standing around in wet clothes,
you're gonna catch a cold.
Um, that's actually a medical misnomer.
All right,
you're gonna be mighty uncomfortable.
Come upstairs,
I'll give you some of my clothes,
and throw these in the dryer.
Or you could stand here and freeze.
No, yeah. Please.
Lead the way.
Well, uh...
A little big for you, but...
at least you'll be dry.
Oh, thank you.
You're welcome. Um...
There's towels down the hall
in the bathroom.
And, um...
yeah, just flip the switch off
when you're done.
Okay. Wait. Jack.
Sorry. I just, um...
Last night...
I just feel like I need to explain.
Do you want to?
No.
Then don't.
I mean, your business is your business.
Come down when you're dry,
and I'll save a spot for you at the bar.
Thank you.
What? Wait a minute.
Can y'all believe this weather?
Will you please let Connie know
that I am not speaking to her?
Whoa. Whoa, whoa. Now, I have no interest
in getting into the middle
of whatever this is.
Okay?
Hope, I came over to make amends.
Canasta tends to rile everyone up,
and for that, I'm real sorry.
You can tell Connie
I appreciate her apology,
but we'd like to get back to our game.
Hope, can we be civil, please?
Connie, I don't know what to say,
but you know how she can be bullheaded.
The girls and I wanna make a quilt
for Lilly and baby Chloe,
and no one can cross stitch
as good as you.
It would mean a lot if you'd come over
and join us.
Well, if I don't,
you'll have a giant mess on your hands.
Oh!
It'll mean a lot to Lilly.
Can you believe her?
She was practically groveling.
I wouldn't call that groveling.
You're coming with me.
I might need a wingman.
What did I do to deserve this?
Don't answer that.
I've never seen my clothes look so good.
You know what I miss about LA?
Traffic? Smog? A little gun violence?
No. The weather.
Oh, the weather.
You're not a fan of the rain?
No. Are you?
Yeah, actually. I find it peaceful.
Peaceful.
No. It's, uh... wet and noisy.
My idea of peaceful is a day at the spa.
I don't understand. People hang out here
until the storm's over, or...
They go home when it's late,
and if the power's still out,
they'll come back in the morning.
Hm.
Ahem.
- Oh. Jack, honey.
- Oh. Yeah.
Let me refill that for you. Sorry.
Oh, and a slice of apple pie,
please, and thank you?
Comin' up.
- Preach.
- Hey.
- What are you doin'?
- Nothin'.
You've been doin' nothin' all day.
We're full here.
Yeah, I'm just, uh...
just going over our invoices.
All right, well, invoices can wait.
I can't find the apple pie.
You know, there's a couple extra
in the... the back of the fridge.
I need help in the kitchen. Come on.
Yeah, okay. Comin'.
I'm surprised you own anything flannel.
Except for maybe a set of sheets.
Oh, yeah, no, this is Jack's.
Oh, you don't say.
Yeah. My clothes were soaked.
À la mode.
And on the house.
Such a big heart.
If you ask me, Charmaine's a damn fool
to let a guy like you get away.
Then again, I always thought
she was a little big for her britches.
So, uh...
what happened?
Charmaine decided she didn't wanna
see me anymore.
Oh. Well, I'm sorry.
Obviously for the best.
We... we want different things, right?
- Yeah.
- Order up.
I gotta get that.
Hey, Doc.
Oh, hey, Bert.
Still comin' down out there?
Cats, dogs... Might even be some cows.
What's Preacher cookin'?
Oh, we got a jerk chicken'll
knock your socks off.
Hi, honey bun.
- Glad to see you finally made it.
- Hi.
Yeah, well, you were right.
My room was freezing.
Aww. I'm sorry.
Bert, you, uh... you want a beer?
Ah, I'm done for the day, so why not?
All right.
Broke an axle on my truck
helping somebody out of a ditch,
so my buddy in Clear River
is gonna cover for me, so...
Well, don't you worry.
The whole town is here.
- Just sit back and relax.
- Mm.
- I'll get you that stew, huh?
- Yeah, thanks.
Hi.
I'm Mel Monroe.
Bert Gordon.
Bert. Yeah.
The... the tow truck driver, right?
Yes, ma'am.
You towed my car when I first got here.
It's a... a red BMW... in a ditch...
Oh, yeah, you're the big shot LA nurse.
Oh! I don't know about big shot,
but I am a nurse.
- Here you go.
- Yeah.
Um... Hey, is your hand okay?
Oh, yeah.
Well, it looks pretty bad.
Oh, it's fine.
It doesn't look fine.
Oh, a few days ago
I was riggin' up an abandoned vehicle.
Got my damn hand caught
when I was lowerin' the sling.
Ah, give it a few days,
it'll... it'll be as good as new.
- Have you had it looked at yet?
- Aah, it's happened before.
I bounce back. I always do, right?
- Okay. Do you want me to check it out?
- Oh, you're off the clock.
I'll be fine as long as Jack
keeps givin' me beers.
Well, I just wanna make sure
it's not broken.
Yeah, well, suit yourself.
All right.
- So...
- Aaah!
Okay. Yeah. Can you move this finger?
- No, not really, no.
- No.
So, what do we got?
Whoa.
Look at the size of that.
Yeah. I think he fractured
his fourth metacarpal
and possibly sprained his wrist.
Yeah, a boxer's fracture.
Do a couple rounds with a bear?
A Chevy.
He needs an X-ray.
Well, hold on a second here.
- Aah!
- Yeah, I think Mel's diagnosis is correct.
- Thank you.
- Well.
Listen, Bert. I think you should get
to the hospital and get an X-ray for that.
Oh, no can do.
Why not?
- Well, no health insurance.
- Now, hold on. Hold on.
There's no cuts or abrasions on the skin.
It's a clean break
with not much deformity.
I think a closed reduction
would do the trick.
Hm.
What's that mean?
It means he wants to manipulate the
bone fragments back into position himself.
So, Bert, I would have to get you
over to the clinic.
- I don't wanna make a big fuss about this.
- No, no fuss.
You know, I fired up the...
the genny this morning, just in case.
Listen, Bert.
If your bone doesn't heal properly,
you could lose full function of your hand.
Yeah. So, I'll go gather my things
and we'll head over there, all right?
You too.
Hey, Doc. Ahem, Doc.
That's your second whiskey, right?
Yeah.
It is Sunday.
Okay, I got your point, son.
Besides, we need you here
in case there's an emergency, yeah?
Why don't you let Mel take care of Bert?
Ahem.
You have done
a closed reduction before, right?
Several. Yeah.
Okay. So, why don't you take care of this?
And I'll, uh... I'll be stayin' here, hm?
You... You're not gonna come?
Well, you're certainly capable
of handling this, right?
Of course. I... Of course.
Yeah. Well, then, just make sure
that you splint the MCP at at least...
Sixty degrees from flexion. I know. But...
Good. Good.
All right?
Just report back to me when you're done.
- Mel will take good care of you.
- Oh.
Okay.
Um, I just don't have my car.
I'm happy to drive.
Why don't I grab us some coats?
Okay.
You're gonna be fine.
Hey, Bert, why don't you hop up
on the exam table?
So, you're just gonna
push my bone back together?
Well, I'm gonna give you something
for the pain, first.
You know, doing this now,
you can most likely avoid having surgery
in the future.
Ah, hell will freeze over before I let
a stranger cut me up with a knife.
Exactly,
which is why we're doing this. All right?
Okay.
Hold your hand out.
Now, this is gonna sting a little bit.
Yeah. I never got a chance to tell you
how sorry I was
I didn't get to you in time that night.
What?
You and Jack bein' kidnapped
and held up at that camp, it's...
If I'd only gotten there sooner, you know?
Oh, no. It... it all turned out okay.
Oh, no. I called the bar
when I should have called the sheriff.
I just thought somebody picked you up
and gave you a ride.
Bert, really, it's okay.
No, I... I should have gone out
and looked for you.
It's okay.
You had no way of knowing what happened.
I went out to the farm yesterday.
And Lilly is doing so well.
Yeah.
That doctor in Clear River
is really doing the trick.
And Chloe is getting so big.
Hope, dear, you know, a running stitch
would be much more efficient.
A rocking stitch is cleaner.
Well, I guess we could always give Chloe
her quilt for her sixteenth birthday.
- Ahem.
- I'm just gonna get some more iced tea.
Dry mouth.
Wasn't that one of the side effects
of the incontinence pills
that you were shilling
in your commercial?
Doc, can I get you anything while I'm up?
He's fine.
- Huh?
- What?
I'm concerned
about the poor girl's health.
Mm-hm.
Um...
So...
For the love of Pete,
don't just stand there.
Spit it out, son.
Uh, there's someone outside
who wants to see you.
- Well, tell whoever it is to come in.
- Well, they...
- They want you to come outside.
- Who is it?
I'm not supposed to say.
Are you kidding me?
Okay, she says it's really important.
Mother of pearl.
Do I have to do everything in this town?
I'll be right back.
- Where are you goin'?
- Outside.
My seat's not even cold.
Mm-hm!
Is that a new cologne you're wearing?
- No.
- Oh, you sure smell good.
What's the, uh...
what's the name of the scent?
Soap.
Oh! What's with all the secrecy?
Jack and I broke up.
Honey, that's no secret.
Everyone in town is talking about it.
Oh.
Well, I... I wanna give him his stuff back.
So, what's stopping you?
I... I don't wanna see him.
Ugh. He's not here.
Just put whatever it is in his office.
I... I don't wanna see anyone right now.
- There... there's a letter inside.
- Oh, no. No, no.
- I'm not getting in the middle.
- Since when?
You're always knee-deep
in everybody's business.
I offer advice.
Please.
It... it'll be easier for Jack this way.
I know we haven't always been close,
but...
I figured... you'd know
what I was going through.
Please.
I can't have his stuff lying around.
It's too hard.
Every instinct in my body
is telling me I'm making a mistake.
Thank you.
Be careful out there in this.
Oh, thanks.
♪ In the night, in the dark, in the cold ♪
♪ As she walks far away ♪
♪ Nobody's watchin' ♪
♪ Drownin' in words so sweet ♪
What the heck was that all about?
Believe me when I tell you,
you don't wanna know.
Hey, hey, hey. Whoa.
Whoa.
Road's washed out, Preacher.
Just gotta ride out the storm.
Yeah, well, you best do it in your car.
I ain't here to cause trouble, Preach.
I'll be leavin'
as soon as the road's open.
Just need a drink, and a...
warm place to sit.
What can I get you?
Bring him a bourbon and a check.
He ain't stayin' long.
- That'll do.
- Sure thing.
Keep that glass full, son. That's for you.
You bet.
You see the knot that guy's carrying?
It's dirty money.
All right.
There you go.
Okay.
I'm gonna need you to take two of these
every four hours with food.
They're not very strong,
but it'll help with the swelling.
I'm gonna call Grace Valley Hospital.
I want you to get an X-ray of the hand.
I told you, I don't have insurance.
Oh, I think Doc
can figure somethin' out for you.
Well, thanks. I look forward
to repayin' your kindness, ma'am.
I'm gonna give Shirley a call.
She's gonna be happy about this.
- Tell her we'll give you a ride home.
- Expect a cobbler comin' your way.
Hey, um...
I was thinkin' maybe since,
you know, we're already out,
I've got something I'd like to show you.
Um... Okay.
Well, I... I'm just not really that
comfortable driving around in the rain.
Okay, well, I got a four-wheel drive.
It's not far.
I just... I think you're gonna like it.
Now, look, you can't stonewall me forever.
Who wanted to talk to you?
God, you're just as nosy as I am.
Oh, yeah.
All right, fine. Fine. Don't tell me.
It was Charmaine.
- Is she okay?
- She seems to be doing okay, considering.
What's... what's in the box?
- Jack's things.
- Oh.
- She doesn't wanna see him face to face.
- Yeah, well, give Jack the box.
- Vernon.
- What?
What if it's something bad?
Whatever it is, it's Jack's business.
There's a letter.
Oh, sweet Jesus.
She told me to make sure he gets it.
Right. Right. Jack. Not you. Jack.
Oh!
Hey, Honest Abe, no one's making you stay.
I'm not leaving you alone with this box.
I should open it.
You should not.
Look, Hope,
you are crossing an ethical boundary.
What's the worst that can happen?
If you had not opened my mail,
then we would still be together.
So, my never knowing you cheated on me
would be an acceptable solution for you?
No, no. I would have told you,
but I would have picked
the right time and place,
and maybe things wouldn't have become
so explosive.
- It wouldn't have changed anything.
- It might have.
I wrote that letter
for Charmaine's mother, not you.
And Charmaine wrote this letter for Jack.
Just Jack.
But it's not sealed.
Oh, as if that would stop you.
- It might have, but we'll never know.
- Uh...
What... what? What does it say?
Hope. What?
- Let's go.
- What is it?
- Let's just go.
We're going.
I don't understand why
Bert feels so guilty.
He's not responsible for what happened.
Well, guilt isn't always
a rational emotion.
Can we not do this?
Let's just do one.
One more round of IVF.
Mark, when we lost our baby,
you promised me
we could have another child.
- Because I believed that we could.
- And we can.
I see this all the time with my patients,
okay?
If we just keep trying, there is a chance.
Please just reconsider.
Sweetheart, you and I,
our marriage is the thing that matters,
okay?
Our marriage.
All I've ever wanted is you.
All I've ever needed has been...
Honey, I love you.
You know, they say death is final,
but it isn't.
For the people left behind,
the pain feels like it never ends.
I thought that moving here,
away from everything that made me sad,
would somehow be freeing, but...
I just... brought all my sadness with me.
Mel, I'm so sorry.
Look, I wish there was... something
I could say to make you feel better.
It's okay.
We can just go back to the bar,
if you want.
No, no, no, no. I wanna go.
You sure?
Yeah.
All righty, then.
You are honestly not gonna tell me
what is in that letter?
- I don't wanna get you involved.
- Well, it's a little late for that.
What are you gonna do?
What I always do. Fix it.
Uh... No. Look.
This is the last time I'm gonna say this.
It is best to let Jack
handle his own business.
No, I can't.
I need to do what's best for Jack.
Another round?
I gotta go.
No, I'm good.
Rain's stopped. Roads are open.
Uh, you're all paid up.
That's for you.
Listen, uh...
you wanna make some real money...
hit me up.
I could always use another good man.
Kidnapping.
Jack?
Not Jack.
I'm sorry to come by so late.
I was just wondering if I could store
some of my pies in your refrigerator.
If the power doesn't come back on soon,
then they're gonna go bad.
Yeah. Huh.
They're just in my car.
- Yeah, okay.
- Oh, thank you so much.
Um, I only have about half a dozen,
so they shouldn't take up too much space
in your fridge.
I'll make room on a shelf.
Okay, thanks.
Hey, who's Michelle?
Close your eyes.
Seriously?
Yeah.
This better be worth it.
All right.
Almost there.
Wait there one second.
Okay.
All right.
- Oh, jeez.
- Just keep your eyes closed.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna carry you down.
One step.
Yep. Ah.
Okay.
Come this way.
- Don't drop me.
- No, I got you.
Okay.
All right. Now you wait there.
Just keep 'em closed.
- Okay.
- Stay there.
Okay.
Okay, open your eyes.
Oh, my gosh.
Did...
Did you do this?
I had some help.
Ricky, and occasionally Brady.
Do you like it?
Yes!
- Here.
- I can't believe it.
You wanna see inside?
Yes!
♪ I look into your eyes ♪
Oh, my...
♪ It's like watchin' the night sky ♪
♪ Or a beautiful sunrise ♪
♪ Well, there's so much there ♪
I can't believe this is the same cabin.
I mean...
this is incredible.
How did you do this?
I mean, look at this fireplace.
Is this is a new bed?
Jack, I...
- I... can't believe this.
- ♪ I won't give up on us ♪
♪ Even if the skies get rough ♪
- ♪ I'm giving you all my love ♪
- You did this for me.
- ♪ I'm still lookin' up ♪
- Well, I...
I know how hard it can be
to make a fresh start.
I really do.
I...
I also know that sometimes you need help.
I don't know...
a whole lot about your story,
but from what I can tell, you've...
you've been through a lot.
Yeah, I have.
Maybe this place can...
offer some comfort?
A place to call home.
It's beautiful.
Well, I hope you'll stick around.
♪ 'Cause even the stars, they burn ♪
♪ Some even fall to the earth ♪
♪ We've got a lot to learn ♪
- Are you sure this is what you want?
- ♪ God knows we're worth it ♪
♪ Oh, I won't give up on us ♪
♪ We're still lookin' up ♪