So, how long have you known?
I've suspected for a couple of weeks.
And you're sure?
Yeah.
I talked to my doctor.
I... I know this isn't
what either of us expected.
Uh, yeah.
This is probably the last chance
that I'm gonna have...
to be a mother.
- Okay.
- Like I said in my letter...
I wish things were different.
Do you... do you think that maybe one day
it... it could be different?
What are you asking me?
Am I in this alone?
I will support you and this baby.
You know that.
Jack, that's not what I'm asking.
I... I need an answer.
I'm sorry. I...
I just need some...
I need a little time to process this,
that's all.
Yeah. That's...
that's fair.
I gotta... I gotta...
go open the salon.
Um...
I still love you, Jack.
Jack.
I... I'm late getting to Doc,
so I'll just cut to the chase.
- Have you spoken to Charmaine yet?
- Hope,
I know it's hard for you
to stay out of everybody's business,
but reading that letter crosses a line,
even for you.
I was afraid Charmaine
had written something hurtful to you.
- And if she had?
- I could've tossed the letter
and spared you some heartache.
It wasn't your letter to toss.
Have you told Mel?
- I'm on my way there now.
- Good.
- Look, I think...
- That I'm handling this.
- Okay?
- But if you need me...
Yeah. What I need is for you
to stay out of my business.
Please.
Hey, Jo.
Bill wants Dexter.
Wait. The dog?
My dog.
I thought you were in counseling.
I think he's dating his assistant.
Kimberly?
Kim was, like, two assistants ago.
I'm talking about Brooke.
Oh. Honey, I'm so sorry.
Oh.
I am not giving up Dexter.
You don't have to.
I don't wanna
talk about it anymore.
What's goin' on there?
Um...
Well, I...
I, uh, went out to dinner
with Jack last night.
As in a date?
Yes...
- Well, that's a big step.
- I know.
I know. I haven't been, uh, on a date
with anyone other than Mark
in, like what, six years?
Did you have a good time?
Yeah, I... I did. I had a great time.
I'm so glad.
I really am.
Yeah.
I really like him.
He likes you, too.
I could see it when I was there.
Yeah, I mean, he's...
he's the total opposite of Mark, you know.
You know what?
This is not about Mark, this is about you.
And this is what he would want.
He would want you to...
to move on and be happy.
Joey, are you crying?
No.
Oh...
Stop crying before I start. Come on.
Jeez. Oh, that's Jack. I gotta...
Hey, come in. I gotta go.
Call me later, okay?
Okay, bye.
Hi.
- Hey.
- Okay. So, I have a question to ask you.
Uh...
Semi-sweet or dark chocolate?
Sorry?
- It's for the pancakes.
- Oh. Um...
- Oh, do you not like pancakes?
- No, I love pancakes. I... uh...
- What?
- I... I just got a call on the way here.
My delivery guy's truck broke down,
so I gotta go to Grace Valley
and pick up an order.
Ah.
Okay. That's too bad.
Yeah. Look, I really wanna...
I wanna see you. So, maybe tonight,
you know, after I'm done with the bar?
Yeah. Okay.
I could make dinner.
Okay. Yeah.
I'd like that.
Okay.
- All right.
- I'll see you later.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- I'll see you then.
- Okay, bye.
Yeah.
Well, where have you been?
Well, I went to get coffee at Paige's,
and I ran into Connie.
And she was a basket case.
Her niece Lizzie, the one who lives in LA?
Well, apparently she's turned into
a bit of a wild child.
Got herself arrested for shoplifting.
Connie says she might have to take her in.
Can you imagine?
Connie, taking care of a teenager
at her age.
- My.
- Then, I talked to Jack,
who's on his way over to Mel's
to tell her about the baby.
What baby?
- If I tell you, you can't tell anyone.
- Lo... Oh...
If it's supposed to be a secret,
let's just keep it that way.
Charmaine is pregnant with Jack's baby.
That's what that letter business
was all about?
- What?
- Uh-huh.
I did not see this comin'.
From the look on his face,
I'm betting neither did Jack.
- What is he gonna do?
- He was on his way over to tell Mel.
Oh, not an easy conversation.
Not an easy decision for Jack, either.
Stay out of this.
Well, you dragged me over here.
What do you want?
Oh! Uh...
to invite you to dinner tonight.
- Why not just tell me that over the phone?
- Because I'm old-fashioned.
I think matters like this
should be attended to in person.
Are you trying to sweet-talk your way
out of paying for the divorce
by buying me dinner?
Well, keep your free grub,
'cause it's not gonna work.
Oh, for Pete's sake, Hope,
you can just stop analyzing it.
It's just a meal.
Where?
Arthur's.
You're paying, right?
Okay.
Fair warning, I'm gonna order lobster.
- Good.
- And two desserts.
- Morning.
- Hey.
I like the new sign.
Well, uh... it's just a formality.
Oh, right. Okay.
Um... You're not supposed
to be drinking coffee
until your next stress test.
- It's decaf.
- Oh, really.
I don't trust doctors.
Yeah, and I don't trust you.
- Oh!
- I'm sorry.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
You made coffee?
Well, don't get used to it.
Uh, I gotta take this call.
- Oh!
- Wh...
The baby doesn't have to change anything.
You guys will figure it out.
Baby?
Hope, what? I'm sorry,
what baby are you talking about?
What's going on?
I thought you knew.
Hope, what are you talking about?
Charmaine's...
pregnant.
What?
Jack said he was gonna tell you.
And who told you?
Charmaine.
Hope.
Actually, I...
I read it... in a letter
Charmaine asked me to give to Jack.
Hey, Doc.
Hey, Sadie.
Excuse me. I have a patient.
Jack said he was gonna tell her.
I need to talk to him.
Did you learn nothing
from what just happened?
- This is Jack we're talking about.
- I have to fix this.
Okay, here we go. Potato skins.
Chili.
Paige. Hey.
Thanks for comin'.
Sorry, I don't have a lot of time.
Jo Ellen is watching Christopher
and minding the truck.
All right. Um...
Look.
Knowing your real name
isn't what's important right now.
Then what is?
That you understand
how much...
I care about you.
Now, I am here.
I'm... I'm not going anywhere.
Okay. All you need to know is that...
I didn't have a choice.
My ex-husband has a...
temper.
At first, it was just me,
but then one night,
he went after Christopher.
When the police arrived,
I was the one that was arrested.
He told the judge that I was unstable.
So, he was awarded sole custody
in the divorce.
I couldn't leave my son with him.
So, I did the only thing I could think of.
Run.
I am so sorry.
I'm scared that if he finds us,
he will kill us both.
- He's threatened to enough times.
- I...
I won't let that happen.
You're very sweet, Preacher,
but he's a police officer.
And he has an entire police force
backing him up.
And I've got ten years of tactical
training in the military backing me up.
I really just need for you
to do one thing for me.
Whatever you need.
Don't tell anybody.
Not even Jack.
I told him.
I... I had to talk to someone.
But, Paige...
he won't tell anyone.
I swear.
Everything's gonna be okay.
I need to go.
Hey, Paige.
I, uh, need to speak with Jack.
Yeah, he, uh... he hasn't come in.
- Can I help you with somethin'?
- I wish.
Oh, I don't even wanna know
- what you're up to.
- You don't.
Uh, I need to run over to Connie's.
But, uh, as soon as you see Jack,
would you tell him I need to talk to him?
Why don't you just call him on his cell?
I need to talk to him face-to-face.
Is everything okay?
God, I hope so.
Drink lots of fluids,
and get plenty of rest,
and call me if your cough gets worse.
- I will.
- Okay.
And next year, I'm gonna make sure
you come in early for your flu shot.
- Thank you, Mel.
- You're welcome.
You know, you really should update
these subscriptions.
This California Living is from 2002.
Well, magazines these days
are very expensive.
Yeah, not enough to make a difference.
A penny saved is a penny earned.
Oh, my God.
Just... forget I said anything.
Oh, boy, somebody's upset.
I'm fine.
When a woman says "I'm fine,"
there's one thing I know.
She's definitely not fine.
I am.
Hogwash.
In my experience,
bottling up your feelings
never does anyone any good.
Jack should have told me.
Yeah.
Is that really what's bothering you?
The message is more important
than who did or didn't give it to you.
Charmaine being pregnant
just changes everything.
Now, the heart of the matter.
I mean, I don't even know
what I'm doing. I...
I didn't come here for this.
You know?
For what, exactly?
To start anything.
Whenever you go somewhere new,
it's always the start of somethin'.
You know...
what this month taught me?
I have no idea.
Get your feelings out in the open.
You know...
maybe if I had done that with Hope...
Well, unlike you and Hope,
Jack and I don't have
a long history together.
But...
maybe you have a future.
Hey, there.
- Hey.
- What can I get you?
- Uh... Whatever's on tap.
- Comin' right up.
So, are you stayin' in town
or just passin' through?
I'm kind of playin' it by ear.
Okay.
Thank you.
That pie looks delicious.
You want a slice?
I do.
Is that apple?
With pears.
My mother used to make pie that way.
My wife, too.
Paige is a pretty good baker.
Paige, huh? She a... she a local?
Uh, yeah, just down the way.
- She's got a bakery...
- Hey, Ricky.
- Yeah.
- Table ten could use some more water.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
So, I don't think I caught your name.
Preacher.
Uh... Paul.
You got a last name there, Paul?
Um... You know...
I think I'm just gonna settle up,
and, uh...
keep the change.
- Ricky...
- Hm?
Be right back.
- Hey.
Can you get Brady to give me a hand
with this order?
Uh, he's not here.
It's after one.
Yeah, it is.
You okay?
Yeah.
Yeah. I just got a lot on my mind.
Oh, and Hope's lookin' for you.
Is somethin' up with her?
Just Hope being Hope.
- Brady.
- What's up?
- You're late, that's what's up.
- All right.
Come here.
You were supposed to be here
three hours ago.
- Yeah, I had some stuff I needed to do.
- Are we inconveniencing you with this job?
This is my business, you understand?
Yes, sir.
You're the boss, Jack. Whatever you say.
Hold on.
- What'd... what'd you say?
- All right.
- I said Jack's the boss.
- I don't like your tone.
- No one's talking to you.
- I'm so sick of...
- Touch me again, I'll...
- Stop! Stop!
Walk away.
- I'm done.
- Hey, listen to me.
You walk away from here right now,
you never come back here.
You understand me?
So long, Jack.
Hm.
Now you listen to me.
He is not your problem.
And you trying to save him
doesn't change the past.
What happened in Mosul,
it wasn't your fault.
What happened to Lonergan
wasn't your fault.
Lonergan!
Brady!
Just hang in there. Okay?
You're gonna be all right.
Please don't leave me.
Ain't gonna happen. Hear me?
Promise.
Hey, I don't leave men behind.
Okay?
Lonergan.
Jack.
Hey.
You do yourself a favor,
and you let Brady stay gone this time.
I can't. I...
Is there somethin' else goin' on, Jack?
Ah, come on, man.
Charmaine's pregnant.
Oh.
Mm. Yeah.
So, what are you gonna do?
I haven't figured that out yet.
- So, have you told Mel?
- No.
I just need a day.
I don't wanna screw things up with her.
Yeah, I get it.
So, what does Charmaine say?
- She says she's still in love with me.
- Yeah. And you don't feel the same way.
Well, if I did...
things would be a lot simpler.
Whatever you decide,
I'm there for you.
Thank you.
I just need to clear my head.
You go. I will, uh... I'll watch the bar.
Finally.
There you are.
All right, not now, Hope, please.
- I made a horrible mistake.
- Yeah, we've already been over this.
No, this is something else,
and you're not gonna like it.
I...
accidentally told Mel
about Charmaine being pregnant.
You what?
You said you were going to tell her,
so I thought she knew.
I... I told you to stay out of my business.
- I made...
- In my defense...
There is no defense, Hope.
- I said stay out of my business.
- I wanted to help you.
You're not helping me!
How does this help me?
God, clearly the only... the only way
that I'm gonna get you
to stop meddling in my life
is to keep you out of it.
- So...
- You don't mean that.
...keep out of it.
Jack. I'm sorry.
Jack.
I need to talk to you.
Uh...
I'm sorry.
I should have told you this morning.
Yes. You should have.
Oh, God. I knew this was a mistake.
- What? No, Mel, don't...
- No, all of this. All of this.
You, moving out here
to the middle of nowhere,
thinking that I could just have
just an ounce of happiness.
- Hey, look, I'm gonna figure this out.
- There's nothing to figure out.
You're... you're having a baby
with another woman.
That doesn't change how I feel about you.
It's not too late, okay?
We just started whatever this is.
- We can...
- No.
We can just be friends. It'll...
I can't do that.
Well, it's not up to you.
Mel.
No.
Okay.
- You're early.
- I am.
And flannel clashes with lobster.
I d... I don't wanna eat.
Oh, you're passin' up free lobster?
I've ruined everything.
Well, maybe not everything.
I'm sorry.
For what?
For refusing to accept your apology
for the past 20 years.
You tried over and over,
and... and I wouldn't have it,
and now I...
finally understand
how bad I must have made you feel.
Thank you...
but it's okay.
You know,
I'm a pretty tough hide.
It's not okay.
Nothing I've done is okay.
I've made a me... a mess.
Yeah, Mel and Jack, they're gonna...
they'll work through this.
I don't think they will,
and it's all my fault.
What if he never speaks to me again?
What if Mel leaves?
Oh, come on.
Look.
You messed up.
I feel awful.
Maybe this time you'll let it sink in.
You... you just can't butt into
other people's business.
- I was trying to help.
- I know.
The truth is
you didn't create this situation.
This was all between Mel, and Jack,
and Charmaine.
But now, what you need to do
is something
that doesn't come naturally to you.
Stay out of it.
Let them find their way through it.
I know how much Jack means to you.
Uh, he'll come around.
I think maybe this time I've gone too far,
and there might not be
any room to come back.
You just had a bad, bad day.
I push people away, Vernon.
It's what I do. What I've always done.
I pushed Connie away, and...
and the other ladies. And you.
Now I've done it to Jack and Mel.
I have somethin' for you.
What's this?
This is somethin' you've wanted
for a long time.
Divorce papers.
Newly drawn, executed, and fully paid.
All it needs is your signature.
We file it.
It's final.
Boom.
We are divorced.
Divorced or married...
you can push as hard as you want,
Hope McCrea.
I'm not goin' anywhere.
You haven't been this quiet
for this long ever.
I mean, wh... you having
another heart attack?
Come on, speak to me, Hope.
Hope.
Well, those don't look like tears of joy.
Hey, Preacher, my grandma called.
Do you need me to stay?
No, you know what?
You, uh... you get going.
I made some trout and vegetables
for you two for dinner.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Hey, leave a message...
Hey, Paige, it's me, uh, just, uh...
just checkin' in,
makin' sure everything is all right.
Listen, I was, um... I was thinkin'
about swingin' by when things slow down,
so just... just give me a call, okay?
Uh, thanks for dinner.
Right. Uh...
- Tell your grandma I say hello.
- All right.
- See you later.
- Yeah.
Sheriff, any word?
The plate's registered
to a Joshua Benson...
- Joshua Benson?
- You heard of him?
No, no, I never heard of him.
You sure that's who
the vehicle's registered to?
That's what's comin' up on the report.
Okay.
Okay, thanks.
Hey. Um...
Can I get a large... uh, decaf latte
with extra foam, please?
Mel.
Hi.
What are you doing in Clear River?
Um...
I was just on my way back
from seeing Lilly and Chloe.
Hm.
Um... Do... do you work around here, or...
I do. I... I just work over on Main Street.
Oh. Nice.
- Do you like it?
- Yeah.
Yeah, the... the girls are really nice,
and I make a decent living.
That's good. Oh, thank you.
Yeah, well, um... it was nice to see you.
Yeah.
Congratulations on your baby.
I... I just wanted you to know I, um...
I... I didn't plan this.
Oh, I... I didn't think you did.
Actually, I didn't even think
that I could get pregnant.
While this isn't necessarily
how I wanted things to go,
I'm... I'm really...
I'm grateful.
I'm gonna be a mom.
That's something I never thought I'd say.
I am sure that you and Jack
are going to be wonderful parents.
Hm.
Yeah, it... it's a bit more complicated
than that.
I've seen the way that he looks at you.
And, uh...
yeah, he... he hasn't ever
looked at me like that...
in two years.
It's not about me.
I don't want Jack to come back to me
because of his damn sense of honor.
It... it has to be a choice, his choice.
And to be honest,
that's never gonna happen
as long as you're here.
Well, I...
Hello again.
Jimmy tells me you're done
workin' that bar job.
Yeah, might be.
What about Jack?
I thought you two were tight.
I got a lot of friends.
What I don't have is money.
From the looks of it,
you don't got that problem.
I got a lot of ex-military guys
workin' for me.
- Yeah?
- I was in the army.
Now you're what?
Into weed?
The syndicate I work for has the support
of virtually every town around here,
including a lot
of the local law enforcement.
Okay.
Now, I can count on Clear River
and Garverville for materials,
security, distribution.
The only holdout in the whole county...
Virgin River.
I think you might be able
to help me with that.
♪ Have a seat upon this branch of mine ♪
♪ It's been a while and honey, I... ♪
We need an ark, not a BMW.
Why don't we just pull over
until the rain stops?
It's okay.
I got it.
I do... think
I took a wrong turn somewhere.
Why don't we just go home?
It took me two weeks
to get this reservation.
- Fine.
- I'm...
- I just don't care about Bestia right now.
- Sweetheart, can we not do this?
- For one night, with the...
- Listen, I know, okay?
You don't want a surrogate.
That's fine. But can we at least just
do one... one more round of IVF?
Mark, when we lost our baby,
you promised me
we could have another child.
Because I thought we could.
- Baby...
- We can.
I see this all the time
with my patients, okay?
If you just keep trying,
there is a chance.
Sweetheart, you and I...
Our marriage is the thing
that matters here, okay?
We are what matters.
And if we don't stop this,
we're gonna lose us.
I don't wanna stop trying.
You're not thinkin' straight.
♪ I wish you would, I wish you might ♪
- I think we need a break.
- That's what I keep saying.
- No, I...
- You know...
No, I mean from us.
Are you gonna leave me?
We don't want the same things anymore,
Mark.
All I've ever wanted is you.
All I've ever needed...
- Oh...
- Hey, honey, I love you.
I just don't think love is enough anymore.
You just don't mean that.
- I do.
- ♪ Oh, my stars ♪
- I'm sorry.
- Listen to me.
Mark. Mark!
♪ Oh, my, my ♪
♪ Oh, my stars ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh, my, my ♪
♪ Oh, my stars ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
I made you some tea and a sandwich.
I'll leave it out here.
Come in. It's open.
I am confused.
I thought the divorce was what you wanted.
I think I just got scared.
Of what?
Dying.
The heart attack
really did a number on me.
It made me feel weak.
You ain't that.
So, you wanted to exert some control
over your life. That's understandable.
I never told you this, but...
when Charmaine's mother...
Rachel, when she got sick,
she asked me to visit her in the hospital.
I refused to go.
We were friends for 30 years, and...
I never gave her a chance
to make amends.
Oh, God.
I regret that choice, and I always will.
You know...
I regret having broken our wedding vows...
every day that I'm alive.
I know you do.
Well...
whether you realize it or not...
ah, there is pretty much nothing
I wouldn't do to make you happy.
You, my dear...
are an original.
And God's honest truth...
I've never stopped loving you.
You've gotta know that.
- Oh, Vernon.
- Yeah.
There's something else.
What?
I love you, too.
Paige?
It's Preacher.
Hey, guys, it's Preacher.
Paige?
You shouldn't be here.
Look, it's been a long day,
and I'm tired.
I just wanna say I'm sorry.
Do you know how embarrassing it was
to have to hear that from Hope?
I can imagine. That's why
I didn't want you to find out that way.
I wanted to talk to you tonight and...
It made me feel like I couldn't trust you.
I know.
And you can.
Jack, this isn't...
this isn't just...
you not telling me
about Charmaine and the baby, okay?
A few years ago...
I had a stillborn baby.
And now I can't have children.
I'm...
sorry.
And her having a baby
is something that I can't ever have.
And...
it's just...
it's just too much for me to handle, okay?
It's just asking too much of me.
I am just as scared as you are, okay?
I have never felt this
for anybody in my life.
I didn't even know I could.
And then you walk in...
and from that first moment
that I saw you, I knew.
Stop, please, Jack.
I can't stop how I feel, okay?
I... I'm falling in love with you.
Don't say that.
I know... what I'm asking is a lot.
Okay, but I... I can't ch...
I can't change your past.
But I wanna be a part of your future.
I just need some time
to think about this, okay?
Take all the time you need.
I'm not goin' anywhere.
I'll call you tomorrow.
Okay.
Everything's gonna be all right.
♪ I got a fear ♪
♪ Oh, in my blood ♪
♪ She was carried up ♪
♪ Into the clouds high above ♪
♪ Ooh, if you bled ♪
♪ I bleed the same ♪
♪ Ooh, if you're scared ♪
♪ I'm on my way ♪
♪ Did you run away?
Did you run away? ♪
♪ I don't need to know ♪
♪ If you ran away, if you ran away ♪
- Joey, it's me.
- ♪ Come back home ♪
I'm coming home.
♪ Just come home ♪