- There you go.
- Thank the Lord.
Home sweet home.
For the love of Pete,
what have you got in here?
I told you I could carry my own damn bag.
So, thank you for accompanying me home.
Now, please feel free
to go about your business.
Hope.
The doctors released me. So can you.
Hell, I... I still think
it was just indigestion.
Okay, well,
your EKG and blood work would disagree.
That's just junk science.
Hope, three days ago
you had a heart attack.
Has that sunk in yet? Because it needs to.
I mean, it was mild, but you're gonna need
to make some lifestyle changes.
Help me out here.
Well, as much as I hate
to agree with Nurse Hollywood,
she has got a good point.
You need to take it easy
until we get the results
of the stress test.
After we get the all-clear,
I'd be happy...
Uh, I wasn't aware
that we had a heart attack.
You seem to be getting all of your energy
from stress and caffeine.
I'm sorry, but how do you think
I manage to run this town?
I don't get a lot of breaks.
I can tell you that much.
Right. Which means
you're not getting enough exercise.
She's certainly flappin' those lips
all day long.
And...
ugh, these stairs are... are really steep.
I would feel much better
if you stayed down here
for just a few days.
Anything else?
You're going to need to adopt
a heart-healthy diet.
- Cut out alcohol. Limit stress.
- Mel, dear.
Those are lovely ideas.
Just super.
For somebody else.
Because I'm not changing a damn thing.
Okay. Hope...
if you wanna continue living,
you're gonna have to learn to adapt.
You're the one who wanted me
to hire her back.
You just... just gonna leave that there?
Delivery!
Hey.
Oh, hey.
I just came by to check on Hope.
Yeah, sure.
Jack, what'd you bring me?
A little welcome-home treat. Aah.
Where's my bacon and eggs
with cheesy potatoes?
Oh, no, no.
Mel gave Preacher a list
of low-cholesterol foods.
- What the hell is this?
- That is a soy-based quiche.
Oh!
What?
I... I... I need firewood.
Would you like me to get it?
God, no.
Okay, well, I got a chicken
for tonight's dinner
and some stir-fry vegetables.
And I'm gonna take this.
Good.
I'm gonna go through your fridge
and throw out anything
that's not on your new diet.
Don't touch my Velveeta.
Cheese is good for you.
So, what's with you two?
Nothin'.
Well, when was the last time you saw Mel?
Uh...
I don't know.
We didn't bump into each other
at the hospital,
so I guess it was that night
we got back from Lilly's.
We were at the bar,
and we ran into Charmaine.
Don't tell me.
Mel hadn't heard about your little friend
before meeting her?
No, I suppose she hadn't.
Good gravy, men can be such idiots.
Well, how was I an idiot?
Not enough time to go into that.
Uh... Mel?
Good news. I've seen the light.
I'm ready to live
under your fascist regime.
What happened in the last two minutes?
You need to learn
to take yes for an answer,
but, um...
I do have a few demands of my own.
Okay.
The mattress in the downstairs bedroom
is older than dirt.
You can feel the springs
jabbing you in the back.
I need the mattress
from my bedroom upstairs.
Okay, I can do that.
Well, no, that, uh... weighs a ton.
- Jack and I can bring it down.
- Hm.
Vernon, let the younger generation
take this one.
I certainly can handle
bringing a mattress down.
So, that's settled.
Jack and Mel will handle the mattress.
You can help me with the kitchen.
In the kitchen.
Don't you need to get back to work?
No, not right now.
Okay. Well, just because you're free
doesn't mean you have to stay.
Oh, I'm happy to help.
I was, uh...
I was at Lilly's the other day.
I must have just missed you.
Oh, yeah. She's doing really well.
Yeah, well, it helps that we have
the whole town pitching in.
Hey, look, about, uh... that night,
you know, after Lilly's,
when we got back to town.
Yeah, your, uh...
your girlfriend was really nice.
I'm glad I got to meet her.
What?
I don't think of Charmaine
as my girlfriend.
I mean, we're more casual than that.
Okay, well, she introduced herself
as your girlfriend.
Yeah. That's just the way she talks.
Great.
But you're dating.
Hm, I wouldn't really call it dating.
What would you call it?
- Here. Let me...
- I got it.
I can help.
You know, we just see each other
from time to time.
- That's gonna get stuck.
- Okay. Listen, I've done this before.
Besides, if it came in through this door,
it's gotta come out through the door.
Well, hate to say I told you so.
You know, I've got it.
You don't have to...
Sure, go ahead.
You know, I think you're only seeing it
from your perspective.
- No, that's definitely stuck.
- No, I mean, with Charmaine.
Listen, Charmaine and I,
we have an understanding.
You know, neither one of us
wanna be tied down.
Uh-huh.
- What?
- Nothing.
Doesn't sound like nothing.
Well, Charmaine didn't seem that casual,
that's all.
- Well, she is. Trust me.
- What makes you say that?
She told me.
- When?
- When we first met.
And when was that?
A couple of years ago, I guess.
Wow. Okay.
Damn it.
Well, I'll just be over here
on my side of the bed if you need me.
You can just go downstairs.
- I got it.
- Mm. Clearly.
Now, we need to go over
your new medications.
No, thanks.
You have got to take this seriously.
I am.
Twice a day.
Once a day. Every other day.
Look, I know what you have been through,
it's very scary.
Confound her!
Mel threw out all the good stuff.
She is trying to help.
Just like we all are.
You have had quite a scare.
It's expected you're gonna be feelin'
a little out of sorts.
After she leaves,
I'll go through the garbage.
Damn it, Hope! That's enough.
This is a wake-up call.
You're gonna have to make some changes,
now, before it's too late.
Vernon, I have always lived my life
on my own terms.
Nothing you say is going to change that.
Look, nobody said it was gonna be easy.
You just gotta take better care
of yourself.
Where's all this newfound concern
coming from?
It is not new. It's concern.
Yes, I am concerned.
As I would be for any patient.
I'm not your patient.
No, but I am a doctor, uh,
with a lifetime of experience.
And you're a brilliant one
when you don't let your ego
and stubbornness get in the way.
Well, that's high praise indeed.
However...
as a husband, Vernon,
you could have done better.
What does that mean?
Divorce papers?
I had them drawn up when you moved out.
Are you... are you asking for a divorce?
It's time. Actually, it's long overdue.
Why? Why are you doing this now?
While I was in the hospital,
I had a lot of time
to think about my life and...
how I wanna live what's left of it.
Well, these papers are 20 years old.
The time has come
to put our affairs in order.
Are you serious about this?
Serious as a heart attack.
One transgression 20 years ago.
Hope...
you realize...
if I sign those papers...
it... it's over.
We haven't been together in decades.
We just don't live together, but I...
I've always been there for you, always.
Don't put this on me.
You're the one who broke us.
It's just time to finish what you started.
Still there?
Yep.
So, you wanna try this again?
Yeah...
No other choice.
I meant together.
Okay, Mel, seriously?
Is there anyone we know
who is not on this list?
The more the merrier.
Mel...
I think this is all too much.
Come on, you know
how much I love planning parties.
Yeah.
Can I be honest?
Always.
I really don't need another shower.
- What? Since when?
- Since this is my third baby.
- I don't need anything.
- Uh...
- But it's a reason to celebrate.
- Mm...
So, we should celebrate.
Yeah.
Mark doesn't think it's a good idea
for you to be hosting a shower.
Yeah, well, we can count Mark as a "no"
'cause he's gonna be on call anyway.
You both just lost a baby.
- Don't look at me like that.
- How am I looking at you?
- Like you pity me.
- No, I don't pity you.
I don't know why
you'd wanna put yourself through this.
Because this is normal.
You having a baby is normal.
Okay? Me planning your shower is normal.
I just want normal again. Do you get that?
I just want something to be happy about.
I know, but forcing yourself to be happy
is not gonna work.
- Ugh...
- Okay?
- Sweetie, just let me help you.
- I don't need your help.
Oh...
How we doin'?
Do you want me to go?
- No.
- All right.
Then let's get this bad boy downstairs,
shall we?
C'mon.
Shall we...
Wait!
You show-off.
Ah, just grab that end, will ya?
- I got it.
- Okay.
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
- What?
- I'm just adjusting my grip.
- All right.
- Yeah, yeah.
Is it too heavy?
Ah, look, I'm gonna be carrying
all the weight down my end.
Oh. Okay.
Well, if you need a break...
- You know...
- I'd be happy to trade places.
Okay, this was a bad idea.
One sec. Okay.
Here we go...
I know. And I know how...
Nice to see you two working together.
All right,
let's just lean this up against here.
We'll swap out the other mattress.
Hey, where'd, uh... where'd Doc go?
- Oh, he had to leave.
- She means he escaped.
- Hah!
- I think I felt pretty much
as you're feeling right now.
- But I think it's a pretty low...
- Hey, Hope,
if this guest bedroom mattress
is too uncomfortable,
- Jack and I can get rid of it for you.
- Don't you dare.
I keep the guest bed lumpy
so people don't stay long.
Well, makes perfect sense.
- Hey, you push. I'll pull.
- Okay.
Okay, ready?
Yep.
But one day you'll realize
you've got to give and take.
- Jeez.
- Oh!
Uh-oh. Here.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, no, I just got a spasm.
- Oh, God.
- Does that happen often?
No, just every once in a while. Oh.
I just gotta sit for a bit.
- Okay.
- You know, I think I have something.
No. Mel, I'm f...
- No, no, I'll be right back.
- I don't need...
Go!
Stay down, sir.
You've lost a lot of blood.
- Move!
- We need to get out of here now.
Gotta go, Jack.
Go!
Wait!
Here you go.
I'm just gonna grab a towel.
It's topical analgesic cream.
It'll help with inflammation.
Oh, you... you carry that in your purse?
- Why, is that weird?
- A little.
- I'm a nurse.
- Still.
You know, I can... I can help.
No, I... I got it, I think.
You know what?
- Okay, you win.
- Okay.
Didn't know it was a competition.
What can I say?
I got a competitive streak.
Oh.
Okay, so where... where is it?
Lower left.
What happened here?
Iraq.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Oh, and two of those
chocolate cream puffs.
My diet doesn't start till tomorrow.
Connie, you are perfect
just the way you are.
Oh, I know you're lying, but I don't care.
I can't believe some nice woman
hasn't snatched you up.
Will that be all?
Let's add six snickerdoodles
and six chocolate chip
for the gals in my sewing circle.
And I assume y'all heard about Lilly.
At her age, having a baby
and then abandoning it.
Oh! You think you know someone,
and then they go on
and do somethin' like that.
Well, I think Lilly is very brave.
She tried to do right by her child.
Well, I don't see how leaving your baby
on a doorstep is doin' right.
Well, I don't think we're in any position
to judge Lilly or her actions.
Well, I heard that Hope was
so stressed out by this whole Lilly thing
that that's what gave her
her heart attack.
- Who told you that?
- Oh, I'm not gonna name names,
but my niece was over
gettin' her hair done in Clear River,
and she heard from one of the ladies,
who's a client of Charmaine,
who obviously heard from Jack,
that Hope was a ball of nerves
over that baby.
That'll be $19.80, Connie.
Thank you.
This is for that sweet boy of yours.
Bless his heart, not havin' a daddy.
You all take care.
Yeah, she means well.
Does she?
I'm not dead yet. Thanks.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I made you
a chicken and biscuit casserole.
- Drop cream biscuits?
- Is there any other kind?
I'll just, uh, tuck this away somewhere.
Preacher said Jack might be here?
Um... He's upstairs.
Oh, yeah?
He insisted on moving some furniture
for me.
My mom always said
you know you got a good man
when he pitches in without...
without being asked.
You know, maybe...
I'm just gonna go upstairs
and tell Jack I'm here.
He's not expecting me,
so I might as well just...
I'm just gonna...
Hi.
- Oh, hey.
- Hey.
What are you doing here?
Well, I just...
Hi, Charmaine.
Did I forget to mention that Mel
is here too?
Uh... I'm gonna go put these down.
- I tried it, and I really liked it.
- Yeah.
Great, huh?
Hey. Where is my apprentice?
Oh, Christopher has two math chapters
to finish before dinner.
Oh.
You ever thought
of enrolling him in school?
Now I hear Virgin River Elementary
is pretty good,
considering we live in the sticks.
Uh... he's gifted.
Yeah, you know what? That he is.
No, what I mean is...
is, uh, I'm afraid he'd be bored
by a standard curriculum.
- Mm.
- Yeah.
- Back off.
- Hey!
Is everything okay?
Yeah. Just some guys blowin' off steam.
Okay. What do I owe you?
You know what? That...
is on the house.
Preacher, you can't keep doing this.
But thanks.
- See ya.
- Yeah.
Oh. Hey.
Paige.
I...
would like to settle... our last order.
Thank you.
I really do appreciate this.
I'll see you later.
- Oh. Oh, God!
- Sorry! Sorry!
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay. Don't worry about it.
Don't wo... Oh, my God.
Michelle?
I haven't seen you
since college graduation.
I think you've mistaken me
for someone else.
My name is Paige.
Oh, uh... you look exactly like
someone I went to BU with.
Oh, gosh, definitely not me, then.
I didn't go to college.
Oh, I'm, uh... Sorry.
I'm just... I can't believe how much
you look like Michelle.
- It's okay.
- Yeah.
- Take care.
- Okay.
Oh, wait. Maybe you can help me. I'm lost.
Well, my husband's lost.
He refuses to ask for directions.
Can you tell me how to get back
to Route 36?
Hey, you know, I got this. You, uh...
You go out. You make a left.
Second stop sign, you take a right.
- You can't miss it.
- Oh! Thank you so much.
Phew!
Uncanny.
That has never happened to me before.
That is so weird.
See ya.
I could have sworn you told me
you had a psychology degree.
Me?
No. You must be thinking of someone else.
I started working
right out of high school.
- Okay, that's it.
- Try it.
Hey!
- Hey, cool it!
- Knock it off!
Cool it. Knock it off!
Get up. Get off.
Now, do we got a problem here?
No problem, Preacher.
No problem at all.
It is so sweet of you to invite me
to eat dinner with you all.
- It was delicious.
- It was bland.
What's for dessert? Gruel?
All right, don't listen to her.
It was great.
Thanks.
I'm sorry about the casserole.
I didn't know about
her dietary restrictions.
If you'd kept your mouth shut,
I could have had it for breakfast.
Jack's always saying
how I can't keep a secret.
I guess I'm just an open book.
And here I am doing all the talking.
What about you, Mel? Are you enjoying
your visit to Virgin River?
She's not visiting.
She's working with Doc.
Mel is a nurse practitioner and midwife.
Oh.
So... so, you just... just moved here.
Yeah, from Los Angeles.
And is your husband here?
Um...
No, he couldn't, uh, make the trip.
Oh. Wh... when's he coming?
I was thinking maybe the four of us
could go grab some dinner one night.
He's, uh... he's not gonna be joining me.
- But why not?
- Um...
What?
It's fine.
Charmaine, not everyone wants to talk
about their personal life with strangers.
Um...
I'm sorry, I...
I didn't mean anything by it, Mel. I'm...
I'm a hairstylist.
I'm just used to asking
a lot of questions.
I'm sorry. It's my sister.
I gotta take this.
Excuse me.
- May I use your bathroom?
- Yeah. Down the hall.
Thank you.
Having fun?
Hey. What's goin' on over there?
Keep it down, please!
I am on the phone.
I got it, honey.
I can crate the dogs.
Why can't I crate the kids?
We both know you're joking.
I left them with Bill so I could go
to the grocery store in peace.
And while he had his head in the computer,
they got all jacked up on sugar.
Where are you? Reception sounds horrible.
Um, I'm at, uh, Hope's house,
having dinner with Jack
and his girlfriend.
The guy from the bar?
You didn't mention anything
about him having a girlfriend.
Oh, I didn't know.
Hm.
Secret girlfriend, huh?
I mean, I'm having dinner
with her. She's not so secret.
From everything you told me,
you've been spending
a lot of time together.
Yeah, I guess... I guess we have.
And he never mentioned anything
about his girlfriend?
- Don't you think that's weird?
- No. I mean, he said it was casual.
And you know, I mean,
he's just being nice to me
because I'm new in town.
She was asking about Mark.
Why would she do that?
I'm still wearing my wedding ring.
You're still wearing it?
Maybe it would help to talk about it.
I don't know.
There are no rules on the best way
to handle these things.
No. Jo, I...
I... I gotta get back to dinner. Um...
I'll talk to you later, okay?
- Fine. Bye.
- Bye.
Hey. You guys are leaving?
Yeah. I need to drive Charmaine back
to Clear River.
I had a friend drop me off,
and Hope doesn't want us to do the dishes.
Are you sure that we can't stay and help?
I'm perfectly capable.
Well, you let me know
if you need anything.
Well, hope to see you around.
Yeah.
Night, Jack.
Night.
Are you sure
I can't help with the dishes?
Knock yourself out.
I just wanted Perky Penny out of my hair.
- Hey.
- Hi.
So, you're not a big fan of Charmaine,
I take it.
Huh! Is it that obvious?
I mean, I don't... I don't see why.
She seems perfectly sweet.
Sweet isn't good enough for Jack.
Hope, Jack's a big boy.
I'm sure he knows what he's doing.
You think it's sweet to ask someone
you hardly know personal questions?
I didn't really mind.
You always answer your cell phone
in the middle of dinner?
There are things that have happened
in the last few years that...
I just don't wanna talk about.
I figured.
You did?
Doesn't take a rocket scientist
to figure out a good-looking,
accomplished nurse from LA
moving to the middle of nowhere
might be running from something.
Well, I'm not a fugitive,
if that's what you're asking.
As far as I'm concerned,
your business is your business.
Thanks, I appreciate that.
But can I give you a piece of advice?
What is it?
I think if you focus on
protecting your heart...
you can avoid a lot of pain.
But you can also end up
living half a life.
Mmm.
You know what we two gals need?
Fred Astaire.
Follow me, girlie.
Come on.
Come on, movie's starting.
What is that face for?
I'm excited.
- Are you?
- Yeah.
I can't wait to watch Die Hard
for the millionth time.
Die Hard is a classic.
Oh, okay.
You know, your definition of classic
is severely flawed.
Why don't you pick
something else from my queue?
No, no. It's not my turn.
- I'm gonna make an exception this time.
- Really?
Okay, you choose. We got...
The Big Wedding.
Wedding Crashers. Royal Wedding.
Muriel's Wedding. The Wedding Singer.
Father of the Bride.
Bridesmaids.
Oh, and my personal favorite...
The Proposal.
I think you should probably look in there.
Are you proposing to me?
No, I just really want to watch
a Sandra Bullock movie.
♪ It's been a while, honey ♪
♪ I think I feel fine ♪
I knew from the first day that I met you
that you are an extraordinary woman.
♪ Atop your spine ♪
♪ I've got a ladder, honey ♪
I actually called my mother,
and I told her,
"Mom, I met the woman
that I wanna grow old with."
Melinda Janson, if you say yes to me,
I promise you, I promise you...
I'm gonna spend the rest of my life
trying to make you happy.
♪ Oh, my, my ♪
♪ Oh, my stars ♪
Yes! Sorry.
Yes.
I love you.
Come here.
Oh!
♪ Oh, my, my ♪
♪ Oh, my stars ♪
Come on, Mel.
You'll miss the opening number.
- Coming.
- ♪ Oh, my, my ♪
♪ Oh, my stars ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
What are you doing?
I didn't think you should be alone
for the first few nights.
So, you slept out here all night?
Well, I didn't feel like coming inside.
Did you sign the papers?
I can't.
You're not going to talk me out of this.
The papers are 20 years old.
They need to be redrafted
with a current date.
- Fine. I'll speak with my lawyer.
- Well, that might be tough.
Your lawyer's deceased.
- Oh.
- Hm.
Well, I could find someone else
to draw up new papers,
if that's what you want.
Oh.
Forskolin?
Yeah.
This will strengthen your heart muscle.
You always said herbs
were a bunch of malarkey.
Yeah, well, I talked to your doctor
at Grace Valley,
and she agrees that this supplement
taken with your other medications
is a good idea.
Where'd you get this?
In Eureka.
You hate the city.
I do, but that was the only store
that had Forskolin in stock.
I appreciate you going
to all this trouble,
but my mind's made up.
Okay.
Well,
the food budget is down a bit.
A lot of the hunters have been generous
with their donations this month.
Oh, and here you were giving me grief
about comping their meals, huh?
Bar sales holding steady.
No more discrepancies.
Good.
Hey, will you, uh... send Brady in?
Brady.
What's up?
Oh.
I thought... payday was Friday.
Oh, it is.
You've been working hard, and...
I appreciate it.
And, hey, if you ever need anything...
money...
whatever...
just ask.
Okay?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Oh, hey.
- Hey.
- How was your run?
- It was great.
- Hah!
Explain to me how running can be great.
Well, I used to run on a treadmill
that projected pictures of the forest,
and now I run through an actual forest.
Oh, no, no, no, no. The forest I get,
but you're never gonna sell me
on the running.
So, last night's dinner was interesting.
Was it?
Did Charmaine enjoy herself?
Look, I'm sorry about all the questions.
No, you don't have to apologize.
I can handle it.
Yeah, I know. It's what I like about you.
I was wondering how long you think
it would take me to get to Myrtle Farms.
Ooh, that's a way.
That's like 40 miles out of town.
Hmm.
Well, Preacher said they have
the best organic produce around,
so I was thinking I could pick up
some things for Hope.
Well, is Doc gonna go with you?
No, why?
Well...
I don't know. I mean...
the turnoff is pretty tricky to find.
And with all the rain we've had,
I mean, the roads could be flooded.
Your best bet would be
to... find a local to take you.
And who might that be?
Well, preferably someone
who's self-employed,
who can take time out of their day.
I don't know anyone like that.
Come on.
Why don't I tell the boys to cover for me?
Okay. I have a short day at the clinic.
You wanna pick me up in a few hours?
Oh. If you insist.
Yeah, Washington Gorge Road,
about ten miles up.
All right, well, tell Bert I said thanks.
Well, I have no bars.
Apparently, I'm not signed up
for Sprint's Wilderness Plan.
Oh, we're good.
They said Bert's out on another job,
but he'll get to us before nightfall.
Nightfall.
- Yeah.
- Is that a time?
Hah! In Virgin River? Yeah.
How do they stay in business?
They're the only gas station
with a tow truck within 100 miles.
Ah. Solid business plan.
I cannot believe you don't have
a spare tire.
I lent it to a neighbor.
You know, right now I wish you were
just a little bit less accommodating.
Okay. I'll work on that for you.
Come on.
Ah, could be a while.
Can I ask you a question?
Shoot.
Why are you so insistent
on keeping things casual with Charmaine?
I don't know.
Yes, you do.
What, you want the real reason?
Of course I want the real reason.
My dad didn't treat my mother
with the kind of respect
that I thought she deserved.
And you're worried
that you're gonna do the same thing?
It's the whole apple doesn't fall far
from the tree thing, I guess.
I've spent my entire life
trying to be different from my dad.
And as I got older,
I'd hear myself say something,
or I'd do something, and I'd realize...
he's right here.
I consider myself
to be a pretty good judge of character.
Mm?
Which is why I think you're worried
about something that will never happen.
Oh, no, I know it's not gonna happen...
'cause I'm not ever gonna be
in a relationship with her.
You are in a relationship with her.
Jack, Charmaine is not just some woman
you occasionally hook up with at a bar.
I have been perfectly clear
with my intentions from the start.
I know, but it doesn't matter.
Sometimes you can't separate your heart
from your head.
I'm beginning to understand that.
This isn't a good idea.
♪ Hoping, hiding ♪
I don't want to be in the middle
of anything.
- You're not.
- Well, last night I felt like I was.
I don't want anyone's feelings
to get hurt.
Well, I'll...
give Bert another call,
see where that tow truck's at.
♪ And I wonder who ♪
♪ Who ♪
♪ Well, I wonder who ♪
This stuff smells.
I know, buddy, but it's only for a bit.
I don't want to do this anymore.
I'm sorry, but we have to.
For how long?
Until I can be sure we're both safe.
Damn it.
Phone just died. Is yours workin'?
No.
Great. This day just keeps getting better
and better.
Look, I'm sorry that I upset you
by bringing up Charmaine.
It's just that I feel like she deserves
to know where she stands.
She knows where she stands,
because from the very beginning,
I have been very clear with her.
I told her
that I didn't want a relationship,
that I wasn't lookin'
for anything permanent.
And she understood.
She said she didn't want that either.
I'm not the bad guy here.
I didn't say you were.
Kind of sounds like you are.
You wouldn't happen to have a spare,
would you?
What y'all doing on this road?
I don't really think
that's any of your business, is it?
Hey, uh, we're, uh...
we're just on our way down the road
to go to a farm near here
to pick up some stuff
for a patient of mine.
You a doctor?
I'm a nurse practitioner.
Oh, that's good. You need to come with me.
- Excuse me?
- You need to back off.
And if I don't?