Hey.
Wouldn't a chainsaw be easier?
Yeah, but not as much fun.
How are you?
I'm all right.
I was just coming
to see how you were doing.
Yeah. I'm good.
Why you asking?
Just curious.
Since we're being curious,
where have you been the last few days?
Doc gave me a few days off,
so I could recover
from the whole pot thing.
How you doin' with that?
I'd kind of rather just forget
it ever happened.
Yeah, well,
some things are better left alone.
But I think if...
they're causing physical distress,
then it's unhealthy not to talk about it.
Somethin' you tryin' to tell me?
I don't know about you,
but I've been having a hard time sleeping.
Look...
you don't have to worry.
Doc and I paid Calvin a visit.
He knows to keep his distance from you,
or he's gonna have to deal with me.
Thank you.
Yeah.
But how have you been sleeping?
Same as usual.
Um...
The night we got back,
and you stayed over
so I could fall asleep...
Yeah.
...I think you were having a night terror.
Night terror?
Yeah. You were thrashing around,
and yelling, and...
Anyhow, I think I'd remember that.
Unlike a nightmare,
people sleep through night terrors.
Mel...
They're really not that uncommon
for vets who've been in combat.
Yeah, not this vet.
But thank you for your concern.
It's nothing to be ashamed of, Jack.
I... Honestly... It...
Ah, there you are. Hello, Mel.
Jack, I need your help.
Preacher's doing a roasted pig
for the Mingle,
but we've always done honey-baked hams.
Do you know how long it takes
to roast a pig?
If it's not ready in time,
we'll have a mutiny on our hands.
- What do you want me to do about it?
- Talk to him. He'll listen to you.
I know better than
to get between Preacher and his grill.
Oh, you have one heart attack,
everything goes to hell
in a handbasket.
And why haven't you RSVP'd?
I know you think we're backwoods,
but folks around here consider it rude
to ignore an invitation.
I... I'm sorry,
I don't know what you're talking about.
Tonight is Virgin River's
annual Moonlight Mingle.
Still lost.
The Moonlight Mingle
is the premier social event
on the Virgin River calendar.
Every year, the entire town gets together
at one of our resident farms
for dinner and dancing.
When you least expect it,
the DJ shouts "Mingle,"
and all dancers
have to switch partners.
- So, it's kind of like a square dance.
- No! It's not like square dancing.
This is a semi-formal event.
Yeah. It's actually kind of elegant.
Okay. Well, thank you very much,
but I'm gonna have to pass.
You can't pass.
That would be considered
highly unsociable.
- By who?
- Me.
And the entire town.
I'm not much of a dancer.
That's a lie.
Hey, sis.
Joey.
I'll get you guys a coffee.
- Oh, no thanks. I'm okay.
- Yeah, that'd be great.
Wow, this place is really committed
to the dead animal motif, huh?
- Well, every one tells a story.
- With a very upsetting ending.
Hey, I just work here.
No, Jack owns the bar.
Oh, that Jack.
Now I get it.
Get what?
Nothing.
- Thank you.
- Any time.
Hey, Ricky.
Come over here
and meet Mel's sister, Joey.
Hi, ma'am.
He called me ma'am.
How cute is that?
You're all my witness. Preacher swears
the pig will be ready by six.
And it will.
So, Joey...
what brings you to town?
I wanted to see the place
that has so captivated my little sister.
Well, if you need anything
while you're here, ask Jack.
Mel, I'll see you at the Mingle.
Feel free to bring your sister.
What's a "Mingle"?
Don't ask.
Come on. I'll show you around town
before I have to go to work.
- Okay.
If you'd given me a little notice,
I could have rearranged my schedule.
If I'd given you a little notice, then my
visit would not have been a surprise.
Hey, hey, hey, leave that.
We'll get that over
to the Fitches' for you.
- Thanks.
- I'll take care of it.
- Thank you.
- Yeah. Any time.
- See you later.
- Yeah.
Okay. Truth. What are you doing here?
Are you kidding?
You were just held up at gunpoint
by drug dealers.
They weren't dealers, they were growers.
And how is that better?
Like I told you, I am fine.
Well, I had to see for myself.
You look lovely.
What about Bill and the kids?
It's your birthday tomorrow?
Well, this was his present to me.
Three days, no kids,
and no responsibilities.
What is the matter?
Aren't you happy to see me?
I am happy to see you.
I just find it really odd that you chose
to have your birthday in Virgin River.
I chose to spend my birthday with you.
Okay?
Hi.
Hey.
Well... the attorney
can meet with us this afternoon.
The Mingle is tonight.
Uh... there are a dozen loose ends.
No way I can take time out
to meet with an attorney today.
He is going on vacation.
He can meet us today or a month from now.
Who takes a month-long vacation?
Do you want the appointment or not?
Fine.
But we need to keep it short.
Yeah, well, believe me,
I want this over as quickly as possible.
Hey, did you hear?
Mel's sister came to town.
No, and why would I care?
I hope she's not gonna
try to talk Mel into leaving.
I would tell you
to stay out of Mel's business,
but that'd be like... like telling a bull
to ignore the color red.
So, in this scenario, I'm the bull?
If the horns fit.
Oh, um... bring your checkbook
to that meeting with the attorney.
For what?
Well, because executing divorce papers
isn't cheap.
It'll be a few thousand dollars.
Are you suggesting we go halfsies
on our divorce?
I don't see why we wouldn't.
Divorce wasn't my idea.
- I don't have that kind of money.
- Oh, woman, you lie like a rug.
Fine. I'll pay my share,
but you should be ashamed of yourself.
It was your indiscretion
that caused all this,
so it should be you who pays the price.
This is nice.
A roll-away.
How quaint.
- Well, they were fully booked...
- Oh.
...which can happen
when you show up unannounced.
I know.
I think we should share your bed.
Uh... okay, we haven't done that
since we were kids.
I know. It'll be fun.
What are you doing?
What do you think
the thread count is here?
'Cause I'm guessing it's 250, tops.
Oh, come on. Don't be a snob.
The Fitches have been very gracious to me.
Oh, grace has nothing to do with it.
I'm allergic to non-organic fibers.
Fortunately, I brought my own sheets.
You always think of everything.
Hah! Bill would disagree.
According to him,
I have no idea how the real world works.
He said that to you?
You know what?
I don't wanna talk about Bill.
I wanna know what's going on with you.
How's the baby doing? Chloe?
Oh, I just went and saw her, actually.
She's doing good.
She's finally at a healthy weight.
She's so adorable.
Must have been really hard to give her up.
I didn't give her up.
I reunited her with her mother.
Still.
Why don't we talk about your birthday?
I heard that there's a decent spa
in Eureka.
Yeah, you know what? I don't really wanna
do anything for my birthday.
Okay, so you came here
to celebrate your birthday,
but you don't want
to celebrate your birthday.
- Got it.
- I don't want to make a big deal of it.
What are you even talking about?
You always wanna do something big.
I mean, last year,
you and Bill went to Tahiti.
Well, this year,
I just feel like being more low-key.
You didn't come here
to celebrate anything.
You came here
to convince me to leave.
That's not true.
It's not. I do think that coming home
would be the best thing for you.
Look, I told you
that no matter what happens here,
I'm not coming back to LA, okay?
And have you ever even considered
that me starting over somewhere
might be the best thing for me?
Except you're not starting over.
- You're living in denial.
- Really?
I mean, you still have
your wedding ring on, for God's sakes.
You know, just because
I'm having trouble letting go
doesn't mean that I'm in denial.
Okay? I came here
so that I could help people.
And I'm staying here for the moment
because I made a commitment.
You made a mistake.
The sooner you realize that,
the better off you'll be.
- Oh, my God. You don't get it.
- Yes, I do.
I know exactly what you're doing.
No, you don't. You haven't for years.
Because life is more to me
than a Barneys mid-year sale.
Okay, look. I may not be as smart
and successful as you are,
but at least I'm honest
about who I am and what I want.
- Mel...
- No, I can't.
♪ You don't really care ♪
What can I get you?
How about an entire bottle of gin?
Uh-oh. How about an iced tea?
- Ugh... fine.
- Everything okay?
No. My sister's been here for five minutes
and we're already fighting.
You know, I got a friend, he has
brothers. They fought all the time.
But then as soon as one hit the other one,
bam, it's all over.
So, what are you saying?
I should punch her?
- It worked for the Hill brothers.
- Great.
Come on. Just apologize.
Enjoy her visit.
- She'll be gone before you know it.
- You're right. You're right.
I know she loves me so much,
but she just can't wrap her head around
why I'm here.
Yeah, well, I get that.
Yeah, my family thought I was crazy
when I moved here.
I guess it was a little unexpected,
but I didn't fit in when I went home
after Iraq.
I just...
You know what, in the end,
what I realized was that I needed
to make a new home for myself.
Right.
That's exactly what I'm trying to do,
but she still wants me to move back to LA.
I don't know. Maybe she's right.
Maybe I should just go back.
Well, I didn't, uh...
I didn't realize
that was still on the table.
My trial period with Doc
is almost up, and...
at some point I have to decide
whether or not I'm going to stay here
for the rest of the year.
Well, you know,
the pull of family is strong.
Especially when you're feeling alone.
Exactly.
You know, there's real value
in being independent.
I am independent.
I know. Otherwise, you wouldn't be here.
Well, regardless,
I need to go apologize to my sister.
Well, the view's always better
from the high road.
Yes, it is.
Wow, did Hope order all of this?
Yeah.
I guess she's expecting quite the turnout.
She ordered enough pecan pie
to feed an army.
Well, unfortunately,
I'll be more than happy
to eat the leftovers.
I have a weakness
for anything pecan related.
I think I get it from my dad.
He grew up on a pecan farm in Texas.
I thought your father grew up
in the northeast.
No...
uh... but he did move to upstate New York
in high school.
So, are you, uh... going tonight?
Yeah, I promised Hope that I would.
If you, uh... if you want, you know,
we could drive out together.
Oh. Um...
I... I would, but I have some things
I need to take care of up in Clear River,
so I was just gonna drive straight
from there.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's, uh...
that's smart.
- I'll see you tonight, kiddo.
- Bye, Preacher.
- Okay. See ya.
- Thanks.
What stuff?
What stuff are we doing in Clear River?
Nothing.
I just said that to make things easier.
So, you lied?
I don't want to hurt Preacher's feelings.
And you shouldn't be eavesdropping,
anyway.
How else am I gonna find out stuff?
Hey, remind me how I got roped into this?
You can go back
to working at the bar with Preacher.
Uh...
Copy that.
Guys, I'd really like to hand the keys
over by the end of the week.
Well, what's the big rush?
I just think it should be done by then.
Oh, uh... okay.
Hey, baby.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I thought you'd be at work.
Well, I had a little bit of a gap
in my schedule,
so I thought I'd come and give you this.
Hm. Preacher told me where to find you.
Wow, you've really transformed this place.
- Yeah, that's the plan.
- Hm.
Well, speaking of plans,
I need you to make a decision.
Dinner. Before or after the Mingle?
Oh, right. Yeah.
Uh, well, I guess we could grab somethin'
in Clear River beforehand.
Sounds like a plan.
Okay. Bye, boys.
- What?
- Nothin'.
Well, hey, if you got somethin' to say.
Nah. Just, uh, thinkin'. You got a lot
on your plate these days.
- Hey.
I thought you wanted to stay in.
I changed my mind.
- Joey.
- What? I want to go to that Mingle thing.
Look, I want to apologize
for what I said earlier.
I'm sorry too.
Now, can I borrow some shoes?
Because if this thing is at a farm,
I'm gonna need, like, a wedge heel.
Can we talk, please?
We both said things we didn't mean. Okay?
Let's just forget about it.
Go out, have some fun.
- Really? You're not mad?
- No. I should not have said what I did.
- Okay.
- So get ready, 'cause I feel like dancing.
Well, I don't think the Mingle
is gonna live up to your expectations.
As long as there's a bar, I will be fine.
Okay?
Let's find something for you to wear
that doesn't involve boots.
♪ I know you'll always be here ♪
♪ You won me from the moment
I was in your atmosphere ♪
♪ What chance did I have ♪
♪ When you looked up and said
You wouldn't be here? ♪
♪ Now, promise me here ♪
♪ You're ready to forgive me ♪
This is really something.
Ah, it looks like
the entire town showed up.
Is Lilly coming?
Oh, she's doing better,
but wasn't ready for a big event.
She's seeing a therapist up in Clear River
who's really helping her.
When she told me about Chloe,
oh, I just said,
"Well, honey, I love you,
and the entire town is here for you."
Huh? It's what we do.
Hope. What the hell?
- Vernon, this isn't the time.
- What is wrong with you?
You're the one who insisted
on this divorce,
- and you don't show up to the meeting?
- I got busy.
Preacher tried
to bait and switch the salad.
Lucky I intervened,
or you'd all be eating arugula.
I don't give a rat's ass about the salad.
You could have had the decency
to let me know you couldn't come.
- Lecturing me about decency. That's rich.
- Oh, come on. You owe me an apology, Hope.
♪ 'Cause I'll always be here ♪
♪ When you're ready to feel ♪
♪ Oh, la, la, la, la, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, la, la, la, la, la ♪
Hi.
♪ Oh, la, la, la, la, oh, oh ♪
We can leave any time you want.
We just got here.
I know.
Thank you.
Don't you want to call Bill and the kids
before it gets too late?
I talked to the kids.
And everybody's good.
No one's in the ER.
Hey. Hey, Mel.
Hey.
I'm Joey, Mel's sister.
I don't think we formally met.
- Preacher.
- Hey.
Nice to meet you, Joey.
Yeah. Have you seen Paige?
Oh, no, we just got here.
Do you mind holding this?
I forgot my clutch.
- Sure.
- I'm gonna go to the bar.
Oh, I'll come with you.
Oh, that's okay. I don't need a chaperone.
- Okay.
- Okay. Nice to meet you.
All right, everybody. Time to mingle.
Uh...
- Mingle?
- Mingle.
- [chuckles[ Okay.
- Okay.
- Like that?
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Sorry,
I'm not the, uh... best dancer.
- Neither am I. It's fine.
- Oh!
That is so sweet of you to lie to me.
So, how are you enjoying Virgin River?
Um... honestly?
It's been a little bit of an adjustment.
Yeah.
- Yeah, I bet.
- Yeah.
Mm.
But Jack's been a big help...
- Yeah.
- ...so that's great.
Yeah, he is a good man.
Yeah.
How long did you guys serve together?
- Ten years.
Yeah.
Wow. You must be really close.
We're brothers.
In fact, I swear I know him better
than he knows himself.
I can't imagine how hard it must've been.
We were all there to... to do a job.
Jack was there
to make sure we all got home alive.
Sounds like a lot of pressure.
Yeah.
Oh, he handled it.
Do you think he's still handling it?
Yeah, I'm sure.
I mean, every now and then, he gets, uh...
a little wound up,
but that's just being human.
Has he ever had any help?
Well, Jack prefers to manage his business
on his own.
Yeah, but if it was a broken bone,
you'd get it set, right?
It's really no different.
Bit of advice.
Wherever you're going with this...
I wouldn't.
See, Jack believes
in lettin' sleepin' dogs lie.
Now it's time for a new partner.
And mingle.
♪ Carry my head low, please ♪
♪ Carry your shinin' eyes ♪
Hey, uh, Mel, do... do you wanna, um...
- you know, uh...
- Dance?
- Yeah.
- Sure.
♪ Carry my simple life
Thanks.
This is so beautiful.
Yeah.
Let's go dancing.
Why don't we get a drink first?
Um, sure. I'm just gonna go say hi
to some of the girls from the shop.
- I'll meet you at the bar.
- Okay.
Can I grab a beer, thanks?
- ♪ Carry your shining eyes ♪
- Let's mingle!
And don't be shy, people.
Hey.
Hey. What are you thinkin'?
- My feet are killing me.
- Not that. I mean, about Doc.
Hm?
Why get a divorce now
after all these years?
Because that chapter of my life is closed,
and I wanna make it official.
Please.
You two are still thick as thieves.
Exactly.
I'm just doing this to remind him
that after what he did,
we aren't a couple anymore,
and haven't been for a long time.
♪ I say be patient ♪
Wow.
You're a really good dancer.
I took, uh, ballroom dancing
in high school.
No.
I cannot picture that.
Well, it's where
all the pretty girls hung out, so...
- Oh.
- Ahem.
That's very clever.
So, is, uh...
is that your sister?
Yes.
Ah.
I have, uh, two.
- Oh, you do?
- Yeah.
Are you close?
Um... no.
No. That's too bad.
Well, it is what it is, you know?
Everyone thinks, uh, families
should all get along.
Sometimes they do, sometimes they do not.
Yeah.
Um, Hope thinks that your sister is here
to convince you to leave.
Is that right?
- Yeah, I suspect that's probably the case.
- Ah.
She hasn't wanted me to come out here
since the beginning, so...
You know.
The pot camp incident didn't help.
Oh.
So, is, uh...
is that something you wanna do?
Go home?
Is that something you want me to do?
Oh, no, no, I'm not here
to tell you what to do.
- That's... that's Hope's job.
- Hm.
And you've dodged that question
really well.
Thank you.
Mingle!
- Hey, you wanna dance?
- Oh, I'm so sorry.
I have to take this. Excuse me.
Oh. Bill?
Hey. No, no, no, no. Joey is fine. I...
What's going on?
♪ Come on ♪
Enjoy.
♪ Listen when I say ♪
Hi. Hi, Mrs. McCrea.
Are you enjoying the event?
My pants itch.
Sounds like a personal problem.
- Does your mom know where you are?
- I have to tell you something.
Oh.
Okay.
You should ask my mom to dance.
I should?
Huh.
Well, you're a little young
to be a matchmaker, aren't you?
Well, what are you waiting for?
Uh... I...
I... I don't know if it's a good idea.
You'll never know if you don't try.
Yeah, well...
Hi, Hope.
...I just don't know
if she wants to dance with me.
Good Lord, you've faced down men
with machine guns,
but you're worried
about asking a woman to dance?
You heard the man. Go. Get your mingle on.
♪ For you to bring it on back ♪
♪ Bring it on back to me ♪
♪ Just like the birds ♪
♪ And the bees ♪
♪ Need the flowers and the trees ♪
♪ I need you to bring it on back ♪
♪ Bring it on back to me ♪
♪ Baby, bring it on back ♪
♪ Bring it on back ♪
- ♪ Bring it on back ♪
- I'm going to have to interrupt.
- He's needed on the dance floor.
- ♪ Bring it on back ♪
♪ Bring it on back to me ♪
You know you want to.
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Just bring it on back ♪
♪ Bring it on back to me ♪
- Isn't this amazing?
- ♪ Bring it on back ♪
Everyone dressed in their Sunday best
just dancing the night away.
- ♪ Bring it on back to me ♪
- Mm.
I could just stay like this forever.
Couldn't you?
Just so lucky.
♪ Cower, doped to recovering ♪
♪ Grow crown and suffer ♪
♪ You stole ♪
- ♪ You stole in featherweight ♪
- Baby?
Mingle.
- You okay?
- ♪ I need the truth ♪
♪ Oh, nothin' but the truth ♪
♪ You keep on runnin' ♪
♪ But there's no use in tryin' ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm comin' after you ♪
♪ Oh, I'm comin' for you ♪
♪ Mm, bring it on back ♪
♪ Bring it on back ♪
♪ Bring it on back to me ♪
Mm. Hear that?
Let's mingle.
♪ When I was young ♪
All right. Fine.
I will pay for the attorney.
Good.
Well, actually,
I think the appropriate response
is "Thank you, thank you very much."
You want me to thank you
for paying for the divorce
that was initiated by your indiscretion?
Never mind. Never mind.
No, no, no. Think about what you said.
You're acting
like you're doing me a favor.
I just want you
to stop holding one bad judgment call
over my head.
By buying my forgiveness?
- Well, I've tried everything else.
- No, you haven't.
What... What does that mean?
♪ Crazy in love ♪
You're still acting
like I'm the one who's being unreasonable.
I just feel like I've been apologizing
for the last 20 years.
I don't want to hear sorry.
I want to see sorry.
Time to find that special someone
and mingle.
Hey.
♪ I never meant to be ♪
You look really nice.
Oh, thank you.
- It's a great party.
- Yeah.
So, you tried the roast pork?
I did. It was delicious.
Christopher went back for thirds.
Ah...
So, how was Clear River?
Oh, um...
Well, uh, at the last minute,
something came up, so we didn't go.
Oh.
Well, either way, I, um...
I'm glad you're here.
- ♪ Now I'm hangin' on here ♪
- No wallflowers.
Get on to that dance floor.
♪ And I don't belong ♪
♪ I'm just bidin' my time ♪
♪ Waitin' to cross your mind ♪
♪ Will I cross your mind? ♪
There's nothing on it.
- I'm telling you.
- Really?
Nothing.
Do I look like someone
who uses moisturizer?
No, you don't.
♪ Beauty's only word is burnin' ♪
Hey, Jo.
- Hey.
- Mel. Hey.
- What are you doing?
- Hey, you have to feel Brady's skin.
It is so soft.
Go ahead. I'm not shy.
- Ah, that's okay.
- Really, you have to feel it.
- No, no.
- He does not use moisturizer.
That's great. I think it's time to go.
- No, it isn't.
- Uh, yeah, it's... it's early.
- Yeah.
- It's really not that early. She...
Well, I think, uh, Joey can decide
for herself when she wants to go home.
Yeah. You wanna go, go.
And I'm sure I can find someone
to give me a ride home.
- Jo.
- Mm-hm?
- Yeah.
- Jo, I talked to Bill.
- You what?
- I... I called Bill.
- Mingle.
- Why did you do that?
I'm sorry, I accidentally saw a text
on your phone from him.
You read my text?
I'm just trying to help you, okay? I...
Why didn't you just tell me
what was going on?
Because my marriage
is none of your business.
Wow. I can't believe you just said that.
You have been running my life
since I was 11 years old,
but I'm not allowed
to discuss Bill with you?
Do you think that I wanted
to run your life?
Yeah, it sure seems like you do.
Do you have any idea
how many things I gave up
so that I could take care of you?
I didn't ask you to take care of me.
Well, who else was gonna do it?
After Mom died, I mean, Dad was a mess.
Overnight, you became my responsibility.
Wow. I'm so sorry that I was such a burden
for you. Okay?
But I'm not a child anymore.
- Then stop acting like one.
- Oh, me?
Yes, you.
You don't wanna face the past
or the future,
so you did what a child would do.
You ran away from home.
Look, you can hide out here
for as long as you want,
but until you deal with reality,
you are never gonna get your life
back on track.
Just because I'm not you
does not mean that my life isn't on track.
It's time to mingle.
Joey. I...
Dance with me.
All righty.
She certainly has a knack
for holdin' a grudge.
Like a dog with a bone.
Oh, it's been 20 years.
Well, heartbreak can be,
you know, a long time to heal.
Yeah, but I... I have apologized.
And I've apologized.
I don't... I don't know what else I can do.
You don't get it.
Well... what is there to get?
The reason Hope can't forgive you
is because...
she believed that you were
the one person in the world
who wouldn't hurt her.
After two crappy husbands,
you were supposed to be
her knight in shining armor.
You were the one she was supposed
to drive off into the sunset with.
Yeah, but Hope, she doesn't... doesn't
believe in all that fairy tale crap.
She used to...
before you broke her heart.
Oh, Jiminy Christmas.
She ain't never gonna forgive me.
As one of Hope's oldest friends...
this is my two cents.
You have to find a way
to earn back her trust.
Time to mingle.
♪ And I'll sell my lies ♪
Ooh!
Ah-ah-ah!
Ah... Mm!
♪ While you fall in mine ♪
Oh, we are gonna get in trouble.
Are you hankering for a new partner?
No.
No, I'm not.
♪ And they say your heart ♪
♪ Is where you've been ♪
- Oh, my God.
- ♪ And you know... ♪
- Christopher?
- Well, he was just here.
Christopher. No, I have
to find Christopher. Christopher!
He... He couldn't have gone far.
Preacher, you don't understand.
Christopher!
I'll check the washroom.
- Christopher!
- Mom.
Mom, did you call me?
Oh, my God.
Okay, sorry.
- Paige, are you okay?
- Um...
Tell Hope that we're very sorry,
but we had to go.
Come on, buddy.
Okay, everybody, mingle.
Oh, my!
I feel dizzy.
You can spin me next time.
Oh, Jack Sheridan.
I can't thank you enough.
For the dance?
No, for taking Ricky under your wing.
Oh, come on. Your grandson is a great kid.
Well, he certainly idolizes you.
Huh. I mean, he never had a real father.
It's good he has you for a role model.
Boys need good men to help them grow up.
Mm-hm.
When he came here after losing his mom
the way he did, it...
He felt so alone.
Hey.
Well, he has you, and he has me,
and he has Doc, and he has Hope.
We're all here for him.
Having the right people love you
and care about you...
can make all the difference.
Let's mingle.
Come on, now, don't be shy.
Hey, stranger.
- Hey.
- Where have you been off to all night?
- Just been mingling.
- Oh, yeah?
How's Lydie?
Yeah, she's a little worried about Ricky,
but I think mostly she's fine.
Mmm. Well...
raising a teenager at her age is...
is quite a commitment.
Yeah, she's got a big heart.
So do you.
- I do?
- Yeah.
You act like a tough guy,
but inside you're just a big softie.
It's one of the things I love about you.
Now, tell me something you love about me.
♪ Oh, your beat stops my heart ♪
You can't think of one thing?
Oh, it's not that.
- Then what is it?
- ♪ Say the word and let it start ♪
It's just... Listen, when we started
seeing each other...
we both agreed that we were just gonna
keep things casual.
♪ Say the word and let it start ♪
So, you're saying that...
for the last two years... you...
you don't feel any more committed
than you did when we first met?
Look, we said from the start
that we didn't want anything serious.
Oh, my God. I...
I can't believe this.
♪ Time can change the colors ♪
Can we just maybe
have this conversation alone?
Jack, I know what we said
when we first met.
I...
♪ Watchin' you bathed in light ♪
I just... I thought that...
♪ The fears are far below us ♪
- After all this time, I thought...
- ♪ In an endless sky ♪
- ...we'd have a future together.
- ♪ I can feel you falling ♪
I love you.
- Look...
- ♪ I can feel you ♪
If you... if you don't feel the same way,
I have to know.
♪ Say the word and let it start ♪
I can't be here right now.
Time to mingle.
♪ When rain is blowin' in your face ♪
Mel.
- ♪ And the whole world ♪
- Hi.
- ♪ Is on your case ♪
- You okay?
Um...
- ♪ I could offer you a warm embrace ♪
- I've had better nights.
- Yeah. You could say that again.
- ♪ To make you feel my love ♪
♪ When the evening's shadows ♪
- ♪ And the stars appear ♪
- You look very nice.
- Thank you. So do you.
- ♪ And there is no one there ♪
♪ To dry your tears ♪
- ♪ I could hold you for a million years ♪
- Glad you came, at least?
- ♪ To make you feel my love ♪
- Yes and no.
- ♪ I know you haven't ♪
- Oh, don't just stand around.
- ♪ Made your mind up yet ♪
- Take a partner to the dance floor.
♪ But I will never do you wrong ♪
♪ I've known it
From the moment that we met ♪
♪ No doubt in my mind where you belong ♪
♪ I'd go hungry, I'd go black and blue ♪
♪ I'd go crawlin' down the avenue ♪
Well, your sister sure seems
to be havin' a good time.
♪ No, there's nothing that I wouldn't do ♪
Yeah. Well, she's, uh...
- ♪ To make you feel my love ♪
- She's gifted when it comes to having fun.
But not you?
Well, I always had to work really hard
to get what I wanted.
And with Joey,
it just kind of... came easily.
It was hard to compete with her.
Come on. I don't see any competition.
Yeah, that's because I've gotten good
at hiding my flaws.
It's too bad you don't see yourself
the way the rest of the world does.
♪ And the whole world is on your case ♪
- Yeah, I don't understand.
- ♪ I could offer you ♪
- Okay. Okay.
- ♪ A warm embrace ♪
- Hey, you. Hi.
- That's enough.
Hey, have you met Brady?
'Cause he's so funny.
- Yes, I know Brady.
- He's so funny.
- Okay.
- Yeah, you do?
Yes, I do. Let's go.
- Whoa. No, no, no.
- What?
Just, everyone settle down. Okay?
I think what needs to happen
is you need to mind your own business.
All right, hey, hey, that's enough.
Come on.
- That's enough. Come on.
- What?
- Hey, man.
- What are you doing?
I'm off duty.
So, the great Jack Sheridan...
doesn't get to tell me what to do.
All right, you're drunk.
Yeah. Well, the big shocker is you're not.
Let's just get someone
to take you home, huh?
- Joey, let's go.
- Uh...
- Hey, hey, she's a married woman.
- No.
Yeah, well, so is Mel,
but it hasn't stopped you.
Is he okay?
Yeah, I got it. I got it.
- We're going. Let's go.
- Okay. Okay.