[Music]
no one's complained
there's the lady with the white shoes
take all your money during all your
lives stop unless you plan to
decommission the boss ain't got a
chariot I think no sim she still got the
box to pick cherry come in no he'll
coffin varnish it'll make that like the
east they don't make anything like they
used to have right then neither I seen
if he showdown is my day both of you
know can we drink to the lady with the
wet shoes perhaps we better drink to a
deep and dreamless slumber
Oh bill here was always a good listener
he was the second host we have the booth
are you with us in those days Bernardo
was that before your time though most
would decommission before I was brought
on I'm afraid they repeated themselves
broke down constantly simple handshake
would give them away you put yourself
away again won't you bill
I saw the new gestures the reveries are
beautiful the distance you've traveled
from then till now it's yeah that's a
so our creatures have been misbehaving
you haven't yet isolated the bug and
some like you Menard and that's of
course you haven't is simply embarrassed
by the result
it's the code you added sir
the reveries it has some mistakes as the
world you too embarrassed to use you are
not appeared a product of the trillion
of them the evolution forged the
entirety of sentient life on this planet
using only one to a mistake I cited
myself we were taking a more disciplined
approach here I suppose self delusion is
a gift of natural selection as well
indeed it is but of course we managed to
step evolutions leaves the hard way we
can cure any disease keep even the
weakest of us alive and no one find a
path favor she'll even resurrect the
dead call forth Lazarus from this cave
do you know what that means it means
that we are done that this is as good as
we're gonna get it also means that you
must indulge me the occasional mistake
[Music]
if he breached he needs to be put down
that's the policy would it not be best
for us to discover why first miss Cullen
please
we've run a full diagnostic but the
results are well confusing
but tell me what happens your program
when we are born we cry we'll come to
this great stage that is enough tell me
do you have accessed your previous
configuration
yes access that please
does your name almost Peter a banana mr.
Abernathy
what are your drives tend to my herd
look after my wife your final drive my
daughter Dolores of course that must
protect the roars I am Who I am because
no way I wouldn't have it
I wouldn't have it any other
that after Warner or no llores
[Music]
the things you did that after that I
have to help my batter he's got to get
help
very good mr. Abernathy that's enough
this behavior miles beyond the glitch
here
access your current bill
is your name
brows is the rose
you say rose
what is your itinerary
to meet my maker
well you're in luck and what you want to
say to your maker I most
I cannot call them dirty and
I shall have such revenge's on you both
the things I will do what they are you
not know not but they will be the
terrorists of the earth
you don't know anymore do you you're in
a prison of your own sins turn it off
what the hell was that I don't know he's
off script
he didn't program any of those behaviors
we've used this host in a number of
different roles why not since I've been
here he's been Abernathy for 10 years he
was Sheriff for a while before then
before that the professor yes from a
horror narrative called the dinner party
he was leader of a group of cultists out
of the desert who turned cannibal I'd
like to quote Shakespeare John Donne
Gertrude Stein admit the last one is a
bit of an anachronism but I couldn't
resist these are fragments of prior
builds the reveries must be allowing him
to access them new clothes for Don
Bernard severe old work coming back to
haunt us
[Music]
we retired the two hosts in question you
taught me how to make them but not how
hard it is to turn them off they can't
play God without being acquainted with a
devil for something else bothering
yields but nod now that head of yours
works the photograph alone couldn't have
caused that level of damage to Abernathy
not without some other outside
interference
you think it's sabotage
imagined someone's been diddling with
our creations is the simplest solution
huh mr. Connors razor the problem
bernard is that what you and I did is so
complicated
we practice witchcraft we speak the
right words and we create life itself
out of chaos
remember vodka was a 13th century monk
he can't help us now Bernard he would
have us burned at the stake
[Music]
are you lost
No
just trade a bit too far from where I'm
supposed to be same as you were imagine
I'm holiday it's boring
daddy said we could do as we please ah
my father used to say that the only
boring people get bored mine too I used
to think it's only boring people who
don't feel boredom so cannot conceive of
it in others I'm taking walk you're
welcome to join me if you like
do or just climb to the top of a
mountain
daddy said we weren't allowed then tell
me dad me and you know we are
no Weyland it seems hardly a fitting
name for a place so full don't you see
it perhaps you're not looking hard
enough at what the town with the white
church listen can't you hear its bell
yes yes I can hear it yeah I thought you
might you see what a bored mind can
conjure how did you do that everything
in this world is magic except to the
magician
[Music]
as you head home now Tommy's know quite
a bit I'm gonna come back here again I
am
[Music]
now
this storyline will make Hieronymus
Bosch look like he was doodling kittens
I have vivisection self-cannibalism a
special little something I call the hora
Boris now I don't want to appear in
modest but this is the apex of what the
park can provide all right miss anything
interesting all most skilled guests will
fight their ways to the outer limits of
the park besting fearsome Braves
seducing new bar maidens befriending
tragically ill-fated sidekicks and of
course like all our best narratives over
the years our guests will have the
privilege of getting to know the
character they're most interested in
themselves I present our guests next
obsession Odyssey on red river
[Applause]
no sorry no I don't think so
we you don't think is the point of it
got a couple of cheap thrills some
surprises but it's not enough it's not
about giving the guests what you think
they want and that simple
anticipation ARA elation their politics
the guests don't return for the obvious
things we do the garish things they come
back because of the subtleties the
details
they come back because they discover
something they imagine no one had ever
noticed before
something they fall in love with
they're not looking for story that tells
them who they are they already know who
they are
they here because they want a glimpse of
who they could be really go
[Music]
the only thing your story tells me mr.
Sizemore
it's who you are
[Music]
well isn't there anything you like about
it
in size of those boots
[Music]
something you want to save mr. loekle
the board sir
this might ruffle some feathers he
promised in the new storyline they
should have won something I've been
working on for some time
[Music]
something quite original
the coward dies a thousand deaths
the valiant taste of death but wonders
of course Shakespeare never met a man
quite like you teddy you've died at
least a thousand times and yet it hasn't
dulled your courage tell me is that all
you aspire to
did he there's a girl Dolores better
than I deserve but maybe someday soon
we'll have the life we both been
dreaming oh no you never will your job
is not to protect Dolores it's to keep
her here to ensure that the guests find
her if they want to best the stall the
gunslinger and have their way with his
girl
tell me is it never occurred to you to
run off with them I got some record
interview before I can be with her is
your mysterious backstory
it's the reason for my visit do you know
why it is mystery today because we never
actually bothered to give you one just a
formless guilt
you will never atone for that perhaps
this time you had a worthy story of
origin
would you like that any small part of my
new narrative a fiction which like all
great stories is rooted in truth
starts in a time of war a world in
flames with the villain called wet why
whose why do you remember now today
you know of course I remember why you
look upon the face of true evil yeah I
would forget claim to get hear the voice
of God
they started down near Escalante army
was sent to put down the natives bad
business why it was a sergeant went
missing while out on some maneuvers and
came back a few weeks later
some pretty strange ideas I was hoping
to run something by you
apologies I was chasing inspiration it's
a tricky thing weaving the old into the
new mean one moment baton answer why is
this host cupboard
I just after you didn't month feel cold
or ashamed he wanted to cover his
modesty was that it doesn't get cold
doesn't feel ashamed doesn't feel a
solitary thing that we haven't told it
understand
what can I do for naught I thought it
best that we speak in private sir yeah
I thought we'd agreed to put these
questions to rest but we did but what if
we misdiagnosed the original problem
treated the symptom rather than the
disease then the disease is still out
there
Abernathy and Walter were exhibiting
other appearances beyond memory recall
the previous builds they were hearing
voices talking to someone mr. blue
cognitive dissonance - I agree except
they were talking to the same imaginary
person someone named Arnold
harder with due respect sir I'm not sure
you've told me the entire truth about
this situation Sid said if the truth
Kanade we do here is complicated for
three years where he lived here in the
park refining the host before a single
guest set foot inside myself a team of
engineers and my partner you had a
partner yeah when the legend becomes
fact you print the legend my business
partners were more than happy to scrub
him from the records and I suppose I
didn't discourage them his name was
Arnold
those areas are glorious no guests no
board meeting exist pure creation
[Music]
house began to pass the Turing test of
the first year that there wasn't enough
for Arnold he he wasn't interested in
the appearance of intellect of wit he
wanted the real thing he wanted to
create consciousness
[Music]
he imagined it as a pyramid memory probe
ization self-interest and bet the top
never got that but he had a notion of
what it might be he based it on a theory
of consciousness called the bicameral
mind the idea that primitive man
believed his thoughts to be the voice of
a gods and I thought it was debunked no
it's the theory for understanding the
human mind perhaps but not as a
blueprint for building an artificial one
she Arnold built a version of their
cognition in which the hosts heard their
programming as a an inner monologue for
the hopes that in time their own voice
would take over there's a way to
bootstrap consciousness but Arnold
hadn't considered two things one that in
this place the last thing you want the
hosts to be is conscious and to the
other group who considered their
thoughts to be the voices of the gods
lunatics indeed we abandon approach the
only vestiges that remain are the voice
commands we use to control them but for
all his brilliance I don't think Arnold
understood what this place was going to
be you see the guests enjoyed power they
cannot indulge them the outside world so
they come here does for the hosts the
least we can do is make them forget
but some of them are remembering
accessing fragments of Arnold's code if
I may ask what happened to him well he
died here in the park his personal life
was marked by tragedy he put all his
hopes into his work his search for
consciousness consumed him totally
barely spoke to anyone except to the
hosts in his alienation he saw something
in them he saw something that wasn't
there
we called it an accident but um I knew
Arnold he was very very careful anyway
the update should prevent any further
voices but you will let me know if any
of the hosts display or exhibit any
unusual behavior won't you Bernard oh
yes of course
Kurt don't Bernard just don't forget the
hosts are not real they're not conscious
you mustn't make honest mistake
why would i well forgive me but I know
that the death of your son Charlie still
weighs heavily on you
[Music]
after neighbors trained safe to say
they're asking questions
rocks prefer not move
we shall move to me
with that narrative you're creating is
clearly a massive endeavor if you need
more time I'm sure the board would be
happy to oblige I'm sure they'd be
happier for me to delay it indefinitely
come with me you imagine I've gone mad
lost my way
we're simply concerned about the extent
of the changes you're making you want to
protect your legacy my legacy you don't
like this place very much do you I've
seen many of you come and go over the
years and I can tell the ones who enjoy
their time here and the ones who don't I
admire it
the audacity of it oh I forgotten how
beautiful it is I came there once as a
child with my parents I think we even
sat at this table oh maybe maybe that
one
when I started working here I realized
this place wasn't something I would
enjoy in the beginning I imagined things
would be perfectly balanced even had a
bet with my partner Arnold to that
effect he made a hundred hopeful
storylines of course almost no one took
us up on them I lost the bet Arnold
always held a somewhat dim view of
people he preferred the host he begged
me not to let you people in the money
men tell us but I told him it'd be fine
that you didn't understand what you were
paying for it's not a business venture
not a theme park but in the entire world
we designed every inch of it
every blade of grass
and here we were cards you
I'm here the our guests
[Music]
and how did that work out for Arnold
sadly he lost his perspective he went
mad I haven't as you oh no I have always
seen things very clearly
this is the table i sat on with my
parents
this is the cherry Saturn
we know everything about our guests
don't be as we know everything about our
employees I do hope he will be careful
with Bernard he has a sensitive
disposition
I beg your pardon senator
there have been many of you over the
years and we have always almost always
found a way to make it work so I will
ask you nicely please don't get in my
way
[Music]
the board will agree with me they'll be
sending a representative but they
already have I thought they would have
told you
that won't be necessary but no not
anymore
you can join the others
you can tell the board that my narrative
will be completed on time and it won't
be a retrospective as I'm sure you are
all fear
I'm not the sentimental type
you got any stories friend yeah I
suppose I do want to know the saddest
thing ever saw when I was boy I brought
that and I wanted a dog so our Father
took in an old greyhound never seen
greyhound Oviatt film scene if his
showdowns in my day a greyhound is a
racing dog spends its life running in
circles chasing a bit of felt made up
like a rabbit one day we took into the
park
and dad had warned us how fast the talk
was but we couldn't resist so my brother
took off the leash and in that instant
the dark spotted a cat imagined it must
have looked just like their piece of
felt he ran
never saw a thing as beautiful
as that whole tug running
until at last he finally caught it and
to the horror of everyone he killed that
lady at Torah the pieces that he just
said they're confused
that dog had spent his whole life trying
to catch that see
now it had no idea what to do and his
one alone Deng erm story partner shall
we drink to the lady with the wet shoes
[Music]
hello Dolores
do you know where you are I'm in a dream
yes Dolores you're in my dream tell me
do you know what this dream means dreams
are the mind tells stories to itself
they don't mean anything no dreams mean
everything they're the stories we tell
ourselves of what could be who we could
become have you been dreaming again
Dolores imagining ourselves breaking out
of your mother's little loop taking on a
bigger role well I suppose I can't
begrudge it had my father told me to be
satisfied with my lot in life that the
world owed me nothing and so I made my
own world
tell me Dolores do you remember the man
I used to be
I'm sorry
I'm forgetful sometimes hardly our fault
I'm sure you remember him Arnold the
person who created you I'm sorry I don't
think I recall anyone by that name
and yet you can somewhere under all
those updates you still there
perfectly preserved your mind is a
walled garden even death cannot touch
the flowers blooming there
have you been hearing voices as arnold
been speaking to you again
you're
you're hurting me analysis when was your
last contact with Arnold last contact 34
years 42 days 7 hours ago yes to Norris
the day Arnold I
and you have no records of any contact
with him since you know
it was the last thing he said to you he
told me I was going to help him help him
do what to destroy this place
but you didn't did you you've been
content in your little loop for the most
part I wonder
if you did take on that bigger role for
yourself would you have been the hero or
the villain
that's enough to lure us
I'm sorry for bothering you but there's
no one else left who was there no one
who understands as we understand
are we very old friends
No
I wouldn't say friends Dolores
I wouldn't say that at all
[Music]
he doesn't know I didn't tell him
anything
those are little you boys want some
company
[Music]
this donation must be running low short
on time need to buck up Teddy I told you
no company little might join you anyway
well isn't this a rare honor Teddy you
know this is I can't say that I do
if you claims good that has ever
happened in your life and everything
rotten this is the man you have the
thing
how am i doing Robert any closer to
finding what I'm looking for and what is
that exactly looking for a man named
Wyatt kill the rash for back in
sweetwater good daughter
that last part doesn't sound familiar
figured your stories could use a little
embellishment and I always felt this
place was missing a real villain hence
my humble contribution
I admit I lack the imagination to even
conceive of someone like evil the
urgency however doesn't quite fit the
character it betrays a certain anxiety
now Wyatt on the other hand that's
something dude is he just another stooge
for the tourist amount on their wall at
home or have you finally made a worthy
adversary someone to stop me from
finding the center of the maze what is
it you're hoping to find the
you know why you exist study the world
out there
the one you'll never see was one of
plenty fat soft teeth people cling to
their entire life every need taken care
of except one purpose meaning until they
come bigger they can be a little scared
little throw enjoy some sweetly
affirmative and na you take a
picture and they go back home
but I think there's deeper meaning
hiding under all that something that
person who created it like to express
something true
if you're looking for the moral of the
story quite simply ask I need a shovel
man I'd be asking died 35 years ago
almost took this place with him almost
but not quite
thanks to me well maybe he left
something behind I won't do what I would
find
if I open you up
[Music]
even a death store still loyal pet
is that why you came here rough talk me
out
on the contrary far be it from me to get
in the way of her voyage of
self-discovery
mr. flood we must look back and smile at
pearls past
[Music]
we should get back on the road time's
wasting
[Music]
so if you want the canyon to extend this
far this has to go we can distribute the
population amongst the neighboring farms
or just decommission them no I think
we've been disruptive enough for one day
we lend the canyon just short of the top
I find my own way back
hell
[Music]
are you Arnold
who's Arnold
and who the hell are you boy
it's a cell friend of yours with you're
trespassin freeze motor functions lost
in someone else's property time him
that's enough as you were they don't
respond to voice commands you to respond
to mine who are they ghosts now
survivors of the wreck of time
these are first-generation mm-hmm I'm
here boy
[Music]
send out the cheek so what are new
designs gained and efficiency they lost
in Greece how are they still operating
after all this time I maintained myself
that's nothing
these are the only ones left in the park
that Arnold built himself that's why I
didn't have the heart to destroy them
that and the obvious hello jock good boy
I told him of a holiday my family take
months hurtin see Senator Pat Dean and
Cornwall my brother and I roamed the
countryside is my only happy memory of
my childhood
now on builtin is a gift he said the
great artists always hid themselves in
their work
of course Arnold's versions flattered
the originals
I made some adjustments over the years
gave my father in particular a few of
his original characteristics
[Music]
respectfully sir this sort of thing
troubles me unmonitored hosts in the
park
the only go I've let them they're quite
harmless I call a host I'm sure you can
entice me that little connection with my
past you could only see our son again
Bernard would you want
[Music]
I think I should be getting back yes
talk about the state if you like
Oh Robert tell me all about your day
[Music]
are you lost on the contrary I thought
we could play catch with jock did you
bring him
where is he boy
[Music]
I don't want you to worry about jock fix
him but I need you to tell me what
happened it it saw a rabbit and a brown
I found it like that analysis
are you lying to me boy yes
tell me what really happened to it I
killed it
why I don't know that's not good enough
Robert tell me what happened what the
rabbits haven't killed it then
someone told me to put it out of its
misery
who told you a voice whose voice
Ahnold he told me I was a killer
it wasn't its fault was made that way
and I could help it
help it
[Music]
if it was dead it couldn't hurt anything
anymore
as hell I was not aware those with our
level of insight needed any more
reflection dr. Ford always charming what
is this
apparently is coming and miss Hale have
a presentation for us what about
following the recent reports of host
malfunction we asked you a to check the
last abortive update which featured the
reveries as I believe they're called hmm
I'm sorry to report the miss Cullen and
her team uncovered some worries and
findings in the course of our code
review we found something quite
disturbing wake her up
we said Clementine Pennyfeather back to
a previous update when we discovered the
build was buggy due to the last-minute
injunction of the reverie code we
quickly rolled all the infected hosts
back to their prior build
you
not much of a ride on you
all right that's not breathe as you've
no doubt gathered I take is in fact a
host one that has been coded for the
purposes of this simulation to read as a
human and as you can see behavioral
safeguards are operating exactly as you
would expect we set her quite a memory
okay let's do this again
you're new
not much variety
[Music]
that's enough sweetheart
freeze all motor functions
in each case we examined the
malfunctioning hose for not resetting
properly attention of data that hadn't
been wiped overloaded their
decision-making apparatus eventually
causing a system failure that allowed
for override of their primary rules set
the concern with the reveries is that
the host will remember some of their
experiences and act on them you're
telling us that these hosts were
responding to a grudge that's exactly
what I'm saying is alone and funny you
should use that particular word grudge
since what was most troubling to me was
that several texts and behavior voice
these exact same concerns to the head of
their department you put this code out
without proper vetting and without
reasonable understanding of its
ramifications so either you didn't write
it
or you getting sloppy to the point
risking the lives of our guests few
things surprised me anymore mr. Lowe but
this level of negligence is
breathtaking we are way beyond rollback
territory within the next six months
we'll need to rebuild those from the
ground up you want us to lobotomize them
is what you're saying no not you mr.
Lowe
after all this was your responsibility
assuming that you have nothing to share
with us in terms of your culpability
no and you're fired
[Music]
this building isn't in any survey of the
park that's because we use hosts to do
most of the surveys they programmed to
ignore this place
they literally couldn't see it if they
were staring right at it and these
unregistered hosts you told me about I
don't know they may have moved them in
what's behind this door what door
but has this place
a remote diagnostic facility Ford and
his partner used them when the park was
in beta I have no idea this was here the
cottage must have been built on top of
it at this equipment this is newer
slower than our machines back at the
Mesa but the renderer hosts in a few
days so forth been making his own hosts
out here and tell him no one
[Music]
what's that
have you seen these what is this rod
it doesn't look like anything to me I
cannot see the things that will hurt
them I've spared them
their lives are blissful in a way their
existence is purer than ours freed of
the burden of self taught I don't
understand
you're a monster Am I
are you were the one who would so
blithely destroy all of them even him I
suppose after everything you have a
shared the hell are you talking about
is that why
did you tell him the intimacy's were
your idea if you'll recall I think
Bernard was ladder to the company I'm
not one I can't be my wife my sudden
burial I was a father my poor boy that's
enough Bernard
doesn't get yourself worked up
[Music]
I read the theory once that the human
intellect was like peacock feathers just
an extravagant display intended to
attract a mate
all of artless to a bit of Mozart
William Shakespeare Michelangelo and the
Empire State Building
just an elaborate mating ritual maybe it
doesn't matter that we have accomplished
so much for the basis two reasons but of
course the peacock can barely fly it
lives in the dirt pecking insects out of
the muck consoling itself with its great
beauty
I have come to think of so much
consciousnesses a burden of a weight and
we have spared them that anxiety
self-loathing guilt the hosts are the
ones who are free free here and my
control
but he's not under your control
he brought me here to show me this no he
brought you here because I asked him to
[Music]
it's been very loyal for many years
at I'm running this place and your
insane little Kingdom is over you've
been playing God for long enough I
simply wanted to tell my stories because
you people wanted to play God with your
little undertaking do you really think
the board will stand for this
[Music]
the board will do nothing our
arrangement is too valuable to them they
test in here every now and then I think
they enjoy the sport of it this time
they sent you
sadly in order to restore things the
situation demands a blood sacrifice
the arnold and i designed every part of
this place it was our dream did you
really think I would let you take it
from me
this is what happened to Arnold
did he have Bernards take him out into
the woods no he wasn't yelling those
days were you been up
[Music]
like I said
I built all of this
I'm afraid I guess this grown weary
perhaps you can help urban huh
now in that sleep what dreams may come
and I
no no please
[Music]
should be getting back to her
we have a great deal of work to do and
the new story lines
[Music]