( thunder rumbling )
Merle:
That's right. You heard me, bitch.
You got a problem?
Bring it on
if you're man enough,
or take it up the chain
if you're a pussy.
You heard me,
you pussy-ass noncom bitch.
You ain't deaf.
Take it up
the damn chain of command
or you can kiss my lily-white ass.
( laughs )
That's right.
That's what I said.
You heard me.
And then this idiot,
he takes a swing,
you know, and well...
( laughing hysterically )
Oh, you should've seen
the look on his face
when I punched out his front teeth.
Yeah, five of ‘em.
Pow! Pow! Just like that.
Huh.
Oh my god.
16 months in the stockade--
oh, that's what them teeth cost me.
That was--
that was hard time,
but by God,
it was worth every minute of it
just to see that prick
spit his teeth out on the ground.
Yes sir,
worth every minute.
Mmm.
( wind blowing )
Oh no.
No no! No no! No no!
God! God!
No no!
( grunts )
God! Jesus!
No no, merciful Christ!
No no. No no.
God, help me! God! God!
Jesus, please! Jesus, please.
Help me! Come on now!
Help me.
( zombies growling, banging )
( softly )
No no. Oh, no no.
Oh my God.
Shh shh shh shh shh.
( crying )
Oh, Jesus. Jesus.
No no no no no no.
Please.
I didn't behave, I know.
I know I'm being punished.
I know. I--
oh, I deserve it. I deserve it.
I've been bad.
Help me now.
Show me the way.
Go on, tell me what to do.
Tell me. Tell me.
God!
( grunting )
That's okay.
Never you mind, silly Christ boy.
I ain't begged you before.
I ain't gonna start begging now.
I ain't gonna beg you now!
Don't you worry about me
begging you ever!
I'll never beg you!
I ain't gonna beg you!
I never begged you before.
- ( grunting )
- ( banging, growling continues )
Oh shit.
No!
( theme music playing )
Best not to dwell on it.
Merle got left behind.
Nobody's gonna be sad
he didn't come back...
except maybe Daryl.
- Daryl?
- His brother.
( car alarm approaching )
( Glenn whooping )
Whoo-hoo!
At least somebody's
having a good day.
- ( rattling )
- ( kids grunting )
- Girl: Give it back.
- Boy: Stop it.
- Girl: No!
- Boy: I found it.
- Boy: Give it.
M'hijo, leave your sister alone.
- Why?
- Come on.
Baby, the more you fidget,
the longer it takes.
- So don't, okay?
- I'm trying.
Well, try harder.
Shane:
If you think this is bad,
wait till you start shaving.
That stings.
That day comes,
you'll be wishing
for one of your mama's haircuts.
- I'll believe that when I see it.
- ( Shane chuckles )
I'll tell you what--
you just get through this
with some manly dignity and tomorrow
I'll teach you something special.
I will teach you to catch frogs.
- I've caught a frog before.
- I said frogs-- plural.
And it is an art, my friend.
It is not to be taken lightly.
There are ways and means.
Few people know about it.
I'm willing to share my secrets.
Oh, I'm a girl.
You talk to him.
( chuckles ) It's a one-time offer,
bud-- not to be repeated.
Carl:
Why do we need frogs, plural?
- Shane: You ever eat frog legs?
- Eww!
- No, yum!
- No, he's right. Eww.
When you get down
to that last can of beans,
you're gonna be loving
those frog legs, lady.
I can see it now-- "Shane, do you think
I could have a second helping, please?
- Please? Just one?"
- Yeah, I doubt that.
( chuckles )
Don't listen to her, man.
You and me, we'll be heroes.
We'll feed these folks
Cajun-style Kermit legs.
I would rather eat Miss Piggy.
- Yes, that came out wrong.
- ( Shane laughs )
Shane: Heroes, son,
spoken of in song and legend.
You and me, Shane and Carl.
- ( Carl and Shane laugh )
- ( car alarm approaching )
Man:
Hey, Dale, can you see what that is?
Shane:
Talk to me, Dale!
- I can't tell yet.
- Man: Let him get a good look at it.
Is it them? Are they back?
Dale:
I'll be damned.
- Amy: What is it?
- A stolen car is my guess.
- Holy crap. Turn that damn thing off!
- I don't know how!
- Pop the hood, please. Pop the hood.
- My sister Andrea--
- Pop the damn hood, please!
- What? Okay okay. Yeah yeah yeah
- yeah yeah!
- Is she okay? Is she all right?
- Yeah yeah. She's okay! She's okay!
- Is she coming back?
- Glenn: Yes!
- Amy: Why isn't she with you?
- Where is she? She's okay?
- Yes!
Yeah, fine. Everybody is.
Well, Merle not so much.
Are you crazy, driving this
wailing bastard up here?
Are you trying to draw
every walker for miles?
- I think we're okay.
- You call being stupid okay?
Dale: Well, the alarm was
echoing all over these hills.
Hard to pinpoint the source.
I'm not arguing. I'm just saying.
It wouldn't hurt you
to think things through
a little more carefully
next time, would it?
5orry.
Got a cool car.
( truck approaches )
- Come meet everybody.
- ( engine stops )
( sliding door opens )
- Amy.
- ( crying ) Andrea!
- Andrea: Oh!
- Oh my God!
You scared the shit out of me.
- Boy: Papi! Daddy!
- Morales: Hey.
Lori:
Come here, sweetie.
Morales: Hey.
I told you I'd be back, didn't I?
( silent )
( whispers )
- Dale: You are a welcome sight.
- ( both laugh )
I thought we had lost
you folks for sure.
How'd y'all get out
of there anyway?
- New guy-- he got us out.
- Shane: New guy?
Morales: Yeah, crazy vato
just got into town.
- Hey, helicopter boy! Come say hello.
- ( truck door opens, shuts )
Morales:
The guy's a cop like you.
Oh my God.
Dad! Dad!
( crying )
Carl.
Oh!
- ( crickets chirping )
- Rick: Disoriented.
I guess that comes closest.
Disoriented.
Fear, confusion--
all those things but...
( thunder rumbling )
disoriented comes closest.
Words can be
meager things.
Sometimes they fall short.
Rick: I felt like I'd been
ripped out of my life
and put somewhere else.
For a while
I thought I was trapped
in some coma dream,
something I might not
wake up from ever.
Mom said you died.
She had every reason
to believe that.
Don't you ever doubt it.
Lori: When things started
to get really bad,
they told me at the hospital that
they were gonna medevac you
and the other patients to Atlanta,
and it never happened.
Well, I'm not surprised
after Atlanta fell.
- Lori: Yeah.
- And from the look of that hospital,
it got overrun.
Yeah, looks don't deceive.
I barely got them out,
you know?
I can't tell you how grateful
I am to you, Shane.
I can't begin to express it.
There go those words
falling short again.
Paltry things.
( wood clatters )
Hey, Ed, you want
to rethink that log?
It's cold, man.
The cold don't change
the rules, does it?
Keep our fires low,
just embers, so we can't be seen
- from a distance, right?
- I said it's cold.
You should mind your own
business for once.
Hey, Ed... ( pats )
( softly ) are you sure you want
to have this conversation, man?
Go on.
Pull the damn thing out.
Go on!
( mutters )
Christ.
( wood thunks, sizzling )
Hey, Carol, Sophia,
how are y'all this evening?
- Fine. We're just fine.
- Shane: Okay.
- I'm sorry about the fire.
- Shane: No no no no.
No apology needed.
Y'all have a good night, okay?
Thank you.
I appreciate the cooperation.
( Shane sighs )
Dale: Have you given
any thought to Daryl Dixon?
He won't be happy to hear
his brother was left behind.
I'll tell him.
I dropped the key. It's on me.
I cuffed him.
That makes it mine.
Glenn:
Guys, it's not a competition.
I don't mean to bring race into this,
but it might sound better
coming from a white guy.
I did what I did.
Hell if I'm gonna hide from him.
- We could lie.
- Or tell the truth.
Merle was out of control.
Something had to be done
or he'd have gotten us killed.
Your husband did
what was necessary.
And if Merle got left behind,
it is nobody's fault but Merle's.
And that's what we tell Daryl?
I don't see a rational discussion
to be had from that, do you?
Word to the wise--
we're gonna have our hands full
when he gets back from his hunt.
T-Dog:
I was scared and I ran.
- I'm not ashamed of it.
- Andrea: We were all scared.
We all ran. What's your point?
I stopped long enough
to chain that door.
Staircase is narrow.
Maybe half a dozen geeks
can squeeze against it
at any one time.
It's not enough
to break through that--
not that chain, not that padlock.
My point-- Dixon's alive
and he's still up there,
handcuffed on that roof.
That's on us.
I found you, didn't I?
I love you, Dad.
I love you, Carl.
I found you both.
- Lori: Yeah.
- ( thunder rumbling )
I knew I would.
You're getting cocky now,
a little bit.
No. No, I knew.
Walking into our home,
finding an empty house,
- both of you gone.
- I'm so sorry.
I knew you were alive.
How?
The photos were gone,
all our family albums.
( chuckles )
I told you so.
Now you're getting cocky, huh?
A lot.
It belongs in here.
Baby, I really thought
I would never see you again.
I'm so sorry...
for everything.
I feel like--
when you were
in the hospital, I just--
I wanted to take it all back--
the anger and the bad times.
But the mistakes--
Maybe we got a second chance.
Not many people get that.
I wondered where that went.
Do you want it back?
Of course.
( rain pattering )
He won't wake up.
( thunder rumbling )
( bugs chittering )
( kids playing )
( people chatting )
- Morning.
- Man: Morning.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Carol: Morning.
- Morning.
They're still a little damp.
The sun'll have ‘em
dry in no time.
- You washed my clothes?
- Well, best we could.
Scrubbing on a washboard
ain't half as good
as my old Maytag back home.
That's very kind.
Thank you.
- ( tools clanging )
- Look at ‘em.
Vultures.
Yeah, go on, strip it clean.
Generators need every drop
of fuel they can get.
Got no power without it.
Sorry, Glenn.
Thought I'd get to drive it
at least a few more days.
Maybe we'll get to steal
another one someday.
Lori:
Morning, officer.
Rick: Hey.
You sleep okay?
Better than in a long time.
( chuckles )
Well, I didn't want to wake you.
I figured you could use it.
- God. What?
- I've been thinking
about the man we left behind.
You're not serious.
( car approaches )
Water's here, y'all.
Just a reminder to boil before use.
Are you asking me or telling me?
- Asking.
- Well, I think it's crazy.
I think it is just
the stupidest way
- to break your son--
- ( woman screams )
- Carl: Mom!
- Carl?
Man:
It's over there!
- Carl: Dad!
- Lori: Baby!
- Girl: Mama! Mommy!
- Glenn: Rick!
- Lori: Carl!
- Man: Over here! Come on, come on!
Lori:
Carl! Baby!
- Carl: Mom!
- Lori: You're okay! I've got him.
Nothing bit you?
Nothing scratched you?
- No, I'm okay.
- ( cans rattle )
( growling )
( gasps )
( men grunting )
It's the first one
we've had up here.
They never come this far
up the mountain.
Well, they're running out
of food in the city, that's what.
- ( branch snaps )
- ( footsteps )
- Oh, Jesus.
- Man: Son of a bitch.
That's my deer!
Look at it.
All gnawed on by this...
( kicking )
filthy, disease-bearing,
motherless poxy bastard!
Calm down, son.
That's not helping.
What do you know
about it, old man?
Why don't you take that stupid hat
and go back to "On Golden Pond"?
I've been tracking
this deer for miles.
Gonna drag it back to camp,
cook us up some venison.
What do you think?
Do you think we can cut around
this chewed up part
right here?
I would not risk that.
( sighs )
That's a damn shame.
I got some squirrel--
about a dozen or so.
That'll have to do.
Oh God.
Come on, people.
What the hell?
It's gotta be the brain.
Don't y'all know nothing?
Merle!
Merle! Get your ugly ass out here!
I got us some squirrel!
Let's stew ‘em up.
Shane: Daryl, just slow up a bit.
I need to talk to you.
Daryl:
About what?
Shane:
About Merle.
There was a--
there was a problem in Atlanta.
He dead?
Shane:
We're not sure.
He either is or he ain't!
No easy way to say this,
so I'll just say it.
- Who are you?
- Rick Grimes.
Rick Grimes, you got something
you want to tell me?
Your brother was
a danger to us all,
so I handcuffed him on a roof,
hooked him to a piece of metal.
He's still there.
Hold on.
Let me process this.
You're saying you handcuffed
my brother to a roof
and you left him there?!
Yeah.
- ( grunts )
- Hey.
Watch the knife!
( shouts, grunting )
Shane:
Okay. Okay.
- You'd best let me go!
- Nah, I think it's better if I don't.
( Daryl grunting )
Choke hold's illegal.
Shane:
You can file a complaint.
Come on, man.
We'll keep this up all day.
I'd like to have
a calm discussion on this topic.
Do you think
we can manage that?
- Do you think we can manage that?
- Shane: Hmm?
Mmm. Yeah.
( Daryl panting )
What I did was not on a whim.
Your brother does not work
and play well with others.
It's not Rick's fault. I had the key.
- I dropped it.
- You couldn't pick it up?
Well, I dropped it
in a drain.
If it's supposed to make me
feel better, it don't.
T-Dog:
Well, maybe this will.
Look, I chained
the door to the roof--
so the geeks couldn't
get at him--
- with a padlock.
- It's gotta count for something.
Hell with all y'all!
Just tell me where he is
so's I can go get him.
Lori:
He'll show you.
Isn't that right?
I'm going back.
( sighs )
So that's it, huh?
You're just gonna walk off?
Just to hell with everybody else?
I'm not saying
to hell with anybody--
not you, Shane;
Lori least of all.
Shane:
Tell her that.
She knows.
Shane:
Well, look, I--
I don't, okay, Rick?
So could you just--
could you throw me
a bone here, man?
Could you just tell me why?
Why would you risk your life
for a douche bag like Merle Dixon?
Daryl: Hey, choose your words
more carefully.
No, I did.
Douche bag's what I meant.
Merle Dixon--
the guy wouldn't give you a glass
of water if you were dying of thirst.
Rick: What he would
or wouldn't do doesn't interest me.
I can't let a man
die of thirst-- me.
Thirst and exposure.
We left him like
an animal caught in a trap.
That's no way for anything to die,
let alone a human being.
So you and Daryl,
that's your big plan?
Oh, come on.
You know the way.
You've been there before--
in and out, no problem.
You said so yourself.
It's not fair of me to ask--
I know that--
but I'd feel a lot better
with you along.
I know she would too.
That's just great. Now you're
gonna risk three men, huh?
- T-Dog: Four.
- ( huffs )
My day just gets better
and better, don't it?
T-Dog: You see anybody else
here stepping up
- to save your brother's cracker ass?
- Why you?
T-Dog: You wouldn't even
begin to understand.
- You don't speak my language.
- Dale: That's four.
It's not just four. You're putting
every single one of us at risk.
Just know that, Rick.
Come on, you saw that walker.
It was here.
It was in camp.
They're moving out of the cities.
They come back, we need
every able body we've got.
We need ‘em here.
We need ‘em to protect camp.
It seems to me what
you really need most here
- are more guns.
- Right, the guns.
- Wait. What guns?
- Six shotguns,
two high-powered rifles,
over a dozen handguns.
I cleaned out the cage
back at the station before I left.
I dropped the bag
in Atlanta when I got swarmed.
It's just sitting there on the street,
waiting to be picked up.
- Ammo?
- 700 rounds, assorted.
Lori: You went through
hell to find us.
You just got here and you're gonna
turn around and leave?
Dad, I don't want you to go.
To hell with the guns.
Shane is right.
Merle Dixon?
He's not worth one of your lives,
even with guns thrown in.
Tell me.
Make me understand.
I owe a debt to a man
I met and his little boy.
Lori, if they hadn't
taken me in,
I'd have died.
It's because of them
that I made it back to you at all.
They said they'd
follow me to Atlanta.
They'll walk into the same trap
I did if I don't warn him.
What's stopping you?
The walkie-talkie,
the one in the bag I dropped.
He's got the other one. Our plan was
to connect when they got closer.
- These are our walkies?
- Yeah.
So use the CB.
What's wrong with that?
The CB's fine.
It's the walkies
that suck to crap--
date back to the '70s,
don't match any other bandwidth--
not even the scanners
in our cars.
I need that bag.
Okay?
All right.
- ( truck beeping )
- Rumor is you have bolt cutters.
- Maybe.
- T-Dog: Yeah, we get to that roof,
we'll need to cut that chain
and the handcuffs.
I never like lending tools.
The last time I did--
and yes, I am talking
about you--
let's just say your bag of guns
wasn't the only bag
that was dropped.
My tools got
left behind with Merle.
Rick:
We'll bring your tools back too.
Think of the bolt cutters
as an investment.
Sounds like more of a gamble.
- What do I get in return?
- Rick: What do you want?
How about one of those guns
you bring back?
- My pick.
- Done.
( man clears throat )
Dale, let's...
sweeten the deal a bit.
Now that cube van of yours--
What about it?
The RV's radiator hose is shot.
That's a problem if we need to get
somewhere and wanna get very far.
And the hose on that van is
just about a perfect match--
well, enough that I can make it fit.
I'll tell you what-- we get back,
you can strip that van down
to the bare metal.
( truck honks )
- Come on, let's go!
- Thank you.
Hey, Rick,
got any rounds in the Python?
No.
Last time we were
on the gun range,
I'm sure I wound up
with a few loose rounds of yours.
You and that bag--
like the bottom of an old lady's purse.
I hate that you're doing this, man.
I think that
it's foolish and reckless.
But if you're gonna go,
you're taking bullets.
I'm not sure I'd want
to fire a shot in the city,
- not after what happened last time.
- That's up to you.
Well...
four men, four rounds.
What are the odds, huh?
Well, let's just hope that--
let's just hope that four is
your lucky number, okay?
- Thank you.
- All right.
( truck starts, revving )
Hey.
( sniffling )
You know,
I bet they'll be just fine.
I'm not worried.
Are you?
Yeah, a little.
Don't be.
- Why?
- Think about it, Mom.
Everything that's
happened to him so far--
nothing's killed him yet.
( chuckles )
Daryl:
He'd better be okay.
It's my only word on the matter.
I told you the geeks
can't get at him.
The only thing that's gonna
get through that door is us.
- ( brakes squeak )
- ( gear shift clicks )
- ( engine stops )
- We walk from here.
Lori: Dale.
- Have you seen Carl?
- Shane took him down to the quarry.
There was some mighty bold talk
about catching frogs.
( women chatting )
Carl:
I'm not getting anything.
Yeah.
Being all wily,
staying submerged.
Little suckers,
they know something's up.
That's what's going on.
Just going to have to do this
the old-fashioned way.
All right, little man, look.
You are the-- you are
the key in all this, okay?
All I'm gonna do is
I'm gonna go after one of them,
all right, scare the rest of them off.
They're all gonna scatter.
- I'm gonna drive ‘em your way, okay?
- All right.
What you need to do
is you need to round up
every bad boy you see,
all right? Are you with me?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Hells yeah. Give me your mean face.
- ( both growl )
- Yes sir. Are you ready?
- Yeah!
- Are you ready? Here we go, boy.
Here we go.
- ( laughing )
- All right, they're coming your way.
They're coming your way.
Go on, get ‘em, get ‘em.
They're coming
your way, come on.
Catch them frogs.
They're coming, little man! Get ‘em!
Get that net in there and get ‘em!
I'm beginning to question
the division of labor here.
They're coming, little man! Get ‘em!
Get that net in there and get ‘em!
What have you got, bad boy?
What do you got? What do you got?
- Dirt.
- Oh boy.
All right, we've got to start over.
- Come on, let's find this bucket.
- ( both laughing )
Can someone explain to me
how the women wound up
doing all the Hattie McDaniel work?
The world ended.
Didn't you get the memo?
It's just the way it is.
( fence clatters )
- Merle first or guns?
- Merle! We ain't even having
- this conversation.
- ( emphatically ) We are.
You know the geography.
It's your call.
Merle's closest.
The guns would mean doubling back.
Merle first.
( scrubbing )
Carol:
I do miss my Maytag.
I miss my Benz, my sat nav.
I miss my coffeemaker
with that dual-drip filter
and built-in grinder, honey.
My computer...
and texting.
I miss my vibrator.
Jacqui: Oh!
- ( women laugh )
- Amy: Oh my God!
- Me too.
- ( women laughing louder )
What's so funny?
Just swapping war stories, Ed.
Yeah.
( water dripping )
Andrea:
Problem, Ed?
Nothin' that concerns you.
And you ought to focus
on your work.
- This ain't no comedy club.
- ( Andrea huffs )
Hey, Carl,
what did I tell you about
not leaving Dale's sight?
But Shane said we could
catch frogs, remember?
It doesn't matter what Shane says.
It matters what I say.
- Go on back to camp.
- ( sighs )
Lori:
I'll be right behind you.
I've got to tell you,
I do not think you should be
taking this out on him.
Lori: You don't tell me what to do.
You lost that privilege.
Lori, could you just wait up a sec?
I think we should talk.
- We haven't had a chance--
- No. No no.
That's over too.
You can tell that to the frogs.
Damn it, Lori. Look, I don't know
how it appears to you
- or what you think--
- How it appears to me? I'm sorry.
Is there a gray area here?
Let me dispel it.
You stay away from me.
You stay away from my son.
You don't look at him.
You don't talk to him.
From now on,
my family is off-limits to you.
Lori, I don't think that's fair.
- Shane, shut up. Don't! ( slapping )
- I don't think that--
My husband is back.
He is alive.
He's my best friend.
Do you think
I'm not happy about that?
How dare you?
Why would you be?
You are the one that
told me that he died.
You son of a bitch.
( shuffling footsteps )
( growling )
Damn. You are one ugly skank.
( thuds )
( scrubbing )
Ed, tell you what--
you don't like how
your laundry is done,
you are welcome to pitch in
and do it yourself. Here.
- Oh!
- Ed: Ain't my job, missy.
- Andrea, don't.
- What is your job, Ed?
Sitting on your ass
smoking cigarettes?
Well, it sure as hell
ain't listening
to some uppity
smart-mouthed bitch.
Tell you what--
come on. Let's go.
I don't think she needs
to go anywhere with you, Ed.
And I say it's none of your business.
Come on now.
- You heard me.
- Carol.
Andrea, please.
It doesn't matter.
Hey, don't think
I won't knock you on your ass
just ‘cause you're some
college-educated cooze,
- All right?
- ( gasps )
Now you come on now
or you gonna regret it later.
So she can show up
with fresh bruises later, Ed?
- Yeah, we've seen them.
- ( laughs )
Stay out of this.
Now come on!
You know what?
This ain't none of y'all's business.
You don't want to keep prodding
the bull here, okay?
Now I am done talking.
Come on.
- No no. Carol, you don't have--
- ( Carol mutters )
You don't tell me what!
I tell you what!
( clamoring )
- You think you can--
- Amy: Get off her!
- Ed: Come here! Come here!
- Get off her! Get off her!
- Ed: Get off me!
- ( Ed grunting )
- Carol: Ed?
- Amy: It's okay. It's okay.
- Carol: No!
- It's okay.
- No!
- ( women yelling )
- Amy: Shane, stop!
Just stop!
Carol:
Stop it!
- Stop!
- You put your hands on your wife,
your little girl
or anybody else in this camp
one more time, I will not stop
next time. Do you hear me?
- Do you hear me?!
- ( slurs ) Yes.
- I'll beat you to death, Ed.
- Carol: Ed!
- I'll beat you to death.
- ( Carol crying ) Oh God!
No.
- God!
- ( grunts )
( crying )
Ed, I'm sorry.
Oh my God. Ed, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Ed.
Ed, I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry, Ed.
- ( coughing )
( chain rattles )
Daryl:
Merle! Merle!
No! No!
No!
( theme music playing )